The Plague Rounds named Ice Oni
that Queen shot
turned the Golden Festival into an inferno.
You'll turn into an oni just by touching them.
It's incredibly infectious...
Yeah...
And they'll attack anyone!
It'll alter not just your appearance,
but also your soul...
By that I mean, it'll rip it out!
How could he spread such a virus!
He himself is an oni!
Outta my way!
Luffy and the gang are trying to reach Kaido.
I won't let you through here!
Prepare yourselves!
I said "Outta my way"!
Wait, Luffy!
What are you doing?!
You're gonna fight Kaido, right?
Save your energy for now!
Water Shot!
Oh! Jimbei!
At the same time, Kin'emon and the others
thought they had finally killed Kaido, but...
I saw Kozuki Oden's shadow
in the spirit you all displayed!
But you guys are not Oden after all...
Too shallow!
You guys aren't strong enough
to reopen the scar from that day!
Kiku!
"I Won't Forgive Him!
Chopper's Determination!"
ONIGASHIMA
RIGHT-BRAIN TOWER
Wait!
No! You're so persistent!
Stop following us!
You can't tell me that!
I have to protect Kozuki Momonosuke!
Why?!
Because I'm Oden!
You're talking nonsense again!
Hey! Where did you go?!
Kozuki Momonosuke!
I guess he's gone now.
Mm... Mm-hm...
Do you think he is serious?
He claimed he is my father
and would protect me...
Luffytaro told us to trust him,
but we don't have time to check up on him!
Let's just run for now!
Okay.
How was it, Bao Huang?
Well, Yamato and Momonosuke are running through
the Right-Brain Tower heading outdoors!
Yamato went slightly off course,
but he'll meet up with them again soon!
--That's good enough.
--Clank.
This is King.
We now know the identities of those fools
who crashed the banquet.
The enemy group has about 5,400 soldiers.
Most of them are samurai
with Oden's retainers in the lead.
So this...
...is a plot to revive the family...
...staking the Kozuki Clan's prestige.
They want to make Oden's son...
...Kozuki Momonosuke
the Shogun of the Land of Wano.
Stop! How dare you attack me...
How dare you attack him!
This is for killing Pay-Pay!
--But he's alive!
For all Gifters and Tobi Roppo members that are free...
Here's my order!
Kill Kozuki Momonosuke
who is now running through the Right-Brain Tower,
and bring his head to me!
That'll take all the fight out of the samurai.
Although I know the pirates are another matter.
--An order he said?!
--Roger!
Don't be so arrogant, you shitty...
Well...
Shinobu, what we just heard...
He told us to kill him
instead of catching him alive...
Don't worry! I promise I'll protect you!
That's easier.
Shoot.
That's so quick.
ANIMAL KINDOM PIRATES
ARMORED DIVISION
--Collect his dead body!
--Yes, sir!
Here it is.
Oh? What's this?
A barrel?
We, of the Armored Division's defense,
can't be broken down with a weapon like that!
Shinobu!
No! Please hide!
Nice try!
The members of this team
all have armored bodies.
There's no way out!
Aim at the brat!
Momonosuke-sama!
Please... run...
Shinobu...
Don't worry...
It's nothing.
But...
You're a future Shogun...
Don't get upset over a little thing like this!
Your master's life is more important than yours?
You're so loyal, kunoichi.
But the future with him as Shogun...
...will never come!
I'll kill you...
...along with the brat!
You can't even shield him!
Shinobu!
...un...
Run, Momonosuke-sama!
Run?
Because I am the man who will become the Shogun?
Is that...
...what a Shogun is supposed to do?
Shinobu! Shinobu!
I'll get you!
Don't...
Don't!!
Well, well...
Do you wanna interfere?
Young Master Yamato.
It's not interference.
I'm gonna fight for the Kozuki.
Because I'm Oden!
This is what my Plague Rounds can do!
I feel cold! I'm gonna become an oni!
But it's still not exciting enough...
Oh, yeah! I've got an idea!
Get ready to be attacked!
Queen-sama... Why did you shoot us, too?
All you can do is laugh!
Come through for me just once, Pleasures!
Oh, I feel cold...
Somebody, help...
There was some humanity left in him.
He'll soon become an oni anyway,
so why not?!
You're right!
More importantly, where did the captain go?!
I don't know! Let's focus on surviving!
No mercy even for their allies?!
Those former members of Oniwabanshu
who served Shogun Orochi directly...
...are crazy!
Well, so are we! Right?!
Don't harm our allies!
Well, we can't defend ourselves like that forever!
Boss Hyogoro!
Are you okay?!
Ohmasa! Thanks!
Leave him to me!
Good job, Ohmasa!
Ohmasa?
Don't tell me...
...you were scratched by that oni's nail?!
Damn! Damn! Damn!
I'm sorry, Boss Hyogoro...
Ohmasa!
I won't forgive him!
If he creates a virus and makes people suffer...
I'll save everyone at any cost!
INSIDE THE CASTLE - FIRST FLOOR
It's Straw Hat and Jimbei!
They're incredibly strong! Watch out!
--Why didn't they mention "Black-Leg"?!
--Keep running!
I know!
I wanna kick Kaido's ass!
--Stop!
--We won't let you through!
You guys are so weak!
I'm sorry... Hamlet-sama, Fourtricks-sama...
We couldn't stop them!
We're gonna show you
what true strength looks like.
--Hamlet-sama!
--Fourtricks-sama!
"Common"? That's the word for you guys!
"Expectation"? That's something we...
...will surpass!
HAMLET
A HEADLINER OF THE ANIMAL KINGDOM PIRATES
WITH THE GIRAFFE SMILE FRUIT
Be quiet, Hamlet!
The truly powerful are silent.
FOURTRICKS
A HEADLINER OF THE ANIMAL KINGDOM PIRATES
WITH THE CHICKEN SMILE FRUIT
FOURTRICKS
A HEADLINER OF THE ANIMAL KINGDOM PIRATES
WITH THE CHICKEN SMILE FRUIT
The way they grow!
--Hamlet-sama!
--Fourtricks-sama!
Wait for me, Kaido!
Kiku!
Get away from the rooftop!
Yes, sir!
I will stop the bleeding...
I'm... ready...
Can you get up, Kikunojo?
Of course.
That's how you guys are.
You guys are always determined.
I...
...like samurai.
Roger...
Whitebeard...
They did it well!
They really did it well!
This may be an outdated concept...
But death brings humans completion!
Don't you think so?
Let's finish it up!
Do not be so arrogant, Kaido!
Getting killed by you is not honorable for us...
...at all!
Hoping to save Momonosuke,
Yamato fights the Armored Division led by Sasaki.
Zoro stands against the enemy's surging attacks,
while trying to save his allies
who were turned into Ice Oni.
And Queen starts a terrifying game!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Zoro's Pursuit! Ice Oni Tag!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!