I feel cold! I'm gonna become an oni!
This is what my Plague Rounds can do!
I won't forgive him!
If he creates a virus and makes people suffer...
I'll save everyone at any cost!
Stop! How dare you attack me...
How dare you attack him!
This is for killing Pay-Pay!
- But he's alive!
Well, well...
Do you wanna interfere?
Young Master Yamato.
It's not interference.
I'm gonna fight for the Kozuki.
Because I'm Oden!
The way they grow!
Wait for me, Kaido!
This may be an outdated concept...
But death brings humans completion!
Let's finish it up!
Do not be so arrogant, Kaido!
Getting killed by you is not honorable for us...
...at all!
"Zoro's Pursuit! Ice Oni Tag!"
He's awful! He even shot his allies...
If I do say so myself, this is a great show!
Yo! Yo! Yo! Yo! Yo! Yo!
Yo! Yo! Yo! Yo!
Like a deer in the headlights
the hard bite will change you into an oni!
We don't need tears! Wake up!
Don't care about tomorrow! Make some noise!
Damn...
I'm sorry, Boss Hyogoro...
Rather than hurting my comrades, I'll...
Don't jump the gun, you fool!
I don't wanna be an oni!
I'm sure there is a cure!
Don't give up, Ohmasa!
Don't sacrifice yourself!
Boss Hyogoro...
I don't have the slightest idea of
what kind of disease this is,
but remember what happened in Udon.
Don't spread the virus!
Guys, don't move!
I'll figure something out!
I promise I'll cure you!
Don't let that pestilence get the better of you!
Don't lose hope!
When there's nothing we can do,
I'll stop you by cutting you!
I got it!
Hey, don't do it! We're on the same side!
Queen-sama, why did you shoot us, too?!
It's cold! It's cold! I'm becoming an oni...
Help!
You guys are amazing!
But...
...we still need more groove!
Dance! Shout!
Go crazier!
Cry more and more!
Scream!
Oh, please...
It's cold...
Help me...
Hey! Stay with me!
I'm gonna turn into an oni! No!
Guys!
Catch some excitement!
What should we do?
We'll all get killed!
Just the right person!
Let's feature him and finish it up.
What can I do to keep them down?
Are they zombies?!
Damn! More and more people are getting infected!
If this continues...
Is there anything you can do, Chopper-san?!
I wish I could cure them now...
But...
...it's not realistically possible
to concoct a medicine while fighting,
and give those oni shots.
Then...
But unlike Udon,
we have the guy who made the virus here!
I'm sure that the virus creator made the antibody
at the same time and kept it.
If I can get hold of it,
I'll be able to make tons of medicine!
Of all people, he's a Lead Performer!
It's not easy to grab that from him!
Rather than their violent behavior,
I'm more worried about what'll happen to them later!
What?
They gained ferocity and physical strength,
and their skin was rapidly cooled down.
Their bodies can't take it!
Then if we let the infected be, they'll...
They'll die!
Once they get infected,
they'll only have an hour at most!
What?!
The person who turned into Ice Oni
was your best friend?
Your boss? Your subordinate?
This could be the most energetic moment of their lives!
Give them a good hug for the last time!
You'll get infected though!
That vermin...
Damn Queen!
How could he make another hideous weapon!
I don't wanna stay on this floor!
Hey! Open the door!
Hey! Brother Apoo!
What's this?
That's the only antibody in the world!
Oh, for Ice Oni?
If you lose it,
your punishment will be a savage death...
What?
An antibody...
...against Ice Oni?
If we can get it...
- It's an antibody!
- If we can get it...
- We gotta grab that!
- What? What?!
What?!
Queen presents!
Game Time!
Zoom! Zoom! Zoom! Zoom!
It finally begins now!
If nothing was up to chance, it wouldn't be called a game!
Murder! Betrayal! There's no rule!
An hour from now, you'll meet your...
...death!
Excite!
That bastard! He thinks so lightly of people's lives!
Ice Oni...
...Tag!
Whoa! Whoa-whoa!
Zoro! Grab that from him!
Okay!
- Don't let them have it!
- Our people will die!
Don't let those samurai get well!
Wait, wait, Queen!
You're too crazy!
Start!
Grab it from each other!
Kill one another!
If you don't get caught you win, Apoo!
Everyone else will die!
Damn!
Crimson Cat Dance!
Canine Scourge!
You guys will die here.
Your lives will be over
without accomplishing anything...
What a meaningless death...
RIGHT-BRAIN TOWER INSIDE THE DOME
You're gonna fight for the Kozuki?
Do you think you can outrun us carrying them?
Well, our mission is complete
if we can kill that brat.
Don't worry. I'll protect you.
Why do you...
...fight for the Kozuki?
I don't know who you are,
but if you're on our side...
Please save Momonosuke-sama!
I'm gonna save you too, Shinobu-san!
What?
20 years ago...
I was watching Kozuki Oden's execution!
I'm counting on you guys!
Open up the Land of Wano!
I'm happy...
I'M HAPPY IF PEOPLE TALK ABOUT ME OVER A DRINK
...if people talk about me over a drink...
Oden wouldn't be oden...
IF IT WASN'T BOILED
...if it wasn't boiled!
Who do you think worked hard,
so you can live in peace?!
Oden-sama had always been protecting this country!
Now, who's the silly lord?!
Say it!
Your speech brought me to tears!
And... Kozuki Oden's way of life brought me to tears!
The Kozuki Clan has no place
in the New Onigashima Project.
Momonosuke-kun.
On that terrible day,
in order to save you...
I ran to Kuri.
What?! Why... are you okay?
But...
I'm sorry...
All I could do was watch you
as you were about to be dropped by Kaido!
Back then,
I had no strength!
What?!
Who are you?
You identified yourself as my father...
Kozuki Oden!
Also known as...
Yamato!
I...
...can die for you!
Under the concentrated fire of the Tobi Roppo,
Nami and Usopp have nowhere to run.
"Those who rebel against Kaido won't be forgiven!"
As Ulti-Mortar closes in on her,
Nami is worn-out both physically and mentally.
In this dire circumstance,
the promise that she made with Luffy comes to mind!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Nami Surrenders?! Ulti's Fierce Headbutt!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!