iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
Draw your own map
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha
ni areta umi no youna jidai
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
kizukiageta kachikan sae
mo kuzuresarou to shita
Even the values we had built
up were about to fall apart
rashinban no sashita saki ga
tadashii no ka douka nante
Who knows if the compass is
pointing in the right direction?
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
No one knows for certain
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
I do it for my own
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And you do yours, don't we?
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
And I'm ready for it
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
With the support of someone I can rely
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Seize the future beyond your imagination
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
We'll go wherever we wanna go
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Tears and doubts in tow
onore no iro de egaite yuke
Let's paint it in our own colors
The raid is getting intense
and battles erupt everywhere.
W-Who are you?
Kozuki Oden!
Also known as...
Yamato!
"Sasaki's Onslaught!
Armored Division vs. Yamato!"
Damn you!
How dare you!
You lowered your guard!
You can't get away now!
Shoot him, Perospero!
Okay, Mama!
Lick.
I can't take it anymore!
How dare he... How dare he...
How dare he...
...do that to Pedro...
Perospero!
Not now... Now isn't the right time...
Carrot!
I know! I shouldn't use this power now
for the sake of the plan!
The Sulong transformation is
a double-edged sword for us Minks.
We must use that deadly power against Kaido!
But...
...having that hateful Perospero in front of me,
I can't be a good girl!
He is...
...Pedro's sworn enemy, you know?!
I can't...
No, Pedro!
I wanted to learn a lot more from Pedro!
It doesn't matter how you fight.
From now on, you must be a strong fighter
and constantly prepared.
Everyone has their own turn.
I wanted to carry on along with Pedro!
But... I can't do that anymore!
So I... at least wanna guarantee
that Pedro can die without any regrets...
On his behalf,
I wanna take that jerk down
even if it's the last thing I do...
...at least...
...with my own hands!
Perospero!
Everyone has...
...their own turn.
Pedro...
Pedro did his own part in turn.
He sacrificed himself...
...to save Luffy and the others!
So...
...don't say that Pedro died with regrets.
Carrot...
Your-teia kindness is very touching.
Caring about your friends...
That's...
...something I do too, Carrot.
We don't have time.
Let's take care of it quickly together!
Thank you...
Sorry, Marco...
...for getting help from Mama!
Damn...
There were times before
I wanted to kill you more than now.
How ironic.
Goodbye...
Moon...
...Raid!
Y-You're the one from that time!
You got in my way again!
This guy killed Pedro?!
Yes! If only he weren't around...
That idiot Pedro blew himself up!
He got me into trouble!
Don't say he blew himself up so lightly!
I know...
...that Pedro's death has
led us to this battle.
I think...
...Luffy and his crew are...
...the ones who our tribe and the Kozuki Clan
have been waiting for over the centuries...
The ones who'll lead the
world to the new dawn!
Listen!
You-gara guys must go forward!
Watch over me, Pedro...
We're gonna head toward
the new dawn of the world!
Oh, what a pain in the ass!
Don't bring a small problem
such as revenge...
...to the far corner of the battlefield!
Do as you like!
Who are you two?!
Carrot.
Wanda.
You're Marco.
A friend of Master Cat Viper, right?
Yeah, kind of-yoi...
Marco!
If you wanna kill me,
come back some other time!
I don't wanna waste any soul to beat you now!
Go, Marco!
Leave him to us!
Okay, I'm counting on you-yoi!
What's that?
Big Sis!
A dog shouldn't eat a dragon!
It goes against the natural order of things!
Stop fooling around, you damn dog!
I was shocked!
Pay-Pay, comfort me!
You smell like a dog!
What? Smell like a dog?!
--Care for me or I'll cry, you fool!
--Quietly, on tiptoe...
stealthily...
I'm here, you damn lizards!
That dog is part of my plan!
The muscle-headed, simple lizards
are easy to handle and exterminate!
Wait, wait, wait, wait! That wasn't me!
It's you again!
--It wasn't! Wait!
--Nose!
Bang! Splash! Wham! Bam! Thunk!
Boink!
I'm flying!
Usopp...
Usopp! Are you okay?!
Who d'ya fink fai fam?!
Of courfe fai'm nof fokay...
You're right...
Of course, you're not okay...
But it's good that I'm okay!
Hey!
Hey, Otama. How did you get here?
One of the enemies gave me a boat ride!
What?! Enemy?!
Pay-Pay! Chew that dog up!
Do it yourself!
Damn! What's this baboon?!
Where did he come from?!
Hihimaru!
Hold them there for three minutes!
They're very vicious!
That giant monkey will get hurt!
Don't underestimate us, Onami-chan!
We're here as samurai!
Get out of my way!
This can go on forever, Young Master Yamato.
Having said that, I don't wanna lose
the impregnable Armored Division.
How dare you harm so many of them?!
We're gonna get rid of that little punk
and end this all.
Aim.
Shoot!
Momonosuke-kun! Shinobu-san!
Yamato...
If you take that many bullets...
It's nothing!
If nothing is done, we'll all be dead...
Don't let Momonosuke-sama die here!
You! If you're a samurai, you must decide!
Leave me here and take Momonosuke-sama...
No!
If it were Oden...
If it were Kozuki Oden...
he wouldn't do that!
Since I'm Kozuki Oden,
I won't do that!
What a hardhead...
I'm one of the Tobi Roppo!
I know you're extremely strong,
but I can't stomach seeing you thinking
that you can defeat me...
...while saving those weaklings,
Young Master Yamato!
Sasaki...
You're lucky if you can make it out of this
with only a mortal wound!
What happened?!
Outta my way! Outta my way!
Get out of my way!
Franosuke!
Hm? Momo?!
I'm glad that you're alive!
Shinobu, you're okay too, right?!
That's...
I know! He's one of Luffy's crewmembers!
Cyborg Franky! 94 million berries!
I can't believe he really exists!
Haccha?! Why are you here?!
Oh, damn!
Don't do it, you fool!
Just because no one can catch you!
How childish!
Armored Division! Don't lose them!
Don't let them get away at any cost!
The floor crumbled!
Oh, yeah! There's a floor underneath!
Momonosuke-kun! Shinobu-san!
Let's make our way down like this!
Momo! Shinobu! Are you okay?!
Did you get caught?!
No! He's helping us!
That's good!
Cyborg Franky! I'll leave them to you!
Who are you?!
Luffy entrusted these two to me!
I don't know who you are...
...but I got it!
Super count on me!
Shinobu-san, take Momonosuke-kun!
What?
I wanna return him a favor!
Be right back!
I gotta take him down at least...
Narikabura Arrow!
NARIKABURA ARROW
Alright!
That guy did it?
Who is he?
Haccha?!
Damn!
Yamato went down, taking Momonosuke!
Organize a pursuit unit! Chase them now!
Armored Division!
Let's take down the damn robot!
Momonosuke-kun!
You must survive!
Survive at any cost!
The one who'll lead the
world to the new dawn...
...is you!
Kozuki Momonosuke!
Luffy keeps running towards the Akazaya members
who are in a deadly battle with Kaido.
Law closes in on the mystery
of the "People of the D."
Kid pushes forward,
knocking down his enemies.
Following in the footsteps
of his brave allies,
Chopper uses his medical skills
to conquer his natural enemy, the Ice Oni.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Eliminate the Ice Oni! Chopper's Fire Trick!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!