Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Draw your own map
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha
ni areta umi no youna jidai
Even the values we had built
up were about to fall apart
kizukiageta kachikan sae
mo kuzuresarou to shita
Who knows if the compass is
pointing in the right direction?
rashinban no sashita saki ga
tadashii no ka douka nante
No one knows for certain
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
I do it for my own
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
And you do yours, don't we?
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And I'm ready for it
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
With the support of someone I can rely
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
Seize the future beyond your imagination
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
We'll go wherever we wanna go
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
Tears and doubts in tow
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Let's paint it in our own colors
onore no iro de egaite yuke
I'm already sick and tired of you fools!
Everyone! It's not time to die yet!
Kin'emon and the others
are still holding out against Kaido.
Shut up!
At the Performance Floor,
the deadly Ice Oni is still raging.
What?!
Thanks!
Can I leave this floor to you?
I don't have time for this damn game.
You won't die, right?
Of course not!
And Luffy keeps running
towards Kin'emon and the others.
That's...
"It's Not Okay!
The Spider lures Sanji!"
Wait for us, Kin'emon!
Which way is the rooftop?!
That way!
Alright!
What's wrong, Sanji?
What are you doing?
Whaddya say? Whaddya say?
You shouldn't do that! You shouldn't do that!
That's naughty!
I have some serious business!
You guys, go ahead!
I'll catch up as soon as I finish it!
Hey, Sanji!
That's what I expected of Luffy's crew.
He might've detected a strong enemy...
Oh well!
Sanji must have something in mind.
Let's just go!
Yeah!
Each of them seems to be
doing their own thing,
but they all do exactly what they need to do.
The Straw Hats...
I need to learn their ways!
I hear it!
A hot woman...
That's naughty!
...is calling for help!
Yes, come closer!
Oh, please stop doing this!
You cute little thing, whaddya say?
You shouldn't do that!
Whaddya say?
You must not do that!
Please stop!
That's naughty!
That old familiar sexual harassment line!
"Whaddya say?", "That's naughty!"
That's naughty!
Someone in a position of power
is untying a helpless woman's kimono.
What the spinning woman
loses with each turn...
...isn't just her dress!
It's her dignity!
Hold on! I'm gonna come help!
Whaddya...
It's not okay!
Stop it!
What?! What's this?!
That's naughty!
A spider's web?!
Hey, stop!
That's naughty!
Naughty Trap!
Another pervy man of justice came...
Damn... It's a trap...
But I'm glad...
...that a lovely woman like you
didn't have to lose your dignity...
Black-Leg Sanji of the Straw Hats.
His bounty is 330 million berries!
I'm sure he was competing
with his crewmate Zoro.
I think this one's bounty is higher.
Wow! We got some big game!
That stupid mosshead is no match for me!
Just like you're no match for us!
Untie me! I'll let it slide for now!
Oh, how scary! You're blackmailing us!
I gotta go somewhere!
If you go, the battlefield
will only spill over.
I don't want this banquet
hall to be caught up in it.
I'm not willing to fight you guys!
I don't want to.
Why don't you stay and have fun?
This place is supposed to be fun.
On the snowy night
The two...
...who missed each other
Missed each other?!
But they didn't get a chance
To see each other for so long
Finally...
...seeing each other
Oh, how mesmerizing!
Under the moonlight
Oh, no...
No, no!
This isn't heaven!
This is hell!
Now you see them...
They stayed and had fun.
The women here treated them nice and sweet.
And they fell into decay.
Being flirted with by women...
That's the forbidden fruit...
Hell or heaven...
Heaven or hell...
Oh, will I end up like them?!
It's a new gate...
Heaven's gate opens!
My allies are waiting for me!
Untie the damn rope already!
When I see a boy with a dirty mouth,
I get the tingles.
"Boy"?! Stop messing with me!
Hey, how about you?
Do you...
...like me?
Cut it out! I don't...
I don't like...
I love you!
The third floor!
Looks like Straw Hat is now
running through the third floor of the castle!
At the stairs ahead,
two Headliners are on standby!
Stop it!
Hey, Gorishiro! Don't drop bananas!
MIZERKA
A HEADLINER OF THE ANIMAL KINGDOM PIRATES
WITH THE GORILLA SMILE FRUIT
Poker-sama! Straw Hat and Jimbei
are heading that way!
Oh, okay!
POKER
A HEADLINER OF THE ANIMAL KINGDOM PIRATES
WITH THE RATTLESNAKE SMILE FRUIT
To my regret, I let Kid through....
Look! Straw Hat's bounty
is 1.5 billion berries!
If I take him down,
that'll do more than clear my name!
1.5 billion?! Then let's split it up into
800 million and 700 million.
I'll take 800 million!
No way! I'll take him down by myself!
I'll have all 1.5 billion to myself!
Then how about I take one billion?
You'll get 500 million. Deal?
How could you come up with
such stupid figures?!
Hey! That's enough!
Anyway, if I bring down Straw Hat,
I'll definitely get promoted.
Becoming a member of the Tobi Roppo...
Not too shabby.
Straw Hat-san! Straw Hat-san!
This way!
Who are they?
Oh, it's you guys!
Good job, guys!
You guys are the heroes of the prisoners!
The guys from Udon!
Hey, Straw Hat isn't here yet?!
He should be there soon!
A ladder...
You guys made it?
Yes, you can get to the
fourth floor with this!
There are a bunch of enemies at the stairs.
That's so helpful. Thanks!
Where is he?!
Not yet...
Not yet!
The Land of Wano will definitely...
...see the dawn...
Everyone, listen!
Use fire against the Ice Oni!
This virus is fused with the gas
that chills our bodies!
Look at me!
If you stop the chill,
the virus won't multiply!
I'll make enough antibodies for everyone!
I'm a doctor!
I'll save everyone, both allies and enemies!
What?!
Everyone?! Meaning Ohmasa, too?!
So survive!
Don't let that nefarious man kill you!
How nice, raccoon!
And you're pathetic, Apoo!
My version of tag...
How dare you ruin the fun game!
You two are annoying!
What?!
Queen-sama!
What? Whaaat?!
Screw the game!
What?
I didn't come to this island
to play this boring game!
I came to chop up Kaido...
...who is said to be the world's strongest!
What?!
His anger provoked an earthquake?!
Is it Haki?! Color of the Supreme King?!
Hang on! Everyone, hold up!
Zoro-san, what did you do?!
I can't believe you did this!
There's no way it's me.
Why is it shaking?!
I'm scared!
No, I'm not scared!
You'll be fine! Just advance!
Go faster!
What's this?! Is it an earthquake, Jimbei?!
Geologically, this island
sure is unique, but...
No! We can't reach the shore!
Pull away from Onigashima for now!
What the...
How impatient...
Is the island gonna sink?!
Onigashima is...
What the hell is going on?!
Do you think our captain is okay?!
Momonosuke-kun!
Your survival is the highest priority!
Let's get out of here by ship!
We gotta hurry up!
I have a bad feeling!
What was that?
It stopped shaking.
I know, Zoro... I saw it, too.
That's...
I saw it, too!
I gotta get to Kaido before it's too late...
Okiku-chan's arm!
I got a late start.
I wish I could just fly there.
But every route has its challenges.
Straw Hats!
Marco the Phoenix!
Yeah, that's who I am-yoi!
You guys are the main force,
why are you still here on this floor?!
It's not like we wanted to be.
Is there anything I can do?
What's wrong?!
The Animal Kingdom Pirates' ship... is gone!
What?!
So is the sea!
What?! What do you mean by that?!
It's too late!
We can't run to the sea anymore!
Isn't this a port?!
That quake before...
I get it now!
What is going on, Yamato?!
Dragons fly through the air
by creating Flame Clouds!
That means now...
...Kaido is lifting up Onigashima!
He's gonna relocate the island
to the Flower Capital!
Th-That cannot be true...
Are you satisfied now?
Kozuki is finished.
The Land of Wano, I mean, New Onigashima...
...will become a stronghold for pirates.
Let's usher in a world of violence!
The New Onigashima Project has been executed.
On top of that, the Tobi Roppo's fierce attacks
make the situation much worse
and the Straw Hats have a hard time.
Marco returns during the
emergency and unleashes
a vortex of fire to the
battlefield with determination.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Turnaround Move! The Flames
of Marco the Phoenix!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!