Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Draw your own map
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha ni areta umi no youna jidai
Even the values we had built up were about to fall apart
kizukiageta kachikan sae mo kuzuresarou to shita
Who knows if the compass is pointing in the right direction?
rashinban no sashita saki ga tadashii no ka douka nante
No one knows for certain
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
I do it for my own
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
And you do yours, don't we?
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And I'm ready for it
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
With the support of someone I can rely
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
Seize the future beyond your imagination
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
We'll go wherever we wanna go
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
Tears and doubts in tow
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Let's paint it in our own colors
onore no iro de egaite yuke
You can't...
...choose your parents, Yamato.
Shut up! You don't have to tell me that!
Even though handcuffs were unavoidable,
if you hate your father so much,
why are you letting them chain your heart?!
WISHFUL MOON
SNOW MOON
Hey, how are things on the outside?!
Are there many young people rising to fame?!
Young ones? Let's see...
Well, I'm in a class of my own,
but I heard some dangerous guys
are running wild in each sea.
Uh-huh, uh-huh!
But the toughest one
will come out to the sea in a few years...
It's my brother!
He'll be extremely powerful!
"Marco's Tears!
The Bond of the Whitebeard Pirates!"
Kick their asses!
Listen! Let's defend the room that Raccoon-san is in
without sparing our lives!
Yeah!
Raccoon-san! How much longer will it take?!
It's almost done!
If we can mass produce this antibody,
we can save everyone!
Miyagi! Tristan! Get ready!
--Yes!
--Okay!
You guys are the last-yoi!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow...
Ouch!
What?
I'm gonna get burned...
It's not that hot!
I'm coming to my senses!
How dare he!
You all! Stop Marco!
Don't let him run free!
Take back the antibody!
He saved us...
But if we don't do anything,
Queen-sama will kill us...
What should I do?
Stop hesitating! Follow my order!
Just kill the enemy!
Yeah, he's Kaido-sama's enemy!
We gotta do it...
He's our enemy...
Just do it already...
Or do you want me to kill you?
I'm not gonna attack Kaido directly now-yoi.
But...
...I comprehend where you stand.
No hard feelings...
--Marco!
--We're coming!
Stay out of this!
Nico Robin! Skeleton Man!
Do what you gotta do!
Run to the castle!
--Let's go!
--If you insist!
Go to hell, Marco!
You're finished! Marco the Phoenix!
You ready?
Do it!
Damn Marco!
This is good!
You're heading for the Emperor of the Sea, Kaido.
How can you be so relaxed?
Why should I be scared of Kaido?
If my captain gives the order, I'll just follow.
I'm counting on Straw Hat, too.
No...
On you guys from the Worst Generation.
I wonder what he would've done if he heard
his brother picked a fight
with an Emperor of the Sea...
I'm begging you, Pops!
I said no, you fool!
I told you several times, Ace...
Who the 2nd division commander was before you,
and why the position was vacant for so long.
I know.
There was a strong samurai named Kozuki Oden
from the Land of Wano.
And because he died a tragic death,
it had been vacant ever since.
The Land of Wano has adopted an isolation policy,
information doesn't come out.
So we didn't know Oden-sama died
until many years later.
I heard Kaido's responsible for his death, too.
You're not gonna do anything about it?
We thought about advancing on the Land of Wano,
but what would happen then?
Can you imagine the toll it would take?
The toll?
It would be a big war.
It'd even involve innocent people-yoi.
Then, let me go by myself!
I made a promise...
When we come back to this country,
I'll make it a place where
you can eat as much as you want!
See you again for sure! Ace!
Of course!
I'm gonna take Kaido's head!
Kozuki Oden couldn't take that guy down...
There's no way you can beat him!
Don't overestimate yourself, Ace!
I remember how strong Oden-san was...
I can relate to your desire to land the head of a big name,
Commander Ace.
Shut up, Teech!
Hunting big names isn't what Ace wants to do-yoi.
He wants to get the head of an Emperor of the Sea.
Is there any purpose other than gaining a reputation?
Damn...
I should get stronger to fulfill the promise...
Is that your purpose?
That's so stupid!
That's what you chose to shoulder-yoi...
You have big shoes to fill
as the 2nd division commander of the Whitebeard Pirates...
Even though he left the ship,
Oden is still like family to us.
We all wanna avenge him.
When I heard you say you'd make the Land of Wano
somewhere everyone can eat as much as they want,
it made me happy!
If you get the go-ahead from Pops, Ace,
don't forget to invite me.
Count me in, too-yoi.
Then, I think we can defeat him already...
How can you be so over-optimistic...
What?!
B...
Big Bro Luffy is Ace's brother?!
That's right. You didn't know?
Because when I talked about Ace,
he coolly said...
Ace died.
Big Bro, you're a liar!
Ace can't come back!
Everyone knows about the Paramount War!
But...
...we made a promise.
Ace will come back!
Tama...
We'll come back!
After we become a greater pirate group!
Then, will you let me join your crew?
I wanna go on adventures with you!
When I come back,
if you become a bewitching kunoichi or something,
I'll take you along!
Ace! Is the "bewitching" thing required?!
Ace!
I got it! That's a promise, okay?!
He said he'd come back...
You don't know how nice he is!
That's why you don't understand my pain!
How could you say he died that casually?!
You... dummy!
I said bad things to Big Bro.
If it bothered him, he would've snapped at you.
Don't worry!
But...
That's so him...
What?
Once in a place called Alabasta...
Don't you think that's too soft-hearted?
And what's wrong with thinking that?
What's wrong with not wanting people to die?!
People die.
He said that like nothing,
but someone told me that he...
Ace is really dead, isn't he?!
Yes, he is dead!
Ace!!
Big Bro... I'm sorry!
Like I said, don't worry.
Mm-hm...
He's the man who has survived the ordeal I gave him!
Usohachi-kun, so you're Big Bro's big bro?!
I'm more like his master!
Master?!
--He's lying!
--What?!
Anyway, let's try the strategy Otama laid out earlier!
But when I see pirates, I get scared...
Don't worry!
We'll save you at any cost!
Really?!
I'll do my best for Big Bro and everyone else!
FORBIDDEN STOREHOUSE, INSIDE THE DOME
What?!
That person is Roger's son,
and Luffy's older brother?!
Is that true?!
Mm-hm.
You guys brought Luffy to the Land of Wano,
didn't you?
That is right...
Pirates are as numerous as stars,
but you met them,
and brought them here...
It can't be anything but fate!
Because...
...there is a "D" in Luffy's name!
Yummy!
Fire is delicious!
It's delicious!
I'm so full!
I'm recharged!
Are you finished eating?
Yes, Mama!
I'm good to go!
Alright, let's go!
Marco!
You can't get through here easily!
QUEEN - A LEAD PERFORMER
DRAGON-DRAGON FRUIT, ANCIENT TYPE
BRACHIOSAURUS MODEL
And I'm sure all the samurai outside are killed by now!
Now all that is left is for Kozuki Oden's son to die
and this battle will be over.
KING - A LEAD PERFORMER
DRAGON-DRAGON FRUIT, ANCIENT TYPE
PTERANODON MODEL
And the Land of Wano...
...will become a pirate empire called New Onigashima!
If you really believe that,
your reasoning is garbage!
Shut up, you little bird!
Damn! Is he invincible?!
What kind of power is that?
You guys are up against the new era now-yoi!
The Animal Kingdom Pirates will dominate
the new era and everything else!
What?!
Whoa-whoa... Just let him go!
Don't get upset!
How could you throw me out of the blue!
Straw Hat isn't here yet?
This is quite a lot of bloodshed.
Hey, Kaido!
You can kill as many as you want,
but don't kill Nico Robin.
The member of the Three-Eyed People you got
can't read the ancient script?
You mean Pudding?! I don't know!
I can't wait until her true awakening any more...
Oh, okay...
We have to defend these stairs
even if it means death!
For the remaining hope!
There are only a few enemies.
Take them down!
You're in my way!
Move!
That must be...
Gum-Gum...
...Rocket!
Whip!
Gatling!
We can only do so much, but please go through here!
These are the stairs to the rooftop!
Thanks, Shishi Viper!
It's Shishilian.
I'll never forget...
...how you guys defended Raizo with your lives!
Thank you!
See you!
Now, where are you gonna drop this island?
There is a castle in the Flower Capital,
that symbolizes the Kozuki.
I heard they're having a festival.
Quite a lot of people will die.
Who cares? It's easy to get more slaves...
It's gonna be a great capital.
What about the Road Ponegliff?
Is it there?
You're already showing your true nature!
Don't underestimate me!
I still think of you like my little brother!
On the day Rox fell, in God Valley,
I gave you the Mythical Type Fish-Fish Fruit.
You're indebted to me for life, Kaido!
Whatever!
Get it, then we'll talk!
Get the One Piece!
Yamato's dark heart opened up when he met Ace.
The Akazaya members and Luffy pledged
to better the future of the Land of Wano.
There is only one direction
in which their commitment will lead them!
Defeating the Emperor of the Sea Kaido!
After two decades of pain, the battle finally begins!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Straw Hat Luffy! The Man Who Will Become the King of the Pirates!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!