Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Draw your own map
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha ni areta umi no youna jidai
Even the values we had built up were about to fall apart
kizukiageta kachikan sae mo kuzuresarou to shita
Who knows if the compass is pointing in the right direction?
rashinban no sashita saki ga tadashii no ka douka nante
No one knows for certain
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
I do it for my own
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
And you do yours, don't we?
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And I'm ready for it
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
With the support of someone I can rely
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
Seize the future beyond your imagination
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
We'll go wherever we wanna go
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
Tears and doubts in tow
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Let's paint it in our own colors
onore no iro de egaite yuke
"Straw Hat Luffy!
The Man Who Will Become the King of the Pirates!"
Jeez...
You pirates know some funny tricks!
Teach me how to do it too!
SEVERAL YEARS AGO
Oh?
ONIGASHIMA DURING KAIDO'S ABSENCE
Um... Hello?
What?!
What? What? What? What?
Ace!
What's wrong all of a sudden?!
You were just having so much fun!
Are you dead...
Stay with me!
Ace!
I fell asleep.
Don't freak me out! I thought you were dead!
It's my bad. I'm sorry.
I was really worried about you!
Gee... Do you wanna call it a night?
You look tired...
What are you talking about, Yamato?!
I still have a lot to tell you!
I gotta meet up with my guys in the morning.
It'd be a waste to sleep tonight.
Then, don't fall asleep again!
I said sorry...
Now, where were we?
You were talking about your brother again!
And you were talking about
wanting to become Oden again!
No, Ace!
I don't want to become him,
I will become him!
I'll make it come true...
It's...
...our future!
ODEN'S TRAVEL RECORD
D?
I never thought I'd meet you one day!
O-Oden...
Is that my father's journal?!
It contains all the details of his dynamic life
and the world he experienced!
On that day, I picked this up
at the river below Oden Castle.
Someone must've protected it
from burning in the castle...
Oden-sama's...
Momonosuke-kun!
There was a lot about you, too, in the journal.
You were born on Whitebeard's ship, right?!
And went on to Roger's ship!
Mm-hm...
B-But since I was little,
I do not remember much...
Whitebeard, Roger, and Oden...
They all said...
...that more than 20 years into the future,
young, strong ones will
come surging into the New World!
That future is now!
I was sure that Ace would
head the list of those pirates.
But when he died, I recalled something!
Of that night!
What?
Oh, no... It slipped out!
I wasn't gonna tell you that.
Never mind! Forget it!
I mean, don't you dare laugh!
Sabo and I won't forgive you if you do!
I've never left this country even once,
so I've barely seen anything with my own eyes...
Whether it's Ace's brother or
the wide world that Oden traveled.
But I saw something clearly at that moment!
That's what my brother's dream is!
We gotta set out to sea someday!
Let's get out of this country
and live freely!
I wanna see the world out there
and write a book about it!
I'm happy to study if it's about sailing!
Let's become stronger
and become pirates someday!
I'm gonna become one -
you don't have to tell me to!
I'm gonna become a pirate
and defeat all the others and become the most notorious!
It'll be the only proof of my life!
It doesn't matter if all the people in the world
reject me or despise me!
I'll become a great pirate
and show them what I can do!
The Government is telling us not to go to the last island
which could hold a vast amount of treasure!
That makes it even more tantalizing!
If we can get there,
we'll be in both name and deed...
...the world's greatest pirate group!
The world's greatest?
I got it!
Alright then...!
That's right!
Then...
--...I'll...
--I'm gonna...
You fool...
I was wondering what you'd have to say...
That's a child's fantasy!
You're funny, Luffy!
I can't wait to see how you turn out
in the future!
I admit that when Luffy said it,
Sabo and I laughed!
But we won't let anyone else laugh at it...
Because we believe in him!
We really think he can do it, so...
Ace!
What...
Hey!
What's wrong, Yamato?
I won't laugh!
Those are the exact words the King of the Pirates said!
The words that Oden was really amazed by!
In Kozuki Oden's journal,
there's this great man who said the same thing!
There's no reason for me to laugh!
Your brother is quite something!
Hmmm... A great man, huh?
That's good to know!
I hope I can drink with him and Luffy someday!
I'm sure you guys would get along!
But he's already dead.
He is?!
Well, in that case, we can't see him...
Hey...
What is it this time?
Um... How about me instead?
You and your brother and me!
If I go out to the sea someday...
Sounds like fun!
Yeah?!
But, Yamato, you know how big the sea is?
If you don't hurry,
I don't know if we can see each other again...
Then, Ace,
can I have...
...your fingernail or hair clipping?!
Either one will be fine!
Okay...
I made this!
This is your Vivre Card!
Is this it?
It's just a piece of paper.
That's right! This piece of paper
will bring us together again!
Bring us together?
Look!
Heh!
Tear off a piece to anyone you don't wanna
get separated from or wanna meet again.
Okay!
I'll do so.
Yamato!
Don't lose it!
Ace!
Yamato!
See you again for sure!
Ace!
Of course!
But...
...that was the last time I saw him.
ODEN'S TRAVEL RECORD
He's doing it again... My foolish son.
But that's fine. I have free time now
because of Red-Haired's interruption.
I can deal with the brat's temper tantrum.
You said you'd come back here!
It doesn't matter what he clings on to...
He'll never be able to get off...
...this island.
I can't get off of this island!
I can't beat my father!
I can't go and save...
...my only friend!
I'm...
...not free...
Why are you letting them chain your heart?!
I wanna...
...live freely like Oden...
Ace!
ODEN'S TRAVEL RECORD
"More than 20 years into the future,
young, strong pirates who will lead the next era
will come surging into the New World!"
But the toughest one
will come out to the sea in a few years...
It's my brother!
Go home, Yamato.
I'll wait, too...
For the thing Kozuki Oden was waiting for...
Please come back, Young Master Yamato!
I'll wait for the next era...
I'll wait forever!
Luffy, I'll be waiting for you!
Until you come here, I'll...
If you don't get it
no matter how many times I tell you,
I'll just keep knocking it into you, Yamato!
And I'll just keep beating it into you, too!
Yes, Yamato!
I'm Oden! You damn old man!
On that day, I didn't know
what was happening in the outer world,
but I read all about it in the newspaper later.
I learned that Ace was the son of
Gol D. Roger, the King of the Pirates,
and his brother was
really making a name as a pirate!
That's Luffy who you brought!
Momonosuke-kun.
ODEN'S TRAVEL RECORD
I, of course, give this to you.
This is what Oden wrote about the future...
"More than 20 years into the future,
young, strong pirates who will lead the next era
will come surging into the New World.
If I die...
they're the ones who'll bring Kaido down!"
The One Piece...
You guys can't even dream of
being able to contend for it...
Do you wanna continue playing pirates?
You're not good at educating people, Kaido...
Let me do it!
Yeah, I know, Killer...
I know how you feel...
I've gathered all these things!
Take them, you damn Emperors!
One after another!
So loose...
You Straw Hats are all like that?
This isn't my fault!
I don't see the loosest one...
Where's Straw Hat-ya?
Now more of them are here.
They're the Worst Generation, aren't they?
They'll scatter like dust in the wind...
You guys aren't strong enough
to reopen this old scar!
Withdraw gracefully, damn rookies!
Like the Akazaya members did...
ODEN'S TRAVEL RECORD
"More than 20 years into the future,
young, strong pirates who will lead the next era
will come surging into the New World!
If I die...
they're the ones...
...who'll bring Kaido down!"
Another one came...
Why don't you guys watch how it's done?!
--I refuse!
--Me, too!
I wanna take all of their heads!
Straw Hat...
Linlin! What do you think that brat said
he was gonna be right in front of me?!
He's impertinent...
You gave me some mouth, too!
And how could you destroy my castle?!
Apologize to me first, Straw Hat!
Hey, you punk...
Say again what you're gonna be...
...right in front of our faces!
I am counting on you guys!
Luffy-dono!
Thank you!
Are you okay, Kin'emon?
I'm sorry...
...for being late.
I... I feel chagrined...
I-I am...
...too ashamed to face Oden-sama in the afterlife!
Kin...
Can you carry...
...the Land of Wano on your back?!
Ple...
You fool! Of course I will!
It's my friend's country!
Hey, brat!
Luffy-dono...
Thank you...
Tra-guy!
Move all of them downstairs!
Why is it shaking again?!
Luffy...
You call it Haki,
but we call it Ryuo in the Land of Wano.
It has the meaning of "flow."
Oden-sama was executed!
GRAVE OF KOZUKI ODEN
By the Shogun of the Land of Wano
and the pirate Kaido!
Raizo-dono is safe!
We'd never sell out our friends!
Listen!
You-gara guys must go forward!
Ebisu Town's happy-go-lucky guy
will cross over to the other side!
The fire of rebellion isn't extinguished!
All ships, to Onigashima!
Charge!
20 years ago,
the day that Oden got killed by Kaido,
this country came to a standstill, right?!
No one in this world deserves to be laughed at
as they die!
A stranger's not allowed to save this country?!
You say it!
I thought you were an important person!
You're a leader of these great men,
aren't you?!
I want to bring down Kaido!
Gum-Gum...
...Red...
...Roc!
Hey, Kaido... What are you doing?!
I can't believe you got knocked down!
I'm Monkey D. Luffy.
I'm the man who'll best you guys...
...and become the King of the Pirates!
Zoro-senpai and Sanji-senpai
who do the heavy lifting for the Straw Hats!
I'll tell you all about their heroic actions in the Land of Wano!
I really can't wait to see their adventures all over again!
On the next episode of One Piece! "A Special Episode
to Admire Zoro-senpai and Sanji-senpai! Barto's Secret Room 2!"
Luffy-senpai's gonna become the King of the Pirates!