Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Draw your own map
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha ni areta umi no youna jidai
Even the values we had built up were about to fall apart
kizukiageta kachikan sae mo kuzuresarou to shita
Who knows if the compass is pointing in the right direction?
rashinban no sashita saki ga tadashii no ka douka nante
No one knows for certain
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
I do it for my own
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
And you do yours, don't we?
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And I'm ready for it
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
With the support of someone I can rely
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
Seize the future beyond your imagination
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
We'll go wherever we wanna go
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
Tears and doubts in tow
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Let's paint it in our own colors
onore no iro de egaite yuke
Can you carry...
...the Land of Wano on your back?!
Ple...
You fool! Of course I will!
It's my friend's country!
Luffy-dono...
Thank you...
Gum-Gum...
...Red...
...Roc!
I'm Monkey D. Luffy.
I'm the one who'll best you guys...
...and become the King of the Pirates!
"The Battle of the Monsters!
The Three Stubborn Captains!"
Hey, Kaido... What are you doing?!
I can't believe you got knocked down!
His attack worked against me?!
You still say that?! You shitty brat!
The King of the Pirates?!
Hey, stop resting!
Are you messing with me?
That was just some squirt's weak punch!
So that's the Haki
that the old man from the Land of Wano taught him...
What was that Haki?
Punches can hurt Kaido?!
Ryuo...
Ryuo?!
The Haki that he wears
destroys his opponents from the inside...
From inside, huh? I like that.
There is a chance of winning!
More importantly,
there's something I have to say to Straw Hat-ya.
Hey, you brat!
Do you have any idea
how influential the King of the Pirates is?!
What happened to him
after he took a pounding from me in Kuri?
Gum-Gum...
...King Kong Gun!
Thunder Bagua!
This little punk didn't even catch my attention...
...at that time!
I only know a few people...
...who are capable of fighting me.
Are you suggesting you're as good as those guys?
Straw Hat!
Are you suggesting you're capable of
fighting a deadly battle against me?
You're still a fledging punk!
You think you're that great?!
Straw Hat!
Look at that relaxed smile...
Let's go to hell together!
I feel a tingling sensation on my skin!
Kill them all!
Everyone and everything will be destroyed!
Thunder Bagua!
Damn! I predicted the attack, but it was...
...too fast!
Well done! You didn't take it directly this time!
You suck, Kaido!
Trash should be burned!
Prometheus!
Yes, Mama!
Get burned to dust!
Heavenly Fire!
Foxfire Style Flame-Rend!
Prometheus!
Kin'emon's technique!
That's amazing, Zoro!
I stole it!
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
You hurt me!
Don't lower your guard even a bit, Luffy!
There are two Emperors of the Sea!
Please stop... That's enough!
Women...
Women!
Don't get fooled!
Th-This is...
...unmistakably...
...heaven!
BANQUET HALL, THIRD FLOOR, INSIDE THE CASTLE
You don't need to go anywhere, do you?
Cut it out!
Do you think I have time to stay here?
I do!
I'll stay here forever!
No! This isn't the time for this!
I gotta go!
Untie me!
You may say so,
but you kind of like writhing too, don't you?
What's the point of being in a hurry anymore?
Stay here forever.
I won't go anywhere.
I gotta get out of here now...
...or not!
I'm gonna stay!
No! What am I saying?!
I have things to do!
But you actually wanna stay here forever, right?
Let's have some fun.
There's no point
in going through all that trouble to get there now...
right?
Screw you!
I really need to get there...
...or not!
I thought so.
Then why don't you stay here for a while
and answer my question...
Stop it!
Don't come any closer!
I'm gonna go...
...crazy!
Tell me...
...where are...
...your fellow crewmembers?
I wish I could stay in heaven!
Farewell, my ladies!
I shall return!
Very funny.
No! Don't run away!
Please, lady, don't stop me!
Hey, you... Wait!
You little cheapskate!
A bunch of ladies,
I'm lucky but cornered!
Sorry, my ladies!
Until the next time,
see you again!
I-I'm so...
...thrilled now!
The famous
"Whaddya say? That's naughty" bit!
I get to... I get to...
I get to...
Whaddya say?!
That's naughty!
I-I-I love it!
No!
Sexual harassment is never allowed!
No matter how good a man you pretend to be,
you're one of those guys who abandon their women...
...to chase their dreams.
Do as you like...
...and use violence to dominate women.
If you wanna leave, it's easy.
Go ahead...
...and kick me.
With that leg that you're proud of
which is burning with a sense of justice.
You realize it yourself, don't you?
You're actually having fun
when you kick someone, right?
I...
...would rather die than kick a woman!
I like you, boy.
Very cute.
How can you survive being so naive?
I guess you have wonderful friends.
I want you to tell me...
...about your wonderful friends.
Especially where the woman named Nico Robin is now.
I refuse!
You didn't even hesitate.
There's no reason for me to hesitate.
That makes me jealous.
I'll ask...
...your body about Nico Robin!
I don't like this!
Don't lower your guard even a bit, Luffy!
There are two Emperors of the Sea!
Chambres!
Hey, Straw Hat-ya.
Tra-guy! You saved me! Thanks!
Listen! We formed an alliance!
Allies must stand as equals!
What are you talking about?!
So there's something I wanna say to you!
I...
...was gonna move them downstairs anyway!
But you...
Tra-guy! Move all of them downstairs!
It was like...
...I followed your order!
Why do you care about such a thing?!
I'm happy for you, Straw Hat!
You got yourself another subordinate!
A subordinate?! Who?!
Trafalgar...
I thought you finally became
Straw Hat's subordinate...
N-No way!
I don't care
if a loser subordinates another loser...
Shut up, loser!
Who did you call "loser"?!
You're the only loser here!
It can't be me!
It's you! You! You!
They're such good friends.
You were freaking out before,
you damn silly monkey!
You were just watching in the back,
Jaggy, you jerk!
I'm not a loser!
Stop chewing the fat!
Burn them all up, Prometheus!
Yes, Mama!
Heavenly Bon-Bons!
Okay, here's the deal!
The one who dodges her attack first loses!
No way, you idiot!
You always think of dumb games like that!
That's why you guys can't become big shots!
All right! Then you guys are losers!
Suit yourselves!
I'm not playing!
Why don't you run, you chickenshit?!
Just dodge, you wimp!
Hey, watch out!
What are you guys doing?!
Now who's gonna become the King of the Pirates?!
Let's see...
How am I gonna kill you?
Linlin, get back!
I wanna see how strong they are.
Why would you wanna see that?
Damn! You guys moved, didn't you?!
I didn't move!
No, I saw both of you moving!
Don't get in my way, Hitokiri Kamazo!
There aren't that many people
who have such a weird laugh.
Onigiri!
If I had these Punishers on at that time,
you would've died!
Zorojuro...
I don't think so.
Beheading Claws!
Three-Sword Style!
Purgatory...
...Onigiri!
The cut is too shallow!
I'm impressed with you!
I gotta unleash Enma's power a little more!
Kaido!
We'll finish you off in one go!
What did you say?
Say that again.
Gear Four!
Punk Rotten!
Room!
They're...
...like monsters!
The great battle over the title of King of the Pirates!
Against the Emperors of the Sea who stand in their way,
the rookies use a triune technique!
Defeat Kaido! To take down his formidable enemy
and fulfill his dream of becoming the King of the Pirates,
Luffy's all-out punch lets loose!
On the next episode of One Piece! "A Barrage of Powerful
Techniques! The Fierce Attacks of the Worst Generation!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!