iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
Draw your own map
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha
ni areta umi no youna jidai
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
kizukiageta kachikan sae
mo kuzuresarou to shita
Even the values we had built
up were about to fall apart
rashinban no sashita saki ga
tadashii no ka douka nante
Who knows if the compass is
pointing in the right direction?
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
No one knows for certain
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
I do it for my own
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And you do yours, don't we?
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
And I'm ready for it
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
With the support of someone I can rely
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Seize the future beyond your imagination
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
We'll go wherever we wanna go
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
Tears and doubts in tow
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Let's paint it in our own colors
onore no iro de egaite yuke
Thunder Bagua!
Damn! I predicted the attack...
Heavenly Fire!
Foxfire Style Flame-Rend!
Kin'emon's technique!
That's amazing, Zoro!
I stole it!
Linlin, get back!
I wanna see how strong they are.
Beheading Claws!
Three-Sword Style!
Purgatory...
...Onigiri!
The cut is too shallow!
Kaido!
We'll finish you off in one go!
"A Barrage of Powerful Techniques!
The Fierce Attacks of the Worst Generation!"
Gear Four!
Bounce-Man!
All right!
Punk Rotten!
Room!
Takt!
They're like monsters!
Bring it on! Let me see if you guys
are strong enough to become...
...the King of the Pirates!
Gum-Gum...
...Kong Gun!
Ow...
That hurts!
I'm well aware of your thick skin!
But I bet you can be crushed to death!
As you wish, I'll show you how strong I am!
Punk Vise!
That's not bad, but it needs more mass.
Then I'm gonna add some.
What the?!
Takt!
Damn!
You bastard!
You were gonna kill me too, weren't you?!
I followed up your half-assed attack
with a stronger one of my own.
What did you say?!
Jaggy! Tra-guy!
Jeez, guys...
Don't fight here now!
You guys are helpless.
--Don't tell me what to do!
--I won't follow your orders!
I could've taken care of them
all by myself without you losers.
My attack harmed him the most!
Straw Hat's punches were so weak!
You losers better stand back!
What did you say, Jaggy?!
--The smaller the dog, the louder the bark!
--The same goes for you!
That's enough for now, Kid.
Don't lower your guard, Luffy.
Okay!
Tsk! But it's not settled...
I know that it wasn't enough to kill him...
Oh, that hurts!
It kills me!
I haven't felt such pain...
...since those days!
Yum-yum! I'm fully charged!
Not bad, you little shits...
That's what I expected from idiots
who aspire to be the King of the Pirates...
But...
...you can't stop me anymore!
It's so sad...
I know you guys won't
last long either anyway.
Once you guys die, I'll take everything!
Which includes your crewmembers
who are here on this island!
I won't let you do that!
Not just your crewmembers.
We'll take your treasure too!
The Ponegliffs.
I'm sure you guys have them with you.
Can't wait!
I'll take your crewmembers
and treasure instead!
Whoever wins this battle
will be one big step closer...
...to becoming the King of the Pirates!
I'm the one who'll become...
...the King of the Pirates!
Demolition Gust!
DEMOLITION GUST
Kid!
It was only made of metal scraps anyway!
Kaido!
You stupid King-of-the-Pirates pretenders!
Entertain me!
The samurai crumbled miserably!
Loyalty to Oden alone...
...won't open the way to the future!
I will reign over the Land of Wano!
Can you carry...
...the Land of Wano on your back?!
Gum-Gum...
...Kong...
KONG
...Rifle!
Wake up, Mr. Emperor of the Sea!
SLAM
Slam Gibson!
Room!
Chambres!
I've never seen
a diagram of a dragon's organs before...
...but I guess your heart is around here!
Gamma Knife!
I'm gonna destroy you from the inside!
How annoying!
So you've learned how strong my body is!
I guess you guys are not
just some ballsy idiots!
This hard skin has been
a big pain in the ass!
I should just cut into the body, right?!
Scyther...
SCYTHER SONIC
...Sonic!
It hurt you a little, didn't it?!
Kaido!
Indra!
Killer!
As long as you're under this sky,
there is no escape for you guys!
They're more entertaining than I expected!
Rhino Schneider!
Not bad!
Tra-guy!
Move me up!
Now you're telling what to do...
I'm not your servant!
Foxfire Style...
Blast Breath!
Flame-Rend!
Zoro!
One more time!
Tra-guy!
I said stop using me as a tool!
What the?!
Dodge, Kaido!
That's not an ordinary sword!
One-Sword Style!
Flying Dragon Blaze!
Why do I feel...
...Oden's presence in his sword?!
Damn! I missed it!
You underestimated us too much.
Indra!
Zoro!
You've got no place to run!
God of Lightning Tenjin!
Damn! A "natural disaster," huh?!
Straw Hat!
Why didn't you get hurt by the lightning?!
Because I'm rubber!
How dare you hurt Zoro and the others!
Blast Breath!
Fire doesn't work either?! Why?!
My guts!
Gum-Gum...
...Kong...
...Gatling!
The game-changing Kong Gatling blasts!
Luffy's highly-trained
punches push Kaido hard!
The hand-to-hand combat becomes more intense!
Will he be able to take
him down in the momentum?!
He devotes his full strength to beat Kaido!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Kaido Laughs! The Emperors of
the Sea vs. the New Generation!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!