Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Draw your own map
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha ni areta umi no youna jidai
Even the values we had built up were about to fall apart
kizukiageta kachikan sae mo kuzuresarou to shita
Who knows if the compass is pointing in the right direction?
rashinban no sashita saki ga tadashii no ka douka nante
No one knows for certain
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
I do it for my own
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
And you do yours, don't we?
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And I'm ready for it
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
With the support of someone I can rely
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
Seize the future beyond your imagination
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
We'll go wherever we wanna go
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
Tears and doubts in tow
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Let's paint it in our own colors
onore no iro de egaite yuke
Luffy, Zoro, Law, Kid, and Killer challenge Kaido.
Purgatory...
...Onigiri!
Beheading Claws!
Kong Gun!
As you wish, I'll show you how strong I am!
Punk Vise!
Takt!
That's what I expected from idiots
who aspire to be the King of the Pirates...
But...
...you can't stop me anymore!
God of Lightning Tenjin!
Big Mom fought back
and the scales have turned against Luffy and the others.
Straw Hat!
Why didn't you get hurt by lightning?!
Because I'm rubber!
How dare you hurt Zoro and the others!
Blast Breath!
Fire doesn't work either?! Why?!
My guts!
Gum-Gum...
...Kong...
...Gatling!
"Kaido Laughs!
The Emperors of the Sea vs. the New Generation!"
He did it?!
Kaido!
This will finish you, Kaido!
Oh, no!
Straw Hat?! When did you get hit?!
He didn't get hit!
It's a by-product of that iron-ball-like technique!
He can't use Haki for 10 minutes or so!
I see. Power with a risk.
But if all of those attacks worked on him,
it's our chance to finish him off!
Don't push your luck!
Luffy! You gotta move or you'll die!
What? You're already worn out?!
Well done rampaging!
Let's get it over with now!
Happy Mother's...
...Blaze!
Hand over Straw Hat to me!
Counter Shock!
Luffy! Wake up!
Let's launch further attacks on Kaido, Killer!
Okay!
Killer! Watch out!
The wind that blows heavenward...
...destroys everything...
Dragon Twister!
Killer!
You've got to be kidding!
This is practically a natural disaster!
Zoro, thanks...
Yeah.
Luffy!
Whoa-whoa!
You bastard! Don't chomp on our captain!
I see!
That sword is where I sense the strange Haki!
Three-Sword Style!
Black Rope Dragon Twister!
He cut his scales!
That punk! He cut Kaido!
Oh, that hurts!
I see...
Just as I thought, that sword...
Oden Two-Sword Style!
...is Oden's sword, isn't it?!
He competes against me using Dragon Twister...
He doesn't know his place!
Hey! Luffy!
Oh, Zoro?
Look out for the big attack!
Dragon Twister...
...Demolition Gust!
Gee...
We never imagined our supplier would die,
and the banquet that we were invited to...
...would turn into a battlefield.
CIPHER POL "AIGIS" ZERO
WORLD'S MOST POWERFUL INTELLIGENCE AGENCY
I heard it's a battle to win vengeance
for one who died 20 years ago in this country.
Yeah...
But when Doflamingo fell from power,
the clash between Kaido and the Worst Generation
became inevitable.
King Kong...
God Thread!
...Gun!
It was fate...
...that brought the samurai
and the pirates together.
At the time when the world's situation
is about to turn over...
If by any chance both of those Emperors of the Sea
get taken down...
No one can tell what will happen in the world.
But there's no worry of that.
The number of enemies that invaded the island...
...is 5,400
But 400 of them have fallen
On the other hand
we Animal Kingdom Pirates...
...have more than 30,000 troops
But 3,000 of them have already fallen
The samurai did a good job.
The difference in power means they can't even
reach the leader if they attacked head-on.
The operation to launch a successful sneak attack
was brilliant.
But this battle won't end
even if they chop off the leader's head.
(27,000) / (5,000)
This is an all-out war, there's no refuge on the island.
If they leave Kaido's powerful top officers at large,
those officers will take down 100 soldiers at a time.
If the Worst Generation can't stop the top officers...
This game of Go will end
with all black pieces on the board.
It's a little too obvious which side will win...
Crush as many of each other as you can...
You pirates.
I've never seen him in that form!
Is that his Man-Beast Form?
Hey, Linlin!
This is fun!
I was just thinking the same!
Kaido!
A girl who wishes a better future for the Land of Wano.
Otama, who runs through the tumultuous Onigashima,
executes her plan with determination!
To save her friends who are fighting unsupported,
will she be able to give them a chance to recover
and turn the one-sided battle against Kaido's army?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Otama's Secret Plan! Operation Kibi Dango!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!