iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
Draw your own map
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha
ni areta umi no youna jidai
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
kizukiageta kachikan sae
mo kuzuresarou to shita
Even the values we had built
up were about to fall apart
Who knows if the compass is
pointing in the right direction?
rashinban no sashita saki ga
tadashii no ka douka nante
No one knows for certain
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
I do it for my own
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
And you do yours, don't we?
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And I'm ready for it
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
With the support of someone I can rely
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
Seize the future beyond your imagination
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
We'll go wherever we wanna go
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
Tears and doubts in tow
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Let's paint it in our own colors
onore no iro de egaite yuke
Luffy! You gotta move or you'll die!
What? You're already worn out?!
Well done rampaging!
Let's get it over with now!
Happy Mother's Blaze!
Counter Shock!
Let's launch further
attacks on Kaido, Killer!
The wind that blows heavenward...
...destroys everything...
Dragon Twister!
Killer!
Hey, Linlin!
This is fun!
I was just thinking the same!
Kaido!
"Otama's Secret Plan!
Operation Kibi Dango!"
Listen up, you guys!
The Straw Hats and the samurai
brazenly made a raid on us.
But we still haven't brought them under yet!
SPEED - A HEADLINER OF THE BEAST PIRATES
WITH THE HORSE SMILE FRUIT
To break the deadlock,
Queen-sama entrusted me with something great.
You're as hot as always, Speed-sama!
Where is the thing?
This is it.
What?
Just a dumpling?
That's not it!
Yeah okay, I know why you doubt it!
But lo and behold.
It'll dramatically enhance curative power,
and improve muscle strength...
...significantly!
--What?!
--Are you sure?!
But...
...it looks really delicious...
Let me eat that dumpling!
BRISCOLA
A HEADLINER OF THE ANIMAL KINGDOM PIRATES
WITH THE GORILLA SMILE FRUIT
Seems like you got beaten
very badly, Briscola.
Shut up!
I need to avenge myself against
those annoying, shitty Straw hats,
otherwise, I'm not gonna be satisfied!
I'll let you eat it then.
If you eat one, it'll change everything.
Here.
How is it, Briscola-san?
Feels like it's working...
Or maybe not...
No way.
You fool...
You're not trying to say this dumpling
that Queen-sama made...
...is a failure, are you?
Gulp!
Boing!
Boing! Boing! Boing!
Wee!
It's amazing!
I feel a surge of power!
That's awesome!
I want one too, Briscola-sama!
Speed-sama! May I have that dumpling, too?!
I want one!
Two for us!
Of course!
I have enough for all Gifters!
Yay!
It's good!
Once you finish eating, get ready to fight!
Don't waste your time!
The Straw Hats won't wait for us!
A FEW HOURS EARLIER
Master-sama.
Horselina-chan...
You were gone for a while,
so I came to see if you're okay...
Is something wrong?
Everyone's left for Onigashima.
I know it's a dangerous place.
No one allowed me to go with them...
But...
Horselina-chan!
I wanna go to Onigashima, too!
I don't wanna just wait like this
while they're fighting for their lives...
So...
Neigh! Leave it to me, Master-sama!
I'll get you a ship immediately!
Take care! Speed-sama!
Catch all samurai who go against Kaido-sama
in one fell swoop!
GAZELLE-MAN - A GIFTER FROM BAKURA TOWN
WITH THE GAZELLE SMILE FRUIT
We managed to set sail!
Of course!
DAIFUGO - A HEADLINER
VICE WARDEN OF UDON'S EXCAVATION LABOR CAMP
Because they don't know
that we ate Master-sama's Kibi Dango.
You can come out now, Master-sama.
Thank you all!
No problem.
But...
...even if we join the samurai and fight,
the Animal Kingdom Pirates on Onigashima
have so many more soldiers than us.
If we clash head-on...
Whoa-whoa...
We don't even have a
slight chance of winning.
I have an idea!
Don't tell me...
Kibi Dango!
For each dumpling, we can make one new ally!
I'll make tons of these before we reach Onigashima
so we can let everyone eat them!
I love the idea, Master-sama!
Kibi Dango...
Kibi Dango!
Kibi Dan...
Master-sama, I think you better stop now...
I'm okay...
Don't push yourself!
You'll fall sick before we get to Onigashima!
I have to make more dumplings...
I can't bring down Kaido myself...
This is all I can do to help...
Momo-kun...
...will become a wonderful Shogun.
Big Bro Luffy...
...said he'd make the Land of Wano
a country where we can eat as much as we want!
And the samurai...
...are all fighting for this country...
So...
...I'll do what I can to help!
The Land of Wano free of Orochi and Kaido,
that's ruled by Momo-kun!
That's what I want!
On top of that, I don't
wanna be hungry anymore...
I wanna eat...
Okay.
Let's fight!
Yeah, let's do it!
Let's have a meal first,
then hide and wait for a chance!
--Okay!
--All right!
And the time...
...has finally come!
I'm a swift runner!
I run at 200 kilometers per hour!
Ready...
Start!
Eat this!
What?! It's good!
Delicious!
--Eat this!
--Delicious!
Come on, eat it, Gifters!
Look! He's the vice warden
from Udon, Daifugo!
Take him down!
You have tormented us so much!
Sorry about that! Forget it for now!
Whooacchoo!
Wee!
Oh, Daifugo-sama!
Thank you for your hard work!
Cut the boring greeting for now!
Eat this!
Wee!
Eat this! Become Master-sama's servant!
W-What the...
Victory! That is our name!
Damn samurai! Show yourselves!
Getting cut by my sword
or trodden down by my giraffe feet!
Go ahead and choose!
Should we make him our ally, too?
Of course! The more troops the better!
Mm-hm!
Here we go! Special Attack!
Millet Dumpling Star!
--Alright!
--You see that?!
I kind of feel itchy...
A girl... Why are you here?!
Shake hands!
Master-sama...
She is the one I worship!
That's a foot!
But it went well!
Keep feeding them like this!
Okay! Leave it to me!
Everybody, I'm counting on you!
Hey, Apoo!
What's taking you so long?!
Take back the antibody already!
I know!
We'll back you up.
The situation remains the same,
we have a definite advantage.
We can overwhelm them with numbers
in no time.
Oniwabanshu and Mimawari-gumi, huh?
Okay! Let's make a fresh start, guys!
Let them know we're out of their league!
Here we go!
Stop them here at any cost!
Do you think we can beat that many enemies?
We have no choice!
Tsk!
One after another!
Leave the front line to me.
How dependable.
Reliable help has arrived!
Just a little more patience!
What's wrong?
Oh yeah, he said...
...once our physical stamina runs out,
the effect of the flame will be gone...
Boss Hyogoro!
General Left!
It's not over yet!
Sasaki-sama!
This is it!
General...
Hold him down!
Hey, come on!
Don't get in my way, you fools!
Even with your tremendous power,
you can't shake off this many of us!
We're the Gifters,
we were given special abilities!
We're no ordinary soldiers!
They're so strong!
Take him down along with us, Sasaki-sama!
Bring him down at any cost!
Of course I will!
Franky!
That must be...
Usopp! Nami! And Otama!
Why are you here?!
This is not the time to ask that!
Thank goodness!
Can you guys do something about...
Help!
They're being chased by tons of enemies?!
I was already in trouble,
but now I'm in even bigger trouble!
Gifters! Keep going and block the way!
You guys are already vastly outnumbered!
You have no chance of winning
unless the tide turns all over the island!
What am I supposed to do?!
T...
To turn the tide, I came here!
Everyone, please!
Help Franosuke-kun!
Got it, Master-sama!
What?!
All right!
Whew! That was close!
That went well!
What are you guys thinking?!
Sasaki!
Page One! Ulti!
They changed sides! Smack them down!
Changed sides?!
What do they gain by
siding with the samurai?!
It's probably their ability!
Isn't that right?!
I guess you want your head
to be crushed this time!
Not again!
Lightning alert!
Your heart might get
paralyzed, so be careful!
Thunder Lance...
...Tempo!
Big Sis!
Damn! That hurts! Tsk!
She did it! That damn bitch!
I knew I couldn't take her down...
It should be more powerful lightning!
She used some weird trick!
Guys! Take them down!
They'll become a nuisance if we leave them be.
Aye-aye, Sasaki-sama!
I won't let you! Special Attack!
Millet Dumpling Star! Millet Dumpling Star!
Millet Dumpling Star!
What was that?
Everybody!
Follow me!
Aye-aye, Master-sama!
What?! Hey! What's going on?!
Wait, Armored Division!
Whoa-whoa.
Pay attention.
You're in a fight with...
...me, right?
Franken-Sword...
V-for-Victory Flash!
Sanji writhes in pain from Black
Maria’s full-course torture!
There is only one condition that will set him free!
Turning over the most important
member of the Straw Hats!
The merciless evil lady forces
him to make a tough choice!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Sanji's Scream! An SOS Echoes Over the Island!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!