Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Draw your own map
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha
ni areta umi no youna jidai
Even the values we had built
up were about to fall apart
kizukiageta kachikan sae
mo kuzuresarou to shita
Who knows if the compass is
pointing in the right direction?
rashinban no sashita saki ga
tadashii no ka douka nante
No one knows for certain
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
I do it for my own
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
And you do yours, don't we?
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And I'm ready for it
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
With the support of someone I can rely
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Seize the future beyond your imagination
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
We'll go wherever we wanna go
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Tears and doubts in tow
onore no iro de egaite yuke
Let's paint it in our own colors
Battles between the top officers
of the Animal Kingdom Pirates and
the Straw Hats erupt one after another!
General Franky and Sasaki
are in heavy hand-to-hand combat.
It's not over yet!
Sasaki-sama!
This is it!
General...
Hold him down!
Take him down along with us, Sasaki-sama!
Bring him down at any cost!
Of course I will!
Otama uses her wit to make
up for the overwhelming
difference in power against
the Animal Kingdom Pirates.
Gifters! Keep going and block the way!
You guys are already vastly outnumbered!
You have no chance to win
unless the tide turns all over the island!
T...
To turn the tide, I came here!
Everyone, please!
Help Franosuke-kun!
Got it, Master-sama!
What?!
Nami and the others inside the castle
start fighting back, too.
I guess you want your head
to be crushed this time!
Not again!
Lightning alert!
Your heart might get
paralyzed, so be careful!
Thunder Lance...
...Tempo!
Big Sis!
Whoa-whoa.
Pay attention.
You're in a fight with...
...me, right?
Franken-Sword...
V-for-Victory Flash!
"Sanji's Scream!
An SOS Echoes Over the Island!"
Roller-san!
Here we go!
Rolling, rolling, rolling, yes!
Roller-san!
Here we go!
Rolling, rolling, rolling!
Roller-san!
Here we go!
Rolling, rolling, rolling!
Roller-san!
Here we go!
It's an advanced version of
a game that is played with geisha!
Exclusively for you!
Oh, I like that look.
Everyone, come!
He's whining about not being rolled enough!
How cute!
Roller-san!
Sudden death!
Oh no! This is...
...too much!
Oh, my dear boy.
Are you tired?
Do you wanna go night-night?
That's enough...
I'm satisfied...
Let me go!
What?! You've already gotten bored?!
Then, let's play something more...
...intense!
Damn...
That's too intense...
W-What the hell is this?!
This isn't my kind of game...
No more games...
Be a good boy.
Black-Leg Sanji.
Gee...
You're acting up. How cute.
You're strong but it's a shame.
You beat the hell out of the men,
but you can't even lay a finger on women.
So you have no chance of winning.
Your life is in the palm of my hand now...
Now, call for...
...Nico Robin!
This is Caiman Lady.
If you speak loudly to her,
you'll be heard all over the castle.
Then I'll set you free.
It's Kaido-san's order.
What are you gonna do to Robin-chan?
Let's see...
We'll gang up to catch her...
...and paralyze her
by grievously wounding her limbs.
But until the end of our little errand
which could take years to complete,
she won't get killed, so don't worry.
Damn you... Don't underestimate Nico Robin!
WIND
The Akazaya samurai got away from the rooftop
and went somewhere, it seems!
Hey, brat!
Tra-guy! Move all of them downstairs!
They must not have gotten
that far yet, I think!
Find them!
Let me try and see if you're truly immortal!
That's what I'd expect from a man
who calls himself King-yoi.
You guys are so cool!
Sulongs!
Are you really okay without Marco?
Lick!
We're gonna take you down at any cost!
I like your high spirits.
But you'll be licked.
Is this his ability?
How annoying!
Wanda! This candy is dangerous!
Carrot!
That's right!
That candy will instantly
coat your whole body...
...and seep into your system.
You can't breathe anymore, can you?
And when it's solidified...
...a sweet corpse...
...Candyman is complete!
Lick, lick!
I'll lick you up later!
Lick!
Anyway, how could you cut my lovely face
over some crappy grudge.
You Minks are such a pain in the ass!
Bombs?!
Let go of me!
Goodbye.
That Jaguar Mink who took
my right arm away...
...really died for nothing after all!
Poor him...
Wanda!
What?! No way!
Don't insult Pedro!
He sacrificed his life
for the world to see the dawn!
He made all this possible!
Eleclaw!
I see...
You softened the candy
with the heat of your electric attack...
Sulong...
You Minks are really annoying...
Lick!
But...
...that power needs the full moon.
The moon...
You better pay attention!
Candy Maiden!
Nice try!
Wanda!
Focus, Carrot!
I found them! I found them!
I found the Akazaya samurai!
They got away from the battle on the rooftop,
it seems!
Covered in blood!
But they're still alive, it seems!
They're located at the
back of the castle tower!
The second floor of the Treasure Repository
at the second bailey!
They must've escaped from Kaido-san.
I'm busy now.
Can someone else handle it?
Go to the Treasure Repository right away
and kill all the samurai!
Did you hear that, Black Maria-sama?
Yes, King...
I'll go.
The second floor of the Treasure Repository
is connected to this floor.
I should just finish the
Akazaya members, right?
Yeah, thanks!
Kin'emon... They got beaten?!
Wait! Don't go!
But be careful!
There are ten people in that...
...room!
It's dark so I can't see clearly,
but someone is trying to help the samurai!
Hurry up and kill them!
Someone's...
...there!
Alright! All we need to do now
is make a lot of them!
B-Boss!
Guys! Don't touch me!
Raccoon-san, how is it?!
It'll be ready soon!
Damn...
I can't believe I'm dying here!
I'm sorry, straw hat man!
I wanted to help you,
but I gave you trouble instead!
No... Not yet!
I haven't paid back my debt
to Luffytaro-san and the others!
If I'm gonna die anyway,
I'll at least stop the enemies for them!
Die, old man!
Boss Hyogoro...
Your body!
BANQUET HALL, THIRD FLOOR, INSIDE THE CASTLE
Okay, I must go and kill the samurai...
But before that,
I have to finish the job at hand quickly.
Caiman Lady, are you ready
to broadcast his voice all over the island?
Yes, I am!
Black-Leg...
Could you call Nico Robin here now?
We're all ready to go...
Around the entrance, multiple
layers of the sticky Hard Gum
that never comes off once it sticks on you...
...are all set up.
It's on the floor too,
so you'll get stuck once you step on it.
And my subordinates with tranquilizer guns
are waiting ahead.
All there is left to do...
...is for you to just call for her!
Nico Robin!
Come on, call for help!
I have another task to do!
Robin-chan...
Let me... join your crew.
What?!
I...
I want to live!
Take me to the sea with you!
I...
Orobi-chan! How does it taste?
Well, it tastes amazing!
Orobi-chan the geisha is more amazing!
You're stubborn...
You don't have to be so patient...
Come on! Come on! Come on!
Oh, I can't watch...
It makes me cry...
I think that man is trying to
protect his crewmate...
He'll die without saying a word!
If he wasn't our enemy,
I would've fallen in love!
W-Wait!
Give me a chance to at least say a few words!
I bet he just wants to say something
like "Screw you" before he dies!
Stop! If you make her any angrier...
Robin-chan...
I... I...
I...
...wanted to see your smile again...
Help me, Robin-chan!
What?!
He was actually ready to call for help!
I'm on the third floor!
The Banquet Hall!
I've been taken hostage! I'm sorry!
Sanji.
If Robin-chan doesn't come, they'll kill me!
Help!
What's that?! How pathetic!
Is that a member of the Straw Hats?!
Whoa-whoa, it's echoing all over the island!
Nico Robin is one of
the most important figures in the world.
I knew they would want her knowledge!
It's obviously a trap to capture Robin!
A man shouldn't sound miserable like that!
They're so funny-yoi!
The enemy is most likely a woman.
Gee.
Hey, Nami! That's where it's coming from!
Be careful!
--I saw one earlier! What is that eye?!
--You're my only hope!
Come quickly!
Robin-chan!
I can't believe it.
I called for Robin-chan, so untie me now.
What?!
Ma'am, someone's coming!
That's very quick!
I won't release you.
You said you loved me.
It's not business, it's personal from now on.
I wanna keep you as a pet like them.
I'll make your body unable
to live without me.
I only love Black Maria-sama...
I wanna love all the ladies!
I forbid you to be unfaithful like that!
I'll discipline you!
Wait! I don't wanna hurt any lady,
so my Color of Arms has been softened!
Mil Fleurs!
Gigantesco Mano!
Spank!
Robin-chan!
Black Maria plots to mesmerize
the bruised Sanji,
but Robin and Brook step
in to teach her a lesson.
The Tobi Roppo member
becomes infuriated seeing
the bond between the
members of the Straw Hats
and the new battle with their pride on the line
erupts with the flames of anger!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Spank Strikes! Sanji's Woman-trouble!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!