iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
Draw your own map
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha
ni areta umi no youna jidai
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
kizukiageta kachikan sae
mo kuzuresarou to shita
Even the values we had built
up were about to fall apart
rashinban no sashita saki ga
tadashii no ka douka nante
Who knows if the compass is
pointing in the right direction?
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
No one knows for certain
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
I do it for my own
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And you do yours, don't we?
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
And I'm ready for it
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
With the support of someone I can rely
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Seize the future beyond your imagination
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
We'll go wherever we wanna go
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Tears and doubts in tow
onore no iro de egaite yuke
Let's paint it in our own colors
The battle between Luffy's group, Kaido, and Big Mom
is getting intense.
God of Lightning Tenjin!
How dare you hurt Zoro and the others!
Blast Breath!
Candy Maiden!
Wanda!
Focus, Carrot!
W-Wait!
Give me a chance to at least say a few words!
I bet he just wants to say something
like "Screw you" before he dies!
Stop! If you make her any angrier...
I wanted to see your smile again...
Help me, Robin-chan!
"Spank Strikes!
Sanji's Woman-trouble!"
I'll make your body unable
to live without me.
I wanna love all the ladies!
I forbid you to be unfaithful like that!
I'll discipline you!
Wait! I don't wanna hurt any lady,
so my Color of Arms has been softened!
Mil Fleurs!
Gigantesco Mano!
Spank!
Black Maria-sama!
How did you get in here?!
I can sprout anywhere.
How dare you hit my face...
You thought you could catch me easily
if you just lured me?
Robin-chan!
I was part of an evil organization
for a long time.
If you mess with my friends,
I can't...
...stop myself...
...from showing my devilish side!
Oh, excuse me! I cut you up
gathering the chill of the underworld!
Brook!
Ma'am, the tranquilizer gun unit
has been taken down!
--The spider thread traps...
--...are all frozen and broken, too!
It seems like the spider thread
and the chill of the underworld go well together!
Ghosts!
Look who's talking!
Thank you! You saved me...
No problem.
I'm sorry, but I'm gonna go help
Kin'emon and the others!
I don't know why,
but I see no chance of winning here!
No wonder.
Wait, Black-Leg! You'll be my pet!
I won't let you go!
Is that it?
That's your last words?
You wanna die for that bastard
who sells out his friend?
No, Black Maria...
You don't understand.
Friends are wonderful.
Sanji!
Thank you for relying on me!
It made me happy!
Oh, it's frozen there.
Whoa-whoa-whoa!
Thank you!
PERFORMANCE FLOOR, INSIDE THE DOME
Attention!
Momonosuke is in the Forbidden Storehouse!
Someone's watching.
What?!
Is it you?!
Take this!
Why is smoke coming out of a mouse?
They're Marys,
the surveillance force of my father's army.
They're cyborgs.
--Cy...
--...borg?
They're animals
with mechanized body parts.
What?!
They're roaming around the island
without purpose,
but they share their vision
with human Marys!
What?!
Momonosuke is in the Forbidden Storehouse!
So what this mouse saw...
Human Marys must've seen
the exact same thing...
That means this place...
Hey, is it really this storehouse?
No one enters this cursed place now...
I see no signs of anyone entering from here.
But they said this was the place!
I'm sure Young Master Yamato's here!
I mean, the next Shogun-sama!
There are a number of them.
This place isn't safe anymore!
Let's run, Yamato!
Show us the way
that'll keep Momonosuke-sama out of their sights!
Shogun-sama! Come on out!
Or we'll break down the door!
One, two!
They'll break through soon!
--Sorry, Momonosuke-kun!
--What?!
Hide in my clothes!
What?
Whaaat?!
Let's go, Shinobu-san!
I told you to keep him out of their sights!
I know! If we don't take them all down,
they'll see him!
That's not what I meant!
Damn you!
NEAR THE ENTRANCE, ONIGASHIMA
How could you do this to Wanda?!
Whoa-whoa...
Don't forget that we're all
fighting for our lives.
Lick!
If I don't do it, I'll get beaten.
Shut up!
Just like with the jaguar named Pedro
or whatever his name is,
you seem to like to hold grudges against people
for unjust reasons.
Perospero!
I'll bring you down at any cost!
With this Electro that
Pedro trained me to use!
You'll die for nothing, too!
Just like that Jaguar!
Candy Maiden!
Candy Armor!
The candy is...
I can't believe it.
How could I get screwed by the Rabbit Mink?!
This is it!
Lick!
They're running!
The enemy leader Momonosuke...
...is getting away from...
...the Forbidden Storehouse!
I can't see Momonosuke!
But I have no doubt!
Momonosuke is with Young Master Yamato
and the kunoichi!
MOMONOSUKE - LEADER
SHOGUN OF THE LAND OF WANO
This place is small and it's hard to breathe,
but for whatever reason,
it feels as if I'm in heaven!
Shinobu-san, this way!
They keep coming!
Lead us to an out-of-sight path already!
Don't worry!
If we beat them all up, we'll be out of their sights!
Again, that's not what I meant!
I repeat!
Momonosuke, who escaped
from the Forbidden Storehouse,
is with Young Master Yamato and the kunoichi!
Definitely!
That broadcast again...
They're going after Momo and Shinobu-chan!
Young Master Yamato?
Oh, well...
Hey, which way is the Forbidden Storehouse?!
I-I'm not gonna tell you.
It's near the entrance of the Skull Dome...
Kin'emon's group is at the
back of the castle tower...
BACK OF THE CASTLE TOWER
DOME ENTRANCE
It's in the opposite direction
of the Dome's entrance.
Kin'emon and the others
are injured from the fight...
Momo and Shinobu-chan
are being chased by the damn Gifters...
Which of them needs me?!
That way?! This way?!
Why am I still thinking?!
The ones who need me are probably this way!
Lick!
Nice try, full-moon warriors!
You guys need luck in weather to win!
Pedro...
Roger said, "Everyone has their own turn"!
This is my turn!
Listen!
You-gara guys must go forward!
I'll avenge Pedro at any cost...
Avenge Pedro?!
That bastard deserved to die!
Did you guys come to the Big Mom Pirates' territory
to have a picnic or something?!
If you don't want your friends to die,
why don't you munch on grass in a forest?!
That's what suits you. Lick!
Now... I'm not thrilled about the alliance
with the Animal Kingdom Pirates,
but if that's what Mama decided,
I have no choice...
We must teach those punks...
...that the Four Emperors of the Sea
are on a different level from them!
Is that...?!
He finally revealed it!
Are you scared?
Zoro...
--I need one minute.
--Yeah, leave it to me.
How could he sleep in this situation?
He's a funny man!
Pirate Hunter!
And Surgeon of Death, don't you think so?
I just formed an alliance
with him and that's it...
When are you gonna stop chatting?
You damn brats, don't disappoint me.
Let's see how strong that Man-Beast Form is!
I'll go!
Don't ruin my fun!
I told you. I'm gonna have some fun, too.
Scyther...
SCYTHER SONIC
...Sonic!
Cutting into his flesh isn't working!
His skin must've become even harder...
Killer!
W-We Gifters are blocking this path!
You shouldn't go fight yet...
Shut up! Get out of my way!
Bao Huang!
Are the Akazaya samurai still in the Treasure Repository?
They are!
Someone treated their wounds,
it seems!
Black Maria! Where are you now?!
I'm still in the Banquet Hall.
Alright, I'm gonna finish off the samurai!
Even if they're critically
injured, they're not weak enough
to be killed by the Tobi Roppo!
You got it?! Don't do anything!
Jack...
He's underestimating us...
But...
...this works out well for me.
WOMAN TROUBLE
I'd appreciate it if he did it.
What is that?
Hey, Nico Robin...
You will belong to...
...Kaido-sama.
No way. I'd rather die!
That's so cool!
With a firm vow to his late comrade-in-arms,
Boss Hyogoro the Flower
takes the final stage!
Keeping his old, worn-out body going,
he cuts a swath through Kaido's army!
The samurai who has
weathered times of turmoil
entrusts his beloved homeland to Straw Hat!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"No Regrets! Luffy and Boss,
a Master-Disciple Bond!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!