Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Draw your own map
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha ni areta umi no youna jidai
Even the values we had built up were about to fall apart
kizukiageta kachikan sae mo kuzuresarou to shita
Who knows if the compass is pointing in the right direction?
rashinban no sashita saki ga tadashii no ka douka nante
No one knows for certain
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
I do it for my own
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
And you do yours, don't we?
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And I'm ready for it
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
With the support of someone I can rely
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
Seize the future beyond your imagination
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
We'll go wherever we wanna go
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
Tears and doubts in tow
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Let's paint it in our own colors
onore no iro de egaite yuke
The stalemate of the battle gradually ends.
How dare you hit my face...
You thought you could catch me easily
if you just lured me?
Robin-chan!
Nice try, full-moon warriors!
You guys need luck in weather to win!
Kaido, finally in his extreme form,
stands in the way of Luffy and the others.
Zoro...
--I need one minute.
--Yeah, leave it to me.
"No Regrets!
Luffy and Boss, a Master-Disciple Bond!"
This...
Damn, it's almost done...
Dr. Chopper?
Dr. Chopper!
I'm gonna fight it!
As a doctor,
I can't succumb to such an annoying virus!
I'm sorry, everyone! Hold out a little longer!
I can't...
This blue flame has to
draw out my physical stamina,
but my stamina itself is...
...running out...
Fight it! Or you'll turn into an Ice Oni again!
You'll run wild until your energy runs out
and you'll die this time!
Don't give up, young man!
Get a hold of yourself!
Raccoon-san is enduring the same pain as you
but is working hard to make antidotes!
We can't give up before he does!
B-Big Boss... Your appearance...
Leave it to this old man!
It's time to show them...
...a samurai's resilience!
Apoo-san, we can't fight anymore!
The antibody is just past them,
but we can't break through their iron-tight defense!
Why should we suffer from Queen-sama's virus
even though we're on his side?!
He's not gonna save you even if you whine!
Just kill that raccoon and take back the antibody!
Damn!
Drake! That traitor!
Stop acting like a hero!
Drake isn't the only obstacle!
The withered old man somehow recovered!
The Land of Wano's legendary great underground boss!
HYOGORO THE FLOWER
LEGENDARY GREAT UNDERGROUND BOSS
Hyogoro the Flower!
X. DRAKE - A FORMER TOBI ROPPO MEMBER
They've got those two monstrous gate guards...
We can't approach the raccoon at all!
Why does he look like that?!
He was just a little old man moments ago!
He's back to the strong man he was
when Kaido was relentlessly recruiting him!
I'm shaking with excitement!
Big Boss! Are you okay?!
Yeah...
It's quite cold...
But...
...I'm confident about my mental capability!
Since I touched the virus by accident,
it's drawn out all the strength I've got
to the very last inch of my life!
When it comes to this...
With this last power...
...in exchange for my life,
I will slice up...
...all their key figures!
Hey, you bosses!
Yes, Big Boss!
I may not have much time left...
If Raccoon-san's cure can't make it
and I turn into an Ice Oni...
Before that happens!
Without hesitation!
Just kill me!
Otherwise,
I'll indiscriminately...
...slash and kill...
...you guys and everyone here!
No way...
But if Big Boss becomes an Ice Oni...
I'm sure no one will be able to stop him...
I'm counting on you...
Damn... What a pain in the ass...
Alright then...
...I, a former Mimawari-gumi member,
would like to see what he's got...
You're a legend?
You're just a has-been swordsman, right?
Get out of my way!
Old fart!
Prepare yourself!
One-Sword Style of the Flower!
Flaming Hair of...
...Holy Rage!
FLAMING HAIR OF HOLY RAGE
Let's overwhelm him with numbers! Go!
Hey, Oden...
I sometimes wished...
...that we had challenged Kaido
back in those days when we had so much energy.
But Kin'emon and the others
executed a perfect raid!
And...
...I landed an interesting disciple!
Straw hat man, you have more potential.
You'll get stronger and stronger!
Don't forget. A moment of crisis...
...will reveal your true power!
Let's defeat Kaido!
Count on me!
With the Ryuo that you taught me,
I'll kick Kaido's ass!
There is no lie or conceit in those words.
He'll achieve mastery of Ryuo
and become stronger...
...and take down Kaido!
Wait and watch, Oden!
The Land of Wano...
...will see its dawn!
Killer! Are you okay?!
Yeah, I'm all right...
You guys are next? Let me have fun!
Well done, you punks!
Take this!
Chambres!
What the?!
Hey, Linlin!
Don't get in my way!
They're quite strong on their own...
Together they're too much to handle.
I like those odds!
Hey, Luffy! Are you awake now?!
Yep!
I'm all good now!
Bring it on, you squirts!
Whoa-whoa!
All our troops on the floor will be wiped out!
Go to hell, geezer!
Phoenix Brand!
You better focus, Queen!
Marco!
That hurts! Was it a shockwave?!
You bastard!
You're in a fight with me!
You should attack those samurai
after you chop off my head-yoi!
Damn! How persistent he is!
Go to hell already!
Bluebird!
I'm gonna finish you off!
You son of a bitch!
Don't push your luck!
Crane Talons!
Not surprisingly,
it's quite hard to stall two with bounties of over a billion...
You bastard!
Hurry up, Raccoon!
What? That's Marco over there!
He looks exhausted...
Lick!
Dr. Chopper!
We're ready!
Thank you...
All there is left to do
is clear the final problem.
It's this cure's reliability.
We need a guinea pig.
Yeah, since it was thrown together,
we can't administer it to patients
until we make sure it's safe.
So...
...I'll try it myself!
Both of you, monitor me closely.
We don't know what external changes may occur
as side effects!
The taste needs to be improved...
There is some difficulty in breathing,
but the pulse is generally
within the expected range.
Don't worry...
This fever is a manifestation of the drug's effect.
It'll be gone soon...
Everyone's turning back into Ice Oni!
Th-The fire's gone...
Help me!
The lives of Ice Oni are at their limits!
Ohmasa! Are you okay?!
Yeah, thanks to the blue flame,
I'm good as new!
How's Big Boss?!
He didn't get the blue flame!
You damn monster...
Big Boss!
I'm glad that you're okay!
Keep your spirits up!
Don't let that weird virus get the best of you!
Boss Hyogoro!
Let's see the Land of Wano's dawn together!
Yeah...
You're right!
I guess it's time...
Do it! I want this!
It's like the heavens have given me
a reward at the end...
I was imprisoned and only waiting to die,
but now I've made it this far...
But if I go on, I'll only risk your lives!
I'm sorry I assigned you a tough role...
But do it for me!
I'll leave the rest to you guys...
This man, Hyogoro the Flower...
I have...
...no regrets!
The hero of the Land of Wano! Kozuki Oden!
I, Yamato A.K.A. Kozuki Oden,
will talk all about his great life with Momonosuke-kun!
Join us for the tales of Oden's spectacular adventure!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Comprehensive Anatomy! The Legend of Kozuki Oden!"
I'm gonna open the borders of the Land of Wano!