Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Draw your own map
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha ni areta umi no youna jidai
Even the values we had built up were about to fall apart
kizukiageta kachikan sae mo kuzuresarou to shita
Who knows if the compass is pointing in the right direction?
rashinban no sashita saki ga tadashii no ka douka nante
No one knows for certain
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
I do it for my own
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
And you do yours, don't we?
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And I'm ready for it
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
With the support of someone I can rely
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
Seize the future beyond your imagination
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
We'll go wherever we wanna go
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
Tears and doubts in tow
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Let's paint it in our own colors
onore no iro de egaite yuke
The fierce battle continues on Onigashima!
Hyogoro, who is suffering from the Ice Oni virus
uses all his remaining strength.
Old fart!
Prepare yourself!
Meanwhile, Chopper is hurrying
to stop the infection...
We're ready!
Thank you...
All there is left to do
is clear the final problem.
It's this cure's reliability.
So...
...I'll try it myself!
Don't let that weird virus get the best of you!
Let's see the Land of Wano's dawn together!
Yeah...
It's like the heavens have given me
a reward at the end...
I was imprisoned and only waiting to die,
but now I've made it this far...
But if I go on, I'll only risk your lives!
I'm sorry I assigned you in a tough role...
But do it for me!
I'll leave the rest to you guys...
Dr. Chopper!
Don't tell me it's unsuccessful!
It's...
Yay! It's successful!
We did it!
I knew you would do it!
We need a lot!
Everyone's waiting!
--Let's get on it!
--Okay!
"All Set!
Chopperphage Nebulizer!"
You don't look well.
Marco!
Is it about time to end this?
I won't let you get away!
Bluebird!
Don't try to act tough, bird brain!
Let go of me!
Prepare yourself!
I'm gonna torment you to my heart's content!
Have fun, you idiots.
I'm gonna turn all the idiots and scum...
...into Ice oni.
What?! I can't believe this!
Oniwabanshu...
...and Mimawari-gumi...
Most of them are beaten!
No... No way...
Daikoku-san!
Kazekage-sama!
Captain Hotei!
This is what the legendary yakuza is capable of?!
He resisted turning into an Ice Oni
but took advantage of its power!
I now understand a little why the Land of Wano...
...has been so feared...
Boss Hyogoro!
Boss!
What are you waiting for, Yatappe?!
Empty your mind!
Boss!
If I turn into an Ice Oni...
I know! Just give me a second!
I'm gonna do it soon! I'm gonna do it now!
Boss Hyogoro!
Of course it's hard...
He's like a father to us!
Tsunagoro, cut me without hesitation!
Boss Hyogoro...
I'll join you soon!
Ohmasa!
Damn! Can't you make it in time somehow?!
Raccoon-san!
Raccoon-san! Isn't the cure ready yet?!
This whole floor...
...and our friends will be taken over by Ice Oni again!
Yatappe! Do it!
Okay! I'm gonna... I'm gonna do it now!
I can't endure it anymore, either!
I have no chance to survive!
Just do it!
Don't make me...
Boss Ohmasa!
Don't make me hurt you all!
Ohmasa!
Queen-sama!
We're your subordinates...
Why do we have to die from your virus?!
He's right! Why should we die?!
You can't do this!
You're irritating me!
Shut up, you peons!
You fools are useless now!
Listen!
If I have no use for you, you're garbage!
No, even garbage is better than you!
I can't stand people like you fools!
You people don't have much ability,
just waiting for handouts!
When you open your mouths,
all you do is complain!
Every time you say something,
I get the urge to kill you!
Ice Oni is my masterpiece virus!
In fact, it's meant for you guys.
Hey, Pleasures!
You've already lost the ability lottery...
You're just cannon fodder who can only laugh!
H-How could you say that?!
Hey, Waiters!
No matter how long you wait,
no more Smile fruits are coming!
You guys lost your chance to gain powers!
The forever Waiters.
As the name suggests, all you can do is wait!
The only way you good-for-nothings can help
the formidable Animal Kingdom Pirates...
...is to become an oni before you die,
and do something worthwhile
to close out your lives!
What?! That's like... you're telling us to die...
Yes, I am!
We have tons of troops.
How could you say that?!
That's terrible...
I gave you a chance!
That antibody could save some of you!
Damn! I'm not gonna die!
Slice up your fellow soldiers who turned into Ice Oni!
And the samurai!
Go get them!
Fight your asses off to survive!
Their master-servant relationship
makes me sick...
Yeah, it's so disgusting.
Hey, you damn samurai!
You may think you're protecting something over there,
but don't forget that the raccoon is...
also a pirate!
Queen...
Producing many antibodies
in just a short amount of time?
That's impossible!
I'm sure he just administered the antibody to himself
and escaped!
He's different from you guys!
How can you be so sure?!
Pirates do cheat!
Boss Hyogoro! I'll follow you sooner or later!
Don't be so hasty to follow me...
Big Boss!
Goodbye...
Wait!
Don't stop me, Raccoon-san!
We have no choice!
I need you to wait! I'll save him now!
Boss! Swallow it!
Yes! I made it in time!
B... Boss...
Boss!
Alright, it's working!
His body's gonna warm up!
Boss Hyogoro! Are you all right?!
Yeah...
It worked!
Raccoon-san, I knew you could do it!
Thank goodness!
It worked?
Well done, Raccoon!
Raccoon-san, give the cure to Boss Ohmasa, too!
Miyagi, Tristan! Hurry up!
Okay, Dr. Chopper!
Is that...
It's all set! Dr. Chopper!
All right! Let's do it!
Dr. Chopper! Give us the order!
A cannon?!
Chopperphage...
...Nebulizer!
CHOPPERPHAGE NEBULIZER
Shoot!
Inhale as much of the mist as you can!
This is the most effective way
to save you from Ice Oni!
Everyone, inhale!
If I inhale it, will I be okay?!
Yes! It's a virus that I made!
Raccoon is right! Inhale it!
Okay!
I trust Raccoon-san!
This mist saved Boss, right?!
Everyone! Inhale the mist!
--Everyone's turning back!
--It's a big success!
Only you could do that, Dr. Chopper!
Your compliment doesn't make me happy, you fool!
What do you think you're doing, Raccoon?!
What have you done to my masterpiece?!
It's impossible to give the medicine individually
to thousands of warriors on this floor!
So I crafted my own virus out of the antibody!
What?!
A bad virus can be beaten by a good virus!
This way, everyone can ingest the cure
by inhaling the mist!
You're just a doctor
from a petty pirate group's ship...
Where did you learn such skills?!
We scattered all over the world
and trained ourselves!
Even my subordinates have recovered from Ice Oni!
How dare you?!
You shouldn't use a virus in a fight so casually!
It'll surely get out of hand!
Why do I have to be taught ethics by a raccoon?
Who do you think I am?!
What?!
Pleasures?!
Why?!
What are you guys doing?!
Get out of my way, you weaklings!
Shut up, Queen!
Our brothers were almost killed by you,
and were saved by Raccoon-san here!
Instead of death due to a crazy superior,
we'd...
...rather die siding with the one who saved us!
Isn't that right, guys?!
Thank you, Raccoon!
Raccoon!
I'm indebted to you, Raccoon-san!
Raccoon-san, thank you!
I'm so impressed with Raccoon.
Raccoon! Raccoon! Raccoon! Raccoon!
Go to hell, Queen!
You shitheads!
What the hell is this?!
That was impressive, Raccoon!
Do it!
Thanks, Marco!
There's one more thing that I wanna say!
Raccoon!
Rumble!
Monster Point!
Go!
What?!
I'm not a raccoon!
Oh, I'm sorry!
Damn!
Guys, think before you move!
Shut up!
What's wrong?! It's not over, right?
Let's keep fighting!
Bring it on, all at once!
Let's go!
Okay!
Where are we...?
Ouch...
Kiku!
Kin-sama...
Are you okay?!
Yes. How's everyone else?
Hey... Are you guys all right?!
Who healed us?
I don't know...
But I think I saw the person...
No, I must've been dreaming...
It's impossible...
Luffy-dono and the others are fighting Kaido for us.
We should not be staying here and doing nothing!
The battle on the island is still on!
Let's go!
We still have life left to give!
Guys! You're badly beaten!
I missed you all!
What?!
You've became quite old!
O-Oden-sama!
His wild laughter!
The Akazaya members
who witness Kozuki Oden's comeback find a ray of hope!
They failed to take down their sworn enemy Kaido once,
but now after 20 years,
they stand up again with Oden to finish the task!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Oden Appears! The Confused Hearts of the Akazaya Members!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!