Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Draw your own map
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha ni areta umi no youna jidai
Even the values we had built up were about to fall apart
kizukiageta kachikan sae mo kuzuresarou to shita
Who knows if the compass is pointing in the right direction?
rashinban no sashita saki ga tadashii no ka douka nante
No one knows for certain
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
I do it for my own
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
And you do yours, don't we?
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And I'm ready for it
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
With the support of someone I can rely
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
Seize the future beyond your imagination
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
We'll go wherever we wanna go
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
Tears and doubts in tow
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Let's paint it in our own colors
onore no iro de egaite yuke
Surprisingly, Oden appeared
in front of Kin'emon and the others.
Momonosuke's group doesn't know
about Oden's comeback yet.
Shinobu-san, this way!
Lead us to an out-of-sight path already!
Don't worry!
If we beat them all up, we'll be out of their sights!
Again, that's not what I meant!
"Oden Appears!
The Confused Hearts of the Akazaya Members!"
RIGHT-BRAIN TOWER, INSIDE THE DOME
There is a big space
between each floor of the castle!
No one'll see us there!
Okay!
Momonosuke-sama! Just a little more patience!
Momonosuke-kun, are you okay?
I am not okay...
I found them! I found them!
I repeat!
Young Master Yamato and the kunoichi...
...are still on the run...
...along with Momonosuke!
I'll make a path for Momonosuke-kun!
This mature woman will go at it, too!
You're strong, Shinobu-san!
You, too!
I'm glad you're here.
With you, I can defend Momonosuke-sama to the end!
Double Kunai Slash!
That was easy.
Shinobu-san, behind you!
Thank you! You saved me!
If I was a little younger,
I would've fallen for you!
Momonosuke-sama, please put your mind at ease.
Yamato and I took care of all the enemies.
I am not okay, I feel bad.
I cannot do anything
except rely on others for protection...
I hate myself.
What are you saying?!
It's natural for us retainers to be your sword and shield
and defend you!
Everyone is overrating me!
I... I...
I am frivolous, stupid...
...weak, foolish, and I am sick of myself...
Momonosuke-sama, you're great!
I am not great at all!
Even if you're small now,
I know you'll be big
and become a great Shogun one day!
You'll be a greater man
than Kozuki Oden ever was!
I am not... I am not...
I am not great at all!
What?! An eel?!
Momonosuke-sama!
Why do you look like that?
This is what he becomes
when he gets excited.
What? Could it be because you ate a Devil Fruit?
Yes, I did...
Momonosuke-kun!
You look like...
...my father!
Looks like Kaido's busy...
Speaking of Kaido...
when the Navy caught him once...
there was a man-made Devil Fruit
which Vegapunk created...
...by extracting Kaido's Bloodline Elements.
The Government asked him to hand it over to them,
but since he viewed it as a disappointing failure,
it was kept at Punk Hazard for a long time.
Why are you bringing that up now?
Punk Hazard was detonated.
That should be gone forever....
I hope it was destroyed in the explosion,
but Naval Base G-5 reported
that one facility was still in operation...
I'm just really glad that it was a failure...
Guys! You're badly beaten!
I missed you all!
What?!
You've become quite old!
O-Oden-sama!
TREASURE REPOSITORY
Did you think I was gonna die just like that?!
At that moment, we were able to get away
because of Oden-sama's quick wit...
We didn't see what happened to him after that.
But...!
What's wrong, you guys?
Why are you all making that face?!
Oh, wait!
I wanna eat ganmodoki, too!
What? You've got shirataki noodles!
People don't live only for shirataki noodles!
Nonsense!
What happened to your principles, Kikunojo?!
Oden is like life!
I wanna cherish everything that's in it!
--You took it!
--My life!
It's unnecessary to hesitate in life!
First come, first served!
How could you, Oden-sama?!
A leader shouldn't do that!
He's right!
Oden-sama?
Oden-sama...
No wonder you're surprised!
I was sent to the future with Toki's special power!
I'll explain it to you later.
It's a long story!
Oden-sama! That is why you are here!
Kin'emon, I heard about everything!
Thank you for protecting Momonosuke!
Oh, please! That is more than I deserve!
And thank you all, too!
It must've been a struggle for 20 years!
And...
...you must've been surprised to see
the drastically changed Land of Wano!
I'm sorry for being late!
But we can't rejoice in our reunion forever!
Let's go!
To face Kaido who we failed to take down that day!
--Of course!
--We'll come with you!
Till we die!
That's been our wish from the beginning!
Let's go!
Yeah!
I knew you guys would say so!
That's what I'd expect from my samurai!
You haven't changed!
In the afterworld, Toki must be happy to know
that I'm alive.
Wait, you guys!
What's wrong, Ashura?
There's no way he's alive!
He must be an imposter!
What are you saying, Ashura?!
Kin'emon!
This is what Toki-sama said!
Leave... to the future!
People can never...
People can never go back to the past...
But you can go forward into the future.
"People can never go back to the past"!
Toki-sama's ability was sending people to the future!
Oden-sama died that day!
That fact wouldn't change even in the future!
No one can change the past!
Have you forgotten my face, Raizo?
No wonder... You're all badly injured!
You tried to take down Kaido on my behalf.
You've been waiting for an opportunity to take revenge
for a long time, it must've been painful...
It's nothing compared to the pain you suffered!
Let's take down Kaido!
Then we'll reconstruct the Land of Wano
and live together like we used to!
Everything will be restored!
Don't worry! I'm not gonna set out to the sea
on my own again!
So you can sleep well too, Izo!
Everyone was always desperate
to stop you from sailing away.
Guys, come to your senses!
We lost our lord,
and couldn't even achieve revenge
which was the only purpose of our lives,
and got beaten by Kaido!
I know why you wanna escape from reality!
But Luffy-dono and the others are still
fighting for the Land of Wano!
So we must face reality!
But maybe he is real!
I know!
But...!
Wake up, Kin'emon!
Look! He's not even bleeding!
No way!
Ashura...
I thought you pledged to become my samurai.
Be my samurai!
Ashura-san!
Ashura!
Now it's clear that he's an imposter...
We all feel the same...
I wish he were the real one...
But he's an imposter!
How vicious!
Who's posing as Oden-sama then?!
It's not him?! Damn!
A-Are you okay?! Ashura-san!
But his behavior...
It looks exactly like Oden!
The one who can mimic him so well must be...
...one of us!
So it's you!
Kanjuro!
Don't be silly! I'm Oden!
How's my drawing of Oden?!
It looks exactly like him, right?
Damn you! Kanjuro!
Hey, Denjiro!
I'm your lord, how could you defy me?!
You bastard!
How much more are you gonna taunt us?
It is my fault!
If I did not try to escape reality like a fool...
No, it's my fault!
Ashura-san, I'm sorry!
Because I failed to finish Kanjuro off, you...
Even a sharp sword will become dull
when you try to cut your friend...
It must've been tough for you...
Is this a drawing?! Where is he?!
I'm manipulating Oden from a distance!
It's really exhausting though!
Hey, Kiku!
Your blade did cut me!
I'm seriously wounded, too!
I think I'm gonna die during this battle!
But what keeps me going now...
...is my grudge toward the Kozuki Clan!
But before I die...
I'm gonna stab at the heart of the Kozuki Clan!
As Kurozumi Kanjuro!
Momonosuke-sama's in danger!
Momonosuke-kun!
Can you change back to yourself?
You're sticking out like that.
Y-Yeah...
Stay still this time, Momonosuke-kun!
I am sorry!
It may not look it,
but I have gained better control over it...
When I first met Luffy and the others,
I would turn into a dragon
every time I got surprised and felt sad.
I'm astonished.
I wonder if it's similar to my father's power...
If I could turn into a monster like he does,
I would be of some help to everyone...
Luffy is still fighting Kaido, right?
I wonder if he's okay!
I wanna take down Kaido too! As Oden!
Luffy is getting much weaker...
But somehow he is in good spirits!
That's good...
What?!
How can you tell, Momonosuke-sama?!
God of Lightning Tenjin!
Take this!
What's wrong?
Are you getting tired of dancing?!
How can we defeat them?
I don't think our attacks are working.
They sure are the Emperors of the Sea...
Their skin is tough.
Can't they at least pretend
that it's working a little bit?!
It's working!
After all this striking,
there's no way it wouldn't work!
They're humans just like us!
Gum-Gum...
You did that earlier and it didn't work!
Think before you attack!
How can you say they're humans just like us
even when the distinction is so clear?
They're monstrous...
You guys think you can't beat them,
and yet here you are?
We're trying to figure out how to win!
We should pull one of them away from here.
I agree.
When those two are side by side,
this place looks like...
...nothing but hell...
So what?
Hell doesn't bother me!
Caution, we're too heated up!
I've been to hell many times...
Your eyes always look vigorous!
Straw Hat!
We have the upper hand!
Kaido and Big Mom overpower the Worst Generation
with their monstrous physiques
and warn them to prepare for the worst.
The conquerors of the sea unleash a furious attack
which would even make ogres cry!
The Four Emperors' special secret art will
destroy Luffy and the others!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Worst Generation Gets Wiped Out?!
The Emperors' Deadly Attack!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!