iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
Draw your own map
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha ni areta umi no youna jidai
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
kizukiageta kachikan sae mo kuzuresarou to shita
Even the values we had built up were about to fall apart
rashinban no sashita saki ga tadashii no ka douka nante
Who knows if the compass is pointing in the right direction?
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
No one knows for certain
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
I do it for my own
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And you do yours, don't we?
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
And I'm ready for it
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
With the support of someone I can rely
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Seize the future beyond your imagination
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
We'll go wherever we wanna go
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Tears and doubts in tow
onore no iro de egaite yuke
Let's paint it in our own colors
Eluding the Marys' surveillance network,
Yamato and Shinobu defend Momonosuke for their lives.
This mature woman will go at it, too!
Luffy and the others' battle
against Kaido and Big Mom continues!
When those two are side by side,
this place looks like...
...nothing but hell...
So what?
Hell doesn't bother me!
Caution, we're too heated up!
I've been to hell many times...
Your eyes always look vigorous!
Straw Hat!
We have the upper hand!
Meanwhile, Kin'emon and his gang
reunited with Oden, however...
Look! He's not even bleeding!
Ashura!
Now it's clear that he's an imposter...
We all feel the same...
I wished he were the real one...
But he's an imposter!
So it's you!
Kanjuro!
Don't be silly! I'm Oden!
How's my drawing of Oden?!
That looks exactly like him, right?
Damn you! Kanjuro!
Hey, Denjiro!
I'm your lord, how could you defy me?!
You bastard!
How much more are you gonna taunt us?
"The Worst Generation Gets Wiped Out?!
The Emperors' Deadly Attack!"
He's going after... Momonosuke-sama...
I can't believe he used
a fake Oden-sama to keep us here...
It's unforgivable!
Kanjuro!
I'll wipe out the Kozuki Clan.
We've got to go save him now!
Oh, I think I heard this voice
from somewhere earlier...
...saying Momonosuke-sama is with a kunoichi...
That must be Shinobu!
Then we can get a connection!
It's not cool to chase a man who is dying.
What's so funny?!
The Akazaya members will meet their end here,
unable to do anything!
Along with me...
What?!
Let's go out with a sensational bang!
You guys!
We're friends, right?
Ashura!
Get away from here, guys!
Go stop Kanjuro!
What are you doing?!
Get off of me!
Save Momonosuke-sama for me!
I'm sorry, Ashura!
You bastard! How could you get in my way?!
Oden-sama...
Now, a Daimyo needs vassals.
Rather than being assigned with
some wise and sober men,
I want you guys.
Be my samurai!
Oden-sama!
Damn you! Get off of me!
Don't sully Kozuki Oden anymore!
Ashura-san...
Kanjuro!!
Those idiots in supporting roles
brilliantly performed in the tear-jerker!
Next is finally my turn in a leading role!
I pretended to be a Kozuki...
...and I'll eliminate the Kozuki, and die!
That's the best way to bring the curtain down!
My life is a beautiful show!
Jack!
You bastard! Do you wanna fight again?!
What a pain in the ass...
They tried to defend their kings...
These small fries stood in my way...
How annoying!
We should've finished you off
in an earlier battle!
This time, I'll get you for sure!
Cat! Raizo! Just move on, everyone!
Dogstorm...
Dog?!
I'll take care of him-gara!
I'll leave him to you!
Everyone, save Momonosuke-sama for me!
Let's go, Kin-san!
Yeah...
Be sure to catch up to us, Dogstorm!
We'll be waiting for you!
Are you gonna handle me all by yourself,
King of the Day?
We're both injured.
So we're a good match!
You're underestimating me...
Are you gonna fight someone
who destroyed your country all by yourself?!
I stayed behind
not because I wanted to pay off an old grudge...
I didn't want anyone to get hurt
by letting you go free!
Jack!
You can't see the moon from here!
There's no poison gas, either!
We both have to prepare for the worst.
Don't forget!
I'm not a raccoon!
How dare you do that to me,
you damn raccoon?!
You didn't just screw up my Ice Oni virus,
but you also struck me...
You're gonna have to pay for that!
Using medicine
for the wrong purpose is unforgivable!
You're just a doctor
from a petty pirate group's ship...
Who do you think I am?!
That looks bad!
Let me help you-yoi!
Marco!
Don't worry! We've got your back-yoi!
He's quite tough.
You fools...
I guess you really want me to kick your asses!
You're gonna get your ass kicked instead, Queen!
We must put it out quickly!
We need water! Bring more!
You are...
I'm gonna teach you idiots a lesson...
Orochi!
No way! But you...
I thought you were dead...
How come you're alive?!
How could you betray me, Kaido?
Orochi-sama certainly...
...got beheaded by Kaido once...
But...
I'll make him pay for it!
I'm gonna burn it all up!
I'm gonna turn Onigashima into a ball of flames!
There's no escape in the air,
so die!
I'm gonna kill them all!
I'll make them regret crossing me!
It's too much to handle those two
at the same time.
Yeah, we can't take it...
Let's strike a blow, Kaido.
I wonder how many of those five will survive.
Trafalgar! Can't you move either of them
downstairs with your ability?
If I could, I would've done it already.
Their Haki is too strong, I can't move them!
Then, let's tear them apart!
Hey, here comes a big one!
I hope your legs are not weakened yet, old bag!
Who do you think you're talking to, brat?!
Conquest of the Sea!
This can't be real!
No! We can't dodge it!
Get away! You guys!
If you don't get away...
we'll be wiped out!
Zoro!
What was that jolt?!
Luffy... Zoro...
They're gone, but I can still hear them...
They got away from it... I'm impressed.
Zoro-ya, are you alive?
I think so...
Good job blocking it even for a moment...
Thanks.
Where's Straw Hat?
Kaido!
Gum-Gum...
...Red!
You dodged it, Kaido!
Must be because it hurts!
Ow, ow, ow...
The iron hammer with the strong Color
of the Supreme King will drag people to hell!
All covered in bruises, Luffy and the others
become single-minded in front of Kaido!
To launch a new era, they pull off a desperate feat
that stuns the Emperors of the Sea!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Supernovas Strike Back!
The Mission to Tear Apart the Emperors!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!