iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
Draw your own map
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha
ni areta umi no youna jidai
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
kizukiageta kachikan sae
mo kuzuresarou to shita
Even the values we had built
up were about to fall apart
rashinban no sashita saki ga
tadashii no ka douka nante
Who knows if the compass is
pointing in the right direction?
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
No one knows for certain
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
I do it for my own
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And you do yours, don't we?
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
And I'm ready for it
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
With the support of someone I can rely
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Seize the future beyond your imagination
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
We'll go wherever we wanna go
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Tears and doubts in tow
onore no iro de egaite yuke
Let's paint it in our own colors
While fighting the fake
Oden that Kanjuro created,
the Akazaya members perceived his motive.
He's going after... Momonosuke-sama...
It's not cool to chase a man who is dying.
The fake Oden ignited a fuse
to the explosives that he hid in his clothes...
...to block the Akazaya members' way!
Damn you! Get off of me!
Don't sully Kozuki Oden anymore!
Cat! Raizo! Just move on, everyone!
Are you gonna handle me all by yourself,
King of the Day?
I stayed behind
not because I wanted to pay off an old grudge...
I didn't want anyone to get hurt
by letting you go free!
Jack!
We both have to prepare for the worst.
Hey, here comes a big one!
Conquest of the Sea!
Get away! You guys!
Zoro-ya, are you alive?
Good job blocking it even for a moment...
Thanks.
Where's Straw Hat?
Kaido!
Gum-Gum...
...Red!
You dodged it, Kaido!
Must be because it hurts!
"The Supernovas Strike Back!
The Mission to Tear Apart the Emperors!"
Nice! Burn!
Burn more!
Damn! It's not going out at all!
Why do we keep having problems?!
Fukurokuju! You know where they store
tons of explosives, don't you?!
Yes, I'll show you the way.
Because I know every last
inch of this castle...
That's my ninja!
This is not the end of it, damn pirates!
Cry! Moan!
Run around in a panic!
I'm gonna burn the island down
and kill you all!
There are flames! What's happening?!
I'm the one who kills people!
I'm the ruler of the Land of Wano!
I'll kill them! I'll kill
them! I'll kill them!
Go to hell, Kaido!
Screw the New Onigashima Project!
Orochi!
So you did this!
Oh, there you are.
The Kozuki's half-ghost bastards!
Orochi-sama...
They don't know that you died once.
Fukurokuju!
Please run. Let me handle them...
Back off, you fool!
You're covered in cuts and bruises...
No wonder!
You voluntarily came to your deaths!
You must be out of your mind!
What the hell do you want?!
For 20 years, you've endured tirelessly,
and followed me all the way here!
Is that how much you hate me? Resent me?!
Is that how bad you wanna take my head?!
Screw you guys! And Kaido!
And everyone else!
If it weren't for you,
Oden-sama wouldn't have died.
But we don't have time to get involved
in your stupid nonsense anymore.
There is only one thing
that we're looking ahead to...
The Land of Wano that Oden-sama dreamed of!
To accomplish that,
we'll take down Kaido and the others!
You fools think
you're defending the Land of Wano?!
Yeah, we do...
Hey, guys.
Do you like this country?
Yes, we love this country...
Are you really going to inherit my will?
Of course.
--Good, good!
--Oden-sama?
Don't compromise on that.
What?
When you're trying to protect something,
it takes a lot of determination...
...to live without compromising your beliefs.
No matter how much time goes by,
stick to what you believe in,
and don't let it go.
That sounds like your last words
and it creeps me out.
Does it?
Please wait, Oden-sama!
That is what Oden-sama told us.
Orochi! We do not have time
for a fool like you. Move!
--What'll happen if I say no?
--What?!
I can't believe you cherish
the stupid words of a dead guy...
I really don't like any part of you guys!
Listen, I...
...wanna have your heads so bad!
Bring it on...
I'm gonna fight you right here!
Do you guys know who you're messing with?!
You have to know your place!
I'm the Shogun of the Land of Wano!
What's that attitude?!
I haven't done anything wrong!
I only took my revenge on the Kozuki Clan
just as they deserved!
I just took back what was
supposed to be mine!
But you idiots don't understand!
Citizens and samurai are supposed to
bow before their Shogun and follow him!
I am a man of power!
Flower Shuriken!
This country that oppressed me is to blame!
Th-That look in your eyes!
Are you trying to tell me that I'm wrong?!
Don't look at me...
Don't look at me!
I'm not wrong!
Stop looking at me like that!
Orochi-sama!
I will leave your punishment to hell!
Let's go!
Are you gonna avenge your lord?
I raised my opinion of you, Fukurokuju!
Even though he was a moron,
you stayed loyal to him till the end...
I can say the same to you guys!
Even without my goal of vengeance,
you and I are destined to fight!
Do you know what I mean, Raizo?!
Yeah!
Are they gonna destroy the whole castle?!
It's a powerful collision... Is it Kaido?!
Maybe with Luffy-dono?!
Do not worry!
I am sure they will be fine!
Moreover...
...we made the promise...
We have no time to waste!
Mm-hm! Let's hurry up!
Luffy-dono...
It's far from enough!
Can't you make it more thrilling?!
To the point of terror!
Hey!
Wouldn't it be great
if you could leave me a scar that won't fade...
...or scare me enough to give me a chill?!
Because you'll die soon!
You shithead!
I'll take away everything from you guys!
You didn't forget about that, did you?
I'm starting to feel like
I need to take these guys' heads soon, too.
Let's finish them off
with the next one, Kaido.
Yeah, let's kill them.
Playing around leisurely
ain't a good way to have fun!
Life requires discipline!
Stop talking nonsense!
You can't end the battle on your own!
What?!
You're not gonna win!
We'll show you how determined we are!
Kaido!
Determination?
What's the point of such a thing?
Don't push your luck, Straw Hat!
Just like you wanted,
I'm gonna twist your head off!
Look out!
--Luffy!
--Pay attention!
I won't let you get away!
Antibacterial Curtain!
How about this?!
Tra-guy!
Begone!
I'm sick of hearing words like
determination and resolution!
Those words are full of shit
and they don't have any impact on the world!
The weak will only die
without leaving anything behind!
So what?
Can you carry...
...the Land of Wano on your back?!
There's something I have to do!
Don't try to act tough, you punk!
As long as I'm here,
you can't do as you please in this world of sea!
You guys are trying to protect something,
but all that effort will have been in vain.
Because of me!
Wait!
If you're gonna invite our captain to hell,
I'll come along as well!
Can't you stand being alone?
"A bad bush is better than the open field"...
Were you inspired by those crazy samurai
and lose your mind?
If that kind of self-sacrifice
is what you call "being friends,"
then it's a really shitty
thing to take pride in!
Say what you want!
Let me tell you something.
That's not an honorable way of life
or a noble spirit or anything!
You'll just die for nothing!
That idiot, what is he thinking?
At least, do something worthwhile
to close your life with,
and let me feast my eyes on it!
There's something I have to do!
That is, Kaido...
I'm gonna kick your ass
and blow right past you!
Sorry... Now you have no reason to die.
I knew that all along!
Tsk! Don't do everything in your group!
How could you push forward without us?!
Anyway, I'm gonna break through!
Let's go!
Don't underestimate me, brat!
I won't let you do that!
Doesn't matter if you come all at once!
--Go attack!
--You shithead!
Thanks!
Kaido!
Conqueror of Three Worlds...
Ragnaraku!
Luffy!
Let's finish off the others, too!
--It's done!
--Okay!
Room!
Chambres!
Where am I?! It's dark!
Zeus!
Can you do it, Roronoa?!
I have no choice!
I won't let you go back to her!
Flame-Rend, Crossing the Six Paths!
Stop! I'm just a sword!
Mama, help!
You guys!
Now's our chance! Punk Pistols!
What's this?!
Did you think you could beat me
if you tore us apart?!
Repel!
Takt!
You fool! You can't beat me
by hitting me with a rock!
Oh, damn!
Mama!
If she can't get help,
we'll have one dropout!
How's that?!
Even after they drove out Big Mom,
the rookies keep fighting a
hellish battle of attrition.
Kaido tries to attack the fallen Luffy,
and Zoro prepares to strike
with his back against the wall.
Just like Asura, Enma the famed sword
activates Nine-Sword Style Secret Move!
He stakes his fate on the big move!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Defend Luffy! Zoro and Law's Sword Technique!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!