Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Draw your own map
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha ni areta umi no youna jidai
Even the values we had built up were about to fall apart
kizukiageta kachikan sae mo kuzuresarou to shita
Who knows if the compass is pointing in the right direction?
rashinban no sashita saki ga tadashii no ka douka nante
No one knows for certain
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
I do it for my own
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
And you do yours, don't we?
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And I'm ready for it
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
With the support of someone I can rely
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
Seize the future beyond your imagination
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
We'll go wherever we wanna go
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
Tears and doubts in tow
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Let's paint it in our own colors
onore no iro de egaite yuke
Flower Shuriken!
This country that oppressed me is to blame!
Th-That look in your eyes!
Are you trying to tell me that I'm wrong?!
Don't look at me...
Don't look at me!
I'm not wrong!
Stop looking at me like that!
Orochi-sama!
I will leave your punishment to hell!
Conqueror of Three Worlds...
Ragnaraku!
Luffy!
Let's finish off the others, too!
--It's done!
--Okay!
Room!
Chambres!
Where am I?! It's dark!
Zeus!
Can you do it, Roronoa?!
I have no choice!
I won't let you go back to her!
Flame-Rend, Crossing the Six Paths!
Stop! I'm just a sword!
Mama, help!
You guys!
Now's our chance! Punk Pistols!
What's this?!
Did you think you could beat me
if you tore us apart?!
Repel!
Takt!
You fool! You can't beat me
by hitting me with a rock!
Oh, damn!
Mama!
If she can't get help, we'll have one dropout!
"Defend Luffy!
Zoro and Law's Sword Technique!"
Help me now!
Zeus!
Mama!
What's wrong, Mama?!
Cry! Scream!
Say goodbye to the old bag!
The sea...
...will take care of the rest.
What are you doing?!
Prometheus!
Mama! I'm on my way...
Mama! I'll come...
That fool.
Conquest of the Sea!
This can't be real!
No! We can't dodge it!
Get away! You guys!
Zoro!
He could've had every bone in his body
shattered from that!
Stop! Mama is...!
Mama is...!
Mama!
That's pathetic, Linlin!
Do I have to do everything for you?
Hey, Pirate Hunter!
Let Prometheus go!
Chambres!
Injection Shot!
Your ability unsettles me!
Trafalgar!
Antibacterial Curtain!
Mama!
Go away!
Hey, Tra-guy!
That fire thing...
...is gonna save Big Mom!
Let him go...
I'd rather the mission failed...
...than have one of us die.
Mama!
What's going on, Mama?!
Our objective is to tear Big Mom and Kaido apart!
You don't have to risk your life for it!
Leave Big Mom to me!
Help, Prometheus...
Mama!
Prome...
Mama! Mama!
Mama!
That was close!
I'm relieved, Mama!
You're so cute!
Prometheus!
And you, Napoleon!
Thanks for coming!
Of course, Mama!
On the other hand...
What is Zeus doing?!
He's so useless!
I...
...agree, Mama!
He's always clumsy and slow.
That guy is no longer family or anything!
You're right!
I would do anything for you, Mama!
Me too! Me too! I would do anything!
How nice of you to say that!
Mama! Mama!
What's going on?!
Zeus!
I can't exercise my true power
when my partner's subpar...
I actually can use stronger techniques...
Oh, yeah!
Hey, hey, I need to ask you something, Mama!
What is it?
The thing is... I want a girlfriend!
That's a good idea!
A new partner for Prometheus...
A new child to replace Zeus...
What's this child gonna look like?
Unfortunately...
...the Emperor of the Sea Big Mom...
...survived!
Damn!
I thought that the sea took care of her...
Prome...
Mama! Mama!
Mama!
That's just how tough
the Emperor of the Sea Big Mom is.
It's no longer possible to land on Onigashima.
Even so, we've got to join Captain somehow!
Yeah!
Look at Straw Hat's face!
It's just like the last time!
He's passed out and is still...
...staring at me!
Should I...
...smash those eyes first?
Or...
...his brain?
Or his heart?
Tra-guy.
What I'm about to do...
...will push me to the limit.
Zoro-ya?!
Fighting sloppily...
...will only wear you down.
If this doesn't work, it'll be my time to die.
I'll leave the rest...
...to you!
Hey, Kaido!
He's our captain!
Why don't you try...
...to smash my head first?!
Demon Aura Nine-Sword Style!
Asura!
Blades Drawn!
Nine-Sword Style!
ASURA: BLADES DRAWN
Asura: Blades Drawn...
DEAD MAN'S GAME
...Dead Man's Game!
Damn!
This brat...
You possess the Color of the Supreme King, too?!
What are you saying?
I don't know what you're talking about!
I launched that attack with all my might!
I wanted you to at least fall...
You should be happy...
This scar will remain.
What an annoying generation.
Hey! Zoro-ya, run!
Don't bother approaching me...
Thunder Bagua!
What a shame...
If you come with me,
we can dominate the world...
With you?
We don't wanna be with you...
Idiot...
We...
...love the samurai...
I'll kick your ass at any cost...
I'll kick your ass at any cost!
Luffy holds the thoughts of
his wounded comrades in his heart
and the promises he made
to the samurai he met in his fists.
He tries to surpass Kaido!
A clash in which neither man yields!
The Color of the Supreme King surges out!
With that fist, he will silence the Emperor of the Sea!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Surpass the Emperor of the Sea!
Luffy Strikes Back with an Iron Fist!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!