iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
Draw your own map
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha ni areta umi no youna jidai
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
kizukiageta kachikan sae mo kuzuresarou to shita
Even the values we had built up were about to fall apart
rashinban no sashita saki ga tadashii no ka douka nante
Who knows if the compass is pointing in the right direction?
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
No one knows for certain
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
I do it for my own
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And you do yours, don't we?
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
And I'm ready for it
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
With the support of someone I can rely
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Seize the future beyond your imagination
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
We'll go wherever we wanna go
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Tears and doubts in tow
onore no iro de egaite yuke
Let's paint it in our own colors
We don't wanna be with you...
Idiot...
We...
...love the samurai...
I'll kick your ass at any cost...
"Surpass the Emperor of the Sea!
Luffy Strikes Back with an Iron Fist!"
You'll...
...kick my ass?
Give it a try.
If you think you can do it...
...with your impulsive punches!
I gotta kill that bastard...
Or I won't be satisfied!
Of course, Mama!
That shitty little punk!
Hey, you vigorous thundercloud right there!
I'll give you...
...a fragment of my own soul especially for you!
Here, eat up!
Yum!
How delicious...
...and powerful the soul is!
What's that?!
She was born!
My girlfriend!
All right...
Come to me!
Come on!
Ya-hoo!
She's here, Mama!
Alright, come on!
Oh, yes!
What's going on?
I thought we caught the thunder one!
How could you do that to me, Kid!
You'll be...
...severely punished
for dropping me into the sea!
Prepare yourself!
What should we do?!
We're in big trouble.
What an energetic old bag. Moreover...
...she seems more powerful, doesn't she?!
This is bad... Let's...
...retreat for now!
I won't let you flee!
It's time to try your skill!
Show me what you can do!
Okay, Mama!
FULGORA
Fulgora!
Did you hear that massive blast somewhere?
Is something coming?!
We just managed to add more allies
with Otama's Kibi Dango!
It doesn't do us any good until I give them
a command at the Performance Floor!
How much farther to
the Performance Floor?!
I don't know! We should just hurry!
Oh, no! Whoa-whoa-whoa!
It's him!
Hey, stop!
Climate Baton!
Rain Spark!
There's no way this works on me!
There's no point in fighting him squarely!
Special Attack: Smoke Stars!
Got him!
Outrun him now!
I won't let you do that!
Nami, ready?!
I'm all ready!
Damn!
Thunderbolt...
...Tempo!
We did it!
The "apply electricity to
a soaking wet body" plan is a success!
He's gone! W-Where did he go?!
U-Usopp!
--No! No! No!
--Sorry! Sorry! Sorry!
You fools!
How dare you make Big Sis mad!
Guys, get down!
Okay!
Damn you!
Whoa-whoa-whoa-whoa!
Wait! Wait! Wait! Wait! Wait!
Wait! Wait! Wait! Wait!
Hey, wait!
Killer...
You there?
Yeah...
Damn! We were sent flying quite far.
Yeah... I can't believe
we broke through the castle wall...
After all, the Emperor of
the Sea's power is extraordinary.
In any event, that old bag is insane.
Anyway, where are we?
We're probably somewhere inside the castle...
Where's Big Mom?
She's not coming after us.
The hole she made is so big,
she must've lost track of where she sent us flying.
Yeah, but don't lower your guard.
I know that old crone won't stop
until she gets her revenge on me.
Kid!
Where are you?!
I'm gonna kill you!
Seems like she's down there...
I won't let that old bag
team up with Kaido again!
I'll send her to hell! Let's hurry up!
I'll send everyone who laughs at you to hell!
Straw Sword!
You are...!
Hawkins!
"MAGICIAN" BASIL HAWKINS - WORST GENERATION
A HEADLINER, ANIMAL KINGDOM PIRATES
Damn you...
You have the nerve to come attack us.
You traitor!
I was betrayed by Apoo, too.
I just avoided a fight I knew I would lose!
How cunning!
That's why you're a small-timer.
If you're so weak that you know you'll lose,
don't ever show your face...
...on the battleground!
I can't believe you guys survived.
Stop talking!
Just breathing the same air as you
makes me wanna throw up!
Kid, go forward!
Don't leave Big Mom unchecked.
I'll...
...take care of him.
Thanks!
Kid fled! Chase him!
Thank you...
I didn't stand a chance against two.
Demon Face!
You're performing your job as
Animal Kingdom Pirates' Headliner quite well.
You're totally domesticated.
Say what you want.
There's a 92 percent chance
you'll die here.
How pitiable! Hitokiri Kamazo!
Fortune-telling again?
We take matters into our own hands.
I wish you luck, Killer.
Screw you.
I don't wish you luck...
Not even one bit.
Wait for me, you shitty old bag!
What a shame...
If you come with me,
we can dominate the world...
With you?
We don't wanna be with you, idiot!
We love the samurai...
I'll kick your ass at any cost!
You'll...
...kick my ass?
Give it a try.
If you think you can do it...
...with your impulsive punches!
Don't press too hard!
It's a very strong power
that defends you like invisible armor,
and can also be used offensively.
But if you take it up a notch,
the Haki that covers you
will become even stronger,
and it will enter your enemy's body
and destroy it from the inside!
Don't strain yourself.
Allow the unused Haki
in your body to flow to your fist.
Kong Gun!
It was still too shallow.
I noticed something
when I got attacked by your spiked club.
You can infuse yourself with
the Color of the Supreme King too, right?
How will knowing that help you?
Can you do it, too?!
Only a handful of strong men...
...can do it!
You half-ghost bastard!
Remember your setback!
Remember that you couldn't beat him by force!
Get away! You guys!
If you don't get away...
we'll be wiped out!
Conqueror of Three Worlds, Ragnaraku!
Remember your setback!
A moment of crisis...
...will reveal your true power!
What?!
Don't strain yourself.
Allow the unused Haki in your body
to flow to your fist.
What kind of king did you say you'd be?
You little punk!
I launched that attack with all my might!
What an annoying generation.
The enemy is a monster!
But you can do this!
He didn't touch him!
Zoro...
Tra-guy...
Thank you for defending me.
You two, go downstairs!
I'll defeat him at any cost!
Tell that to everyone...
...for me!
Luffy, a boy who dreams of
a great adventure, meets a girl.
Uta, the musician of the Red-Hair Pirates.
Her singing voice prays for world peace
and makes people smile.
This is the story of Luffy's friend
that no one knows yet.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Faint Memory! Luffy and Red-Haired's Daughter Uta!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!