iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
Draw your own map
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha
ni areta umi no youna jidai
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
kizukiageta kachikan sae
mo kuzuresarou to shita
Even the values we had built
up were about to fall apart
rashinban no sashita saki ga
tadashii no ka douka nante
Who knows if the compass is
pointing in the right direction?
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
No one knows for certain
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
I do it for my own
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
And you do yours, don't we?
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And I'm ready for it
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
With the support of someone I can rely
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
Seize the future beyond your imagination
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
We'll go wherever we wanna go
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
Tears and doubts in tow
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Let's paint it in our own colors
onore no iro de egaite yuke
"A Pledge for the New Genesis!
Luffy and Uta!"
WINDMILL VILLAGE
I've had enough!
Who would jump off a cliff
to train your nerve?!
Luffy is so reckless!
You think so, right?!
Yeah. It makes you nervous
just to watch him.
Thank you for hanging out
with Luffy, Uta-chan.
No! I'm just protecting Shanks!
Because he's unbelievably persistent!
So I have no choice!
I beg your pardon!
See?
Shanks!
Hey, Luffy.
Let me aboard your ship!
No.
Let me! Let me! Let me!
No means no.
Cheapskate Shanks!
Let me! Let me! Let me!
Let me! Let me!
Let me aboard! Let me!
Please, Shanks!
Get off of me!
Hey!
Why are you whining?!
Weren't we gonna do
our training at sea today?
Oh, yeah!
But the ship...
Stop grumbling!
Let's go, Luffy!
Uta! Take good care of Luffy.
Uh-huh!
No, Shanks!
I take care of her.
Hey!
When did I get taken care of
by a child like you?
I'm not a child.
You're just a child to me!
Because I'm two years older than you!
Let's race to the sea!
Wait!
The loser will get punished!
Hey, no fair, Uta!
Can't tell whether
they like each other or not...
They're so cute together.
It's always nice to have
a friend who is close in age.
When will your next voyage be?
I'm planning to leave soon.
He'll miss you.
Well, it's not a final farewell.
When we return,
they can play together again.
You're right.
I'm sure I'm faster than you!
No, I'm faster!
Whoever gets to the rock first wins!
Sounds good!
I'll be the winner!
No, I will!
I'm gonna win!
What?!
Why are you turning back, Luffy?!
The race's not over yet!
You too, Uta! Are you scared?!
No way!
That was close...
What was that?
That's our local Sea Monster!
You should've told me there's such a thing!
Gee. Shanks would've
kicked its butt like wham...
You screamed and ran away!
How pathetic!
You ran when we bumped into
mountain bandits the other day, too!
I landed them one at that time!
And you ran away, too!
Because I'm the musician
of the Red-Hair Pirates.
My job is to sing.
If I can go aboard Shanks' ship
and become a pirate,
I won't get beaten by that thing!
Hmm...
What?
You're always talking about
becoming a pirate,
but what do you wanna do
when you become one?
I have a dream!
I will travel around the world with Shanks,
make so many songs,
and make the world happy
with great performances and my singing!
I'll build a new genesis!
Wow...
Okay! I'll build a new genesis, too!
Don't say it like it's easy.
So what's your new genesis like?
I wanna explore all over the world!
I wanna go to a variety of places,
meet a variety of people,
and eat a wide variety of food!
Just like Shanks!
That won't change the world!
Yeah?
I'll think of what to do soon.
That's so you!
Yeah? I'm flattered.
I didn't mean it as a compliment!
Let's build a new genesis!
Yeah!
Damn! Take me with you!
I can't believe you snuck in...
Uta-chan, I heard you found him.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I thought you were gonna support my dream!
When Shanks says no, it's no.
You...
What do you take the most pride in?!
My strength!
Then, become even stronger.
If you become much stronger than now,
I'll ask him with you.
What?
Did you think I'd say that?
Nyah, nyah, bleah!
Let's go, Shanks!
Guys! Set sail!
Yeah!
Shanks!
I'll definitely get on board next time!
Yeah, try it if you can!
Uta!
Nyah, nyah, bleah!
When I return,
I'll test you to see if you became any stronger!
Luffy!
Welcome back!
What was your adventure like this time?
Tell me!
Oh? What's your problem, guys?
You look down.
Forget it! I'll ask Uta!
Uta!
I'll let you brag
about your adventures again.
Where are you, Uta?!
Shanks! Where's Uta?!
Where did she go?!
No way. Don't tell me...
Did something happen to her?
Don't worry, Luffy.
Uta left the ship to become a singer.
That's all.
What?
No way.
Why?!
She loves you so much!
She'd never leave the ship!
Something must've happened!
Say something, Shanks!
I'm done with you!
Some time later, a piece of news
spread across the world.
ISSHIN DOJO
I won again.
D-Damn!
Elegia...
Terrible news, everyone!
Pirates are here!
Oh! It's time for him already?
I have to prepare breakfast.
I can't believe the residents are all dead.
How cruel.
Ouch!
Watch it, you damn geezer!
I'm using a knife!
You amateur!
Why don't you do the dishes?!
He destroyed the country?
What a crazy fruit punch!
He's an irredeemable villain.
He was a crewmember of
the King of the Pirates.
I wouldn't be surprised if he did that.
Your bad cat did it again!
What do you want?
What kind of education are you giving her,
Belle-Mere?!
What kind?
Unconstrained.
Too unconstrained!
Go play with Nojiko over there.
Uh-huh!
I'll overlook it just this time!
From the next time, I'll...
Okay, okay. I'll make sure to talk to her.
Have you read about it?
Yeah, that's a big deal.
I'm sure the Navy won't keep quiet...
NAVY
Elegia has been annihilated.
They say it's devastated.
I heard Red-Haired did it...
It has something to do with Tot Musica.
Tot Musica...
I think he went a little too far.
Yeah...
He revealed his true nature.
His recent behavior is inexplicable.
Roger must be crying, Red-Haired...
Hey, Luffy!
Oh, it's you, Beckman.
Don't be disappointed.
You wished I was Boss?
No way! I'm done with Shanks!
Hey, Luffy...
Forgive Boss.
Why?! He's not telling me what happened,
so it's his fault!
Everyone has a thing or two
that they can't talk about.
I don't understand!
That means you can't talk about it either?!
If Boss won't talk about it, yes.
Forget it!
Uta!
You're the squirt from the other day.
You guys...
Are you alone today?
Did you guys have a fight?
Shut up!
You shut up, shitty brat!
I'll make you pay for the attack that day!
I'm... s... s... strong...
When I return,
I'll test you to see if you became any stronger!
Luffy!
Don't worry, Luffy.
Uta left the ship to become a singer.
Everyone has a thing or two
that they can't talk about.
Let's build a new genesis!
Damn... Damn...
Ouch!
Beck...
I'm taking the boy back!
Shut up, you fool!
Go away, mountain bandits!
W-What's with him?!
You're up...
Hey...
I wanna be strong...
Yeah...
I wanna be strong!
I know...
Hey, Luffy.
Let me aboard your ship!
No.
Cheapskate!
Aren't you done with me?
No, I'm not.
Oh, why are you hurt?
I fell.
No way.
How did you fall to get hurt like....
I fell!
Okay, you fell.
Then I have no further questions for you.
I have no further questions for you too,
because it's yours and Uta's business.
You're talking like a grown-up.
Then can I come on board?!
You must be hungry.
Thank you, Makino!
I'll pay you back with treasure!
Luffy, I've got something
to celebrate your maturity, too.
What?
Cool!
See, you're a kid!
That's not fair, Shanks!
Don't laugh!
Where's Red-Haired?
He disappeared.
He has become troublesome.
Really troublesome.
FIRST SHOW
Luffy! Luffy, Luffy!
What's the matter, Usopp?
The diva's having a show!
I get to see her in person?!
Don't get excited, Kinky Cook!
What did you say?!
Whoa-whoa...
It's her first show!
I'd like to see it live.
I wanna burn it into my eyes!
I don't have eyes though!
Super funky!
This is the biggest favor I'll ask!
Let's go to Elegia!
Singing, huh... Sounds interesting!
What? A change of course?
All right!
The new destination is Elegia!
Let's go!
Yeah!
From now on,
a world of everlasting peace will begin,
where there is no war or poverty,
and where music resounds forever.
The Four Emperors of the
Sea, Red-Haired, the divac
The Red-Hair Pirates' disturbing behavior
behind the singing voice of the new genesis.
"Red-Haired" Shanks.
The legendary man still shrouded in mystery.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Captain's Log of the
Legend! Red-Haired Shanks!"
I'm gonna become a Navy admiral!