Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Draw your own map
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha ni areta umi no youna jidai
Even the values we had built up were about to fall apart
kizukiageta kachikan sae mo kuzuresarou to shita
Who knows if the compass is pointing in the right direction?
rashinban no sashita saki ga tadashii no ka douka nante
No one knows for certain
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
I do it for my own
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
And you do yours, don't we?
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And I'm ready for it
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
With the support of someone I can rely
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
Seize the future beyond your imagination
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
We'll go wherever we wanna go
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Tears and doubts in tow
Let's paint it in our own colors
onore no iro de egaite yuke
This is bad... Let's...
...retreat for now!
I won't let you flee!
It's time to try your skill!
Show me what you can do!
Fulgora!
FULGORA
Oh? I'm free.
Where's Mama?
Mama! Where are you?!
I'll be there! Mama!
Mama, where are you?!
Answer me! Let me help you!
Eustass-ya became weaker.
Big Mom went back to the castle...
It'll be a pain if she returns
for that thundercloud.
Hey! I'm gonna take everyone else
except you!
Okay!
Mama!
What?!
"Nami Screams -
A Deadly Death Race!"
You two, go downstairs!
I'll defeat him at any cost!
Tell that to everyone...
...for me!
You seem to be enjoying yourself.
The higher the risk, the bigger the smile
and the bigger the smile...
Luffy!
Please! Take him down!
Kaido!
Ring, ring, ring...
Clank.
Kin-sama?!
Shinobu! Is Momonosuke-sama doing okay?!
He is, but we're getting
more and more attacks from the enemy!
We're now in a hidden room, but...
Do not lower your guard!
Kanjuro is after you guys!
Stay alert! He will come to annihilate
the Kozuki Clan!
I will be there to defend you!
We're in a crawl space on the first floor
of the castle! Be safe!
I got it! I am counting on you, Shinobu!
Kin'emon!
Momonosuke-sama!
Please be patient for now!
Sorry, sorry! Did it hit you?
What are you doing?
Could you help me a little bit?
We must get ready
to overcome this situation!
Gee! If you make a move now,
you'll risk Momonosuke-sama's life!
Hunker down for now!
This is the only way to protect you!
And I must sort things out
with my old man!
Together with you!
Momonosuke-kun!
You guys, why don't you give up already?!
He got on! The dinosaur guy!
Go away!
Usopp! Hit his weak spots!
I know!
We won't give up! We're not gonna die!
The temple!
The chin!
The Adam's apple!
Damn you...
Leave us alone, you damn lizard!
The eyeball!
The nostril!
Just fall already!
BAM! WHACK! THUD! BONK!
WHACK! CRACK! THUD! WHACK!
How many hits will you take before you fall?!
He's unbelievably tough!
BAM! THUD! WHACK! BAM!
You can do it, Komachiyo!
We'll be there soon!
If we can get to the stage
on the Performance Floor,
I can give a command to the enemies
who were forced to eat Kibi Dango...
...by Horselina-chan and the others!
And if they become our allies...
I'm...
...no longer needed!
If I can help everyone, I...
...don't care what'll happen to me!
So get me to the stage!
Don't be silly, Tama!
Get a grip!
Until we take back the Land of Wano,
this fight won't be over!
Otama! Let's keeping fighting!
This young lady and this old man
will protect you at any cost!
Who did you call an old man?!
I'm only 19!
Just like Big Bro Luffy,
I wanted to help everyone!
But I'm...
...scared and I can't take it anymore...
Even if you make the Gifters your allies,
it's no use!
You stupid brat! Don't push your luck!
The child is scared!
I won't let you touch her!
I'm sorry, Tama.
Usohachi-kun...
I won't make you nervous anymore!
Leave it to me!
Usopp!
Get ready, you damn lizard!
You long-nose shit!
Everything you do annoys me!
Special Attack Green Star!
What?! What are you doing,
you damn long-nose freak?!
Firework Flowers!
It's hot!
Watch it, Usopp!
Sorry! I don't have that many
close-range weapons!
Anyway, I'll take him down!
Special Attack Green Star!
Exploding Pine Cones!
Come on! Usopp!
I did it! it was a direct hit!
How's that, you bastard?!
Lizard extermination complete!
To me, Usopp-sama,
the Tobi Roppo is like nothing!
Hey...
Hey, you!
He got up again!
What's wrong with those
dinosaur power-users?!
Komachiyo, run!
Damn...
That long-nose fool!
I wish Kibi Dango worked against him, too...
It only works with Smile fruit eaters!
What should we do if he comes back?!
In any case,
let's get to the Performance Floor!
We must fulfill Otama's plan!
That brat!
Repel!
I'll make him pay!
Show yourself, Kid!
What?!
Big Mom?!
You fools!
Cat Burglar and the one with the long nose...
She's gonna kill us!
You're Straw Hat's peers.
Olin-chan!
Otama!
It's been so long!
It's you, Otama!
I'm happy to see you again!
What are you doing
in a dangerous place like this?!
Why?!
I've never seen Big Mom like that!
I've been worried about you, Olin-chan!
You suddenly disappeared in Udon!
Sorry...
But I've been worried about you, too.
I'm not mad!
I'm happy to see you again!
Uh-huh! Thank you for taking care of me
when I lost my memory!
Great! So you got your memory back!
Mm-hm!
Oh, no...
She went into Mother Mode which she only enters
around kids under 10 every now and then.
Whoa... Whoa-whoa, Otama!
I-Is she your friend?!
You're looking great in kimono!
Really?!
I got a new hairpin!
Otama! Make her go away!
Hey, the person who did my hair...
That meddlesome and poor woman
from Okobore Town...
Oh, Otsuru! How is she doing?
I'll never forget how that small amount of
red-bean soup tasted!
It was so delicious!
I wish I could eat it again.
Thing is... Olin-chan...
That Okobore Town is gone now.
Gone? What do you mean by that?
After we left for Udon,
Okobore Town got attacked!
We burned down
the mountain bandit's mountain!
But instead of seeking revenge,
they keep stealing tons of food
from our farm!
Do you guys have something to do with it?!
W-We don't know anything!
I heard samurai are preparing to make a raid...
Is that why, maybe?!
If so, we can't let them know!
What are you guys whispering about?!
I will guide you!
So do not hurt anyone!
O-Otsuru-san!
Guide me?
Do you know anything about this?
You will see once you get there.
It is a little far though...
No, Otsuru-san!
You don't have to cover for us!
It's okay now! We just wanted to eat
as much as we wanted before we die!
What?
So it's you guys who did it!
They lied about being the ones
who ate the food...
...which was actually eaten by
Samurai-san's group before the raid.
So Kaido's subordinates...
...burned down the town.
What?
Olin-san.
They're rebels! Don't let them get away!
Burn them along with the houses!
The people of Okobore Town got...
Otsuru!
This is sweet red-bean soup.
Go ahead, Olin-san, try it!
So good!
It's delicious!
I'm glad that you like it.
Thank you, Tsuru-san.
Okobore Town?!
Oh, you're looking great, Olin-san!
Am I?
That's so cute!
I want my hair done like you two!
I will do your hair
once you get a little older.
--Really?!
--I'll help that, too!
Oh, gee!
Olin-san, you look beautiful!
That looks good on you!
Thank you all!
Kaido's subordinates killed them...
Destroy them along with the town!
Burn it all up!
The people who helped me
when I lost my memory...
Olin-san!
Everyone...
Everyone in Okobore Town
who was so nice to me...
Is that what you're telling me?!
I won't forgive you guys!
Are you okay?
--What?!
--Olin-chan!
What's the matter?!
--It's over...
--Don't kill us!
This is perfect!
You guys are cornered rats!
The dinosaur guy's coming!
Olin-chan! Kaido's subordinate
is attacking us!
Kaido?
Go away! We're busy now!
Keep yelping until you die!
Run, Komachiyo!
Hey, Big Mom!
Don't let them get past you!
Go, Komachiyo!
I won't let you go!
Too slow! This is it!
Shut up!
You fools...
Even in the immoral world of pirates,
there's supposed to be
humanity and justice!
Damn you!
You idiot!
Big Sis!
It's that way... Big Mom!
That's Mama! Great! She's alive!
Are you okay, Komachiyo?!
You must get up!
Momonosuke contemplates Luffy
and Kaido's battle.
Yamato heads out to the battlefield.
Ulti challenges Big Mom
to get her revenge.
Their alliance cracks.
Hate grows as rancor piles up,
and anger ignites a new phase.
On the next episode of One Piece! "The Dawn of
the Land of Wano - The All-Out Battle Heats Up!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!