Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Draw your own map
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha ni areta umi no youna jidai
Even the values we had built up were about to fall apart
kizukiageta kachikan sae mo kuzuresarou to shita
Who knows if the compass is pointing in the right direction?
rashinban no sashita saki ga tadashii no ka douka nante
No one knows for certain
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
I do it for my own
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And you do yours, don't we?
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
And I'm ready for it
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
With the support of someone I can rely
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Seize the future beyond your imagination
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
We'll go wherever we wanna go
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Tears and doubts in tow
onore no iro de egaite yuke
Let's paint it in our own colors
Hey! I'm gonna take everyone else
except you!
Okay!
After Law and Zoro left the rooftop,
Luffy and Kaido's one-on-one fight began.
You seem to be enjoying yourself.
The higher the risk, the bigger the smile
and the bigger the smile...
Meanwhile, Nami and Usopp
were defending Otama.
With Big Mom's appearance,
the battle became chaotic!
Olin-chan!
Otama!
It's been so long!
Otama! Make her go away!
Thing is... Olin-chan...
Okobore Town?!
They killed the people who helped me
when I lost my memory...
Everyone...
Everyone in Okobore Town
who was so nice to me...
Is that what you're telling me?!
I won't forgive you guys!
--It's over...
--Don't kill us!
This is perfect!
Run, Komachiyo!
Too slow! This is it!
Shut up!
You fools...
Even in the immoral world of pirates,
there's supposed to be
humanity and justice!
Damn you!
You idiot!
Big Sis!
"The Dawn of the Land of Wano -
The All-Out Battle Heats Up!"
CONNECTING HALLWAY
FROM TREASURE REPOSITORY 2F TO CASTLE 3F
Kiku, does your arm hurt?
You don't ask such things of a samurai.
It's merely "itching"
until my life is extinguished.
Just like my heart "itched"
on the day you disappeared...
Oden-sama is gone!
Whitebeard's ship left the port, too!
I was afraid of this!
Big Bro Izo...
Dog-chan and Cat-chan are gone, too!
Don't cry, Okiku!
Instead of fearing the worst,
let's look for them!
--Okay?!
--Mm-hm.
Search! Search across the country!
Hey! What's going on?!
I knew you would do this!
Whitebeard!
Oden?!
Let me on board the ship!
Oden-sama! I knew you would do this!
I won't let you go!
That fool!
Let me come!
Show me the world!
Come back! You are the next Shogun!
Big Bro-sama!
I can still vividly remember that day.
Hey...
Well, if you're fine enough
to tease me, that's good.
I'm really sorry
that I disappeared without telling you...
No, I would've done the same
if I were in your shoes.
It's more important to protect Oden-sama
than to warn the others of the urgency.
You and I would've died
if it weren't for Oden-sama...
If we hadn't met him,
we wouldn't have lived to see today.
I'll always be with Oden-sama!
So this "itch" in my arm is nothing
compared to the pain of losing Oden-sama!
Mm-hm.
Izo.
If the Land of Wano is successfully opened,
how do you think it'll change?
Well...
Let's talk about it tomorrow morning
if we survive.
That's a tall task!
Now it is an all-out war!
It is win or die!
There must be
a shortage of forces everywhere.
I can protect Momonosuke-sama
all by myself!
Kanjuro will attack Momonosuke-sama!
I will try to reach Momonosuke-sama
before him,
and take him down with my own hands!
You guys, scatter and help the others out!
Roger!
Okay, Kin'emon!
Cat, let's spread out!
I'll do so!
Mm-hm! Good luck!
Kin-sama!
Let me take care of Kanjuro!
I'll get him this time!
Kiku! Follow me!
Okay!
That's...!
Master Cat Viper!
I knew it was you-saru!
Shishilian! Bariete!
SHISHILIAN - CAPTAIN OF DOGSTORM MUSKETEERS
BARIETE - MINK RECON SQUAD
Where are you dashing off to?!
We need your help!
The thing is... Pedro...
Goodbye.
Pedro... died?!
Yes, in Big Mom's territory.
I think Luffy-kun's group wouldn't be here
if it weren't for him!
I see.
Pedro...
You did a great job-meow!
The one responsible for his death
is here on the island?!
Yes, we need your help-saru!
It seems like Wanda and Carrot
are struggling against him!
Of course I was gonna help you!
Master!
The cat is flying!
CRAWL SPACE, FIRST FLOOR INSIDE THE CASTLE
Momonosuke-kun.
Shinobu-san... Watch out for the Marys!
They're roaming around Onigashima
to do recon!
They could be anywhere.
They could be watching us from somewhere now!
What? Where?! Where are they?!
Don't worry! We got this!
Do not tell me that is...
It's you!
I thought so!
I'll use this to make myself a decoy!
You and I are targeted as a group.
So I'm gonna carry this and run!
The enemy will think I'm carrying you
and come after me!
And I'll hit them like wham!
You two can stay hiding here!
All right!
I can see you're itching to fight.
Go ahead, Yamato.
We're in contact with Kin-sama!
I'll protect Momonosuke-sama here!
Uh-huh! Thanks! Shinobu-san!
Oh, yeah!
Momonosuke-kun,
you can hear Luffy's voice, right?
Is he okay?
Mm-hm, I can hear it.
It hasn't changed from before.
He became weaker, but he's fine.
But...
...there are only two voices now!
What?
One on one...
Luffy and Kaido must be fighting head to head!
I gotta hurry!
ODEN'S TRAVEL RECORD
I never thought I'd meet you one day!
On that day, I picked this up
at the river below Oden Castle.
I, of course, give this to you.
I see... All the details of
my father's adventures are here...
Oh, no! Pardon me!
Th-That was delivered to you after all this time
and contains everything about Oden-sama!
Go ahead and read it.
Mm-hm.
Mm-hm, mm-hm...
I had heard so many stories about him...
but to actually read them like this...
Take this!
Gum-Gum...
...Hawk Gatling!
Gear Three!
Gum-Gum...
...Grizzly Magnum!
Let's smile more, Straw Hat!
I'm not enjoying myself at all, Kaido!
Just smile all by yourself!
Then I'll make it more enjoyable for you!
You stupid swordsman!
Don't sleep and dream so peacefully!
SECOND FLOOR INSIDE THE CASTLE
Damn! You're heavy...
...and hard to carry...
...and there's no joy in carrying you!
That's Black-Leg Sanji
with a bounty of 330 million berries!
Take him down!
Look who he's carrying!
Maybe that's Pirate Hunter Zoro!
What?!
The big money is carrying the big money!
Watch what you say!
The 330-million is carrying the 320-million!
That's not what I meant! Damn...
Can't you beat them more quietly?
You're in my way, Mosshead!
PERFORMANCE FLOOR
It's showtime!
Dance, Rac-Raccoon!
Cloven Rose, Palm!
So many people suffered
because of you!
Give it some thought!
Don't preach at me!
Goodbye! Mr. Raccoon Dog!
So long, Raccoon-san!
Damn...
Another enemy?!
Chopperemon-san!
Lick!
What the?!
I came to help, Animal Kingdom Pirates...
How could you ruin my show?!
Just when I was gonna liven it up!
That guy's the one from
the Big Mom Pirates...
It's good to see you again...
Lick!
P-Pay-Pay!
P... P-P-P... Page One-sama!
Was it you...
...who burned down Okobore Town?
Hey!
Hey, you...
How could you do that to my brother-arinsu?!
Your brother?
Damn you!
I'll make you pay-arinsu! Big Mom!
How dare you hurt Pay-Pay?!
She's coming!
Okay, let's have Big Mom
beat that woman, too!
Yeah...
Big Mom's starting to...
...look like a godness!
Hey!
Olin-san!
That woman is bad!
She's the one who did the thing
that made you sad!
Whatever it is...
Shut up!
Cut the crap, Straw Hats!
After that tramp, you'll be next!
Ulti-chan! Beat her!
Let's take down Big Mom together!
Shut up! Stay there!
After that old bag, you'll be next-arinsu!
Run, Komachiyo!
Get as far away as possible!
Hey!
I said "Stay there"!
Ulti-Mortar!
Komachiyo!
I've had it with chasing-arinsu...
Komainu...
Your speed has given me nothing but trouble!
Did that break a few bones?
Komachiyo...
You're badly beaten, poor you...
You asked for it!
Just stay down there!
Damn...
Komachiyo!
Stop it!
Tama...
Komachiyo is my best friend!
Shut up!
Tama!
Otama!
Tama! You okay?!
Otama! Stay with me!
Hey, Nami! Carry her and beat it!
Let's flee for now!
Hey, tramp.
You just messed with my friend.
You hurt my brother...
You shitty lizard!
How could you do that to Otama?!
What?!
W-Wait, Nami! We gotta run!
No!
I don't think I can forgive...
...people who hit children!
This bastard...
I'll kick her ass right here!
Bearing the future of the Land of Wano on his shoulders,
Luffy confronts the greatest obstacle of all!
His limit-breaking special attacks
drive Kaido to the wall!
Can his all-out blow with a dream of
becoming the King of the Pirates...
...break open the door to the new era?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Conclusion! Luffy, Accelerating Fist of the Supreme King"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!