iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
Draw your own map
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha ni areta umi no youna jidai
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
kizukiageta kachikan sae mo kuzuresarou to shita
Even the values we had built up were about to fall apart
rashinban no sashita saki ga tadashii no ka douka nante
Who knows if the compass is pointing in the right direction?
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
No one knows for certain
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
I do it for my own
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And you do yours, don't we?
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
And I'm ready for it
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
With the support of someone I can rely
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Seize the future beyond your imagination
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
We'll go wherever we wanna go
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Tears and doubts in tow
onore no iro de egaite yuke
Let's paint it in our own colors
"The Conclusion!
Luffy, Accelerating Fist of the Supreme King"
Get out of my way!
Why?!
I've got a bounty of 330 million!
And he's got a bounty of only 320 million,
which makes him a loser!
Why should I carry him on my shoulder?!
I'm thirsty. I want sake.
Can't you see the situation?!
You must be sleep-talking!
You really were sleep-talking!
Damn...
How did it come to this?
SEVERAL MINUTES AGO
Hey! Momo! Shinobu-chan!
Captain Kid!
Kid! I mean, what?
We won't let you through!
This is good for me!
I need more metal scraps!
I don't, however, need you fools!
T-Take this!
What?
Outta my way!
Where are you, Big Mom?!
Kid?
Oh, crap!
I switched us with some flying object!
Black-Leg-ya?!
Tra-guy? Mosshead?
Catch us!
What's this all about?
Where am I?! Where's Mama?!
I'm on my way to help!
Zeus!
Where's Nami-san?
I thought you were working for her!
--Hey!
--Leave him be.
Why are you relaxing on my shoulder?!
At the very least, I'd like a girl!
I moved us to the right place.
No, you didn't!
Where did you guys come from?!
I'm not obligated to carry
you scruffy guys! Get down already!
Are you listening?!
Look after him, Black-Leg-ya.
What happened?
Wait! Explain the situation before you go!
Zoro-ya probably had
20 to 30 bones broken.
Splint up his body, put him on his back,
make sure he's conscious and breathing.
Not his situation!
Why don't you look after him?!
I have to stop Big Mom!
You can at least tend to his wounds, right?!
--I'll leave it to you!
--Hey!
I'm not a doctor!
And I don't have time to tend to his wounds!
That bastard!
I have no choice!
Do you even know how to apply a bandage?
It's the same as trussing a ham.
Am I a ham to you?
You're not that appetizing!
And?
Who could hurt you like this?
Kaido and Big Mom.
No wonder. I can't believe
you made it to the rooftop.
Tell me Luffy is okay.
I think he figured something out...
He'll win!
I know that!
Anyway...
--Wait! Big money!
--I won't let you escape!
I wanna leave you somewhere!
Sangoro-dono!
Kappa! You guys are all right!
Great!
Now, how can Zorojuro-dono
sleep under these circumstances?
Maybe he got beaten by Kaido...
He seems seriously injured.
Don't worry.
This idiot won't die that easily.
You're the idiot...
You're actually awake, aren't you?
Sangoro-dono, where are you heading?
To the best of our poor abilities,
we'll help you.
I was gonna get to Momonosuke.
You weren't?
Kin'emon is heading for him,
so he'll be okay.
If you wanna help,
go to the Performance Floor.
The Performance Floor?
What's going on there?!
Don't just make a request
and then fall asleep!
Let's go to the Performance Floor!
Considering their strength, if we don't hurry,
the casualties will only increase.
Yeah!
Thunder...
...Bagua!
I know how you feel now.
It's fun to punch someone
stronger than you!
Like a kid, you're caught up in trying to
defeat the enemy in front of you!
Gum-Gum...
...Red Roc!
I kept bringing down those people
who were said to be stronger than me,
and I found myself
being called the strongest...
But what do I see from here?
It's boring to look at a landscape
in which no one is stronger than you.
You're lucky.
Because you don't have to feel this way.
Give up. You're different from me.
You can't change anything.
The Kozuki Clan will be destroyed and the
Land of Wano will become New Onigashima.
I'll still be the strongest and bored...
The Kozuki Clan won't be destroyed...
The Land of Wano...
...will be free!
And...
This fool...
I'm gonna become...
...the King of the Pirates!
I'll kick her ass right here!
Hey, Nami...
What are you doing?! We gotta run!
She'll get up again!
You know how tough those dinosaurs are!
Big Mom is behind us, too!
There's no path to victory for us!
Even if we run away,
she'll never stop chasing us!
More than anything,
she even hurt Otama and that's unforgivable!
Hey, Tama! Stay with me!
Otama, are you alive?!
I know you're already up!
Just get up already!
Are you ready to be taken down by me now?
Whoa-whoa, twirling a baton?!
A loser like you is no match for Ulti-sama,
Cheerleader!
Tornado...
...Tempo!
That's a good surprise-attack, Nami!
But...
You'll have to do better than that!
I got you!
Don't worry-arinsu.
When I finish with this tramp,
you're next.
I'm determined to beat the shit out of
everyone who messes with Pay-Pay.
You're no exception, old bag!
Just as Pay-Pay suffered...
No, I'll make you suffer
100 million times more than him!
Do you have any idea...
...what you have done?
I don't care about that brat!
Should I have hurt her more?!
I'm sorry-arinsu. You're first.
I didn't like you from
the beginning-arinsu.
After you ran like a rat,
you told that unfunny joke that your captain
would become the King of the Pirates...
But now,
I finally get to smash your head in.
Ulti...
No...
Onami-chan...
--Hera!
--Yes, Mama!
--Prometheus!
--Yeah, Mama!
Napoleon!
Yes, Mama!
Let's go!
Combine!
Ow, ow...
Maser Cannon!
First, it was Page One-sama...
A-And now,
Ulti-sama was beaten by Big Mom...
Isn't she our ally?
Can you get up, Nami?!
That was crazy, but you saved us!
Let's run!
Mm-hm!
Komachiyo...
Sorry, Tama! We can't save him now!
Let's come back for him later!
Zeus?!
Come to think of it,
who is that thundercloud?
Hey!
We hit it off so well, Hera!
I couldn't do that attack
with the stupid Zeus!
No, that's because you got on
with me well, right, Hera?!
Don't push your luck, you dummies.
I just followed Mama's lead.
Don't be so cold!
I begged Mama for a girlfriend
and she created you!
Your girlfriend? No thanks.
What?! But I even like that part of you!
It's nice to have a girl in the group!
Prometheus...
Yeah! The three of us should
work closely together from now on!
Napoleon...
Seems like you're gonna be
a better team than with Zeus.
Hey, Mama... Who is that girl?
A predecessor sets
a good example for what not to do.
Who is she?
That's supposed to be my place...
Hey...
Am I gonna be all alone?
That's Nami!
No wonder...
I once tried to kill her...
Zeus!
It's you, Zeus!
Oh, Mama! I'm sorry to be late!
We have a new member?
It's reassuring to have a fourth member!
Four? No, Zeus.
What?
You're no longer needed!
Are you still trying to defeat me?!
This is fun!
What's the matter?
You're getting weaker!
Oh?
Is it over now?
It's over.
In the end, this is your limit.
You can still smile?! Interesting!
Bring it on!
I'll knock you down again and again!
I see... While I was unaware...
No, the outcome was obvious
from the beginning...
You sure did infuse yourself
with the Haki during the battle...
But such a strong weapon
made you cocky, squirt...
Humans don't give up hope...
No, they just can't give it up...
That's the problem...
It's been a long time since I got
this worked up so I screwed up...
I should have chopped your head off
and declared victory...
Otherwise...
...they'll all keep the false hope
that you're gonna win, won't they?
Kaido's destructive power has taken
down Luffy along with his Color of the Supreme King!
Top officers' fierce onslaughts
gradually drive the Straw Hats to the wall!
After the captain fell, is there still any hope
left in the Land of Wano?
Or only despair?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Luffy, Defeated! The Straw Hats in Jeopardy?!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!