Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Draw your own map
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha ni areta umi no youna jidai
Even the values we had built up were about to fall apart
kizukiageta kachikan sae mo kuzuresarou to shita
Who knows if the compass is pointing in the right direction?
rashinban no sashita saki ga tadashii no ka douka nante
No one knows for certain
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
I do it for my own
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
And you do yours, don't we?
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And I'm ready for it
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
With the support of someone I can rely
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Seize the future beyond your imagination
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
We'll go wherever we wanna go
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
Tears and doubts in tow
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Let's paint it in our own colors
onore no iro de egaite yuke
Luffy launched an all-out attack
against Kaido.
But...
"Luffy, Defeated!
The Straw Hats in Jeopardy?!"
He infused himself...
...with the Color of the Supreme King...
But the way he handled it...
...was just awful...
Gum-Gum...
Are you still trying to defeat me?!
This is fun!
What was it?
You couldn't be Joyboy...
...either, I guess...
SECOND FLOOR INSIDE THE CASTLE
No, Zeus.
What?
You're no longer...
...needed!
Hey, Nami!
You didn't really mean
I'm no longer needed.
Right, Mama?!
What are you talking about, Zeus?!
You left Mama in the lurch!
No, I didn't mean to...
You have screwed up
so much until now as well!
We're better off without you!
Mama!
What are you doing? We better run now!
Hera!
Eat Zeus!
What?!
By consuming his soul,
you'll become even stronger!
How could you say that, Mama?!
I'd be happy to eat him!
Mama!
Zeus-senpai! I'm gonna eat you!
Don't! Stop her, Mama!
I'm sorry for always messing up!
If you don't wanna see me, I'll go away!
Hey! Stop moving!
I swear I'll never show my face
to you again!
So please!
Don't kill me!
That makes you a thief!
You're stealing a piece of my soul!
If you're truly sorry, let her eat you
and become part of her power!
Help, Mama!
That serves you right!
Right, Otama?
Oh no!
You guys...
I won't let you live!
Huh?
It's dangerous,
so stay out of the way for now.
Otama!
Otama! You're awake!
Stay there!
Onami-chan! Usohachi-kun!
They're bad pirates called the Straw Hats!
So...
...I'm gonna kill them!
Wait!
Don't do it, Olin-chan!
They're my friends!
We're doomed!
Nami!
I'm sorry!
For trying to kill you earlier!
Get this straight, Zeus!
If you hold back, I'll wipe you out!
I'm sorry, Nami!
Rest in peace!
I hate you!
I'm done with you!
I'm a coward...
...so I couldn't refuse Mama's order!
Hera!
I didn't wanna die so I betrayed you
even though you were so kind to me...
I'm a weakling and a coward!
I don't care!
I said I was done with you!
Nami?!
I know you did!
But I got dumped by the other side too,
and I'm all alone now!
I know I'm doomed to die soon...
...but I don't wanna die
with everyone hating me!
You don't have to forgive me,
but watch me!
I'm gonna rebel
for the first and last time!
Tama!
Usohachi-kun!
--Let's run!
--Mm-hm!
At least one person!
I wanna make it up to at least one person!
And then I'll die!
Nami! Run!
This is my way of life!
Zeus!
What?
I'm already running out of energy...
What?!
Is this for real?!
His soul is being extracted!
Mama!
Now eat him, Hera!
He's such a doofus!
Here are Black Balls out of pity!
Eat them and run!
Zeus!
Oh, no! He's soulless now,
he's not even going for his favorite!
Eat them, Zeus!
Wake up!
I'm gonna eat you! Zeus-senpai!
Zeus!
PERFORMANCE FLOOR, SKULL DOME
Way to go! Chopperemon-san!
That serves you right, Queen! You bastard!
You don't mind if I kill traitors,
do you?! Lick!
Perospero! I don't need your help!
Doesn't matter if you don't.
I'm just doing this for Mama.
Whatever! No...
Get rid of all the small fries!
That'll save me the trouble!
Everyone, take shelter!
Hide behind something!
That's a lot of arrows!
Hurry up! Run now!
Run!
Run! Hurry!
--He's gonna shoot'em!
--Hurry up and hide!
Go to hell!
Apocalyptic Candy Shower!
Watch out!
Oh, no!
Are you okay?!
Wake up! Stay with me!
How dare they do this...
That was a hell of an attack!
I couldn't take down so many of them. Lick!
But that's fine.
That means I get to enjoy it again.
Raccoon...
Take this!
He grabbed his head!
Chopperemon-san is overpowering Queen...
How strong!
That's not the kind of breath I'd expect
from someone who's winning the battle!
Huh, Raccoon?!
I wonder how much more he can take.
Lick!
THIRD FLOOR INSIDE THE CASTLE
I...
No.
We'll never flee or hide!
Bring it on from anywhere!
There you are, Young Master Yamato!
Come back without resisting!
That's...
Momonosuke!
Yeah, that cocky look in his eyes!
That insolent mouth!
That sure is Kozuki's stupid son!
Oh?
He's not handcuffed!
That's right. I'm not captive anymore!
I'm...
...Oden!
Listen, everyone!
I'm Kozuki Oden!
I'm with my son, Momonosuke!
CRAWL SPACE, FIRST FLOOR
Father's logbook...
It contains a series of his adventures
that I do not know of.
When he joined the Whitebeard Pirates
led by Edward Newgate,
his journey began.
What's this place?!
He was surprised and excited
by the world he had never seen before...
And...
...he fought, too!
He eventually met the great pirate,
Gold Roger.
Divine Departure!
The Final Island which is said to
hold a vast amount of treasure.
Father heard about it from Roger then he...
White-Kichi-chan!
I wanna go!
Please allow me to go!
...went aboard Roger's ship.
And he advanced toward
his desired island little by little...
I found it!
This is where it was?!
The writing is about a weapon
named Poseidon.
I see...
Have you completed the train?!
You mean the Sea Train?! No way!
I'm still designing it!
Toki! That's the Fish-Man Island!
How interesting... It seems like
the whole island is in a bubble...
--How is it, Oden?
--Well...
one of them isn't so important.
It's an apology letter
from someone named Joyboy.
I can't believe it!
He really can read the script!
Yeah, by the way, do you have a weapon
to control the Neptunians?!
Once every few centuries in this country,
a Mermaid who can talk to
the Neptunians is born.
Maybe, that Mermaid is...
So your daughter will become the weapon
that will destroy the world someday?!
I never thought that Poseidon
was a Mermaid!
Then...
...finally...
Now we've got all the Road Ponegliffs...
Let's go, guys! To the Final Island!
Yeah!
The Final Island
no man has set foot on for 800 years...
...was named Laugh Tale.
Laugh Tale...
--Shinobu.
--Yes.
I think I must not die.
Of course not!
Why are you saying that now?!
What is it?!
Who is it?!
What?! What is it this time?!
What's wrong?! Stay with me!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Clank.
Kaido-sama! We found Momonosuke!
--I'll be there soon.
--Okay!
Let the whole of Onigashima know, Bao Huang.
My battle against Straw Hat is over.
There's no point in doing anything now.
Zeus!
Zeus...
I feel a surge of power!
He got eaten...
Usohachi-kun! Onami-chan!
We must get away!
--Otama!
--Hurry up!
Usopp!
Yeah!
Otama, why are you running away?
Hey, come here!
I see...
You're leaving me!
I hate those who leave me!
Don't look at her!
What should I do about the ones I hate?
I should kill them!
What?!
You're...!
Punk Gibson!
Mama!
Are you okay?! Stay with me!
Kid!
Captain Kid!
Go away, Straw Hats.
This bastard...
...is my prey!
We can win this!
The Animal Kingdom Pirates gain momentum
and upset the Straw Hats!
Will they be swallowed
by the sea along with Luffy?
On top of that,
the vengeful Kanjuro attacks Momonosuke!
Hurry up, Kin'emon!
What is the fate of the Kozuki Clan?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Animal Kingdom Pirates Trample Down!
The End of the Kozuki Clan!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!