Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Draw your own map
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha ni areta umi no youna jidai
Even the values we had built up were about to fall apart
kizukiageta kachikan sae mo kuzuresarou to shita
Who knows if the compass is pointing in the right direction?
rashinban no sashita saki ga tadashii no ka douka nante
No one knows for certain
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
I do it for my own
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
And you do yours, don't we?
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And I'm ready for it
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
With the support of someone I can rely
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
Seize the future beyond your imagination
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
We'll go wherever we wanna go
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
Tears and doubts in tow
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Let's paint it in our own colors
onore no iro de egaite yuke
Luffy was defeated by Kaido
and sank into the sea.
Kaido-sama! We found Momonosuke!
--I'll be there soon.
--Okay!
You're...!
Punk Gibson!
Go away, Straw Hats.
This bastard...
...is my prey!
Captain Kid!
What?! What is it this time?!
Who is it?!
"The Animal Kingdom Pirates Trample Down!
The End of the Kozuki Clan!"
Momonosuke-sama!
Oh, what should I do?!
What am I supposed to do?!
Kin-sama!
Just get here already!
--Kiku.
--Yeah...
Momonosuke-sama!
Kin-sama!
Oh, Shinobu!
I am glad that you are okay!
I'll send the ladder down now!
Momonosuke-sama is...!
--What?!
--Momonosuke-sama!
It's not working!
I feel no pain, not even a little bit!
Your attacks can't hurt me at all!
I guess you can't keep it up anymore...
Lick!
It's coming again!
The shower of candy arrows!
Take cover!
Chopperemon-san!
The Rumble Ball's effect
will be gone in less than 10 minutes...
Even though the duration was increased...
That's not good enough!
Three minutes of gigantification?
What can you do in that short time?
What?
The Rumble Ball?
Look at that formula.
I can improve that Rumble Ball!
Five times...
No, I can make the drug
10 times more effective!
But there'll be a side effect if I remain
as a monster for more than three minutes...
A side effect?
So what?!
You only care about yourself?!
And you call yourself a pirate?!
What?!
The enemies you guys will face hereafter...
...can't be beaten in three minutes!
If you say
"Oh, I'm scared of the side effect,"
you can't even protect your dear playmates,
kiddo! Do you understand?
Take a risk!
I...
...wanna help the others!
Get the chemicals I ask for!
The gigantification time
will be increased to 30 minutes!
10 times longer than now!
It will be riskier...
...but you're not scared, are you?
Of course not!
I'm a pirate!
Black Coffee Beam!
Scurrying around...
He doesn't know when to give up!
Well done!
How's this then?!
Luffy left this to me!
Yeah! Let's do it one more time! Ready?!
Everyone! I'll leave the rest to you!
Back us up!
So until Luffy defeats Kaido,
I'm not gonna lose, either!
Such a miracle won't happen!
Reality is cruel! Sadly!
Stop dodging!
How's this strangulation?!
Isn't it painful, Raccoon?!
I'm a reindeer!
Come on, boy!
Shut up!
You insolent raccoon!
Marys!
Diffusion Mode!
Announcement to all of Onigashima!
The duel is over!
The man with the highest bounty
amongst the enemies, Straw Hat...
...has been defeated!
What?!
Chopperemon-san!
Straw Hat!
It's all over...
Kaido-sama choked the life out of him...
You hear that?
No way!
...and Straw Hat Luffy sank
to the bottom of the dark nighttime sea!
Good news!
Did you hear that?
I don't care about that idiot!
Both the Kozuki samurai
and the captain lost!
Who's next? Can anyone else win?!
Kin'emon's group, too?!
Big Bro Luffy!
Kaido-sama will go downstairs
to start "cleaning"!
I can't believe she broke the castle
like this... Damn Linlin...
Kaido-sama will accept your surrender!
Those who put their hands in the air
to surrender and obey...
...will be spared
and welcomed as subordinates!
Screw that!
Luffy!
Momonosuke-sama! What is wrong?!
Kin'emon!
I am here!
I must tell everyone!
Tell?!
What do you wanna tell them?!
Surrender, Land of Wano!
It's a losing battle!
It's already over!
Straw Hat...
...sank to the bottom
of the dark nighttime sea!
This is a Mary, right?!
It's here which means...
...we're in trouble,
aren't we, Kin-sama?!
Maybe the enemies know where we are!
What?!
I'm disgusted!
Hey!
This voice...!
Momonosuke!
It's been a long time!
What?! No way!
Shinobu, you're looking good too!
F-Father!
No, Shinobu-san!
Father! Father!
Do not look at him!
What?!
Father!
What?! Let go of him!
It's a tear-jerking reunion of
a father and son!
It's not!
Get back, Shinobu!
What?!
I'm Kozuki Oden!
You did it once and you're doing it again!
You're telling an obvious lie!
Hey, Kiku, what's wrong?!
Get that grim look off your face!
It's me!
Shut up!
How dare you...
...kill Ashura-san...
Damn you! Get off of me!
Don't sully Kozuki Oden anymore!
No, Kiku! What are you thinking?!
Don't say my name with that appearance!
Kanjuro!
Hey, Kiku. You've got to be kidding!
I took you and Izo into my care.
Now, you two...
Where are your parents?
I see... What's your name?
Izo.
Kiku.
Okay!
You two... Eat all you want!
Uh-huh!
Can you cut me?!
I can't cut you...
Kin-sama... I can't...
Kanjuro!
Kiku!
Because you cut me before...
I'm critically injured too, Kiku!
Kiku!
Kin-sama...
I'm ashamed of myself.
I, Kikunojo of the Fallen Snow...
...can't live any longer...
But...
...if the fallen snow is melting...
this country's dawn will
definitely come soon.
Do not be silly...
Of course, it will!
The light from the dawn of the Land of Wano
will reach to the afterworld!
Kiku!
Kikunojo!
The way you fell
was very beautiful, Kiku...
You truly were a loyal retainer!
If it was a stage play, it would've been
the masterpiece of the century!
Now you're the next actor, Kin!
I'm gonna set the stage
for your final moments!
The poor man whose lord was killed
and who was betrayed by his friend,
and now he lost his comrade...
What awaits him?
Is it a tragedy?!
Or a comedy?
Play your role, Kin'emon!
Decorate the stage
with your honorable death!
Kanjuro!
That's it!
Please wait!
Are you gonna take in a pervert like him,
Oden-san?!
Forgive me already!
How many times should I apologize?!
Oden-sama, will you please elaborate on
how you feel today?
This ganmodoki is exquisite!
What's wrong with you guys?!
You're so creepy these days!
Go after Momonosuke!
Don't worry about me!
I missed you so much!
I'm glad that you're okay!
Kanjuro!
That's right!
Raizo runs with that kind of rhythm.
I think he has this kind of power...
Ninpo: Blindfold Jutsu! Guess who!
I-Is it Kanjuro?
I mean I know you're the only person there.
Look out! Duck!
Hey! Stop the silly ninpo nonsense...
If I need someone
to drop the curtain on my play,
it should be you!
Because on the stage...
we were... best... friends...
Kiku! Kiku!
Kin-sama!
The Marys have already found us here!
Let's leave before the enemies come!
K-Kaido!
So you were hiding here, brat!
Shinobu!
Take Momonosuke-sama and run!
O-Okay!
Get out of my way!
Samurai of the Land of Wano!
I will not!
I cannot let you get past me!
I'll get rid of you then!
Kin'emon!
This is Kid!
We challenged
the Emperors of the Sea to a fight!
You guys should engrave our fierce battles
really far in your memory!
No one can stop the swell of the new era!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Comprehensive Anatomy! Fierce Fight!
The Five from the New Generation"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!