iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
Draw your own map
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha
ni areta umi no youna jidai
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
kizukiageta kachikan sae
mo kuzuresarou to shita
Even the values we had built
up were about to fall apart
rashinban no sashita saki ga
tadashii no ka douka nante
Who knows if the compass is
pointing in the right direction?
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
No one knows for certain
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
I do it for my own
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And you do yours, don't we?
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
And I'm ready for it
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
With the support of someone I can rely
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Seize the future beyond your imagination
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
We'll go wherever we wanna go
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Tears and doubts in tow
onore no iro de egaite yuke
Let's paint it in our own colors
In the castle where the fierce fight
still continues, shocking news has spread.
Kaido-sama choked the life out of him...
...and Straw Hat Luffy sank
to the bottom of the dark nighttime sea!
"Fight Against the Dark Night
The Commander-in-chief
of the Land of Wano Sounds Off"
Luffy!
Luffy...
Have you really been defeated?
Then what should we...
What should we do?!
Luffy!
Straw Hat's been defeated?!
There's no point in fighting anymore?!
Bao Huang's announcement...
...terribly upset the samurai soldiers who
were working together to take down Kaido.
The straw hat man? No way...
What about Momonosuke-sama?!
Luffy won't be defeated that easily!
That's right!
Don't underestimate our captain!
Big Bro Luffy!
And then the flying Onigashima...
...finally reaches the sky
above the mainland of the Land of Wano.
ONIGASHIMA REACHES THE SKY
ABOVE THE MAINLAND OF THE LAND OF WANO
Ever since I ate that dumpling from Speed,
I feel like I've been boosted!
Here.
It's amazing!
I'm at my best!
Just give up already!
You guys have lost!
I don't know how,
but you brought the strongest rookies
you could think of in the world now!
They're not weak!
It's just that Kaido-sama...
...is too strong!
The Akazaya samurai and even Luffytaro-san
were defeated...
What's gonna happen now?
Look at yourselves! Prepare to die!
Slicing Rounds!
Kappa Style!
RIVER OF RETRIBUTION
River of Retribution!
Even if Straw Hat is dead,
don't give up until we defeat Kaido!
But...
Straw Hat's death isn't confirmed yet!
But the hint of it
is enough to crush morale...
Yeah, there's no way
to find out the truth!
How dare you all...
...think you're losing!
I'm not gonna be worried.
Luffy!
Luffy...
Don't cry...
You gotta fight, fight more!
Raccoon-san.
I was toying with you
because you were so high-spirited!
Your shepherd was killed
and you've become panic-stricken!
I have a present for you, sheep.
Lick!
Not that attack again!
Apocalyptic Candy Shower!
I can't take it anymore!
There's no escape!
You must give up too,
you cowardly monster!
Your meat looks so tender!
Diable Jambe...
...Rotisserie...
...Strike!
No way!
Whoa-whoa-whoa-whoa!
Wait a minute!
Lick!
Sanji!
Well done holding on, Chopper.
Lu... Luffy has...
Don't cry, you fool.
But...
How many times have we seen...
...miracles?
Damn...
Damn!
Look after him.
What? Whoa!
What? Sanji! What's this?
Once he recovers,
he'll have the strength of 10 men.
Of 2,000 men!
What?! Zoro?!
Leave the dinosaur to me!
Are you the one who did it?!
Judge's son!
He doesn't stop fighting at all...
His captain is dead...
Why does he keep fighting?
That's why I like you guys...
Kin'emon!
Wait...
Wait!
You have to...
...fight...
...me!
I will not...
...allow you to...
...lay a finger...
...on Momonosuke-sama!
Momonosuke-sama...
"These are serious criminals
who rebelled against...
...Shogun Orochi
and Supreme Commander Kaido...
...to overthrow the country..."
The Land of Wano really
fell into Kaido and Orochi's hands...
We were sent to the future
with Toki-sama's special power,
and we're looking just the way Orochi
knew us, exactly as these posters.
So the enemy could come get us
at any moment...
GRAVE OF KOZUKI ODEN
VASSAL KANJURO     KOZUKI MOMONOSUKE
VASSAL KIN'EMON     VASSAL RAIZO
Momonosuke-sama.
Let me humbly suggest you...
...call me...
..."Father" from today!
KOZUKI ODEN
Call you "Father"?
That is right!
I do not want them...
KOZUKI ODEN
I do not want them to know
that you are Oden-sama's son!
They could come after you
at any moment now.
Please understand!
Okay. I am counting on you, Kin'emon...
Thank you, Momonosuke-sama!
So call me "Father," Momonosuke-sama.
I can do it, Kin'emon!
Still calling each other by "sama" and his name...
You two haven't changed at all!
Oh, it's going to be so hard!
Momonosuke, Momonosuke,
Momonosuke...
...sama.
Momonosuke, Momonosuke,
Momonosuke...
...sama.
Momonosuke! Momonosuke!
Momonosuke...
...sama.
Momonosuke! Momonosuke!
Momonosuke...
...sama.
Momonosuke, Momonosuke,
Momonosuke...
...sama.
Momonosuke, Momonosuke,
Momonosuke...
...sama.
Momonosuke! Momonosuke!
Momonosuke...
...sama.
You are adding "sama" in an undertone...
I don't see any improvement!
Mo... Mo...
It is so hard for me to say!
Get it together, Kin...
F-Father...
Should I take that role?!
Father! I know it is hard,
but that is too terrible!
Father...
Father!
Momonosuke!
Keep living!
You don't have to worry
about anything anymore!
Let's hope that everybody else
is okay, too!
Now,
let's keep living, Momonosuke!
Uh-huh.
Momonosuke... sama...
What's the point of stalling for time?
What's gonna change by fleeing?
Run! Shinobu!
Please get away safely, Momonosuke-sama!
Momonosuke!
Father!
You must keep living.
Kaido!
Die gracefully, like a samurai!
It's always hard to believe...
...that you're defeated!
Kin'emon...
Ouch!
Do not cry!
Let's do it again!
Even if it is hard, get up.
Momonosuke!
Hang in there!
What? A frog?
Momonosuke-sama! Why?!
I need to tell them...
I can hear...
I can hear a voice...
Luffy's voice!
Momo!
Luffy?
Tell them!
I am...
...Kozuki Momonosuke!
That must be...
Momonosuke-sama!
I'm glad that you're okay!
I am going to tell you...
...Luffy's words!
Is he crying?
But Luffytaro was defeated by Kaido...
Luffy is alive!
He is talking to me
saying he will be back!
So...!
So keep fighting!
Even if it is painful and hard!
I am sorry...
...but fight as long as you live!
If it's Momonosuke-sama's order...
We'll fight as long as we live!
Mm-hm!
Momo!
Tell them!
I will surely...
...defeat Kaido!
Samurai hold out
on the battlefield without Luffy!
Kid stands up to Big Mom!
Law burns with an inner fighting spirit!
When unwavering resolves come together
in the face of adversity,
a new power is born
that will break through the status quo!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Believe in Luffy!
The Alliance's Counterattack Begins!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!