iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
Draw your own map
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha ni areta umi no youna jidai
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
kizukiageta kachikan sae mo kuzuresarou to shita
Even the values we had built up were about to fall apart
rashinban no sashita saki ga tadashii no ka douka nante
Who knows if the compass is pointing in the right direction?
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
No one knows for certain
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
I do it for my own
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And you do yours, don't we?
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
And I'm ready for it
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
With the support of someone I can rely
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Seize the future beyond your imagination
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
We'll go wherever we wanna go
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Tears and doubts in tow
Let's paint it in our own colors
onore no iro de egaite yuke
The news of Luffy's loss
discouraged the samurai.
Diable Jambe...
Sanji!
Well done holding on, Chopper.
Lu... Luffy has...
Don't cry, you fool.
But...
How many times have we seen...
...miracles?
Meanwhile, to let Momonosuke flee,
Kin'emon fights Kaido at the risk of his life.
Kaido!
Die gracefully, like a samurai!
It's always hard to believe...
...that you're defeated!
And Momonosuke declares!
Luffy is alive!
He is talking to me
saying he will be back!
So...!
So keep fighting!
Even if it is painful and hard!
I am sorry...
...but fight as long as you live!
"Believe in Luffy!
The Alliance's Counterattack Begins!"
Momo!
Tell them!
I will surely...
...defeat Kaido!
Everyone!
Luffy will...
...surely...
...defeat Kaido!
You heard him!
Don't stop fighting!
Momonosuke-sama,
you're as great as I thought!
I'm truly impressed!
You're the real Shogun of the Land of Wano!
Are you satisfied now, son of Oden?
W-W-Where's Kin'emon?!
He was just a loser
who couldn't even buy any time...
Momonosuke-sama, are you hurt?
Kin'emon got...
You're the Commander-in-chief
of the samurai, right?
You have to accept your death with dignity...
There's no place to go.
The last man of the Kozuki Clan
will die sinking into the sea...
Just like Straw Hat!
There is no hope!
Straw Hat will defeat me?
And the Land of Wano will open up?
They'll all live happily ever after?
Are you dreaming?!
I will...
...surely defeat Kaido!
Not just Luffy!
We will surely defeat you people, too!
Stupid brat...
Momonosuke-sama!
When we die, we die together!
Ripe-Ripe Jutsu!
Momonosuke...
...fell, as well!
Yeah!
The enemy's de facto leader is dead!
If we announce it to all of Onigashima,
the damn samurai will lose their morale
this time for sure!
You're right! Let's crush their spirits!
Big Bro! He's alive!
Let's keep making for
the stage on the Performance Floor, Nami!
Uh-huh! And she'll give a command there
to those who were forced to eat Kibi Dango!
Yeah! Then we can turn
the whole thing around! Right, Tama?!
Uh-huh!
I'm just glad that Big Bro is alive!
Luffy's doing his best!
We gotta do so, too!
Yeah!
I'm happy for Straw Hat!
--Uh-huh!
--I'm happy for myself, too!
You saved me, Nami!
What? Who is it?
I'm here!
What?!
Don't tell me you're the Climate Baton?
What's this?
The Climate Baton...
...talked!
It's so cute!
Straw Hat will defeat Kaido?
Is that some kind of a joke?
Do you care about
that rubber fool so much?
I just wanted to take him out myself.
But if he fell into the sea,
I'm sure he's dead by now!
After working together for a long time,
I have an odd feeling
he'll manage to survive.
Trafalgar!
Another one on my kill list shows up...
Shut up!
You guys are such nuisances!
You have no place in the new era
that I'm gonna create!
You old-time pirate!
W-What did you say?!
I've had enough, too...
How could you always disturb me
when I try to learn something or do something...
I need you guys to go away!
We're already in the new era!
Trafalgar, are you here to interfere?!
Our enemy is Big Mom.
Grow up, Eustass-ya...
Let's form a temporary alliance.
Drink up!
Sing!
FLOWER CAPITAL, LAND OF WANO
It's gorgeous, isn't it, Otoko?
Mm-hm!
The Fire Festival is
for the repose of the deceased...
We build a fire to reach heaven.
I wonder if Daddy is looking at it.
Yeah, of course.
The sky is really clear...
I'm sure he's watching over you
and the fate of this country...
Uh-huh!
GUEST PARLOR INSIDE THE CASTLE
Even after they lost Straw Hat Luffy,
none of them surrendered.
CIPHER POL "AIGIS" ZERO
WORLD'S MOST POWERFUL INTELLIGENCE AGENCY
Yes, the current situation is...
...a total of 5,000 men on both sides
incapable of fighting.
The Animal Kingdom Pirates had 24,000
fit for combat and the rebels had 3,000.
However, all of the Pleasures and Waiters
on the Performance Floor...
...turned against Queen-sama,
so 4,000 troops changed sides.
20 THOUSAND    7 THOUSAND
As a result,
the Animal Kingdom Pirates have 20,000,
and the rebels have 7,000.
I didn't expect to see the gap
between strengths diminishing now...
The situation is totally unpredictable.
And we've already got information
that can change the situation...
SECOND FLOOR - NAMI, USOPP, AND OTAMA
Maybe I'm too much of a genius
to realize it myself?!
It talked!
The Climate Baton that I created!
No, can't you see?!
It's me! Formerly known as Zeus!
How did you become the Climate Baton?!
You were eaten earlier!
At that moment...
Nami! Run!
This is my way of life!
Zeus!
What?
I'm already running out of energy...
What?!
My spirit was leaving my body
before I knew it...
Now eat him, Hera!
I was just about to be consumed
by the girl named Hera while in a daze...
Here are Black Balls out of pity!
Eat them and run!
Zeus!
Nami stretched out the Climate Baton
towards me at that moment...
Eat them, Zeus!
Wake up!
I'm gonna eat you! Zeus-senpai!
And it seems like when Hera bit me,
I was pressed into this Climate Baton.
And look!
I was born again!
What?! My weapon is annoying me!
Oh, yeah! She hasn't forgiven me yet!
Of course not! You tried to kill me!
Just get out already!
But I can't get out of here
without Mama's power...
Oh, hey! There's the stage!
--Tama! Give a command from there!
--Okay!
Announcement to all of Onigashima!
The enemy's leader Momo...
Bao Huang-sama,
the Straw Hats are behind you!
Oh, Usohachi-kun!
--Ulti-Mortar!
--What?!
Usopp!
In the end,
it's all because of this brat, right?!
Otama!
Because of her, our subordinates
betrayed us one after another!
I can't believe
she even manipulated Big Mom!
She still got up
after taking that deadly attack?!
--Hera!
--Yes, Mama!
--Prometheus!
--Yeah, Mama!
--Napoleon!
--Yes, Mama!
Let's go!
Combine!
Maser Cannon!
Pay-Pay got beaten up because of you!
Didn't you hear me say "Stop"?!
What?
The baton can do that?!
Nami, use it as usual! I'll assist you!
Her skin is too hard!
But her insides are messed up
by Mama's attack!
We can take her down by a Lightning Blast!
No! That's too destructive!
Otama will get hurt, too!
Black Kabuto...
I need your help...
I'll kill you fools!
Special Attack Green Star!
Sargasso!
I separated them! Do it, Nami!
Okay!
Whose voice?
I'm sure I heard a voice!
Don't scare me! We're in the sea!
That voice sounded familiar!
Let's just check... Head towards
the point where he heard the voice!
--Someone's there!
--What?!
Someone's really there!
Hey, isn't that Straw Hat?!
How can you hear a voice in the sea?!
Who cares! Just rescue him!
Hurry up! Is he alive?!
Where are you?!
Kaido!
It's "Father" to you!
Yamato!
I'm here to cut ties with you!
The all-out war between unbalanced forces!
To find a way out of the close battle,
Nami's mighty thunderbolt blasts!
When elite troops of Kaido's army surge in,
Otama's undaunted command echoes
all over the island and turns the tide of the war!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Nami's Lethal Attack! Otama's Desperate Challenge!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!