Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Draw your own map
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha ni areta umi no youna jidai
Even the values we had built up were about to fall apart
kizukiageta kachikan sae mo kuzuresarou to shita
Who knows if the compass is pointing in the right direction?
rashinban no sashita saki ga tadashii no ka douka nante
No one knows for certain
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
I do it for my own
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
And you do yours, don't we?
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And I'm ready for it
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
With the support of someone I can rely
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
Seize the future beyond your imagination
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
We'll go wherever we wanna go
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
Tears and doubts in tow
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Let's paint it in our own colors
onore no iro de egaite yuke
Momo!
Luffy?
Tell them!
Everyone!
Luffy will...
...defeat Kaido!
Momonosuke's declaration reignited
the samurai's fighting spirit.
However...
Straw Hat will defeat me?
Are you dreaming?!
Not just Luffy!
We will surely defeat you people, too!
Stupid brat...
Ripe-Ripe Jutsu!
"Nami's Lethal Attack!
Otama's Desperate Challenge!"
The voice I heard from the sea...
So that was you!
Straw Hat Luffy!
Maybe it's too late.
Don't say that!
Calm down!
Go under him and let him hang on the deck!
Aye-aye, sir!
Hurry up, hurry up!
Hurry up. Be careful.
Yes, good job! Very nice!
Rapid ascension!
What the hell is this?!
Like I said, it's too late.
I told you not to say that!
Captain's not here
so we don't know what to do!
Come on!
Let's clear his lungs!
One, two!
Move!
Isn't that a little too violent?
Should be fine.
He's rubber.
Okay!
Not okay!
Maybe it's too late as I said...
Captain, help!
I-It's... so... so...
So high!
Momonosuke-sama! I'm with you!
Don't worry!
Count on my ninpo!
Ninpo: Great Kite!
NIN
Ninpo: Great Kite is
one of the ninpo I'm best at!
Mm-hm...
Let's land somewhere safe first!
Momonosuke-sama,
Onigashima is heading towards the capital...
That was scary...
I guess I managed to escape.
But...
...what is going on?!
Are they... Are they all okay?!
Kiku! Kin'emon!
Everyone!
We barely succeeded escaping from Kaido...
But if the island falls
on Flower Capital...
...the Land of Wano could end.
Pay-Pay got beaten up because of you!
Didn't you hear me say "Stop"?!
What?
The baton can do that?!
Nami, use it as usual! I'll assist you!
Her skin is too hard!
But her insides are messed up
by Mama's attack!
We can take her down by a Lightning Blast!
No! That's too destructive!
Otama will get hurt, too!
Black Kabuto...
I need your help...
I'll kill you fools!
Special Attack Green Star!
Sargasso!
I separated them! Do it, Nami!
Weather Egg!
Come on out, thundercloud!
Okay!
Zeus?!
Not exactly!
So Nami, give me a new name!
What?
What?! What is it?!
Tell me now!
Ha...
Fluff!
I'm Zeus!
Nami's right-hand man! Prepare yourself!
Let's go, Zeus!
Damn you!
Ulti!
The game of tag with you...
...will end with this!
Lightning Blast!
No...
This is it...
No, it's not!
My job...
...is to hit my target!
What?
Ulti-sama has been taken down!
Following Page One-sama!
Two members of the Tobi Roppo
have been defeated!
What?!
No way!
That's never happened before!
Don't tell me we're losing!
Bao Huang-sama,
all of Onigashima heard you!
Oh, no!
I announced it by accident!
That wasn't true! I take it back!
So that one works as a transmitter!
Then...!
What?
WIND
Special Attack Green Star!
Devil!
What?! What is it?!
What's this monster?!
Hey, Tama!
I don't know how it works
but that one is a transmitter!
Your order will echo
throughout the island!
Speak!
Uh-huh!
I...
I'm Otama!
A child?!
Otama-chan?!
Why's she here on Onigashima?!
There she is! Master-sama!
What is a child...
...doing on the battlefield?!
What happened, Bao Huang?!
Who are you?!
Otama!
Tama, get it together!
You don't complain even a bit, Jimbei!
At first, it was 5,000 vs. 30,000!
Of course, you have many more men than us.
I know I can't fight you one-on-one.
You're seeing the situation clearly!
How annoying!
It's our job not to let you top officers
go unchecked!
They keep coming...
Their numbers won't decline!
No matter how desperately
you challenge us,
in the end it's a game of numbers.
That's what an all-out war is!
Don't blame me...
Th-There they come, the Gifters!
We're in trouble!
We're the elite corps of the Gifters!
Is it true that the Pleasures and Waiters
on this floor...
...revolted against Queen-sama?!
Yes, it is!
They said they were getting back at him
for sacrificing them with Ice Oni!
How stupid!
They're expendable,
why are they being so cocky?
Washed-up trash should be
beaten up and kicked out!
Get rid of the traitors on the floor!
Gorilla Punch Punch!
GORILLA PUNCH PUNCH
Damn! I've made it this far!
New ones?
Oh, no! We're now in a pinch
due to unbalanced forces!
Don't be afraid, Tama!
We got your back!
I'm... I'm...
...gonna fight, too!
Big Bro is getting hurt so much
and going through a lot of pain...
...but he still fights...
...for all of us!
Don't set the bar too low!
I'll make it your everyday life!
By the time we leave this country,
I'll make it a place where
you can eat as much as you want!
And everyone else...
...is fighting very hard as well!
I'll do my best, too!
I'll... I'll...
...fight along everyone!
That brat! She's still there?!
Hey, drag her down already!
Yes, sir! Leave it to us!
--Let's go!
--Yeah!
--You can do it, Otama!
--Go for it!
M-My friends who ate Kibi Dango!
I need to ask you all a favor!
Please side with Big Bro Luffy's group...
...and Momonosuke-kun's group!
And take down Kaido with us!
What the hell was that?!
There's no way that
the Animal Kingdom Pirates...
...will act on some brat's order!
Certainly, Master-sama!
My pleasure!
Take down Kaido!
Damn you!
Have you gone mad?!
Briscola-san, what's the matter?
Let's beat up those traitors already!
That's easily done, Master-sama!
Gorilla Punch Punch!
GORILLA PUNCH PUNCH
For Master-sama!
FOR MASTER-SAMA
Alright, the order's been issued!
Daifugo! Gazelle-man!
Let's join the fight!
Yeah!
Leave it to me, Master-sama!
The Gifters are acting strange!
What are they doing?!
Take down Kaido! Let's go!
Guys, follow me!
Our strengths!
We use them all for Master-sama!
Everyone! Thanks!
Kaido!
It's "Father" to you!
Yamato!
I'm here to cut ties with you!
So you came to cut ties
between father and son...
That's laughable...
What do you have?
Straw Hat has sunk into the sea...
So has Kozuki Oden's son...
If you have the will to fight,
you should've protected what you needed to!
Neither Luffy nor Momonosuke-kun
is the one I needed to protect!
They're...
...the ones I fight alongside!
They're the ones who will take you down
and lead the Land of Wano to its dawn!
You snot-nosed brat...
Are you gonna cut ties
and get out of here?!
Yeah! I'm gonna set out to sea with Luffy!
After I kick you out of this country!
Kaido!
Kick me out?
That's right!
You can pirate elsewhere, right?
It can't be elsewhere, Yamato!
I'm staying here
because this is the Land of Wano!
There's no way you can beat me!
Become the Shogun of the Land of Wano,
Yamato!
I refuse!
I know I can't beat you!
But...
...Luffy is the man
Kozuki Oden was waiting for!
Until he returns,
I'm gonna keep you here!
Don't expect me to go easy on you!
Yamato!
Unexpected reinforcements!
Attacks from the Gifters who changed sides
due to Otama's power upset the Tobi Roppo!
Queen takes secret measures,
but Sanji and the others won't back down!
The changing tide of the war reignites
the samurai's flame of faith that was almost lost!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Dramatic Increase of Allies! Straw Hats Fight Back!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!