Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Draw your own map
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha ni areta umi no youna jidai
Even the values we had built up were about to fall apart
kizukiageta kachikan sae mo kuzuresarou to shita
Who knows if the compass is pointing in the right direction?
rashinban no sashita saki ga tadashii no ka douka nante
No one knows for certain
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
I do it for my own
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
And you do yours, don't we?
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And I'm ready for it
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
With the support of someone I can rely
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
Seize the future beyond your imagination
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
We'll go wherever we wanna go
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
Tears and doubts in tow
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Let's paint it in our own colors
onore no iro de egaite yuke
Luffy was plunged into the sea by Kaido,
but was rescued by the Heart Pirates.
What the hell is this?!
M-My friends who ate Kibi Dango!
On Onigashima,
Otama began to desperately address...
...the Animal Kingdom Pirates members
who ate Kibi Dango.
I need to ask you all a favor!
Please side with Big Bro Luffy's group...
...and Momonosuke-kun's group!
And take down Kaido with us!
Certainly, Master-sama!
Alright, the order's been issued!
Let's join the fight!
Yeah!
This order drastically
changed the tide of the war.
Everyone! Thanks!
"A Dramatic Increase of Allies!
Straw Hats Fight Back!"
You all!
Please side with Big Bro Luffy's group...
...and Momonosuke-kun's group!
Side with?!
And take down Kaido with us!
Kaido?!
Hamlet-sama?! What's the matter?
Hamlet-sama?
All right!
Master-sama!
Watch me in action!
Hamlet-sama is going crazy!
No, I'm not...
I just woke up...
FOURTH FLOOR INSIDE THE CASTLE
BIG CAT CAFE
It's tough, isn't it, Jimbei?
We're gonna attack you
in greater numbers now.
Please side with us!
And take down Kaido with us!
A child?
What is she talking about?!
She must be nuts!
I got you, Master-sama!
What?!
Ya-hoo!
"First Son of the Sea" Jimbei!
Leave the spectators to me!
Beat the shit out of Who's-Who!
Poker! You...!
SECOND FLOOR INSIDE THE CASTLE
Let me help you, samurai!
No one but Straw Hat will win!
This is the second floor inside the castle.
The Gifters changed sides.
That's odd...
I wonder what happened...
I need to ask you all a favor!
Please side with us!
Master-sama gave a command!
The target is the Animal Kingdom Pirates!
What are you guys talking about?!
Whoa-whoa-whoa,
are you gonna fight amongst yourselves?!
Oh, well.
I can't ask for a better situation!
PERFORMANCE FLOOR, INSIDE THE DOME
I'm gonna cut you into pieces!
You fools!
I'm impressed, Otama-chan!
Hey! Have you gone mad?!
Boss! What's going on?!
Are they taking sides with us?!
Yes, it seems so.
Was her name Otama?
She did an incredible thing!
This is definitely as good as
a million reinforcements!
You did it, Otama!
Onami-chan.
That was amazing, Tama!
Everyone heard your words!
And they acted on them!
Mm-hm! Mm-hm!
It was well worth the effort, Otama!
Thank you, Onami-chan!
Mm-hm!
The operation was a huge success!
Yay! A huge success!
All right! Now the tide has turned!
Don't tell me that brat did something!
Oh, no!
Otama!
Oh, gee! Run!
Go to hell!
The end!
Collier Strike!
Damn you...
Son of Judge!
Don't ever say that name again!
Were you a member of
the mad scientist team, too?
You mean MADS?
That was a long time ago.
Look at my body!
As a matter of fact,
I'm a cyborg!
I noticed that a long time ago!
--Oh, no!
--Queen's Man-Beast Form!
Get back!
It doesn't matter that you noticed
if you can't beat me!
Chopper, will Mosshead be alright?
Mm-hm...
He...
He's gonna be okay... Sanji.
Hey, are you okay?
Even your voice is trembling!
What did you say?
Can you say that again?
I said,
"Are you okay?" I'm worried!
Yeah, thank you for your concern...
I'm gonna be okay...
BABY GEEZER CHOPPER
(SIDE EFFECT OF THE RUMBLE BALL)
This is a mere side effect
of the Rumble Ball...
That's not "mere"!
Son of Judge!
This mechanical cyborg's power!
Watch closely!
Dr. Chopper!
Yes, I am Chopper.
A side effect?
So what?!
You only care about yourself?!
And you call yourself a pirate?!
What?!
The enemies you guys will face hereafter...
...can't be beaten in three minutes!
If you say
"Oh, I'm scared of the side effect,"
you can't even protect your dear playmates,
kiddo! Do you understand?
Take a risk!
You were so huge before...
The Rumble Ball with a longer
gigantification time... How severe...
Becoming a geezer and a baby
at the same time was unexpected...
I used it fully aware of the risk...
I thought if I could fight in that form
for a while,
I could take down Queen...
Raccoon!
Rumble!
Monster Point!
Go!
What?!
I'm not a raccoon!
That guy... I think there are still
tons of abilities he hasn't shown...
That's my Sanji.
The way he fights fascinates me...
Miyagi, how is Zoro doing?
It's unbelievable!
He must have 20 to 30 bones broken,
but his breathing and pulse are steady.
However, if he keeps on fighting,
it'll endanger his life.
That's not what I want to hear.
Zoro! Leave it to me.
It's draining even to speak.
Get on with it...
He fell asleep...
I guess any more stress
will cost him his life...
He can't fight anymore?
There's one good drug
to inject him with.
Dr. Miyagi!
I think Zoro-san should rest like this!
Wait. Let's hear it!
We, Minks, have...
I mean, there is a medicine
that's been handed down in Zou.
It's a drug that heals
even the most severe wounds in no time,
so it could be called a super-healer.
Can he even return to combat?
Yes, temporarily...
In exchange,
the side effects later will cause him
to suffer twice as much as he does now...
Twice?!
I want him to fight...
But can his body take
that severe side effect?
I don't know...
I can't administer it at my discretion...
Just do it!
Were you listening?
There's no time to debate.
Just give me the drug!
Are you sure?
After the super-healing effectiveness is gone,
you'll have to suffer
twice as much as you are now!
I don't care!
No matter what happens to my body later,
if I can't fight now, what's the point?!
The Headliners and the Gifters
who went over to the samurai army...
...number about 300!
The order from the girl who got
on the stage at the Performance Floor...
...very likely affected them
in some way!
There she is!
That brat!
They came!
Usopp, hurry up!
How dare she use such a strange trick!
If we kill her, will those
who are being manipulated wake up?!
Oh, no! They're after Tama!
How dare they target a child!
They can't call themselves pirates!
I'll defend Otama!
Onami-chan!
Usopp! I'll kick their asses first
so go ahead!
Here comes a headliner!
Scorpion...
...Death Needle!
Poison!
--Poison!
--What?
You're doomed.
You guys are already poisoned.
Ow!
Daifugo-kun, thank you!
Yay!
Master-sama!
The operation was a huge success,
Now, get on my back!
Horselina-chan,
thank you for coming!
You, too!
Thank you!
I'm exhausted from all the running!
What?!
Both of you, hang onto me firmly!
Take me, too! If you can!
I'm begging you!
Master-sama!
Gazelle-man-kun!
I just saw Komachiyo down over there!
What?!
Ulti-Mortar!
Komachiyo...
A rebellion?
Changing sides?
I don't know what's happening...
...but it's time to get serious.
Blade Pistol!
Fish-Man Karate!
Arabesque Brick Fist!
Shave!
Tempest Kick!
And this is "Iron Body," right?
That is the style of combat
the Government agents use...
...called the Six Powers.
Come to think of it,
I heard a rumor a long time ago...
...that a member of CP9, the Government's
secret intelligence agency, escaped from prison.
It's strange...
...that an intelligence agent
was imprisoned.
How could you remember such an incident?
The escaped agent...
Yes, that's me!
Do we know each other?
No, but I saw you once!
When I was in CP9...
You were one of the Seven Warlords
of the Sea at that time!
We both have
totally different positions now.
I'm happy with who I am now...
...but I went through a lot.
Because of one single screw-up
13 years ago...
I was told that I was
as promising as the brilliant Rob Lucci!
I think that has nothing to do with me...
Shut up! Just listen!
Fang Pistol!
I've never seen
the Six Powers like that...
I feel pity for you,
but again, that has nothing to do with me.
That's not really true!
Didn't you proudly say...
...you're a member of the Straw Hats?
Yes, I am the helmsman of the Straw Hats!
Straw Hat...
That name reminds me of my bitter past.
13 years ago,
a Devil Fruit that was being transported
on a Government ship was stolen.
And two years ago, when Straw Hat Luffy
rose to prominence,
I was shocked...
Because that stolen Gum-Gum Fruit...
...was eaten by him!
Endless resentment towards Straw Hat!
Who's-Who unleashes a fierce attack,
mentioning his grudge against Shanks.
His provocations that trample on
the dignity of his friend sets off Jimbei.
With his loyalty to Luffy and the pride
of the Sun Pirates at stake,
his Fish-Man Karate unfurls!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Pride of a Helmsman ? The Enraged Jimbei!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!