Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Draw your own map
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha
ni areta umi no youna jidai
Even the values we had built
up were about to fall apart
kizukiageta kachikan sae
mo kuzuresarou to shita
Who knows if the compass is
pointing in the right direction?
rashinban no sashita saki ga
tadashii no ka douka nante
No one knows for certain
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
I do it for my own
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
And you do yours, don't we?
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And I'm ready for it
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
With the support of someone I can rely
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
Seize the future beyond your imagination
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
We'll go wherever we wanna go
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
Tears and doubts in tow
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Let's paint it in our own colors
onore no iro de egaite yuke
M-My friends who ate Kibi Dango!
I need to ask you all a favor!
Please side with Big Bro Luffy's group...
...and Momonosuke-kun's group!
By Otama's order,
the Gifters who ate Kibi Dango...
...go at Kaido's troops.
Alright, the order's been issued!
Let's join the fight!
Yeah!
The Gifters are acting strange!
What are they doing?!
Master-sama gave a command!
The target is the Animal Kingdom Pirates!
What are you guys talking about?!
I said,
"Are you okay?" I'm worried!
Yeah, thank you for your concern...
I'm gonna be okay...
This is a mere side effect
of the Rumble Ball...
BABY GEEZER CHOPPER
(SIDE EFFECT OF THE RUMBLE BALL)
That's not "mere"!
While all hell breaks loose in the castle,
Sanji clashes with Queen.
Son of Judge!
This mechanical cyborg's power!
Watch closely!
Come to think of it,
I heard a rumor a long time ago...
...that a member of CP9, the Government's
secret intelligence agency, escaped from prison.
It's strange...
...that an intelligence agent
was imprisoned.
The escaped agent...
Yes, that's me!
Jimbei learned about
Who's-Who's surprising past.
I went through a lot.
Because of one single screw-up
13 years ago...
Didn't you proudly say...
...you're a member of the Straw Hats?
Yes, I am the helmsman of the Straw Hats!
Straw Hat...
That name reminds me of my bitter past.
13 years ago,
a Devil Fruit that was being transported
on a Government ship was stolen.
And two years ago, when Straw Hat Luffy
rose to prominence,
I was shocked...
Because that stolen Gum-Gum Fruit...
...was eaten by him!
"The Pride of a Helmsman ?
The Enraged Jimbei!"
Komachiyo...
He'll be okay.
You're right.
Hurry up, Horselina-chan!
I got it, Master-sama!
The Headliners and
the Gifters' insurrection was initiated...
...by the command from the girl
on the Performance Floor.
There she is!
Kill that brat!
I won't let you do that!
We'll protect Master-sama!
Scorpion Death Needle!
I won't let you touch Master-sama!
Daifugo-kun!
Leave Komachiyo to us!
You sure?! Thank you!
Both of you, Daifugo-kun and
Gazelle-man-kun, please be careful!
You're both...
...precious friends to me!
Friends...
Master-sama!
All right!
Kidnap the brat!
Make her undo the spell!
Wait for us, Komachiyo!
Here's a counterattack!
What an incredible ability.
Yeah, you can't usually make friends
on battlefields.
Hey Nami, speaking of which,
will you make me an attendant like before?
What are you talking about?! No!
What?!
Then, a servant is fine.
Aren't they the same?
Then, a henchman?
I don't need one.
Then, a pet. Meow, meow!
Not cute.
Gah!
It can't be helped.
I did a bad thing to you.
What should I do?!
What can I do to win your trust?!
You know what to do.
Take her down!
Get this straight, Zeus!
If you hold back, I'll wipe you out!
No!
I'm sorry, Nami!
Rest in peace!
I don't need a servant,
a henchman, or a pet...
How about a partner?
Nami!
There they are! The Straw Hats!
Go away!
I'm Nami's partner!
Leave them to me!
I'm gonna take them down!
I'm gonna fight for Nami from today.
You've got yourself
an incredible power, too...
Good luck, partner!
She totally has him
wrapped around her little finger...
Take down Kaido!
Lead Master-sama
and the Straw Hats to victory!
About 2,000 have changed sides.
GUEST PARLOR INSIDE THE CASTLE
The number of troops who were blindsided
and taken down by them is 2,000!
That means the Animal Kingdom Pirates
that had 30,000
at the beginning and then 20,000...
...lost 2,000 to the other side
and another 2,000 to injury,
so their force shrank more.
16,000 vs. 9,000!
It was 30,000 vs. 5,400 at the beginning.
The gap between forces
is much smaller now...
If the Gifters rampage more,
there'll be more white playing pieces.
I don't care which side will win,
but we have to make sure
to confirm that guy's death...
Is it really him?
It seems so.
Either way,
the information that he stole is now old.
It poses no threat to the Government.
No, it's not good to have the precedent...
...that you can escape
from the organization and still live.
Well, only if he can survive...
He's fighting against...
...the mighty Jimbei.
You're a former CP9 agent...
Why did you become a pirate?
Are you insinuating I've fallen?
So have you.
You won fame as
a Warlord of the Sea at that time,
but now you're working
under a brat like that.
So you're holding a grudge against Luffy?
Because you failed to guard
the Gum-Gum Fruit 13 years ago,
and were imprisoned...
To be exact, I'm holding a grudge against
the one who stole the Gum-Gum Fruit from us,
which is "Red-Haired" Shanks!
Shanks!
That asshole screwed up my life!
Damn!
Moon Walk!
Fang Pistol!
The straw hat
that he was wearing at that time,
and the Gum-Gum Fruit
were inherited by that kid,
so of course, he became my target!
You got the wrong sow by the ear.
After what happened 13 years ago,
I got locked up and went through hell.
Meanwhile, he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and was making a name for himself.
And he came to the Land of Wano
so nonchalantly.
How could I not bother him?!
But he was just an overconfident brat.
He was defeated by Kaido-san easily!
Luffy will return.
I know he will!
He fought against Kaido-san.
There's no way he'll return!
Don't die, Straw Hat!
He looks pale...
His pulse is weak!
We gotta do something!
Luffy is alive!
If that's true, I'll just kill him.
After I kill you!
If you're gonna mess with our captain,
I've got to take you down right here!
That's...
...my duty!
Why is a man of your stature
so devoted to him?
You'll never understand!
Have mercy on me!
Take me with you!
I can help you for sure!
I was arrested because
I objected to the war!
I wanna save Ace-san, too!
So please!
Let me die for him!
I know that it's painful now, Luffy,
but you have to bottle up those feelings!
Don't just think about
the ones you've lost!
You can't get back what you've lost!
What is it that you still have?!
I still have my friends!
Hey, Jimbei.
Join...
...my crew!
Let me bring up...
...the rear!
I'll pull it off and come back alive!
Don't forget, Jimbei!
I'm your captain now!
I won't stop the ship!
I'll be waiting for you at the Land of Wano!
Come at any cost!
Thank you!
Don't die no matter what!
--Jimbei!
--Jimbei-san!
Boss!
Jimbei!
Thank you for indulging me!
Luffy! I came back alive
as I promised you!
I'm glad I made it in time for the battle!
I'll fight.
As the helmsman of the Straw Hats!
Looks like I overestimated you.
Fang Pistol!
Even with your Color of Arms,
you can't block them?
That was a good decision.
They can chew up ordinary Color of Arms.
I didn't know you could
move so fast on land, Jimbei.
Even though you're a Fish-Man.
My goodness... Nowadays, it's out of style
to discriminate against the Fish-Men.
Don't get so mad.
Let's talk peacefully.
I wanna ask you something.
Unfortunately, I'm not willing to have
small talk with you!
What if I chew up some of your limbs?
Will you answer me honestly then?
Iron Body!
Prepare yourself, Jimbei!
Fang Flash!
Fish-Man Jiu-Jitsu!
Low Tide...
...Shoulder Throw!
Water Shot!
Shave!
Ouch...
Gee... You're merciless...
Hey, you...
Listen to me for a minute...
When I was behind bars, I heard this story.
As I received severe punishment,
I was mockingly told to pray for salvation.
To the "Sun God" Nika!
He is a legendary warrior of ancient times
who slaves believed...
...would free them one day.
I don't know if he really existed.
A warrior who would make you laugh
and put you out of your misery.
Imprisonment felt like forever,
so I hung on to this strange legend.
Thinking "I don't care who it is.
Just help me!"
What does that have to do with me?
I heard that the Sun Pirates
you once led had members...
...who used to be slaves!
The history of the Fish-Men
is a history of slavery, right?!
You know something, don't you?
Tell me, Jimbei!
The guard who told me about Nika...
...was later executed!
I thought I was in danger too,
so I broke out risking my life and I'm here now!
Is it dangerous just to know?
I can't help but be curious.
Tell me what you know!
Finger Pistol!
Spots!
There, there, there, there!
You know a lot about slaves, don't you?!
Because you're a Fish-Man!
Tell me, Jimbei!
Fish-Man Karate!
Shark Grip!
I have nothing to tell you!
Why did you get so pissed
all of a sudden?!
Let me hollow you out! Fang Pistol!
What's going on?!
Fish-Man Karate Secret Art!
Damn!
Hey, my tail!
Demon Brick Fist!
You bastard!
If you wanna nose into history,
you better be prepared for
what you're stepping into!
To cut ties with Kaido,
Yamato unleashes his true power.
Franky intercepts Sasaki's tricky attacks
with the spirit of steel.
Challenge the rampaging
mighty enemies boldly!
Extraordinary, super do-or-die
contests now begin!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Showdown Battles of the Monsters! Yamato and Franky"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!