Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Draw your own map
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha ni areta umi no youna jidai
Even the values we had built up were about to fall apart
kizukiageta kachikan sae mo kuzuresarou to shita
Who knows if the compass is pointing in the right direction?
rashinban no sashita saki ga tadashii no ka douka nante
No one knows for certain
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
I do it for my own
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
And you do yours, don't we?
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And I'm ready for it
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
With the support of someone I can rely
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
Seize the future beyond your imagination
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
We'll go wherever we wanna go
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
Tears and doubts in tow
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Let's paint it in our own colors
onore no iro de egaite yuke
Nami and Usopp run through the battlefield
protecting Otama.
Hurry up, Horselina-chan!
I got it, Master-sama!
There she is!
Kill that brat!
I won't let you do that!
We'll protect Master-sama!
Scorpion Death Needle!
I won't let you touch Master-sama!
Daifugo-kun!
Leave Komachiyo to us!
You sure?! Thank you!
Both of you, Daifugo-kun and
Gazelle-man-kun, please be careful!
You're both...
...precious friends to me!
What an incredible ability.
Yeah, you can't usually make friends
on battlefields.
The Animal Kingdom Pirates keep losing their
troops to the power of Otama's Kibi Dango.
Jimbei and Who's-Who fight a deadly battle
in one corner of castle.
As I received severe punishment,
I was mockingly told to pray for salvation.
To the "Sun God" Nika!
He is a legendary warrior of ancient times
who slaves believed...
...would free them one day.
I don't know if he really existed.
A warrior who would make you laugh
and put you out of your misery.
Imprisonment felt like forever,
so I hung on to this strange legend.
Thinking "I don't care who it is.
Just help me!"
What does that have to do with me?
I heard that the Sun Pirates
you once led had members...
...who used to be slaves!
I have nothing to tell you!
Let me hollow you out! Fang Pistol!
What's going on?!
Fish-Man Karate Secret Art!
Damn!
Hey, my tail!
Demon Brick Fist!
Meanwhile,
on the rooftop of the Skull Dome...
Kaido!
It's "Father" to you!
Yamato!
I'm here to cut ties with you!
"Showdown Battles of the Monsters!
Yamato and Franky"
Yamato!
You're strong!
Become the Shogun for me
without resistance...
You better listen to your parent.
Flex your strength all you want
as the Shogun of the Land of Wano!
Dominate everything and do as you will!
I won't dominate anything!
I won't be dominated, either!
What a pain...
They all died.
All of those who said something like that!
I know Luffy will come back!
Until then,
I'm gonna stall you!
You don't know what's right
and what's wrong.
I'm...
...Oden!
I'm gonna defend the Land of Wano!
PERFORMANCE FLOOR INSIDE THE CASTLE
My skin's so hard, isn't it?
It hurts, doesn't it?
This is the power of a cyborg!
Yeah...
All you can do is use what you're given.
It's the power of a pathetic fool!
What?!
Damn you!
No matter how much you try,
you can't beat me!
Beam!
There you are!
You're a damn lizard
who sparkles too much!
Sparkle!
Technology that allows you
to fire laser shots in a row...
Franky would want that!
I'll kill you!
Do you really want it?
Do it already!
Take this! Beam!
Twirly Eyebrows alone
can't get us through here!
That's my Zoro...
All right! Prepare the injection!
Miyagi!
Obtain informed consent!
Make sure you fully understand
the explanation before agreeing to it.
This medicine that's been handed down in Zou
will provide a super-healing effect,
but it's only temporary.
In exchange,
the serious side effects later...
...will cause you
to suffer twice as much as you do now!
Yeah, I'm okay with that.
I'm okay with that, but...
...isn't that needle too long?!
Zoro, hang in there!
You can do it!
Hey!
Too deep, too deep!
Oh! I'm sorry!
The bandages are too thick,
so I can't see your vein...
Take them off first!
Yes, you're right.
Oh well, let's just do it.
Are you sure? Hey!
RIGHT-BRAIN TOWER, SKULL DOME, ONIGASHIMA
Leave the others to us!
Take down Sasaki!
Iron Big Bro!
You guys came back to side with me?!
Yeah!
M-My friends who ate Kibi Dango!
I need to ask you all a favor!
Please side with Big Bro Luffy's group...
...and Momonosuke-kun's group!
Certainly, Master-sama!
Leave it to me, Master-sama!
Take down Kaido! Let's go!
Guys, follow me!
Our strengths!
We use them all for Master-sama!
They're no longer your subordinates!
They're my...
...buddies!
Super!
Hey, Armored Division!
I know you're manipulated by the enemy's
ability, but what you're doing...
...is in fact treason!
Oh, no!
You're really tough!
I think I delivered some deadly attacks!
It's you who is tough and annoying!
Why don't you...
...get out of my way now!
I heard all of our subordinates changed
sides on the Performance Floor, too...
I'm gonna go there
and kill everyone who stands against us!
Protect the Land of Wano for me!
I recognize you
as part of our force, Yamato!
Parents don't say that to their child!
That Devil Fruit was hard-earned,
and I wasn't gonna let you eat it!
I...
...was hungry!
I was shocked, too!
I wanna go out to sea,
but now I can't swim!
I've attempted to kill you
countless times,
and I've been struck down countless times!
I became stronger thanks to you!
What kept me on the island...
...wasn't only those handcuffs!
If I don't fight for this country...
I can't call myself Oden!
I'm gonna do it!
I'm gonna blow everything away!
Hmm... So that's what they call
a Man-Beast Form!
Damn robot!
I'm gonna kick you out of my way!
Trick Mechanism...
...Screw Sword!
That dangerous sword again?!
I won't move out of the way!
Iron Big Bro!
Let us help you!
Sasaki, bring it on!
Come on!
I got this!
You guys, go help the others!
That's hilarious!
You must be glad those nuisances are gone.
Seems like I don't have
any allies around here.
What?! That thing rotates?!
Is that how...
...dinosaurs are?!
Yes, we are!
Th-That technique...
You're in danger! Run! Iron Big Bro!
You idiots!
Why don't you worry about yourselves?!
Heliceratops!
Guys!
What kind of move is that?!
Is it gonna be an aerial fight?!
General Left!
I...
...dominate the sky!
So that's how dinosaurs are...
So cool!
Triceratops...
...is a dinosaur like this!
I didn't know...
Is he gonna charge?
At that speed?!
All right!
Hey, dinosaur!
Bring it on!
General Shield!
That's too small!
Are you desperate?
I'm gonna let it crumble like a cookie!
Here I...
What?!
What?
No way...
Propellers change the direction of thrust
depending on which way they turn.
He just had it rotate the wrong way...
That's why he went backward.
Secured more space to run up.
Don't lie!
Shut up!
The longer you run up,
the stronger the charge!
I'm counting on you! General Shield!
Bulle-Triceratops!
Oh no! The launcher on my shoulder
will explode!
Goodbye!
Damn you!
I got you!
General...
...Suplex!
Straw Hat!
Come back to life!
POLAR TANG
ON THE SEA AROUND THE LAND OF WANO
Come back to life! Straw Hat!
Damn!
If only Captain were here!
His lungs have been cleared, right?
What else can we do?!
Should we give him a pill?
No, it should be an injection!
He looks pale!
Straw Hat!
Wake up!
What should we do?!
Straw Hat!
Hey!
Straw Hat!!
Straw Hat! Thank goodness!
Mea...!
Mea?
Mea...
Meat!
What?!
Give me meat!
Is this a dream or reality?
Kind people who Robin met in Ohara and
her mother Olvia appear in front of her.
They shed a ray of light
on the young Robin.
Will their voices lead her
to the end of a tragic cycle,
or the beginning of a lonely journey?
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Predator's Trap - Black Maria's Temptation"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!