iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
Draw your own map
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha ni areta umi no youna jidai
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
kizukiageta kachikan sae mo kuzuresarou to shita
Even the values we had built up were about to fall apart
rashinban no sashita saki ga tadashii no ka douka nante
Who knows if the compass is pointing in the right direction?
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
No one knows for certain
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
I do it for my own
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And you do yours, don't we?
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
And I'm ready for it
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
With the support of someone I can rely
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Seize the future beyond your imagination
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
We'll go wherever we wanna go
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Tears and doubts in tow
onore no iro de egaite yuke
Let's paint it in our own colors
The Onigashima battle gets intense!
Sparkle!
Bulle-Triceratops!
Damn you!
I got you!
General...
...Suplex!
If only Captain were here!
What else can we do?!
Straw Hat!
Hey!
Meat!
What?!
Give me meat!
"The Predator's Trap -
Black Maria's Temptation"
I've attempted to kill you
countless times,
and I've been struck down countless times!
I became stronger thanks to you!
What kept me on the island
wasn't only those handcuffs!
If I don't fight for this country...
I...
...can't call myself Oden!
Your whole body is so tough,
but you got a cut on your stomach!
This will end you!
Franken-Sword!
V-for-Victory Flash!
Nice try, you stupid robot!
This will end you!
Damn! I'm not good with swords!
If it's come to this,
I'll use the strongest game-changing...
How could you run?! Shame on you!
Oh, no...
I ended up close to the Performance Floor!
I can't let this guy reach it!
Bulle-Triceratops!
It's ready!
Gaon Cannon, Portable Version!
General Cannon!
The symbol of terror!
The Animal Kingdom Pirates' Tobi Roppo!
Don't mess with us!
I'll bring you down with me!
Mag... num-ceratops!
It's ready!
Franky Radical Beam!
Dog-Dog Fruit!
Mythical Type!
Model Okuchi-no-Makami.
It's a valuable Mythical Type fruit!
It's a guardian deity of the Land of Wano!
I can't believe it was eaten by someone
who calls himself Oden!
It's nothing but a blunder.
That's why I'm telling you.
Protect the Land of Wano for me.
As a guardian deity.
That's not what I want!
Orochi had a talent for exploitation.
This country is a weapon factory!
Dominate it by forcing its people to labor!
I'm Kozuki Oden!
I'll open the borders of Land of Wano.
I'll...
...free them!
The samurai...
...and this country...
...will be unleashed on the world!
Blast Breath!
Namuji Glacier Fang!
I won't let you open the borders!
What's this?
I guess it's not just fog.
Robin-san!
Robin!
Professor Clover!
Saul!
W... W...
Wa...
Worms?
I know it's a long shot,
but I'll ask you anyway.
When you get home,
I don't want you to tell anyone about me.
Okay.
That was too easy. She'll definitely tell.
I won't tell.
That's a lie! There's no way
that a child can keep a secret.
I won't tell
because I'm not interested in you.
"Dereshi"? What does that mean?
What does it mean?
I'm just laughing.
You're laughing?
You're a funny girl.
You're cute when you laugh.
You've grown.
Amazingly, you scored 100% on the exam
for the doctoral degree you took the other day!
From today on, you can introduce yourself
as an archaeologist.
Professor Clover...
Looks like you've become
a fine archaeologist, Robin!
Are you... my mom?
Are you my mom?!
I'm sorry I've left you alone
for a long time.
Mom...
Yes.
I'm your mother.
Come here.
Don't go, Robin-san!
To sea? So you wanna set out to sea, too?
Yep.
My mom has been busy with her
archaeological research all this time.
But when she comes back
to this island next time,
I'm going to ask her
to take me with her to sea.
So I studied hard and I was finally
able to become an archaeologist.
An archaeologist?
When you're still so small?
You don't even remember
your mom's face, right?
Right... but she's still my mom.
I wanna see her.
Of course you do.
Say, Saul...
Do you know that the world has a blank history
of 100 years that no one knows about?
I heard that my mom is traveling
around the world investigating it.
C-Could it mean...
...that she's traveling in search of
those stones called Ponegliffs?
So you know about Ponegliffs?
Robin... Do you know your mom's name?
Olvia.
Saul?!
Robin is Olvia's daughter...!
Then could this place be...
an island called Ohara?!
Yeah.
This is no time to be
sitting around talking! Robin!
This might shock you,
but listen to me carefully!
Navy battleships should be
headed to Ohara right now.
Navy? Why?
In order to eliminate
the scholars on this island!
Robin... You fool!
You shouldn't be here.
Are you... my mom?
Are you my mom?!
I think you're confusing me
with someone else.
I'm Robin!
I've grown, but don't you remember me?!
I've been waiting for you
to return all this time!
Saul!
This is it for me. I got caught.
Go! Set out to sea!
No! There's no one on the sea!
Listen carefully, Robin!
You're alone now,
but you'll meet friends someday for sure!
Friends?
The sea is vast, so someday, definitely...
...you'll come across friends
who'll protect you!
No one is born
into this world to be alone!
When you're having a hard time,
I taught you what to do!
Saul!
I knew it.
Illusion Mist...
Sweet memories ruin you.
What's the matter, Robin?
Come here.
I know. This is an illusion.
What a shame.
This illusion is a mirror.
A mirror that reflects my childish heart...
But...
...when my friends are fighting,
I can't just indulge in my memories.
Forget about your friends.
Saul wouldn't say such a thing.
History is the treasure of mankind.
It'll certainly light up the future
we'll live in.
You people can't understand it.
Tres Mano!
Freesia!
How come the Illusion Mist...
How come it didn't work?
Robin.
Mom!
Live, Robin!
Robin!
Say you want to live!
I wanted you to hold my hand...
...and walk with me someday...
So I studied hard and
was able to become an archaeologist!
I can read Ponegliffs, too!
All this time...
Mom!
Live, Robin...
I decided to live...
...alongside my friends.
The Rumbar Pirates appear in the heavy mist!
It evokes the voice of an old friend, Laboon.
Seeing his old buddies confuses Brook!
Their blades come to attack him!
A tragedy that shouldn't be possible
terrifies Brook's mind!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Slash the Nightmare - Brook Draws His Freezing Sword!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!