Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Draw your own map
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha ni areta umi no youna jidai
Even the values we had built up were about to fall apart
kizukiageta kachikan sae mo kuzuresarou to shita
rashinban no sashita saki ga tadashii no ka douka nante
Who knows if the compass is pointing in the right direction?
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
No one knows for certain
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
I do it for my own
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And you do yours, don't we?
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
And I'm ready for it
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
With the support of someone I can rely
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Seize the future beyond your imagination
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
We'll go wherever we wanna go
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Tears and doubts in tow
onore no iro de egaite yuke
Let's paint it in our own colors
Dominate it by forcing its people to labor!
I won't let you open the borders!
Meanwhile, Robin was fighting Black Maria
in the castle, however...
Mom...
Yes.
I'm your mother.
Come here.
Illusion Mist...
Sweet memories ruin you.
Are you my mom?!
I'm sorry I've left you alone
for a long time.
Tres Mano!
Freesia!
How come the Illusion Mist...
How come it didn't work?
I decided to live...
...alongside my friends.
"Slash the Nightmare -
Brook Draws His Freezing Sword!"
She ran!
Go! Catch her!
I was worried!
You should've told me
if it wasn't working!
Thanks for caring, Brook!
How dare they mess with people's memories!
I can't believe Black Maria-sama's
Illusion Mist didn't affect either of them!
Oh, no...
Seriously?!
She beat up her own mother...
How wretched of her!
Go away!
I'm scared...
...of this place!
You let down your parent,
the people you owe, and your friends.
Do you privilege your own life that much?!
--No!
--Brook!
You're not affected by it, either...
Oh, yes!
That Illusion Mist thing is so cruel.
Where am I?
Who am I? Bones?!
Robin-san?
Robin-san!
Hey! You've changed a lot!
What?!
I was wondering whose bones you are.
You're Brook.
Captain Yorky!
You're Captain Yorky!
Yes, as you thought, I'm Captain Yorky!
Gather up all of the crew!
Time to ship out Binks's Brew!
Sea wind blows to where, who knows?
The waves will be our guide!
O'er across the ocean's tide,
the sunset is goin' wild
See the sky!
Birds singing in circles passing by!
Bid farewell to weaver's town!
Say so long to port renowned!
Sing a song, it won't be long
before we're casting off!
Cross the gold and silver waves,
changin' into water sprays!
Sailing out on our journey
to the ends of the sea!
Play it!
My beloved Rumbar Pirates!
Laboon!
He's smitten with you the most, Brook.
That's because he likes music!
Go to hell!
What?!
Brook!
Where did you go?!
Gee...
It really is cruel.
I realized again.
That my crewmates are all dead.
That I'll never be able to see them again!
What are you doing, Brook?!
I'm in pain.
I'm sad.
And it...
...breaks my heart.
Even though I no longer have a heart!
Die!
Song of Scratches...
Blizzard Slice!
Honestly!
If you're gonna show me anything,
at least show me your panties
rather than an illusion.
Stop! I won't let you flee!
How could she do such a terrible thing!
I'm not okay but I'm...
...okay.
For 50 years, in the mist,
I kept wishing that the deaths
of my crewmates were a dream...
Everyone!
I saw visions every day...
...and felt hurt...
We have so much in common!
Every ordeal was for the present!
I-I'm...
I'm so happy to be alive!
I am so very happy to be alive!!!
Of course you are.
Because today came!
For my friends' sake,
I can't stay depressed!
My spirit is unbreakable!
Because I'm bones!
Wanyudo Sleeve Swing!
That weird weapon again!
WANYUDO - PUG SMILE FRUIT
I won't let you get away!
Did you say illusions don't affect you?
But you're still dreaming!
Dreaming that you can defeat Kaido-sama!
Spider Net!
Thank you!
The place is in flames!
If you don't stop,
fire will spread throughout the castle!
Are you worrying about our castle?
Thanks...
Then why don't you surrender yourself already?
Nico Robin!
Robin-san,
could you keep holding me for a minute?
If that weapon is a living thing...
Soul!
Cold Soul!
It's cold!
Wanyudo!
Being hot or too hot is prohibited.
Damn you!
Soul Parade!
Iceburn!
That was so close. Thanks, Brook.
You don't know when to give up.
Nico Robin!
Don't you see?
No matter how you look at it,
you were sold out by your friend!
Black-Leg called you in front of me
knowing that you were my target!
Help me, Robin-chan!
In other words,
since you're targeted
by such big names across the world,
you're a liability to your crewmates!
That's why he called you in so easily!
Help me, Robin-chan!
Black-Leg is the laughingstock
of the whole of Onigashima!
His bounty is the second highest
in your group, right?
That shows how weak you guys are!
What Sanji-san did...
...was very funny!
Robin-san! May I leave her to you?
Thanks! That's what I want.
Leave the other creatures to me!
But I'm scared of ghosts!
Are you hurt?
No.
He's so kind.
You don't need to know...
...why he asked for my help!
He's a man worthy of being
one of the two arms...
...of the King of the Pirates.
Gigante Fleur!
You're pissed off...
I didn't know
you could make yourself so huge.
But looks like it's exhausting.
Don't worry.
It'll be over before you know it!
Sea Serpent Snapdragon!
You...
Don't even try!
Take this!
I'm not gonna get caught
without putting up a fight!
So your real body gets hurt!
In that case,
it's good that the target is big!
And has many arms!
They're big, too!
Oh, you noticed?
Poison barbs at the ends of my legs!
Maria-Nette!
Onigashima is moving farther away...
What should we do?!
If it falls onto the Flower Capital,
the Land of Wano will...
Meat!
Meat! I need more meat!
TOKAGE PORT
Meat!
Straw Hat?
More meat!
Hey, bring more!
He's already eaten
all the provisions on the ship!
I don't think
we can find meat around here.
Meat! I need more meat!
Anyway, his vitality is incredible.
Who can believe he's barely alive...
Luffy!
Momo!
--I thought you guys were on Onigashima.
--How did you get here?
You picked him up in the sea?
How's that for a miracle?!
Well, we heard a voice in the sea...
We turned in that direction
and found him.
Luffytaro's voice?
Is that what Momonosuke-sama heard?!
Luffy! How lucky you are!
You are really alive!
You came falling, too?
Yeah, we got away from Kaido
with Shinobu's kite!
But Luffy...
To let me flee, in front of my very eyes,
Kiku and Kin'emon were...
Kin-sama...
I'm ashamed of myself.
I, Kikunojo of the Fallen Snow...
...can't live any longer...
I will not move!
I cannot let you get past me!
I'll get rid of you then!
Kin'emon!
Save it for later!
You've always been like that!
You're the commander-in-chief!
It's not over yet!
Stop whining!
Until we kick Kaido's ass, it's not over!
Luffytaro! Don't be so harsh!
I said stop crying, Momo!
You're the future Shogun!
Good.
I want more! Meat!
We told you we don't have anymore!
All right! We're gonna go find some!
Meat!
Straw Hat's getting weak.
This is a bad sign, isn't it?!
If he dies now,
I'll be in so much trouble!
Cut it out! Caribou!
Don't be so mean...
Mister, you'll do it, right?
Shut up!
You're gonna do the jailbreak thing, right?
I beg you!
Don't touch me!
Take me with you!
If you don't win,
I can't get out of this country!
Come on!
He's still gonna eat a ridiculous amount!
We have no choice. It'll take some time,
but let's go to a nearby town to get some...
Hey!
I bet this is what you guys want!
That's... a lot!
Damn!
Momo!
Take me back up there!
Transform into a dragon and fly me up!
What?!
I'll defeat...
Kaido!
Black Maria's wicked verbal attacks
weaken Robin's spirit!
As she falls prey to a raging hellfire
and has both her body and soul burned to ash,
will it be light or darkness that blooms?
The roar that she raises for her loved ones
leads her to the black flower!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Clutch! A Demon Incarnate, Robin!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!