iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
Draw your own map
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha ni areta umi no youna jidai
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
kizukiageta kachikan sae mo kuzuresarou to shita
Even the values we had built up were about to fall apart
rashinban no sashita saki ga tadashii no ka douka nante
Who knows if the compass is pointing in the right direction?
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
No one knows for certain
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
I do it for my own
And you do yours, don't we?
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And I'm ready for it
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
With the support of someone I can rely
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
Seize the future beyond your imagination
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
We'll go wherever we wanna go
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
Tears and doubts in tow
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Let's paint it in our own colors
onore no iro de egaite yuke
"Clutch!
A Demon Incarnate, Robin!"
Mari-Apprehend!
MARI-APPREHEND
Can you endure it?
Don't be shy. Come on.
Come to me!
Nice.
Now, how should I torment you?
I'm a fighter.
I won't...
...go easy on women, either!
Oiran...
...Knuckles!
OIRAN KNUCKLES
It feels good to punch you!
Because you're so big!
It's great!
You're beautiful!
Very!
What looks good on you...
...is blood makeup.
Nico Robin!
I'll make you look more beautiful, okay?!
I think you'll look
the most beautiful with...
...a fractured face!
Oh? Are you running away?!
Sea Serpent Snapdragon!
MARI-CADE
Mari-Cade!
The webs that barred your way...
...are flammable!
Mari-Arson!
MARI-ARSON
Didn't you say
it'd be over before I knew it?!
You strutted in like a hero to cover up
Black-Leg Sanji's pathetic blunder,
and if you get beaten so easily,
you'll make a fool of yourself
just like he did!
Try to bloom in this sea of flames!
Can flowers bloom in fire?!
No!
Get fully warmed up with Mari-Arson.
And die by flames!
I'm sorry that you can't move...
This is payback...
...for punching my face earlier!
It's great!
How...
...beautiful!
What can you do now?
Demon Child!
She is the child of a demon
and shouldn't be allowed to live!
Your sin is being alive!
Like I said earlier,
you're a burden to your crewmates!
A tramp like you...
...is sought after by the biggest names
in the world...
...only because of that brain
which can decipher Ponegliffs!
They don't need your personality
as long as you're alive!
You're nothing but a tool!
Those hands and feet are also unnecessary!
What else can you do?!
Demon Child!
She's a survivor of the Demons of Ohara!
Kill her!
She shouldn't be allowed to live!
Punching such an annoying tramp...
...feels good!
Look! Because you disgracefully rampaged,
the fire is everywhere.
It's all your fault!
Are you gonna ask that skeleton monster
to put it out again?
Go ask him to clean up the mess you made.
Are you just gonna take it?
You're really useless.
Did they really call you Demon Child?
Oh, you're so pathetic!
Shame on you!
I heard you say silly things,
Black Maria-san.
If I were you...
I would get away from there!
Damn you!
Stop cackling like you're in no danger!
I think we're interrupting them...
Let's leave the two alone.
Soul Parade! Ice Wall!
Oh, no!
Maybe even that skeleton monster
finally abandoned you.
Don't worry.
I'll take care of you.
I'll take my time...
...and beat the hell out of you!
Hey! Monster! Monster!
Geez... You really are a creepy child.
Do you know how much bounty
is on her head?
She's a survivor of those demons
who planned the world's annihilation!
It'll be a problem if she's left at large.
She is the child of a demon
and shouldn't be allowed to live!
Your sin is being alive!
There're too many enemies...
to achieve my dream...
When did I ask you guys to rescue me?!
I just want to... die!
Laugh.
When you're having a hard time,
just laugh.
Robin-san!
Hey, are you listening?
I said...
...you need to learn to punch
just in case.
I don't like hitting people with my fist.
Can't it be slapping, Koala?
They want to kill you!
Slapping is too weak!
How about using the heel of your palm?
Hitting with your palm?
Speed matters more than power!
Throw it quickly
and pull it back quickly!
Wham!
What?
Robin, do you want me to teach you
Dragon Claw Fist?
It'll become your strong weapon.
Why did you come?!
I'm gonna teach her!
Doesn't matter who teaches her.
Then I will!
No, I will!
I'm more suited than you!
I'm a Fish-Man Karate assistant instructor!
Whoa-whoa... Both of you,
don't be so obtrusive.
Oh, Hack!
She is strong enough
with her locking techniques.
But once we part from her,
we can't protect her!
I said she's strong.
With Fish-Man Karate,
she can make use of her specialty!
Dragon Claw Fist
is better suited for that!
Robin has her own way of fighting!
Palms can be used
without special abilities like yours!
An application of Dragon Claw Fist
is good enough!
Palms!
Neither of you are listening to me!
Robin!
We still haven't heard you say it!
Say you want to live!
Help me, Robin-chan!
I've never thought
that I want to become stronger...
...for somebody else.
If you leave it to me, it'll be alright!
Then...
What?
Can you teach me
the "palm" thing a little bit?
Okay!
Are you sure you want to teach that to me?
Of course I am!
You are so precious to us!
Robin-san!
This is...
...a special move.
It uses your palms, too.
But it's a secret art of
Fish-Man Karate!
Mil Fleurs...
Giganteum!
Where were you aiming?!
Certainly...
Certainly, my palms came in handy
so many times.
Figure out where your enemy's core is!
Figure out where my enemy's core is!
Listen carefully, Robin!
No one is born into this world to be alone!
Go meet your friends!
Live together with them.
We cannot give up the future
you young ones will live in!
Live, Robin!
No way!
Is that what she wanted to do?!
Dammit! The fire has been put out!
Where is she?!
Just give up.
No matter what means you use,
I can see right through you
most of the time!
What is that appearance?
A demon?
A demon!
So what?!
I don't know
if you're Demon Child or what,
but you've never seen hell!
I'll destroy everything!
With the Oiran Knuckles and poison...
I'm gonna show you...
...how gruesome my hell can be!
Let go of me!
Demonio Fleur.
What are you gonna do?!
There are the people who truly need me,
and rely on me!
And for those people, I would even...
...turn into a demon!
Grand Jacuzzi...
...Clutch!
Black Maria-sama has
way more momentum than usual!
That tramp is finished!
S... top... it...
"Hands and feet are unnecessary"?
No! Not mine...
I was talking about yours!
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
What did you say?!
What was that noise?!
Black Maria-sama!
The ice is in the way!
That damn skeleton monster!
Is something wrong?!
Black Maria-sama...
Black Maria... sama?
Black Maria-sama got...!
A demon!
Thank you for lining up!
Now... Phrase d'armes!
Orchestra!
Welcome back.
Robin-san.
It's good to be back.
Thank you for...
...waiting.
I'm a little... tired.
Whoa.
Robin-san.
Do you guys really understand?!
That's a month worth of my food!
Make sure to return the favor,
or I'll be in trouble.
TOKAGE PORT, UDON
Anyway, I can't believe
you had this much food!
My Swamp-Swamp Fruit power
is bottomless!
Straw Hat! What happened to
our captain, Bepo, and the others?!
Ooaa-ay...
TRA-GUY
IS ALIVE!!
...iw aaiu!!
"Iw aaiu"?
I am begging you!
Only you can do it!
Yes, I can
but why do you want to do that?!
I want to grant Luffy his wish!
His wish?
I have to take Luffy there!
So I want to go to Onigashima again!
What?!
Why... are you saying
such a ridiculous thing?!
I'll never let you go
to a dangerous place like that again!
Listen, Shinobu!
If nothing is done, the Flower Capital
and the Land of Wano will be annihilated!
That is why I have to go there
at any cost!
Please! So I need you to...
Momonosuke-sama,
listen to me very carefully.
If I do that, you'll never...
...be able to turn back
to your current appearance!
That means your mind
will remain that of a child...
...while only your body will be matured.
If you do such a thing...
That is fine!
I might be able to become...
...a bigger dragon that way!
But I can't do such a thing!
Momonosuke-sama!
I am begging you!
D-Don't do that, Momonosuke-sama!
Please, Shinobu!
With your Ripe-Ripe Jutsu,
make me grow older...
Please...
Make me grow older!
A vicious spell
that sees through people's minds!
Killer agonizes when his slash to finish off Hawkins
cuts his partner Kid in the chest instead.
Sanji faces the brutes
who come after Zoro by himself!
He is nearing his limit!
Push yourself hard
and save your injured friend!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Spell! Kid and Zoro Facing Threats!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!