iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
Draw your own map
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha ni areta umi no youna jidai
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
kizukiageta kachikan sae mo kuzuresarou to shita
Even the values we had built up were about to fall apart
rashinban no sashita saki ga tadashii no ka douka nante
Who knows if the compass is pointing in the right direction?
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
No one knows for certain
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
I do it for my own
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And you do yours, don't we?
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
And I'm ready for it
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
With the support of someone I can rely
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Seize the future beyond your imagination
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
We'll go wherever we wanna go
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Tears and doubts in tow
onore no iro de egaite yuke
Let's paint it in our own colors
The fierce battle continues on Onigashima!
Down on the ground, the resuscitated Luffy
is devouring meat and regaining his strength.
TOKAGE PORT, UDON
Anyway, I can't believe
you had this much food!
Ooaa-ay...
TRA-GUY
...iw aaiu!!
IS ALIVE!!
And Momonosuke asks Shinobu
to do something for him.
I have to take Luffy there!
So I want to go to Onigashima again!
What?!
Why... are you saying
such a ridiculous thing?!
I'll never let you go
to a dangerous place like that again!
I might be able to become...
...a bigger dragon that way!
I am begging you!
D-Don't do that, Momonosuke-sama!
Please, Shinobu!
With your Ripe-Ripe Jutsu,
make me grow older...
Please... make me grow older...
Make me grow older!
Meanwhile, Robin and Brook
made remarkable gains.
Demonio Fleur.
There are the people who truly need me,
and rely on me!
And for those people, I would even...
...turn into a demon!
Grand Jacuzzi...
...Clutch!
Now... Phrase d'armes!
Orchestra!
Welcome back.
Robin-san.
It's good to be back.
Thank you for...
...waiting.
I'm a little... tired.
Whoa.
Robin-san.
Black Maria-sama from the Tobi Roppo...
...is defeated...
...by Nico Robin from the Straw Hats.
Such an unpleasant name to hear.
I'm sure that pirates will flock around her
to exploit her abilities.
"A Spell!
Kid and Zoro Facing Threats!"
To challenge the Animal Kingdom Pirates'
30,000 troops,
the 5,400 Samurai-Pirate Allied Troops
made a raid!
The gap between forces diminished...
...through Otama's Kibi Dango strategy...
...and the samurai
and the pirates' valiant fights.
The enemy's tough top officers,
the Tobi Roppo, are all defeated!
Onigashima, up above the mainland
of the Land of Wano...
...will soon arrive at the Flower Capital!
Thank you for the meal!
You've eaten it all!
Mr. Straw Hat!
I gave you a month worth of my food!
Do something about that!
Otherwise, I can't go back!
Yeah, count on me!
Oh, come on!
The problem is his stomach!
He can't even move properly like that!
Oh please, mister!
What?! He digested it all!
Kaido!
Wait for me!
THIRD FLOOR INSIDE THE CASTLE,
ONIGASHIMA
Why did you serve Kurozumi Orochi,
that hideous man?!
Fukurokuju!
We're a group of ninja
who serve the reigning Shogun to the end!
NIN
You're in no position to lecture me!
Raizo!
You mean you would serve any Shogun?!
Ninpo: Clone Jutsu!
How annoying!
What about the man you serve?!
He's a ghost!
Are you talking about Oden-sama?!
There's the real one!
An extremely emotional man like you...
...will never make a good ninja!
No matter how skilled you are
at ninja techniques!
Because of our emotions...
we're happy!
That day, we...
...cried and laughed together.
We died with Oden-sama!
Now we're just ghosts
who are trying to fulfill our lord's wish!
We don't consider it our job!
Because we're all servants with emotions,
we're even happy to die in battle!
Today, the night called Orochi-Kaido will end,
and the bright sun will rise!
With Momonosuke-sama as the Shogun!
How great you've become...
That ability is so irritating!
No matter how many times you attack,
my stand-ins will take the blows...
Come on, bring it on.
Until you finish me,
just accept your fate,
and curse yourself!
I'm not crazy like you are!
I will...
...send you to hell soon enough!
Go to hell! Old bag!
You're annoying! Brat!
Is that all you've got?
Don't mess with the Four Emperors!
Oh, no!
Even metal scraps are turning against you!
Say what you want!
Listen, Eustass-ya!
Shut up!
She is my prey!
Get ready, Big Mom!
Hawkins!
How many stand-ins do you have?!
There are only a few left...
I'm in trouble...
I mourn those lives.
Who killed them?
Bring it on, you little punk!
Damn!
There are only a few left...
...but the important thing is...
...whose lives are in them!
What?!
I suddenly got stabbed!
Hey, what happened to you?!
Don't tell me that straw doll...
Now you notice.
It would've been entertaining to watch you
kill Kid without realizing that it's him...
...but it'll also be interesting
to see you...
...become helpless.
You can only kill me...
...by killing your own captain.
Damn you!
You monster!
I'm gonna kill you both!
Enjoy each other's company
in the afterlife, too!
It's amusing...
...just to imagine you suffering
under that mask.
Now, do what you gotta do.
Don't hold back!
You're disgusting!
Move aside, Trafalgar!
Isn't it intriguing?! My cyborg?!
Show me your true colors already, Vinsmoke!
Show me Judge's scientific capabilities!
Prepare yourself, Black-Leg!
Damn! This is going nowhere!
You and I are two of a kind!
Let's become friends, Vinsmoke!
Don't call me that!
Don't lump me with...
...that crazy scientist!
Diable Jambe!
Concasser!
Blood will tell!
I'm the cook of the Straw Hats!
Any more fighting will be a waste of time!
Shut up!
I'm gonna cut up that leg
and your precious hands!
You fool! I won't let you!
Damn King!
Whoa!
Sangoro-san!
Hey, King! How dare you?!
You made a perfect decoy
so I just used you.
The price of betrayal is high!
Hey, you scum, formerly part
of the Animal Kingdom Pirates!
I'm gonna execute you all by flames!
Where's Marco-san?!
Please do something!
He reached his physical limit!
We've got to do it!
Sangoro-san!
Are you okay?!
Damn! It's hard to deal with two at once!
They're looking for Zorojuro!
What is Mosshead doing?!
Is it gonna take more time?
He was in critical condition
in the first place...
Chopper! Miyagi!
If the drug's not working,
take that green mummy and get away!
Sanji...
We've already injected him with it!
Hang in there, Zoro!
Who can stop them?!
If nothing is done,
everyone on this floor will die!
Sangoro-san!
Gee... There's no choice...
Burn! Burn!
I'm gonna entertain you until you die!
Find Roronoa Zoro...
...and kill him!
They gave him some strange treatment.
Don't let him recover!
Yeah!
After I have some fun with you,
Judge's son is next!
I'm here!
Sangoro-san!
Damn you!
I won't let you guys do as you like!
Silly monsters...
The dust is so thick
I can barely see!
I'm gonna finish Vinsmoke Sanji!
Lick!
If you had married Pudding...
we wouldn't have to work
with those idiots!
I may forgive the others,
but I'll never forgive you!
It's him, Master!
I see...
Lick!
Go to hell, Germa's failure!
Let's step outside!
I'm gonna avenge Pedro!
I won't let you get away!
I found Roronoa Zoro!
Kill him!
Yeah!
They found him!
What should we do, Dr. Chopper?!
Protect Zorojuro!
His wounds were earned honorably!
Yeah!
They're all wounded!
Finish them off along with Roronoa!
Take him and get away!
Yeah!
Keep up with them!
Hang in there, Miyagi, Tristan!
Okay!
King's here!
Just wake up already, Mosshead!
This is it, Roronoa Zoro!
Our friends and the Tobi Roppo
have an all-out confrontation!
Enjoy a full-course meal of fierce fights!
The great battle of Onigashima!
Its intensity keeps increasing!
Don't miss the series of bruising fights.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Recapping Fierce Fights! Straw Hats vs. Tobi Roppo"
Luffy's gonna become the King of the Pirates!