iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
Draw your own map
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha ni areta umi no youna jidai
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
kizukiageta kachikan sae mo kuzuresarou to shita
Even the values we had built up were about to fall apart
rashinban no sashita saki ga tadashii no ka douka nante
Who knows if the compass is pointing in the right direction?
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
No one knows for certain
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
I do it for my own
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And you do yours, don't we?
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
And I'm ready for it
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
With the support of someone I can rely
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Seize the future beyond your imagination
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
We'll go wherever we wanna go
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Tears and doubts in tow
onore no iro de egaite yuke
Let's paint it in our own colors
How annoying!
That ability is so irritating!
Go to hell! Old bag!
You're annoying! Brat!
Move aside, Trafalgar!
What?! He digested it all!
Kaido!
Wait for me!
On Onigashima, fierce battles
were being fought in various places.
And...
Marco and Sanji are about to
reach their limits.
King's here!
This is it, Roronoa Zoro!
"Taking a Chance!
The Two Arms Go into Battle!"
Don't do it!
Damn! Do I have to do everything
for Mosshead?!
I won't let you get in our way, Black-Leg!
This is it!
Imperial Flame!
Undying Thistle!
Marco!
Yoi!
He still had that much of power?!
Yeah!
Where's Marco-san?!
Please do something!
He reached his physical limit!
We've got to do it!
He's that powerful
even after reaching his limit!
You're so strong, Marco-san!
I've heard of it.
A long, long time ago,
on the top of the red wall...
...dwelled a race of people
who could ignite themselves.
King the "Wildfire," huh?
I didn't expect to meet
a survivor from that race here...
Are you still alive?!
Marco!
Go to hell already!
Whitebeard Pirates!
Yeah... I surrender!
I'm satisfied now! This is it for me!
Here comes the star-yoi.
Roronoa!
Diable!
Three-Sword Style!
Purgatory...
--Mouton Mallet!
--Oni Giri!
Way to go! Straw Hats!
He returned! He is healed!
It really healed his wounds!
But I'm scared of what will come later.
You didn't have to do that.
Why don't you sleep forever?!
Isn't it too much for you
to fight those two at once?
No way!
Whether there are two enemies or three,
it doesn't matter to me!
Okay.
Then leave the rest to me and sleep.
You idiot!
I guess while you were sleeping,
your naturally slow mind stopped working!
What?!
I'm saying, "Stop talking nonsense."
Shitty swordsman.
Now it's time to exercise!
Hey, where's my breakfast?!
Who do you think you're talking to?!
I'm gonna kick your ass!
It's not my ass you wanna kick.
Hey, Twirly Eyebrows.
If we win this battle...
Yeah, it'll give us a glimpse...
...of Luffy...
...becoming the King of the Pirates!
What is this? Why does it make me...
...feel so nostalgic?
The way he stands reminds me of...
...that man from the old days.
How dare they attack
our Lead Performers...
Don't do that.
Yes, Kawamatsu!
We have momentum!
Now is our chance to press on!
Yeah, let's beat them to a pulp!
Hey, you bosses!
Don't even think about helping them...
...in this battle!
Boss Hyogoro!
But they're confronting the Lead Performers!
Let's fight together
to take them down now.
Both our enemies and allies!
Keep all of our enemies and allies
away from that fight!
Look!
"Don't get in our way"
is written across their faces!
On the top of the Red Line...
...lies Marijoa-yoi.
You're not the type of a guy
who asks for god's help-yoi.
You must be drunk, Pops.
Indeed.
And it's the great, great Celestial Dragons
that are living in Marijoa-yoi.
Not gods.
No, I'm talking about way way back.
Long before Marijoa.
I heard there was
the Land of Gods at its top.
The Land of Gods?
Don't say something out of character,
Pops.
A long time ago,
on the top of the red wall...
Hey, Marco! Don't space out!
You're in a battle!
I was waiting for your help.
Don't be a fool! Let's get out of here!
Izo, do you believe in god?
You're like Pops when he was drunk.
Yo! Young men!
Don't think that you can beat us!
Your attacks didn't work on us at all!
Listen carefully!
DROUGHT
Drought!
WILDFIRE
Wildfire!
PLAGUE
And plague!
We're the three Calamities
that protect Kaido-san!
We're called the Lead Performers
because no one can beat us!
What's the matter?
Well, after I put on my Raid Suit
for the third time, my body has felt off...
You don't feel well?
Don't give me any trouble.
Look who's talking! You sleepy Mosshead!
I'm not saying I don't feel well.
It's just that I felt strange.
Your eyebrows?
I said my body!
You owe me one.
Bridal Grabber!
I owe nothing.
Judge's son!
I told you not to call me that!
Germa!
I heard that all of his kids are cyborgs!
Vinsmoke Judge! He's crazy!
That burning leg is a machine?
Unfortunately, I'm 100-percent human
unlike the others!
Humans can't ignite themselves, you fool!
Unless you're a Lunarian!
Yes, we can!
I can ignite myself!
My passion is hotter than fire!
I can even cook Sea Monsters with it!
You damn dinosaur!
I'm gonna show you
the quintessence of cyborgs...
...that even Vegapunk can't create!
Stay focused, Mummy in Black!
What's that blade?!
I see, you're a killing machine...
I misunderstood you
since you use a sword.
Do you need styles and forms in fights?
Yeah, you certainly
didn't call yourself a swordsman.
Have it your way.
I might be feasting on your throat
when this fight is over.
I can't lose!
Is that Enma?
Boss Hyogoro.
When Hiyori-sama said
she'd give Enma to him,
there was a reason I couldn't stop her.
If your sword is the real Shusui,
give it back to the Land of Wano!
I told you! That's mine!
I will give you a replacement!
A sword that was handed down to me
from my late father...
I will give it to you...
If you give me a replacement, then...
Yeah, I know why you couldn't.
He's a pirate from abroad, so it's strange.
He looks so much like
the Daimyo of Ringo...
... Shimotsuki Ushimaru in his youth.
That's right!
Even down to his swordplay.
Ushimaru-sama was a descendant
of the God of the Blade, Shimotsuki Ryuma,
and a great swordsman.
Even the fact that he returned Shusui
to the Land of Wano feels like fate.
And the fact that Ryuma
was also a one-eyed samurai.
TOKAGE PORT, UDON
All right! Let's go!
Momo, have you transformed into a dragon?
I regained my strength!
Hey, Momo!
Are you having a meal?
Luffytaro!
Momonosuke-sama is here.
Burning Samurai Spirit!
Dogstorm risks his life
to defeat his sworn enemy.
Cat Viper, thinking of his deceased friend,
howls at the fortuitous chance to avenge him!
Fed by the wish of the Akazaya members
who endured so much suffering and believed in tomorrow,
Momonosuke lets out a majestic war cry!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Ascend to the Dawn! A Pink Dragon Gets Agitated"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!