iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
Draw your own map
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha ni areta umi no youna jidai
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
kizukiageta kachikan sae mo kuzuresarou to shita
Even the values we had built up were about to fall apart
rashinban no sashita saki ga tadashii no ka douka nante
Who knows if the compass is pointing in the right direction?
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
No one knows for certain
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
I do it for my own
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And you do yours, don't we?
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
And I'm ready for it
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
With the support of someone I can rely
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Seize the future beyond your imagination
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
We'll go wherever we wanna go
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Tears and doubts in tow
onore no iro de egaite yuke
Let's paint it in our own colors
Here comes the star-yoi.
Diable!
Three-Sword Style!
Purgatory...
--Mouton Mallet!
--Oni Giri!
Hey, Twirly Eyebrows.
If we win this battle...
Yeah, it'll give us a glimpse...
...of Luffy...
...becoming the King of the Pirates!
"Ascend to the Dawn!
A Pink Dragon Gets Agitated"
The enemies keep coming out of the castle!
We can't let you onto this floor!
We won't let anyone
interfere with the fight!
The big battle is going on in here!
Screw you! This is our territory!
Get out of our way, you damn samurai!
If you don't wanna get hurt,
I suggest you leave!
That tricera monster!
I've got to hand it to him!
Franky Radical Beam!
You took down Sasaki-sama!
Do you wanna avenge him?
Strong Right!
One more!
Weapons Lef...
Now's the chance!
Looks like you overworked yourself!
You only fought one of the Tobi Roppo
and you're pretty worn out!
You fools!
--We, the Heart Pirates...
--...will take care of them!
So back off, you piece of trash!
Trash?
Who are you calling trash?!
SECOND FLOOR INSIDE THE CASTLE
--Kill that brat!
--She used that strange trick!
They can't catch up with Speed
at her fastest!
Nami! Excuse me.
He went back in!
Croc, croc, croc!
I won't let you through here-croc!
--I'll force my way through!
--Thanks!
What? No, I'm not ready...
Usohachi-kun!
Usopp! Thank you!
He threw himself at him to help us flee!
Yeah! I'll use this chance
to take Master-sama somewhere safe!
Don't worry! He's a strong man! Just go!
We're gonna go ahead!
Hey! You got it wrong!
Please wait!
SECOND FLOOR INSIDE THE CASTLE
Not bad, guys.
The Color of the Supreme King!
Y-You fools!
If you come close to me,
you'll regret it!
What?!
They all collapsed!
--What's the matter, you guys?!
--Get up!
D-Don't tell me...
...you used
the Color of the Supreme King Haki-croc!
You got me...
I-I thought so-croc!
Can't be helped!
You can't remain awake in front of me
if you're not fully ready!
I took down two of the Tobi Roppo!
I'm Usohachi the Sibling-Hunter!
The Tobi Roppo?!
Two of them?!
Don't try to fight me! Come to my side!
Bend your knee!
Eustass-ya!
Shit!
Oh?
Do you still wanna fight?
Here I come!
I don't know what's really happening,
but it's just amazing!
It's because Big Mom is fighting
on the same floor.
Troops are falling because of the aftereffects
of the Color of the Supreme King.
Franky!
Yeah! How's it going over there?
We're barely alive! Are you okay, too?
Yeah!
I'm cleaning up the enemies with Law's men!
Do you know what happened to Luffy?!
No, I don't! I think what Momo said earlier
is all that matters!
Luffy is alive!
He is talking to me
saying he will be back!
I can't reach Shinobu-chan
who is supposed to be with him!
No news is good news!
Gee! Be serious!
When you finish your job, come down!
For some reason, enemies keep coming
onto the Performance Floor.
--Help us fight!
--What? The Performance Floor?
Clank.
Hey, guys!
Don't let them in!
On the Performance Floor,
Zoro and Sanji are fighting the Lead Performers!
Don't tell me what to do! Aye-aye!
Allies should be on equal terms!
THIRD FLOOR INSIDE THE CASTLE
It's... It's... It's burning too much!
Gee! This is all that woman's fault!
You did great, Robin-san...
Don't worry! I will...
...protect you even if it means death!
I'm already dead though!
Ouch! Ow, ow, ow! I think I feel hot!
I've already been cremated though!
No! Who says
that I've already been cremated?!
Robin-san's gonna get burned!
Baron Corpse! Are you okay?!
We can't stay here in the castle anymore.
Does anybody know
the situation of the war?
No, there's just chaos everywhere...
But I saw "First Son of the Sea" Jimbei
on the fourth floor!
FOURTH FLOOR INSIDE THE CASTLE
Arabesque Brick Fist!
Is your captain still fighting
against Kaido?
I don't know...
I'd like to ask someone myself.
I see... The situation is chaotic.
We have to find out
where all the strong enemies...
Ring, ring, ring...
Ring, ring, ring... Clank.
Jimbei-san! Jimbei-san!
We have a problem!
The third floor will
soon be engulfed in fire!
Run down the stairs while you can!
Fire? That's not good...
But up there...
Who is keeping Kaido busy?!
That was a good one!
You got much stronger, Yamato!
Straw Hat won't come back!
Your efforts are futile!
Luffy will come back!
Kaido!
You can't drive me to despair anymore!
All I see is hope now!
Narikabura Arrow!
TREASURE REPOSITORY
You must've reached your limit.
You can't even transform into your Sulong form
since you can't see the moon from here.
Sleep, King of the Day!
I forgive you guys...
...for lying that there was no samurai...
...since you got your country destroyed!
Just bring Raizo already!
Or I'll chop it off this time!
I swear that I don't know
anyone named Raizo!
If he is here, I'll cut my own belly!
Yeah?!
Then...!
If we had sold Raizo out at that time,
we would've been
so ashamed of ourselves...
...that we'd never have returned
to this country again!
Are those your last words?!
I'll help you end your life
by beheading you!
Since the day Oden-sama died,
we spent every single day...
...preparing for this final battle!
We asked ourselves for two decades!
"Are you still Oden-sama's...
...samurai?!"
Y-You bastard!
No way!
How did you transform
into your Sulong form?!
A hole in the ceiling?!
Don't sully Kozuki Oden anymore!
Even if a millennium-old city falls...
we had to reach this decisive battle!
No matter who among us dies,
if we win this battle...
dawn will break for the world!
Are you okay, Carrot?!
Th-Thank you...
You did a good job-saru!
Thanks...
Carrot! Wanda!
Master Cat Viper!
You-gara guys,
thank you for saving some for me.
Leave the rest to me!
If it weren't for Pedro,
Luffy and the others wouldn't be here!
This raid would be a failure!
Pedro, huh?
So you wanna avenge that jaguar!
Bring it on!
Pay for this right arm on his behalf!
Lick!
What a beautiful...
...full moon tonight!
Pedro! Watch over us!
Having a drink or two-meow!
However, you Lick-Spittle...
This is the last moon...
...you'll ever see!
THIRD FLOOR INSIDE THE CASTLE
Now that Oden's gone,
you ghosts serve that brat and it's hilarious!
Shut up! Don't laugh at youthfulness!
Just as people like us
have grown up to become Samurai,
people grow up!
My name is...
...Kozuki Momonosuke!
I'm the one who'll become...
...the Shogun of the Land of Wano!!
The Land of Wano will watch
Momonosuke-sama grow up!
That's why we won't let you guys
take it over!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
With my ninpo
to which I dedicate all my strength,
I'm gonna wipe out the Kozuki's enemies!
TOKAGE PORT, UDON
Y-You've got to be kidding!
W... W-W-What's going on here?!
A-A-A dragon?!
Why is he here?!
Why is Kaido here?!
Can we fight him?!
I won't do it!
You can't eat me!
If you try to eat me, I'll eat you first!
Behave yourself!
Straw Hat! It's dangerous!
Get away from him!
Are you Momo?
Indeed.
--That's the brat from earlier?!
--What's this all about?!
What?!
It's my Ripe-Ripe Jutsu!
At Momonosuke-sama's request,
I made him a 28-year-old!
You're capable of that?!
Why are you crying?
Because...!
Momonosuke-sama! You look just like...
All right!
Let's go, Momo!
To take back the Land of Wano!
Yeah!
The struggle between
a father and a son gets fierce!
Backed into a corner,
Yamato remembers three great samurai!
He turns his bond of passion
with these heroes,
who risked their lives
for the future of the Land of Wano,
into strength to sever ties
with his sworn enemy, Kaido!
On the next episode of One Piece! "For the Future!
Yamato and the Great Swordsmen's Pledge"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!