Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Draw your own map
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha ni areta umi no youna jidai
Even the values we had built up were about to fall apart
kizukiageta kachikan sae mo kuzuresarou to shita
Who knows if the compass is pointing in the right direction?
rashinban no sashita saki ga tadashii no ka douka nante
No one knows for certain
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
I do it for my own
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
And you do yours, don't we?
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And I'm ready for it
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
With the support of someone I can rely
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
Seize the future beyond your imagination
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Kick away the darkness
kurayami wo kettobashite
We'll go wherever we wanna go
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
Tears and doubts in tow
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Let's paint it in our own colors
onore no iro de egaite yuke
Outside of Onigashima,
Momonosuke and Yamato were...
The situation is more serious
than we thought!
Even if it lands as Kaido planned,
there'll be so many casualties
in the capital!
In the worst-case scenario, if
by any chance Kaido runs out of strength,
the Flame Clouds will disappear
and Onigashima will hit the ground!
Onigashima is like a huge bomb!
If the island falls,
all our enemies and allies will die!
Everyone in the Flower Capital, too?!
We're gonna get through this crisis
without anyone knowing!
"Sanji's Mutation ?
The Two Arms in Crisis!"
More powerful Flame Clouds than Kaido's...
Come out, Flame Clouds!
Flame Clouds!
How can I create Flame Clouds
more powerful than Kaido's?!
It's faster than I thought.
The speed of the collapse...
Listen, Momonosuke-kun!
To minimize the worst possible damage,
I'm gonna go back to the Skull Dome.
What?!
There are thousands of explosives
in the armory underneath the dome...
...that I must somehow take care of.
Otherwise, if anything goes wrong,
the damage will be multiplied many times.
I'll leave the rest to you!
Yamato!
Push back Onigashima!
What?! Are you going to leave me?!
I'm sure you can create
Flame Clouds more powerful than Kaido's.
I can't!
You're overestimating me...
Who else besides you
can stop this crisis?!
Kozuki Oden...
...sacrificed his life
to protect the Land of Wano!
Who can save it now, Momonosuke-kun?!
I'm Kozuki Oden and I trust you!
GUEST PARLOR INSIDE THE CASTLE
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Clank.
Pick up immediately when I call you.
We have a series of unexpected events.
We don't even have time to breathe.
Unexpected? Is that your excuse?
You could say this is within expectations.
A dragon like Kaido...
What are you talking about?
You're not explaining clearly.
Keep your reports brief.
Another dragon appeared.
Of course it's not Kaido...
It's a pink dragon.
Oh...
Are you doubting me?
Do you think I'm lying?
I didn't say that.
I'm saying another dragon who isn't Kaido
appeared in front of us.
That must be a Devil Fruit
Vegapunk created!
It was with Straw Hat Luffy.
That means it's Kaido's enemy.
That's fine, isn't it? It's just
pirates trying to destroy one another.
Now, what did you call me for?
I got orders from above.
If by any chance Kaido loses...
the Land of Wano,
a non-World Government member state,
is to be placed under
the direct control of the Government.
We've already sent ships
to the Land of Wano...
Seizing a country by force, huh?
They're no better than pirates...
What are the chances of defeat for Kaido?
At the beginning, Kaido had 30,000 troops,
but it decreased to 12,000...
KAIDO'S ARMY   SAMURAI ARMY
In contrast, the samurai army only had 5,400,
AT THE BEGINNING: 30,000 VS 5,400
NOW: 12,000 VS 8,000
but now it's 8,000...
Frankly, it's an interesting battle...
I can't imagine Kaido going down.
I bet you can't.
Keep me updated.
And I received another order.
Bring Nico Robin in!
ROB LUCCI - CIPHER POL "AIGIS" ZERO
WORLD GOVERNMENT INTELLIGENCE AGENCY
No matter who wins the battle,
her existence will be the key
for the pirates.
We can't blow it again.
I know.
Clank.
THIRD FLOOR INSIDE THE CASTLE
There's the treasure!
Let's get the credit!
Nico Robin! Embrace Kaido-sama!
Enough with that! I'd rather die!
Me, too!
I'm already dead though!
Don't kill her! There is no point
in bringing in her dead body!
Capture her!
Yeah!
There's no way
I'll let you take my friend!
Three-pace Hum...
Notch Slash!
How did I do?
Did I help you even a little?
That was very helpful.
Whoa!
Are you okay?
Thank you, Brook.
There she is! Nico Robin!
Don't let her get away!
Catch her!
Whoa-whoa, they came in great numbers.
Robin-san, you're quite a star!
It's really a pain.
What should I do?
I know how hard it is to be a star.
Don't worry!
I'll protect you at any cost!
How dependable you are, Brook.
I'll let myself get carried away!
Stop!
Damn! Damn! Damn!
Come out! Flame Clouds!
Come out!
More powerful clouds!
How could he...
...leave me alone?
No! Stop whining, Momonosuke!
You can do it! I know you can!
No, I can't do it!
No, no! I have to do it!
Create clouds and grab them!
Come out!
Flame Clouds!
I have to do it
or so many people will die!
I won't let it fall!
This huge bomb!
--What?!
--A big wolf?!
I'm counting on you, Momonosuke-kun!
Come out, Flame Clouds!
I'm sure...
...you can do it!
Vinsmoke Sanji!
Show me the power of
Germa 66's combat suit!
I told you not to mention Germa!
It makes me sick!
I'm begging you! Show me!
Please!
Judge's son!
You're getting on my nerves!
Black...
...Coffee Beam!
Diable Jambe!
Bien Cuit...
...Grill Shot!
I got fired up, too, Sangoro!
The roast dinosaur is done!
Dinosaurs were such powerful creatures?!
No damage?! But that was Sanji-san's kick!
What should I do...
...about that dinosaur's toughness?
That's pretty good for a raw kick.
Then I'll show you a dinosaur's
unmodified true strength!
The power of the champions who ruled
the world for over 100 million years!
You damn humans...
Get down on your knees!
Here comes the raw power
of ancient creatures!
Cry! Scream! Cower!
Here I go!
Brachiosnakeus!
What?!
POP
That's how it works?!
Damn!
You dropped your guard!
This is how a brachiosaurus is!
I didn't know! Damn!
The rulers of the world!
Know what the dinosaurs are capable of!
No one's ever gotten away from
this Brachiocoilus!
Sangoro-san!
If nothing is done, Sanji-san will die!
He's in real danger!
A human body can't stand that!
Sanji!
I didn't know
dinosaurs were that terrifying...
Sangoro-san!
Not even a Color-of-the-Supreme-King
master can avoid...
...this pressure shattering their bones,
crushing their internal organs,
and rendering them
incapable of reanimation.
This is too easy, Judge's son!
If you're gonna show me Germa's power,
I'll let you go.
I refuse...
Look at that!
If I was a normal brachiosaurus,
the torso and legs are totally useless!
But I'm a scientist!
The super weapons
that I mounted in the torso!
A genius idea to use the useless!
If I call their name,
they'll be shot at you.
They're the Brachio Launchers!
What?!
Queen-sama!
No...
I was just...
...explaining...
You idiot! Only when I shout it out loud
like a technique name...
Like "Brachio Launchers"...
Queen-sama!
I-I took a heavy blow...
But my constriction technique
was successful. It's done!
You are already... dead.
No way!
Every bone in his body must be broken,
and there's no way
his internal organs are okay...
We have to use the super-healer!
--Okay!
--Yes!
What?!
Oh, damn... I dropped my guard...
Sanji?!
What's going on with your body?!
What do you mean?
Sanji-san...
Are you okay?!
Well, it hurts,
but I can move as normal...
You're freaking me out, Sanji!
Did you become a zombie?!
A zombie?
What's with...
...my body?!
What's...
What's happening to my body?!
I'm surprised.
I didn't know Sanji-san is
that kind of person.
We haven't given him any treatment...
Is he something special?
I've known him for a long time...
...but is that what he is?
I didn't know...
I recovered?
I got this feeling earlier...
Damn... I took a big hit...
I think some of my ribs got broken...
Not my ribs... Is it my back?!
Maybe my neck?!
Don't tell me...
...I've awakened the same enhancements
as them...
Sanji!
Stay focused! Behind you!
You brat!
Ouch.
What?
Listen! You kids are
my greatest scientific achievements!
You were born as superhumans
through scientific modifications...
...representing the best
that research has to offer!
Without living under the sway of
foolish emotions,
each of you will eventually
lead your own troops
and rule Germa 66...
...which will make further advances
using the power of science!
I gave you abilities!
All you need is training!
Why is Sanji weaker than the others?
It pains me to say...
Sanji-sama is a normal human.
Unlike your siblings,
you have no talent!
Don't disappoint me!
You are... a failure.
No...
I don't want...
...to become a monster like them!
Killer is cornered by a crafty trap!
The Kid is dying, consumed by a spell!
Both struggling in a negative spiral,
and all that comes to mind is the oath
they swore when they split up.
In order to live up to the trust
he earned and the promise,
Killer takes a big chance
with Kid's life on the line!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Death to Your Partner! Killer's Deadly Gamble"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!