iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand and cut through the wind
onore no chizu wo egaite yuke
Draw your own map
migi mo hidari mo guchagucha ni areta umi no youna jidai
As we live our days just like the stormy seas
kizukiageta kachikan sae mo kuzuresarou to shita
Even the values we had built up were about to fall apart
rashinban no sashita saki ga tadashii no ka douka nante
Who knows if the compass is pointing in the right direction?
douse dare ni mo wakaranainda
No one knows for certain
fukaku iki wo suikonde hitomi tojireba
If you breathe deeply and close your eyes
ukabiagaru no wa tamashii no shimesu michi
What emerges is the path your soul reveals
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
ima boku wa boku no tame ni
I do it for my own
kimi wa kimi no tame ni sou darou
And you do yours, don't we?
kakugo wa dekiteiru sa
And I'm ready for it
toki ni tayoriaeru youna sonzai ni sasaerare
With the support of someone I can rely
souzou wo koeta mirai tsukamitore
Seize the future beyond your imagination
iza te wo nobashite kaze wo kirisaite
Reach out your hand, cut through the wind
kurayami wo kettobashite
Kick away the darkness
bokura wa dokomade mo yukeru
We'll go wherever we wanna go
namida mo mayoi mo isso hikitsurete
Tears and doubts in tow
onore no iro de egaite yuke
Let's paint it in our own colors
"Luffy Is Defeated?!
The Determination of Those Left Behind"
What?
Luffy's voice...
I can't hear it.
The battle on the rooftop of
the Skull Dome.
The winner is...
..."King of the Beasts" Kaido.
So you know what you've done.
You bastard!
How boring.
This is no fun...
Fools...
Can you see...
...the outcome that I want?
Let's finish up the story.
If this doesn't work...
Bring it on, brat!
...I'll lose!
This is really boring!
What the hell is this?!
Kawamatsu-san!
The ceiling's gonna collapse!
Please evacuate!
There are still thousands of our comrades
inside the castle!
We've got to make it home together!
We're in the air! There's no water!
We can't put out this massive fire!
Please! Everyone, get out!
There's no honor in burning to death!
Blast Breath?!
No... way...
Kaido...
Where is your boss?!
Bring Oden's son here!
Let Momonosuke announce surrender!
What happened to... the straw hat man?
Kaido...
Straw hat man!
I'm sorry about the boring outcome...
Straw Hat Luffy died!
What?
Luffy died?
Straw Hat-ya's voice...
...is gone!
So he was no match for
the Emperor of the Sea...
What did you say... about Luffy?
That can't be true...
That can't be...
Luffy got killed!
Those of you who still wanna
rise against me, step up!
I'm in the mood for more fighting.
He did it!
It's Kaido-sama's complete victory!
He's not dead!
Big Bro Luffy will never die!
He's stood up to take down the bad guys
time and time again!
I've seen it!
He's not dead! He's alive!
Big Bro Luffy...
I don't want you to die...
Tama, don't worry! He'll be alright!
Even if he's been killed,
he can never die!
Hey!
No! Don't step up!
You want him to say whatever he wants?
What is that snake talking about?!
Stop telling stupid lies!
Did Straw Hat's death break your spirits?!
Damn samurai!
This is the end of the Land of Wano!
Stop bullshitting
just because you can't defeat Luffy!
You stupid lizard! Lying snake!
How many times did you get hit by Luffy?!
You're beat up!
Luffy died?
Don't you dare tell me a lie
that can't possibly be true!
When Luffy says he'll win...
he will no matter what!
There's no way he'll lose!
He couldn't die! That's ridiculous!
You liar!
Oh, there is a high-spirited one.
I won't believe it!
I'll be kind and tell you
what it means to be defeated.
Blast Breath!
Get back!
Onami-chan!
Get a hold of yourself
until everything's over!
Luffy...
Onigashima will land on the Flower Capital
as planned!
Unlike Orochi,
I'm not gonna be soft on you!
He was too lenient.
This country is a giant weapon factory!
Doesn't matter if you're a woman or a kid,
everyone's a slave!
When you're exhausted from working,
just roll over and die!
That's your life!
Every time we lose a slave,
we replace it.
You all rose against me and made me mad!
This is what happens
when you lose a battle.
You must pay a price for your defeat and
surrender your rights and hopes to me!
Bring Momonosuke here!
I won't stop fighting until that happens!
Kaido-sama!
You slaves!
The Land of Wano is finished!
Your children and your children's children
will sink into despair!
Accept the price of losing the battle!
L-Leave my wife and child alone!
Hey, now's our chance!
Take Kid and Law's heads!
They're both barely alive!
Even though Big Mom was defeated,
we still have Kaido-san!
You guys never had a chance to win!
You damn small fries...
Protect the captains!
I'm gonna stop them!
Boss, get away now!
Don't try to act like a hero!
Are they still gonna make me fight?
Kaido?! This is bad!
We gotta save everyone!
Let's go!
Okay!
Meow!
There's fire everywhere! We're finished!
BASEMENT INSIDE THE CASTLE
--Isn't there a way out?!
--Look for an exit!
I'm gonna fight, Trafalgar...
I don't wanna surrender
or remain unprovoked.
Damn Straw Hat-ya!
What we need is determination!
Let's do it!
We should do whatever it takes!
Th-That is ridiculous! It is impossible!
We're still alive!
Let's show him our fangs!
We can still move our limbs!
We're not powerless!
What can we do against someone
who even Luffy could not defeat?!
We've got to live until we die!
We must put our lives on the line
until the last minute!
That's what a samurai does!
Who else would do it but us?!
Everyone's beat up now!
I think Kaido is also heavily wounded!
Do not be ridiculous!
After all, he is an Emperor of the Sea!
We misjudged his real strength!
We no longer have a chance!
There will only be more deaths!
It is time to give up!
We did our best!
It is frustrating, but if Luffy has lost,
we must surrender!
No! I won't allow that!
What's the point in surviving...
...if we go back to being slaves again
and wait for the day we decay and die?!
We don't know if we can save everyone
by surrendering!
I won't allow you to surrender!
All the regional Daimyo
who didn't yield to Orochi...
...died to their great chagrin
seeking revenge.
We're fighting this battle with 20 years' worth
of the Land of Wano's weight on our shoulders!
Momonosuke-kun.
Rather than surrender here,
let's die together!
Blast Breath!
The dream isn't over yet!
The future of the Land of Wano
that the straw hat man showed us...
I'm still not giving up on that!
Don't fight so sloppily!
This will make me a top officer!
Don't make me use my energy!
I've got enough on my plate already...
Serve yourself from now on!
I didn't ask for it,
so I don't know why you're telling me that!
There are still so many treats to feast on.
We finished the main dish,
so let's have some dessert now.
I'm gonna eat them all!
Luffy died?!
No way! That's ridiculous!
When he says he's gonna win,
he'll definitely win, at any cost!
So stop lying, you disgusting snake!
Luffy! I know you can hear me!
Keep your word as always!
Momonosuke...
What?
Zunesha?!
Momonosuke!
I can hear them!
It's been a while...
You can hear them? It's been a while?
Zunesha! What are you talking about?!
I can hear the Drums of Liberation.
I'm hearing them
for the first time in 800 years...
I'm positive that he is here!
Wh-Who's here?!
Joyboy...
...has returned!
An amusing heartbeat unleashed!
Both his allies and enemies
get involved and are astounded.
Is that free and flexible power a ridiculous thing
or a token of freedom?!
Fortune comes in by a merry gate... of Nika.
Here comes the Warrior of Liberation
who transcends all imagination!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Luffy's Peak - Attained! Gear Five"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!