With weakness as my ally
yowasa wo mikata ni tsuketa boku wa
I soar higher than anybody else
dare yori mo takaku toberu no dakara
It's a pity to linger in a place like this
konna tokoro de tomatte tara
For the things that's been lost will lose their spark
nakushita mono ga kagayakanaku naru
At times when you're lost somewhere
kimi ga dokoka mayotta tokini
If my heart is also adrift
boku no kokoro mo samayotte itara
I won't be able to find you
mitsukete agerarenainda
Your kindness, nor your strength
yasashisa dake janaku sono tsuyosa mo
I already know
wakatterunda
It's the break of dawn
yoake no toki sa
To the highest point of reach
saikou toutatsu ten ni made
I'll dash through all the way, yeah
ikki ni kakenukete iku kara, yeah
I bet you're laughing, numbed by it all
mahi shite waratterundarou
For the pain of those days is now in the past, perhaps
ano hibino itami mo kako dakara tabun
With the world as my enemy
sekai wo teki ni shinagara
I stand my ground on quivering legs
kuzuresouna ashi de fumitodomaru
Keep moving, just a bit more for me
ato sukoshi dake ugoite kure
The awakening moment
The time of resurrection has come, now
saa fukkatsu da mezame no toki ga kita ima
The awakening moment
The time of resurrection has come, now
saa fukkatsu da mezame no toki ga kita ima
I wanna marry Luffy...
"Luffy's Dream"
KUJA
I'm really glad...
...that you're alive.
Thank you, Rayleigh.
SILVERS RAYLEIGH, DARK KING
RIGHT HAND OF THE KING OF THE PIRATES
Advances in technology
can create new menaces.
SHAKUYAKU, FORMER CAPTAIN OF THE KUJA PIRATES
EMPRESS OF AMAZON LILY TWO GENERATIONS AGO
Because of Vegapunk's
Sea Prism Stone paddle ships,
the Calm Belts are no longer safe...
The Navy's siege.
The introduction of the new weapons.
Blackbeard's raid.
I thought we were doomed...
Frankly,
I was only able to save you
due to the circumstances.
I'm old now.
I can't beat today's Blackbeard head-on.
Your power is amazing,
but your neck is so thin...
They're really in "love-love"
and now they're rock solid!
Everyone knows that I care about my crew.
So... Please...
If you want me to turn them back,
get your dirty hand off of me!
What should I do?! How should I move?!
In this situation
where all lives are in Blackbeard's hands!
We're getting nowhere.
Koby the hero!
You did me a favor
during the Rocky Port Incident!
Thanks to you,
I was able to take down Wang Zhi,
and become the ruler of the Pirate Island!
Hey, hero!
If I take my hand off this tramp...
do you think she'll just turn back my men?
She needs to change back our soldiers, too!
If you guys just leave,
I'll do it!
No.
You're lying!
If I unhand you, you'll petrify us.
And that'll be it.
Am I wrong?
Frankly, it's impossible...
...for a man to not fall for your technique.
What should I do?
I guess I should just kill you!
Wait!
The losses will be too great!
I knew the Navy would lay siege here...
But I didn't expect it
to change even the shape of the island...
D...
Dark King Rayleigh!
I'm sorry that I'm late. Hancock.
Rayleigh.
Hey.
Whitebeard's little apprentice!
I know it's childish,
but I don't like you!
What?!
Is that the infamous Silvers Rayleigh?!
Hancock.
Turn them back to normal.
I'm gonna watch to the end.
No one do anything foolish,
and leave the island!
So the Navy thought...
...those new weapons...
...could replace you guys,
the Seven Warlords...
In the end, those two...
...didn't even get a scratch!
That was strange...
One of them looked just like
Big Sis-sama when she was a child...
Okay, we'll enter
straight into the port of Egghead.
About Captain Koby who was kidnapped...
JUSTICE
CAPTAIN KOBY
Captain Koby,
the hero from the Rocky Port Incident,
was abducted by
the Emperor of the Sea Blackbeard's group.
His fate is unknown!
Don't be hard on yourself, Koala.
Sabo must be okay!
Mm-hm...
I'm glad that everyone is okay.
That's right!
KAMABAKKA QUEENDOM,
GRAND LINE
You have to be happy about that miracle!
Heehaw!
Gee!
How could Sabo leave us worried...
It's unforgivable!
It happened after we split from him...
But I believe in Sabo.
Oh, I was gonna say that
but you said it first!
--Heehaw! Heehaw!
--Hey, boy! I wanted to say that, too!
Be quiet! You guys are annoying!
Dragon-san...
Sabo is okay.
But...
...if he really killed King Cobra,
it doesn't matter what the reason is,
I won't forgive him!
Hey, Kuma...
Tell me... what you saw.
A... A... A...
As you wish...
Ring, ring, ring...
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
An incoming call to Kamabakka Queendom!
Maybe it's the Flame Emperor!
NAVY HEADQUARTERS,
NEW WORLD
Record it! Trace the call!
Yes, sir!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Everyone, quiet!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring...
Clank.
Hello!
This is Koala!
It's me...
Sabo!
I'm sorry...
...to cause you trouble...
I'm sure it's not true!
He would never kill Vivi's father!
Sabo would never do such a thing!
Of course,
I agree with you.
The Revolutionary Army's enemies
are the World Nobles.
Not the kings!
"The Revolutionary Army
declared war on the Celestial Dragons"...
"The Chief of Staff Sabo
assassinated King Cobra of Alabasta"?!
"His daughter Vivi,
the princess of Alabasta, disappeared"?!
Where are you
and what's on your mind, Vivi-chan?!
I hope you're okay!
Let's go to Alabasta!
Now!
King Cobra is dead.
What's the point of us going there?
And Vivi disappeared.
While in Marijoa!
Then,
let's go to Marijoa!
What?
What? Are they going to Marijoa?
No way.
I can't really hear them!
It's our enemies' stronghold, idiot!
Do you wanna fight the Navy Headquarters?!
I will!
What? Are you scared, Zoro?!
I'm just saying we have no leads!
Cool your head!
Vivi's father died?!
He was nice even to pirates like us...
I'd like to thank you...
...from the bottom of my heart
as a father and as a resident of this land.
Thank you very much.
Yeah! No king is that good!
Vivi!
I'm worried, worried!
I'm worried about her heart!
I'm worried about her!
Vivi-chan!
Vivi!
It seems like the last Reverie
was quite tumultuous.
I've never heard of any rumors about
a bad government in the Kingdom of Alabasta.
The Revolutionary Army's
Chief of Staff, Sabo...
We met your big brother in Dressrosa,
didn't we?
Luffy!
I can't take it! I'm worried about Vivi!
Where is she?!
Me, too! All right! Let's go rescue her!
Let's go!
Yeah!
That's enough, you guys!
Luffy!
What did you say...
...when Ace was in trouble?
Ace has his own adventures.
You trusted him to pull through on his own
until he actually needed help.
Are you underestimating Vivi?
You know she's a tough woman!
When it's time for us to do something,
we'll fight anyone.
We can't do anything now,
so stop making a fuss!
All we can do is make a fuss,
so just let us!
He's an oni (demon)!
You Onigashima!
Green Kaido!
Green Mom!
Shitty Mosshead!
Boo!
Boo! Boo! Boo!
Shut up, fourth-placer.
You said it again!
It's not so easy...
...being above you!
Since when are you above me?!
Always have been and always will be!
While we were in the Land of Wano,
so many things have occurred,
and they're developing rapidly...
Are they bad things? Is everything okay?
We can't relax, but it should be okay.
What do you mean?!
The abolition of
the Seven Warlords system...
...sent those elite pirates back to sea.
And that led to...
...the foundation of Cross Guild,
and Buggy the Genius Jester's ascension
as a new Emperor of the Sea!
That must be a mistake!
Maybe it is and maybe it isn't.
Thanks!
Luffy.
There are a few other names
that are involved with you...
Wanna hear?
I'll leave it to you!
Tell me the ones that are big.
All right. Let's do that.
You've already got a lot on your mind.
Sabo is innocent!
He...
...grew up in a strict home,
so he just wants to set everyone free!
We gotta set out to sea someday!
Let's get out of this country
and live freely!
I wanna see the world out there
and write a book about it!
I'm happy to study if it's about sailing!
Let's become stronger
and become pirates someday!
I'm gonna become one,
you don't have to tell me to!
I'm gonna become a pirate and defeat all the others
and become the most notorious!
It'll be the only proof of my life!
It doesn't matter if all the people in the world
reject me or despise me!
I'll become a great pirate
and show them what I can do!
I won't run from anybody
or lose to anyone!
Because I'm feared or hated or whatever,
my name will be known all over!
We made an oath.
The three of us including Ace!
I got it! Alright then...!
I...
We're going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
What did you just say?
What?
That's so funny!
Hey!
No, no, no... No way!
I like it! That's great!
Hey, Chopper. Examine his head!
No way! That's impossible!
Maybe it's possible
once I become the King of the Pirates!
No one would think something like that...
Huh? Didn't I tell you?
Any of you?
Well, I don't care if you didn't...
Because it's impossible!
I guess I only told Shanks, Ace, and Sabo.
What did they say?
They just laughed.
Shanks was even in tears.
That's what I want at the end of my dream.
"Time's up"
"jikan gire sa"
Someone laughed again
dareka ga mata waratta
All right, now hide-and-seek
joutou saa kakurenbo wa
Is over
owari
Let's go, come on
(We can see it soon)
ikou hora
(mou sugu mieru)
Make our hearts beat loudly
(Our island)
kodoku nari kishimase
(boku tachi no shima ga)
Something will change
(We can see it soon)
nanika ga kawaru
(mou sugu mieru)
Be tough, there's still time
(1-2-3)
chikara zuyoku nare jikan wa aru zo
Let's raise it
kakage you
We can't go on
Living a life of nothing but loneliness
kono mune afureteru
kodoku dake ja ikirenai
We're young, so we're free
osanai boku ra nara jiyuu dana
A foolish dream
baka na yume
We live it
ikiru
We'll illuminate the dark path ahead
mienai saki wo terashite yuku
Get on our feet and try
jibun no ashi de Try
Let's see the ends of the world together
sekai no hate wo tomo ni miyou
Together we can go and fly
issho nara ikeru Fly
We'll feature the Land of Wano
after Kaido and Orochi were taken down!
Watch Momonosuke-sama,
the new Shogun, in action!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Very Special Feature!
Momonosuke's Road to Becoming a Great Shogun"
I will surpass Kozuki Oden someday!