(All of us) us, us
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
The end of a dream, the end of the sea
We all have different places we want to go
But first, we need
To make a shining legend out of ourselves
Sparks fly, no limit
This is where it starts
ONE PIECE!!
All of us, I ask you travelers
Are your dreams still pure?
Sleepless cells are shaken and burst
Still, all of us
In the middle of an adventure
All of us, I tell you travelers
No such thing as a pointless fight
When random contexts
Start to make sense on their own
The threads of time are spun back together
The world keeps changing along with us
(All of us) us, us
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
I saw something unbelievable...
at Marijoa!
The Pangaea Castle
where the Reverie took place...
On the Empty Throne there...
No one should be sitting on it
since there's no king of the world, but...
Sabo tried to contact the Revolutionary
Army from the Kingdom of Lulusia, but...
Meanwhile, Luffy and the others
set out on a new quest,
and ran into a mysterious girl on the sea.
It's still there!
Down!
Look down!
"A New Island! Future Island Egghead"
What's going on?!
Go away!
- Oh god! Oh god! Oh god!
- What's going on?!
Help!
This area isn't safe!
Get us out of here!
Is this it for us?!
Jimbei! Hurry up!
Jimbei! Get us out of here!
Hold on!
Hurry!
What's that?!
It's not an ordinary shark!
It's too big and made of iron?!
Hold on tight! We'll land on the water!
Oh, no!
Luffy and the others fell into the sea!
This is no good!
Franky!
Take the helm!
Bring the ship around to us!
All right! Count on me!
Luffy!
Chopper!
Where are you?!
There they are!
I said, "Count on me"...
but how can I find them
in this rough sea?!
Well, I've just gotta find a way!
Let's go, Sunny!
Ship's Bottom...
Rabbit...
Screw!
SHIP'S BOTTOM, RABBIT SCREW
All right!
Let's save Luffy and the others!
Luffy! Chopper!
Where are you?!
Franky! Get us out of here!
Torpedoes!
Robin-chan! Nami-san!
Oh, no!
It's gonna capsize!
What was that explosion?
Luffy! Chopper!
I'm here! You'll be fine!
Hey, you three! Stay with me!
We'll surface!
The current is strong! It's not navigable!
Is the Sunny okay?!
Thank you, Jimbei...
Oh, Luffy! You're okay!
I'm still alive...
I think I saw heaven...
I'm glad that all of you are okay!
The Sunny will be here soon!
That's...
What's the matter, Jimbei?
Hold on tight!
We'll escape under the sea!
Take a deep breath, guys!
Let's go!
Oh, no... The current is too fast!
We can't surface!
Somebody, help!
Why am I in the sea?! What's going on?!
Hang in there, Robin-chan!
Nami-san!
Gee... If nothing is done, we'll all...
die...
MARINE BRANCH G-14
All right, everyone!
It's time for your medication!
TASHIGI, MARINE HQ CAPTAIN
One cup each! You can drink it!
I'm drinking it for you, Tashigi-chan!
Mm-hm! Thank you!
- Guys, drink it all up!
- It tastes strange!
I don't want it
because it's tastes terrible!
But let's try to drink it!
Do I have to drink it all?
Yeah, to return to your original size.
I wanna return faster, so I'll drink two!
Tashigi-chan!
I think I have shrunk quite a bit!
Mm-hm! You've changed a lot, Mocha!
I can't wait to go home!
Yeah, be patient just a little longer.
Mm-hm!
Then I'll go see those big brothers
and sisters!
These slightly larger children were once...
kidnapped by Caesar Clown,
an infamous scientist,
and were experimentally giganticized
at a lab on Punk Hazard.
Luffy allied with Trafalgar Law
who happened to be there,
and beat Caesar.
The rescued children
were taken care of by the marines
under Tashigi's watch,
and are undergoing treatment here
in order to return to their original size.
I wonder how they are doing.
Like Chopper-chan!
Mm-hm. I hope you can see them soon.
Everyone, let's hang tough!
Tashigi!
Vice Admiral Doll!
Can I steal you for a sec?
Could you do something about
that annoying brat, Helmeppo?
There's...
nothing I can do.
His best friend's fate is unknown.
I understand that, but...
Captain Koby is a dear
junior colleague to me, too...
I'm begging you guys!
We're comrades! Please!
I'm beggin' you, too!
HIBARI
HELMEPPO
Koby-senpai has been so good to me!
Please come with us to the Pirate Island!
"Prince"!
Please! We alone can't...
We alone can't possibly save him!
Please, "Prince"!
I'm begging you!
Stop that and raise your head.
Please! I won't move an inch
until you help us!
It's the Pirate Island
where Koby had been taken!
The Emperor of the Sea
Blackbeard's home turf!
You know that, right?!
If you poke that island even a little,
bloodthirsty pirates will swarm out
and shoot you up like bees!
That's why it's known as the Beehive!
PIRATE ISLAND OF BEEHIVE
It's not a place we can screw with
that easily.
I know!
That's why I'm asking for your help!
Please!
You guys...
Egghead is close to here!
Let's take the Seraphim!
The Seraphim?! Are you out of your mind?!
Calm down a little!
We can't contact Drake now, either...
There's nothing we can do!
You must understand.
Koby!
What?!
LUFFY'S GROUP
You don't know who I am?!
Yeah, I don't know.
I've been called the Worst Generation
along with you and the others!
Oh, you're one of the worst, too?!
You damn fool!
I was there at Sabaody too, two years ago!
I'm Bonney!
I'm your enemy! Don't forget!
But you saved me...
Thanks for that.
Don't mention it, Bogey!
It's Bonney!
What the...
That's cold!
I'm invincible with my woven hat!
I won't lose either, Chopper!
He's an Emperor of the Sea?
I don't get it.
"First Son of the Sea" Jimbei
is really with them, too...
Oh yeah,
what's wrong with that wanted poster?
I thought your hair turned white.
The newspapers were
making a fuss about it.
Oh, that's just...
how I look when I'm free!
What the hell?
What happened to your friends?
They should be fine.
What happened to your ship and friends?
I came here alone.
That iron monster ate my ship.
Screw that thing!
That's terrible...
Yeah! I'm getting hungry.
I'm hungry, too!
Let's find a restaurant.
But, Luffy, do you have any money?
Hey, you ignorant fools!
There's no restaurant here!
This island belongs to the Government.
I'll fill you in.
The name of this island is Egghead!
It houses Dr. Vegapunk's lab and
is said to be "500 years in the future"!
Vegapunk! I know that name!
I have business with...
that guy!
Everyone! Are you all right?!
Is the Sunny okay?
A... A...
- A giant robot!
Who is operating this?
Someone's coming out!
It's no good...
I failed again.
Why can't I control
living things' primal urges?!
Boy, it troubles me...
I don't know who you are but thank you!
You saved us!
I only ordered the Mecha-Shark...
to scout, report, and fire.
If it eats them,
their money and goods will be gone too.
It must be a programming glitch.
Now...
Who said anything about
rescuing you pirates?!
I'm only a genius scientist
working for the Government!
I'm Dr. Vegapunk!
What?!
How far I have run
Without knowing it, I counted scars
A treasure map in my head all along
Still looking for the future
The real promise
Lies much deeper in my heart
A dream
That no one can catch up with
That's all I hold on to
To you who smiles like the sun
I'll sing the same song as that day
This wish I don't want to forget
Even when I grow up
Until it reaches you
"Tell Me, Robin!
Chopper's I-Wanna-Learn-More-You-Fool!"
Hey, guys! I'm Chopper,
the ship's doctor of the Straw Hats!
I'm Robin, an archaeologist.
Robin, I can't wait to learn as always!
Information can be a strong weapon.
Let's keep learning!
Yeah! Today we'll learn about this one!
Jewelry Bonney!
Her bounty is 320 million berries.
She is the captain of the Bonney Pirates
and her nickname is Glutton.
She sure is eating a lot there!
She was born on September 1st
and her favorite food is pizza.
She is a rookie pirate who made her name
around the same time as us.
Called Supernovas at the time,
these pirates are now called
the Worst Generation.
So she is in the same generation
as us and Tra-guy!
After the Paramount War,
she was defeated by the Blackbeard Pirates
and detained by the marines at one point,
but she escaped
and snuck into Sacred Marijoa.
I'll never forgive them!
Ever!
And she met us this time on Egghead!
Looks like she has an ability to
manipulate the ages of herself and others.
Seems like she knows Vegapunk,
but what exactly is their relationship?
That's it for this week!
See you next time!
Bye!
They finally reached Egghead,
an island housing Vegapunk.
Fish fly in the sky
and a giant monster and robot fight!
Urban landscapes with
the best of technology abound!
An unknown world full of dreams
attracts the excited Luffy.
On the next episode of ONE PIECE!
"Brimming with the Future!
An Adventure on the Island of Science!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!