(All of us) us, us
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
The end of a dream, the end of the sea
We all have different places we want to go
But first, we need
To make a shining legend out of ourselves
Sparks fly, no limit
This is where it starts
ONE PIECE!!
All of us, I ask you travelers
Are your dreams still pure?
Sleepless cells are shaken and burst
Still, all of us
In the middle of an adventure
All of us, I tell you travelers
No such thing as a pointless fight
When random contexts
Start to make sense on their own
The threads of time are spun back together
The world keeps changing along with us
(All of us) us, us
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
"Brimming with the Future!
An Adventure on the Island of Science!"
What?!
That Vegapunk?!
You guys are so noisy...
Vegapunk! I respect you!
I spent...
two years at the lab in your home...
Baldimore!
There are so many things
that I wanna show you!
Hey!
My dream giant robot!
I wonder how many times bigger than
General Franky it is?
I wish Luffy and Chopper
were here to see it!
B...
Beautiful!
Vegapunk is a beautiful lady!
Let me see your panties!
- Panties!
- Cute!
A giant robot!
Super!
- Robot!
- Super!
Wait!
What's wrong, Robin?
I've never heard of Vegapunk...
being a woman.
Oh yeah, Vegapunk is said to have
the biggest brain in the world.
Obviously, there's no way I'm Stella!
Stella?
I'm Punk-02!
Vegapunk "Lilith"!
EVIL (LILITH)
Lilith? Punk-02?
A beauty!
Our research budget is always tight!
Hand over your valuables!
Then I'll be done with you guys!
What?! What are you talking about?!
The sea is freezing here!
You saved us from drowning
so follow through!
I didn't mean to save you!
It is essentially impossible for a ship
to enter this area!
If you try, these guys will sink you
and you'll be dead!
These...
Sea Beast Weapons!
Sea Beast Weapons?!
Cool!
- Now I'm scared more than excited!
- Oh no!
Robin!
If you don't wanna get sunk,
just hand over your valuables!
Okay!
Hey, Lilith! What are you doing?
Shaka! Shut up!
I'm just doing what I do always!
Plundering again?!
Have some pride as a scientist!
Pride won't get me more budget!
Who is she talking to?
Don't get all high and mighty on me!
They won't surrender.
They're the Straw Hats.
Their captain just became
an Emperor of the Sea.
I know!
An Emperor must have tons of treasure!
If that's what you want,
you made a mistake.
A mistake?
I tactically surrounded them with
the Sea Beasts! There's no way out!
No, you underestimated them.
Look at the swordsman on the ship.
His bounty is
1 billion 111 million berries.
Pirate Hunter Zoro.
He's calm because
he knows he can kill you
in an instant from there.
Demon Child Nico Robin behind him
is the same.
But how could they fight
against this many Sea Beast Weapons?!
The strong figure out
who they need to take down first!
You're the one who's in trouble.
Those noisy fools are decoys!
Cool!
I dropped my guard!
Hey, Vegapunk.
I need you to agree with our demands...
Okay?
Are you threatening me?!
That's fine. Bring them here.
I'm interested in that group.
GOOD (SHAKA)
Is this the right way?
Are you sure?
How far are you willing to go, Bonney?
Have you ever been here before?
Yeah, when I was a child.
It was just an ordinary lab back then.
And what did you come back for?
You said you had business with Vegapunk.
Depending on his answer,
I may kill him!
Wait!
What happened?!
My father...
was turned into a cyborg by Vegapunk.
A cyborg?! That's cool!
Screw you!
He lost all sense of himself now...
and doesn't even know who he is...
He became
nothing more than a living weapon.
Gee! That's quite disturbing...
Yeah, I'll make him pay for it.
I'm sorry, Bogey!
Bonney!
I'm sorry, Bonney!
Just climb!
I think we can get to the surface.
Okay!
What are you guys gonna do?
It's up to our captain, but first,
we must find the rest of our crew.
I see...
I'll make him pay...
Oh! We're almost there!
I can't wait to see the Future Island!
Wait for me, food!
We made it to the surface!
All right! Let's find food...
Luffy! What's out there?!
I'll come with you!
Oh yeah! I saw Sabo at Marijoa.
Oh well.
What is this place?!
What is all this stuff?!
A giant robot?!
What is all this?!
A space monster?!
So many things are flying!
Cool!
Okay! I'm gonna ride that thing!
Luffy! Be careful!
Hey! We're intruders!
Gum-Gum...
Listen!
...Rocket!
What?!
Luffy got swallowed!
Are you okay?! Luffy!
I warned you.
Oh?
I thought I was swallowed...
Hey! Are you okay?!
Gee! What's wrong with him?!
Why does he want to
work up even more of an appetite?
What?
That's...
Don't tell me that's...
A giant parfait!
Food!
Cookies! Fruit!
Hey! Where are you going?!
It must be a trap!
Parfait!
Food!
Tons of cream!
I'll dig in!
Parfait!
Food!
Tons of cream!
I'll dig in!
What's going on?!
What?! My hands passed through!
What is this?!
It's there but I can't touch it!
It makes me even more hungry!
I can't eat it!
GRRRR
Don't tell me, we...
What?! Luffy!
Did we die without realizing it?!
Are we dead?!
Wait a minute, Luffy.
Shut up! I'm dead now!
There's no way you are!
Then why is this happening?
It's not because we're ghosts.
It seems like...
I thought so...
This parfait is a hologram.
Holoholo?
Hologram.
How can we eat it?
Hmmm... Well, to put it simply,
that parfait isn't real.
Then give me a real one.
I'm hungry. Where is it?
I don't know,
but one thing that's for sure is...
there's no food here!
So there is none?!
There's no way they keep food here
that conveniently.
I've never seen a hologram before.
I can't believe it! It's unforgivable!
A three-dimensional image
produced by light.
It's like something out of a comic strip
or fantasy.
An image?!
How dare it fool me!
What's there isn't there? Damn holoholo!
That's why I passed through
that space monster!
That giant robot must be a hologram, too.
No one can make something like that.
If you're gonna make something,
why don't you make food?!
Hey, look at this!
What's this?
There are pictures of food and buttons.
Didn't you just see it?
Forget it.
Everything's fake on this island.
What should I do then?
I don't know.
I just noticed...
this place is so warm even though
the sea around here was extremely cold.
Yeah. This is a tropical island.
What?
This is undoubtedly
a Winter Island though.
The reason this place is warm
is due to the Island A.C. I created.
I'm controlling the temperature of
the island itself from its soil.
You bastards don't look familiar to me...
A girl?!
More than anything...
She's huge!
What's with this child?
She's bigger than Kaido.
I don't know who you are,
but the temperature's comfy here,
so stick around.
I'm on my way to work, so let me through.
Hey, big one! I'm hungry!
You made that fake parfait, didn't you?!
Oh, if you're hungry...
You must be a holoholo, too!
What? I hit her! Is she real?!
Cut that "I hit her, is she real" crap!
What are you doing, you idiot?!
Sorry!
Oh, no! She's real!
What?
This texture... This smell...
A hamburger served with a drink and fries!
Is it real?!
Isn't it a holoholo?!
Can I touch it?
Can I eat it?
Yum!
This is real!
What? Who made it?!
Wasn't it this thing?!
It's not a person...
He pushed the button and it came out.
Whatever, as long as we can get food!
Push the next one!
All right!
Steak! Omelet with rice! Pork cutlet!
Yum!
Next!
- Cotton candy cake!
- No, pizza!
I'll choose first!
Ramen, fried chicken, and a hot dog!
Wait! If you push them at once,
they might all be served at once!
You're smart!
You're smart, Chopper!
Your compliment doesn't make me happy!
Jimbei, choose one too!
I'm okay.
Yum!
Yum! Yum!
Wow, you eat a lot.
Of course! I was hungry the whole time!
Me, too!
This too!
I'm glad that they like it.
What's going on? What is that thing?
Do you wanna know?
It's an Automated Cooking Machine!
As long as there are ingredients,
it can prepare 500 different dishes
within a minute!
The leftover ingredients auto mode
is particularly handy!
If only we could build it
according to the blueprints!
But due to a lack of technicians,
we can't mass produce it!
The Island A.C. is the same.
If we can control the temperature
of the whole island,
we can also pinpoint
all living creatures on it.
I've invented such a wonderful thing,
but the circumstances around me
haven't kept up with the value!
If I had more money to spend,
I could even control the weather!
The world lacks technology and funds!
I'm working so hard to invent things,
why is this happening?!
Dammit!
There aren't enough resources!
She punched a hologram!
- Fried shrimp!
- Waffle!
I feel better!
How's that possible?
How did you punch a hologram?
Do you wanna know? I'll tell you.
With these Light-Pressure Gloves,
light is no longer something you just see.
Hi!
People perceive something as an object
when you touch it.
What? So she isn't real?
Real?
Luffy! Look up!
So she wasn't real.
I thought she was real.
Don't ask me if something is real or not!
You decide what's real and what's not!
Even the word "real"
is an old-fashioned concept to me!
This is yummy!
You aren't listening!
Who in the world are you?
Me?
I'm only a genius scientist for hire!
Dr. Vegapunk!
VIOLENCE (ATLAS)
Yum!
You're Dr. Vegapunk?!
Koby told me about you!
You're too big and too young!
No way! What is she talking about?
How far I have run
Without knowing it, I counted scars
A treasure map in my head all along
Still looking for the future
The real promise
Lies much deeper in my heart
A dream
That no one can catch up with
That's all I hold on to
To you who smiles like the sun
I'll sing the same song as that day
This wish I don't want to forget
Even when I grow up
Until it reaches you
"Tell Me, Robin!
Chopper's I-Wanna-Learn-More-You-Fool!"
Hey, guys! I'm Chopper,
the ship's doctor of the Straw Hats!
I'm Robin, an archaeologist.
Robin, I can't wait to learn as always!
Information can be a strong weapon.
Let's keep learning!
Yeah! Today we'll learn about this one!
Dr. Vegapunk!
The Government's genius scientist
who is said to have
the biggest brain in the world.
He is from the Future Land Baldimore.
I know that country!
That's where Kuma sent Franky!
That's right.
Franky was impressed
by his research material.
I can't believe
these are all from his younger days.
There are a lot of ideas that would need
a couple hundred years to implement fully.
After Dr. Vegapunk left Baldimore,
he became part of the research team MADS
along with Caesar and Vinsmoke Judge.
And he discovered the Bloodline Elements
within living things.
It was just one step away from
usurping God's place
because it was akin
to discovering the blueprints of life.
In addition, he created a warship
covered with Sea Prism Stone,
and artificial Devil Fruits,
and established the technique of enabling
objects to "eat" the Devil Fruits.
He has a lot of accomplishments.
Maybe he'll make some amazing inventions
in the field of medicine!
Several Vegapunks with different
appearances and ages turned up,
deepening the mystery.
That's it for this week!
See you next time!
Bye!
A man comes after Straw Hat and the others
who are enjoying futuristic gizmos.
He looks exactly like Bartholomew Kuma!
Bonney stops Luffy
who tries to fight back!
Unable to contain her heightened emotions,
she reveals
her shocking relationship with Kuma!
On the next episode of ONE PIECE!
"Bonney's Lamentation!
Darkness Lurking on the Future Island"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!