(All of us) us, us
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
The end of a dream, the end of the sea
We all have different places we want to go
But first, we need
To make a shining legend out of ourselves
Sparks fly, no limit
This is where it starts
ONE PIECE!!
All of us, I ask you travelers
Are your dreams still pure?
Sleepless cells are shaken and burst
Still, all of us
In the middle of an adventure
All of us, I tell you travelers
No such thing as a pointless fight
When random contexts
Start to make sense on their own
The threads of time are spun back together
The world keeps changing along with us
(All of us) us, us
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
The Straw Hats that got separated from
Luffy, Chopper, and Jimbei
came across an unexpected party.
I'm only a genius scientist
working for the Government!
I'm Dr. Vegapunk!
What is all this stuff?!
Meanwhile, Luffy and the others
were exploring the Future Island Egghead.
And they ran into...
You bastards don't look familiar to me...
A girl?!
More than anything...
She's huge!
What's with that child?
She's bigger than Kaido.
Who in the world are you?
Me?
I'm only a genius scientist for hire!
Dr. Vegapunk!
VIOLENCE (ATLAS)
You're Dr. Vegapunk?!
Koby told me about you!
You're too big and too young!
No way! What is she talking about?
"Bonney's Lamentation!
Darkness Lurking on the Future Island"
NEW WORLD
So what should we do?
Listen carefully.
There's only one Vegapunk.
That's stating the obvious.
Don't interrupt.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Listen.
There's only one Vegapunk in the world.
But he's so busy
because he's such a genius.
He doesn't have enough time.
He'll take all the help he can get.
Then he came up with an idea...
to split himself into six.
Those offshoots are called Satellites.
Punk-01, Shaka!
SHAKA (GOOD)
Punk-02, Lilith!
LILITH (EVIL)
Punk-03, Edison!
EDISON (THINKER)
Punk-04, Pythagoras!
PYTHAGORAS (WISDOM)
Punk-05, Atlas!
ATLAS (VIOLENCE)
Punk-06, York!
YORK (GREED)
In other words, these six Satellites
are all Vegapunk!
DR. VEGAPUNK
Am I crazy to think that can't be true?
Being a genius is a pain...
His "cats" are quite troublesome, too!
Just like their owner.
So our mission is...
to return this bastard to Egghead,
and eliminate all the Vegapunks.
MASKED ASSASSINS
KAKU / LUCCI / STUSSY
The lab is full of valuable stuff.
Be careful with those while you're at it.
We will eliminate the handiest man
in the world...
Does this have something to do with
what happened to Lulusia the other day?
Don't be nosy.
Not when your intuition
is as good as yours.
She's right!
Don't get us involved, Lucci!
You're that well-known Vegapunk?
Yeah, I am!
I've never heard
that Vegapunk was a child...
And so huge...
Are you guys satisfied?
Oh, it was so good.
Everyone will be surprised
when they see the food machine.
It's a shame that they aren't here yet
to see such a great thing.
Oh, maybe Sanji will get mad.
You guys ate so much!
All your stomachs are about to burst!
Mine's always been like this.
What's that?
That's Recycollie.
It consumes and breaks down garbage
and reconstitutes it to be a resource.
It's so brilliant!
RECYCOLLIE
So that's like its food.
Cool.
Here's your food. Eat it!
What?!
Go away! I feel heavy!
Why am I being chased too?!
Luffy's the one who did it!
By the way,
Recycollie won't tolerate littering.
You should've told me!
They are so funny.
You have to throw garbage
into a trash can.
Yes... I'm sorry...
I gotta go now.
Are you leaving already?
My job is to be violent.
What kind of job is that?
Thanks for the food!
Enjoy your stay on Egghead.
What are they?
It's a lab,
so I think they're researchers.
There wasn't anybody in the town,
but now I see some people...
Maybe they were taking precautions
against us.
Their outfits look heavy
even though this is a tropical island.
Oh?
Where's Luffy?
Is this also a food machine?
Welcome. Choose the clothes you like.
I'd rather have food.
Oh, well!
Here we go.
Are there any other requests?
This and this and this...
And this!
Oh! It's moving!
W-What are you doing?!
That's Luffy!
What?! What are you doing?!
Don't take the hat!
Luffy!
Is he in there?
Hey, guys!
How do I look?
I love it!
How funny!
Isn't it heavy?
It's really light!
And it's cooler inside!
It's fashionable.
I wanna wear it, too!
Where did you get it?
This!
They're giving us food and clothes!
This island is awesome!
To be honest,
I feel sticky because of the seawater!
Choose the clothes you like.
I like?
A combat dress!
A cool one!
This looks light.
It's really high-tech!
I can take them off myself!
You're right!
They're really light!
I feel like I'm floating with these shoes!
Cool!
The future!
There was a tropical style one, too.
That looks good on you, Jimbei!
Yeah? It's just right for a disguise.
Maybe it's too late though...
Don't forget that you're intruders.
Be careful.
I'll go find a weapon
and track down Vegapunk.
So bye.
You must be careful, too!
Thanks for everything!
Hey!
What's wrong?
Did something happen?
That's Kuma!
Kuma?!
Is he looking for us?
Is it just my imagination?
Let's run!
What?!
He's gonna run!
- He's targeting us!
- Hey!
What's going on?! Explain it to me!
Just keep running!
Oh, no!
Dine and dash! Stealing clothes!
Here comes the laser cannon!
I didn't know I needed to pay!
It came out when I kicked it!
That's vandalism.
They'd kill us over an eat and run?!
That's a little too harsh.
If we don't fight back,
we'll be in danger!
This is a form of self-defense if
we put aside the fact that we're pirates!
All right! I feel bad, but...
Gum-Gum...
Wait!
Hey! Why did you do that, Bonney?!
He's using laser beams!
Why can't I at least punch...
He's my father...
The only...
family I have left!
What?!
Your father
who was turned into a cyborg...
...is Kuma?!
So please!
Don't hurt my father!
Idiot! Run!
It's a Pacifista!
Bonney!
A CERTAIN SEA AREA, NEW WORLD
It's nice and sunny!
It's a lovely day!
So peaceful!
Bepo, do your job!
You're on cleaning duty, too!
I've already finished cleaning
the area that I'm in charge of!
I'm sunbathing now.
Because you're rolling around there...
Our work will never be done!
Look at this! This is all your fur!
There's fur all over the deck!
Is it shedding season?!
Don't you guys lose your hair?
We'd be shocked if we lost this much!
Why don't you just shut up and help us?!
What?!
Here they come.
Our prey!
Brace your nerves, guys!
No matter what happens from here on,
there's no way we're running away!
While we fight pirates like them...
We're gonna just keep going!
JESUS BURGESS (STRONG-STRONG FRUIT)
VAN OGRE (WARP-WARP FRUIT)
STRONGER (HORSE-HORSE FRUIT,
MYTHICAL TYPE, MODEL: PEGASUS)
DOC Q (SICK-SICK FRUIT)
EMPEROR OF THE SEA, BLACKBEARD
BOUNTY: 3,996 BILLION BERRIES
Guys!
Let's get this party started!
Let's go, guys!
How far I have run
Without knowing it, I counted scars
A treasure map in my head all along
Still looking for the future
The real promise
Lies much deeper in my heart
A dream
That no one can catch up with
That's all I hold on to
To you who smiles like the sun
I'll sing the same song as that day
This wish I don't want to forget
Even when I grow up
Until it reaches you
"Tell Me, Robin!
Chopper's I-Wanna-Learn-More-You-Fool!"
Hey, guys! I'm Chopper,
the ship's doctor of the Straw Hats!
I'm Robin, an archaeologist.
Robin, I can't wait to learn as always!
Information can be a strong weapon.
Let's keep learning!
Today we'll learn about this one!
Rob Lucci!
He's an agent of Cipher Pol,
an intelligence organization
working directly
under the World Government.
He uses Six Powers, martial arts that turn
a well-trained body into a weapon.
He was born on June 2nd
and he likes brandy.
He's also a user of
the Zoan type Devil Fruit,
Cat-Cat Fruit, Leopard Model.
We first met him in Water Seven.
To obtain the blueprints for
Pluton, the Ancient Weapon,
he was working for
the Galley-La Company for five years,
hiding that he was a CP9 agent.
After he and the others
revealed their true identities,
they took Robin away to Enies Lobby,
the World Government's island.
In the name of dark justice!
If you guys didn't come then,
I wouldn't be where I am today.
Luffy busted Lucci
and we were able to take Robin back!
Looks like he is an agent
of Cipher Pol "Aigis" Zero
which is working
directly under the World Nobles.
I wonder why
he has a pigeon on his shoulder.
Egghead is becoming even more chaotic.
That's it for this week!
See you next time!
Bye!