(All of us) us, us
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
The end of a dream, the end of the sea
We all have different places we want to go
But first, we need
To make a shining legend out of ourselves
Sparks fly, no limit
This is where it starts
ONE PIECE!!
All of us, I ask you travelers
Are your dreams still pure?
Sleepless cells are shaken and burst
Still, all of us
In the middle of an adventure
All of us, I tell you travelers
No such thing as a pointless fight
When random contexts
Start to make sense on their own
The threads of time are spun back together
The world keeps changing along with us
(All of us) us, us
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
Here they come.
Our prey!
"The Winner Takes All!
Law vs. Blackbeard!"
A CERTAIN SEA AREA, NEW WORLD
Close valve two!
Cover this up!
Here, too!
Something dead ahead!
Turn away!
It's impossible, Captain!
We can't get away!
I won't let you escape!
One more hit and the ship
will be crushed by water pressure!
We can't get away now!
Let's surface.
To the northeast near land!
Aye-aye, Captain!
Head for land!
Hard to starboard!
Get ready to fight! Hurry up!
A woman!
Aye! Even Captain became a woman!
Aye?
Damn! I'm less strong than usual...
What happened to me?
Anyway, we're in trouble!
You're so cute, Captain!
Cut it out or I'll knock you guys down!
But you're still cute!
Oh, no!
Even I...
My sex has been changed!
Don't touch the infected!
S-Sorry...
This is infectious!
Your sex will change!
But I learned something in the battle
against the Emperors of the Sea.
I can break through it!
An over-abundance of Haki...
can nullify Devil Fruit powers!
We surfaced, Captain!
I turned back!
I changed back into a man!
Good.
That's our captain!
There's no time to relax.
Dock the ship! We'll go ashore!
Aye-aye, sir!
The disease is cured.
Only a man with a 3 billion bounty
could do that...
That's right. The antibodies of the cured
spread just like the disease itself.
I bet you enjoyed it.
The feminization disease.
DOC Q
(SICK-SICK FRUIT)
Burgess! Let's move to the island.
VAN OGRE
(WARP-WARP FRUIT)
Okay!
What?! The mountain is moving!
Hey! There is someone deep in the island!
It's the best!
The Strong-Strong Fruit power!
JESUS BURGESS
(STRONG-STRONG FRUIT)
Burgess?!
How could he lift up
that humongous, rugged mountain?!
When did they come ashore
in the first place?!
That's also a Devil Fruit power.
Superhuman strength,
contagion, teleportation.
By hunting power-users,
they all obtained ridiculous powers!
No wonder their bounties keep going up!
Room!
Amputate!
It's been a while, Trafalgar Law!
Blackbeard! Why are you here?!
Don't be mean! We're both
members of the Worst Generation!
Commodore!
Stronger says you're too heavy...
I feel the same...
STRONGER (HORSE-HORSE FRUIT,
MYTHICAL TYPE, PEGASUS MODEL)
Either Straw Hat or Kid or you...
I knew one of you would come here
after departing the Land of Wano!
I can't believe Kaido and Big Mom fell!
The world has been turned upside down!
It feels good!
Of course, Kaido had it, didn't he?!
How many do you have now?
I'll take them all. The Road Ponegliffs!
Conditions are the same for me and you!
The winner...
takes all!
No matter where you go,
there's nowhere to run!
Hakugan, take charge of the Polar Tang!
Okay!
Shachi! Penguin! Into the sea!
Count on us!
Re-Room!
What?!
Amputate!
That's not what I was told he could do!
Is it an Awakened technique?!
All right! Fall!
Not yet!
Damn you!
Tremor Crush!
Damn that monster!
Damn!
Stronger, are you dead?
I see...
He was a good guy.
You're alive?!
Don't scare me.
Take this!
Hey, look up!
What are they?!
Get away! They're exploding apples!
What?!
We're from an extremely cold port
in the North Blue! Screw you!
Don't think you can beat us at sea!
We're gonna sink your ship!
Prepare to attack!
Yeah!
Jeanbart! Three o'clock! A sniper!
Defend Captain!
All right!
Oops...
His guard is tight.
K-Room!
That doesn't hurt at all!
Shock Wille!
See, that's what happens
when you charge before you think...
Warp.
Commodore, do you want to
go back to the ship?
No way! We'll just keep pushing!
I see. Then...
Warp.
Blackbeard!
All your top officers are power-users!
That means all of them
are weak against the sea!
Devil Fruits have more advantages
than weaknesses!
An enemy attack from under the sea!
They wanna sink our ship!
No one told me
that they were strong in the sea!
The torpedo is loaded!
Target locked! Distance 500!
Fire!
Whew!
It's shaking due to enemy attacks,
but it'll be over soon.
Because our commodore is the strongest!
If Mama were alive,
you wouldn't be able to say such a thing.
CHARLOTTE PUDDING, BIG MOM PIRATES
Who we're fighting now
is the very person who killed Big Mom!
If legends are allowed to prevail,
the times won't move forward!
You better know your place!
Cacao Island is one of the islands
surrounding the Whole Cake Island.
Two intruders came to Chocolat Town
where Pudding resided.
Cracker fought them back, but...
There was nothing he could do.
The intruders' goal was to abduct Pudding.
Their identities were
the Blackbeard Pirates' Van Ogre and...
Kuzan.
I know what you people
are trying to make me do.
I won't let you do what you want.
The Emperor of the Sea Blackbeard
and Trafalgar Law
clashed at Winner Island in the New World.
I have to wait
to see the conclusion again.
It's frustrating to be
the Admiral of the Fleet...
Room!
Interesting!
Takt!
Your power is so handy!
K-Room!
Black Vortex!
How far I have run
Without knowing it, I counted scars
A treasure map in my head all along
Still looking for the future
The real promise
Lies much deeper in my heart
A dream
That no one can catch up with
That's all I hold on to
To you who smiles like the sun
I'll sing the same song as that day
This wish I don't want to forget
Even when I grow up
Until it reaches you
"Tell Me, Robin!
Chopper's I-Wanna-Learn-More-You-Fool!"
Hey, guys! I'm Chopper,
the ship's doctor of the Straw Hats!
I'm Robin, an archaeologist.
Robin, I can't wait to learn as always!
Information can be a strong weapon.
Let's keep learning!
Yeah! Today we'll learn about this one!
Charlotte Pudding!
She is the daughter
of former Emperor of the Sea, Big Mom,
and is a half Three-Eyed Person.
She uses the Memo-Memo Fruit power
which enables her
to edit memories at will.
She was born on June 25th,
and likes ganache and pudding.
In order for Big Mom
to get Germa's scientific power,
she was gonna marry Sanji!
She seemed very nice at first,
but it was an act,
she was deceiving Sanji.
But she seemed to have had
a change of heart.
What a beautiful eye!
What?
And she helped us to get away from Big Mom
who was suffering from Hunger Pangs.
I-If you act like my master,
I'll kill you, Sanji...
san!
Thanks to Pudding,
we were able to escape Whole Cake Island.
I didn't know it was that dramatic.
I hope you guys can see her again.
That would definitely make Sanji happy!
That's it for this week!
See you next time!
Bye!
On the clouds far above the ground,
a whole laboratory appears!
What research is the head of the lab,
Vegapunk, doing behind closed doors?
A new threat awaits the Straw Hats
as they enter the heart of science.
On the next episode of ONE PIECE!
"The Mystery Deepens! Egghead Labophase"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!