(All of us) us, us
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
The end of a dream, the end of the sea
We all have different places we want to go
But first, we need
To make a shining legend out of ourselves
Sparks fly, no limit
This is where it starts
ONE PIECE!!
All of us, I ask you travelers
Are your dreams still pure?
Sleepless cells are shaken and burst
Still, all of us
In the middle of an adventure
All of us, I tell you travelers
No such thing as a pointless fight
When random contexts
Start to make sense on their own
The threads of time are spun back together
The world keeps changing along with us
(All of us) us, us
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
Nami and the others made it to Labophase
and encountered a surprising person.
Jimbei?!
Hey! Who are you?!
I have a bad feeling!
"The Brain of a Genius - Six Vegapunks!"
Oh, no!
This is a set-up!
I knew that the Government
wouldn't welcome us!
I thought it was strange
that we could get this far so easily!
Luring and killing us all...
Is that what they're up to?!
They had the Pacifista ready for that.
And he looks like Jimbei.
Gee, the ways of a scientist
are beyond our understanding.
Stop, Jimbei!
He's not reacting to that name.
Does that mean he's Jimbei's clone?!
Don't be fooled by his appearance!
He's our enemy!
It's not that simple!
I even hesitate to attack him
just because he's a kid!
What?! Is he a power-user?!
What's going on?!
What do you wanna do, Nami?!
Do you wanna fight?!
Wait, Zeus!
Hey! You've got to be kidding!
That power belongs to...
Nami!
Hey! Stop!
Jimbei...
You bastard! Let go of Nami!
Damn you!
I'll make you pay
even if Vegapunk is responsible for this!
Okay, death penalty it is!
Even if you're...
Jimbei!
Nami! Are you all right?!
Yeah...
I feel the same as them!
What you just did is unforgivable!
Gigante Fleur!
What's going on?! A giant woman appeared!
Wow! Awesome!
Opportunities like this are rare!
The Seraphim will get even stronger!
Sea Serpent Snapdragon!
Spank!
What?!
He blocked the attack
using the water in the air?!
Get away, Robin!
He uses the Fish-Man Karate, too!
Special Attack Green Star!
Skull Bomb-Grass!
Even though I know he's not Jimbei,
I'm reluctant to do this!
Did it get him?!
Yeah, I think it did!
He's gone!
He's gone?!
Why?! He got hit, didn't he?!
Hey! Let go of me!
Usopp!
Sanji, leave it to me!
Usopp, don't move!
Damn you! Let go of me!
I said, "Don't move"!
That energy... Don't tell me it's...
Radical...
Dodge it, S-Shark!
...Beam!
He used a laser beam! Who is he?!
And it was extremely high power!
That was close!
THINKER (EDISON)
I let him get away!
I thought I was gonna die!
There he is again!
Go away!
He didn't get a scratch from that attack.
That's impossible!
I don't think he is just a clone.
That's enough!
Vegapunk!
Shut up, you little tramp!
The Seraphim is still a child. He's not
ready for a laser beam experiment yet!
That's right!
How much does he think
one Seraphim costs?!
That fool! Should I rip his head off?!
You're evil!
There's no need to show pirates any mercy!
I'm gonna make this place their graveyard!
You're devilish!
S-Shark, beat them thoroughly!
Kick their asses!
That's enough! I wasn't gonna go that far!
Oh, I got an idea for a new invention!
Oh, yeah?
Then leave everything to me from now!
I'll leave the rest to you, Pythagoras!
What?!
Of course!
Interesting battle data like this
is hard to get!
WISDOM (PYTHAGORAS)
I have to draw blueprints now!
So busy, so busy!
I'd welcome even a cat's help!
Wonderful!
I keep getting exceptional data!
This is a great fight!
Yay!
The Seraphim's attack patterns
are developing as he grows!
Does that mean experiences get stored
in their Bloodline Elements as I thought?
Come on! Really give it to them!
S-Shark!
His accelerated growth
allows him to solve problems!
From a heart rate of 90 BPM,
Green Blood concentration went up!
Show them your true power!
I can't stop! I can't stop!
I can't stop the ideas from coming!
Damn!
I'm running out of energy!
GREED (YORK)
I'm hungry!
The more I write,
the more my stomach growls!
I can't stop the ideas from coming!
I don't have time to eat!
Eat something for me, York!
Okay!
Here it comes!
Nutrition is soaking into my brain!
I got even more ideas!
Eat! Eat! York!
Give me more!
Hurry up! Hurry up!
Get more food for York-sama!
Guys, hurry up!
I'm sorry to keep you waiting!
Here's more food! York-sama!
That's not enough! Get me more!
Yes, ma'am! Right away!
Yummy!
Her current BMI is over 600.
I don't want more!
That's it, S-Shark!
Battle data keeps getting updated!
Not now...
Ow, ow, ow... Let's call a temporary truce!
I don't want to miss his growth!
I wanna go to the bathroom,
but I don't wanna waste any time!
I feel much better!
Digestion Punch!
It's done! Let's do an experiment!
Could you bring me
all materials on Devil Fruits?!
Bring all materials to Pythagoras-sama!
Prepare for Mr. Edison's experiment!
To simulation room 88!
I'm sleepy.
That's York-sama's fourth
Kuu Dasu Neru (Eat Poop Sleep) today!
Hey, Pythagoras!
I think you got enough data.
I need to talk to them.
Wait, wait! I want some more information
on S-Shark's evolution...
Shut up! Back off, Shaka!
Don't tell us what to do!
Get off of me, Lilith!
We're moving on to the next step.
This is an order.
What?
No!
What's the matter, guys?!
W-What?!
You've got to be kidding!
Damn! My feet are stuck!
Stop it! This is not fair!
Are you gonna get rid of us all at once?!
Damn!
Move!
That's enough, Seraphim. Retreat.
Edison, Lilith, Pythagoras!
I think you've had enough.
Oh, what a shame...
Damn!
Ouch!
What's wrong with that bastard?!
We were just getting to the best part!
I got an idea!
GOOD
Did he come to help us?!
He's shady no matter how you look at him!
Looks like he's Lilith's colleague.
Then maybe he's also...
I'm Dr. Vegapunk Shaka.
GOOD (SHAKA)
Another one?! What's with you guys?!
So you guys are the Straw Hats.
Yeah! What's wrong with these shoes?!
They're stuck to the floor!
Dom Shoes can always be controlled easily
by the power of magnets in the lab.
I guess it's no use to resist.
We can't trust pirates.
There was a female Vegapunk
and a Vegapunk
who was talking through speakers.
Yeah... I am Vegapunk, too.
I don't get it!
How many of you guys are there?!
Maybe I'm Vegapunk, too...
What?! No, you're not!
Is there anything interesting here?
I can't believe it!
These are all Vegapunk's inventions!
There are tons of them.
They're all failures...
All he makes is crap.
Oh! There is something big!
Let's go, Chopper!
Yeah!
Does this island look like
the future to you guys?
Yeah, it's amazing!
It's not just an ordinary future.
Those mechanical Sea Beasts!
Vegaforce-01 and
air-conditioning on the island, too!
It's a hell of a future!
And I've never seen a city like that...
I wanna look around to see
what kind of technology is used!
Don't say that we're enemies!
Let's be friends, Vega-chan!
There is something
that even I can't surpass.
This island is from the past.
Not just anyone can create
technology like this!
What do you mean from the past?!
For example, if I said...
there was an advanced kingdom
like Egghead 900 years ago,
would you believe it?
900 years ago?!
What are you talking about?!
This is real!
Look, Chopper! It's not a holoholo!
It's really there! It's made of iron!
Awesome! It's a giant robot!
So cool!
What is this?! It's pretty beat-up.
Did it used to work?
Only technology of the future
could make it work...
Isn't it too old?!
I wanna ride it!
Yeah, let's ride it!
Let's go, Chopper!
How far I have run
Without knowing it, I counted scars
A treasure map in my head all along
Still looking for the future
The real promise
Lies much deeper in my heart
A dream
That no one can catch up with
That's all I hold on to
To you who smiles like the sun
I'll sing the same song as that day
This wish I don't want to forget
Even when I grow up
Until it reaches you
"Tell Me, Robin!
Chopper's I-Wanna-Learn-More-You-Fool!"
Hey, guys! I'm Chopper,
the ship's doctor of the Straw Hats!
I'm Robin, an archaeologist.
Robin, I can't wait to learn as always!
Information can be a strong weapon.
Let's keep learning!
Yeah! Today we'll learn about this one!
Our crewmate, Jimbei!
He is the helmsman of the Straw Hats.
He was born on April 2nd and
likes vinegared mozuku seaweed and fruit.
He used to be
the captain of the Sun Pirates
and one of the Seven Warlords!
But he opposed Ace's execution
and resigned from the Seven Warlords.
And he later scolded and encouraged Luffy
who gave in to despair after losing Ace.
They also fought together
on Fish-Man Island
and he donated his blood to save Luffy.
Luffy asked him to join his crew
at that time,
but Jimbei turned him down
to fulfill his duty
because he was affiliated with Big Mom.
And after all that happened,
he finally managed
to cut ties with Big Mom.
Please remember my face,
and I request your continued support!
HELMSMAN "FIRST SON OF THE SEA" JIMBEI
BOUNTY: 438 MILLION BERRIES
-Jimbei!
-Jimbei-san!
And he formally joined our crew
in the Land of Wano.
I wanna go on
a lot of adventures with him!
By the way, that Pacifista
who resembles Jimbei is really strong!
That's it for this week!
See you next time!
Bye!
What happened in the 100-Year Void that
the World Government has covered up?
The future that scholars
risked their lives to save.
After a long period of time,
their will is now passed down
to the only survivor of Ohara
who was once a little girl.
On the next episode of ONE PIECE!
"A Forbidden Piece of History!
A Theory Concerning a Kingdom"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!