(All of us) us, us
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
The end of a dream, the end of the sea
We all have different places we want to go
But first, we need
To make a shining legend out of ourselves
Sparks fly, no limit
This is where it starts
ONE PIECE!!
All of us, I ask you travelers
Are your dreams still pure?
Sleepless cells are shaken and burst
Still, all of us
In the middle of an adventure
All of us, I tell you travelers
No such thing as a pointless fight
When random contexts
Start to make sense on their own
The threads of time are spun back together
The world keeps changing along with us
(All of us) us, us
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
This is real!
Look, Chopper! It's not a holoholo!
Did it used to work?
Only technology of the future
could make it work...
Isn't it too old?!
For example, if I said...
there was an advanced kingdom
like Egghead 900 years ago,
would you believe it?
"A Forbidden Piece of History!
A Theory Concerning a Kingdom"
900 years ago?
What are you talking about?!
Do you mean a futuristic city like this
existed that many years ago?!
It's just a theory.
A man who once risked his life
for archaeology...
shed light on a certain ancient kingdom.
And the manufacture of machinery which
has been discovered at a certain site
coincides with the reign of that kingdom.
Was that machine built
during the 100-Year Void?!
How much do you know about that?
Robin! Do you know something?!
I bet you don't even want to think back,
but 22 years ago,
your birthplace Ohara was destroyed
by the marine's Buster Call.
I believe...
that's because Ohara learned of
the existence of that kingdom.
The 100-Year Void...
contains the history of the conflict
between the advanced kingdom
and the Twenty Kingdoms.
The Twenty Kingdoms who won the battle
later founded the World Government
and created the world as we know it.
And to prevent anyone from inheriting
that ancient kingdom's ideology,
they erased it completely from history.
I can't believe it!
What?! What?! Is that true?!
What an exciting story!
It's too grand a story
for me to comprehend...
Yeah, I mean, "erase completely"?
Wait a minute, Vegapunk!
If Ohara received a Buster Call
because of that,
that means people who learn about this...
Yeah, they'll be killed.
Hey! We didn't even ask!
Why did you tell us about it?!
Damn! I've heard it!
I've heard it so...
Let's forget it! I don't know anything!
I didn't hear a thing!
I don't know anything!
-I didn't hear a thing! Forget it!
-Calm down a little.
-I didn't hear anything! Forget it!
-I said it was just a theory.
This is horrible! I don't wanna die!
Now, Nico Robin.
If Ohara was destroyed
because of this theory,
don't you think that means the Government
has admitted it to be true?
Vegapunk...
Whose side are you on anyway?
The scholars of Ohara continued to study
the valuable materials and made a theory...
With a position as high as yours,
would the Government tell you?
No, they didn't tell me anything...
The rule still stands.
While I am affiliated with the Government,
I'll be killed if I mention it.
Then I don't wanna know!
This is like torture!
Get me out of here!
Then how did you find out
about the kingdom?!
The books that Ohara acquired
from all over the world must be...
The will of Ohara lives on.
That day,
the world was thrown into confusion...
Ohara, an academic island with
the most advanced knowledge in the world,
was destroyed overnight
leaving just one girl behind...
Ohara was accused of being
an evil group of scholars
plotting to overthrow
the World Government.
Several months after the incident,
I visited Ohara.
Because I knew the late Professor Clover,
the archaeologic czar,
so I wanted to lay flowers.
You knew him?!
Yeah.
He was obsessed with the 100-Year Void,
and went on adventures
to scour the world for documents about it.
He was arrested by the marines,
and jailed ten times...
There he is!
And he became the most famous
archaeologist in the world.
Eventually,
scholars who were impressed by him
came together at Ohara,
and the island became
the center for archaeology.
You can say the tragedy occurred
because he was talented.
The past belongs to all mankind.
No one has the right to stop one from
wanting to know our unspoken history!
By analyzing the ancient
documents and some Ponegliffs,
we eventually noticed
the existence of a country.
There is no trace of it left now,
but what the documents brought to light
was the existence of a grand kingdom.
Although it seems to have
boasted much power in the past,
the information on this country
has obsessively been erased.
They probably sensed they'd be defeated
by the allied countries,
later to become the World Government,
and so inscribed all the truth on stones
to pass it down to the future.
Indeed, those stones are the Ponegliffs
that remain to this very day.
I see. That's a bold hypothesis.
It's true that the Ancient Weapon
would threaten the world.
However, isn't it actually that
the World Government is more threatened
by people becoming aware of
that kingdom's existence and ideology?
The name of this once-prosperous kingdom
that holds the key to everything is...
Ohara has...
come to know too much.
Give the attack signal.
I'll initiate a Buster Call!
When I set foot on Ohara,
the place was an absolute disaster.
Even the Tree of Knowledge
was burned to the ground,
and it seemed like everything
was reduced to ashes.
But when I walked deeper into the island,
I witnessed something astonishing.
What is all of this?!
A vast amount of books of all kinds
were submerged in the lake
at the center of the island!
Perhaps the scholars stayed on the island
which was burning under the Buster Call,
and died protecting the legacy
they were to leave for the future.
The books that so many scholars protected
at the risk of their lives...
Even if ignorant soldiers found them,
they wouldn't know how valuable they are.
It's a victory for Ohara.
When I saw it,
I couldn't stop my tears from falling.
Please take care of Robin!
Please let my daughter escape
from the island at any cost!
What?! No! What about you, Mom?!
Aren't you gonna come with me?!
Olvia... What are you gonna...
There's still something
that I have to do here, so...
Mom! I don't wanna be separated!
I'll stay here, too!
Robin...
You're an Ohara scholar,
so you should know this very well.
History is the treasure of mankind.
It'll certainly light up the future
you young ones will live in.
But the history we received
from the past will disappear
unless we pass it on to the next era.
-Put out the fire!
-Protect the books!
Save as many books as we can!
Throw the books out of the library!
Revealing the history isn't
what Ohara was trying to do.
We just wanted to accept the voices
of the past and protect them.
Our research will end now,
but even if Ohara is obliterated
we cannot give up the future
you young ones will live in!
I don't understand!
You will understand someday.
Now...
Go, Saul!
Are you sure about this?
Yes.
No! I'll stay here, too! Mom!
Mom!
Live, Robin!
Be proud, Robin!
Your mom is honorable!
Someday,
pass down this island's history, Robin!
Ohara fought against the world!
What's the matter, Robin-chan?
Hey! How dare you make her cry,
you helmet fool!
-Unforgivable! Vegapunk! I'll kick you!
-Gee! How insensitive you are!
So get these shoes off me, you bastard!
-Get them off!
-Look at me, you damn helmet!
Vegapunk.
Just as you guessed,
Ohara uncovered
the existence of the kingdom.
I see. Then that's a fact.
Where are the books...
that were in the lake now?
I wanted to bring them back
to Punk Hazard,
but if the higher-ups heard about it,
it would all be over.
Actually...
I ran into those guys that day.
Hey! There's no cockpit
on this thing, Chopper.
We haven't checked under its jaw.
Jaw?
Okay!
General Franky has its cockpit
at the front,
but since this is so big,
it could be someplace we never imagined.
I don't see anything from here...
All right, Chopper. When there is a robot...
Yeah, we've got to do it.
Let's go!
Combine!
Pirates Docking Two!
We're a robot warrior on a search mission!
Let's show everyone!
Our combined power!
SCRAP HEAP, FABRIOPHASE
EGGHEAD
All right! Rocket Booster!
Leave it to me!
What are they doing?
-Where is the cockpit?!
-I guess you can't understand.
That's a dream come true for them.
A dream, huh?
Is there a door? I don't think it's here.
I can't find it either.
It's not here?
Maybe it's on its back.
Yeah, let's get down then.
No, behind me there's...
Sorry!
Don't move your head!
Sorry! I'll be careful!
Didn't you hear what I said?!
What?
Phew!
What did they combine for after all?!
I guess there is no cockpit.
Ah! Maybe this robot is autonomous!
Oh, one of those?!
I see...
Maybe it'll react
if we say something to it!
Like... Like...
Move! Move, robot!
It didn't work...
I wonder what the magic phrase is...
No! It must have a name!
We should call that!
Move, Robonosuke!
That's not it...
Let's call it by different names!
Yeah!
Move, Robomaru!
Move, Big Robo!
Move, Robotaro!
Move, Miracle Robo!
Robo Ace!
Victory Robo!
Robo King!
Gee... What are you guys, kids?
There's no way
you could get it to work like that.
What?!
Are you okay?
Yeah...
What was that?! The robot exploded?!
No, it wasn't an explosion.
Then what just happened?!
Hey!
Help me-Quasar!
"Quasar"?
Oh, no! I failed again!
Somebody, help me-Quasar!
Maybe space-time distorted
while I was warping!
Was that old man there before?
-I'm sinking! Hey!
-I don't think so.
My body's sinking!
Somebody!
I don't know what's going on.
Old man, do you need help?!
Help me-Quasar!
What the... You're just like Kin'emon.
Hurry up!
I'll get you out!
Thanks!
I thought so! It's him!
Thank you!
By the way, you're Dragon's son, right?
Who are you, old man?
I knew you were here. I'm glad you came.
And you're Bonney!
You've grown up.
Vegapunk!
I'm glad to see you doing well!
Old man, are you floating?!
You're wearing them, too.
What?
Those Dom Shoes have a hover function!
What?! A hover function?!
How can we use it?!
First, press the button on the side...
Oh, this one.
And this lever!
Push it further down!
Like this?!
That's it!
We've flown too far!
Help me-Quasar!
THE MAN WITH THE BEST BRAIN IN THE WORLD
The man with the best brain in the world.
A genius scientist, Dr. Vegapunk, appears!
LEADER OF THE MARINES'
SPECIAL SCIENCE GROUP
How far I have run
Without knowing it, I counted scars
A treasure map in my head all along
Still looking for the future
The real promise
Lies much deeper in my heart
A dream
That no one can catch up with
That's all I hold on to
To you who smiles like the sun
I'll sing the same song as that day
This wish I don't want to forget
Even when I grow up
Until it reaches you
"Tell Me, Robin!
Chopper's I-Wanna-Learn-More-You-Fool!"
Hey, guys! I'm Chopper,
the ship's doctor of the Straw Hats!
I'm Robin, an archaeologist.
Robin, I can't wait to learn as always!
Information can be a strong weapon.
Let's keep learning!
Yeah! Today we'll learn about this one!
Jaguar D. Saul!
He is a Giant and a former marine
Vice Admiral.
He and Kuzan, also a former marine
officer, were close friends.
He was born on March 6th
and likes roasted whale.
When he met my mother Olvia,
he began to question
the marine's brand of justice.
And he ran away from the marines
along with my mother.
He washed ashore on Ohara...
Then he met you!
Yes, he protected me from the Buster Call.
You're alone now,
but you'll meet friends someday for sure!
The sea is vast, so someday, definitely...
you'll come across friends
who'll protect you!
No one is born into this world
to be alone!
You were a prophet.
Who is it?!
I took over this segment!
No!
A scientist with an inner passion
and a young man with a fighting spirit
to start a revolution.
Vegapunk and Dragon's past
is revealed by Shaka.
A wish for the future
quietly passed down from Ohara's scholars
moves the hearts of the Straw Hats
from the next generation.
On the next episode of ONE PIECE!
"The Will of Ohara!
The Inherited Research"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!