(All of us) us, us
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
The end of a dream, the end of the sea
We all have different places we want to go
But first, we need
To make a shining legend out of ourselves
Sparks fly, no limit
This is where it starts
ONE PIECE!!
All of us, I ask you travelers
Are your dreams still pure?
Sleepless cells are shaken and burst
Still, all of us
In the middle of an adventure
All of us, I tell you travelers
No such thing as a pointless fight
When random contexts
Start to make sense on their own
The threads of time are spun back together
The world keeps changing along with us
(All of us) us, us
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
"The Will of Ohara!
The Inherited Research"
OHARA, WEST BLUE, 22 YEARS AGO
SEVERAL MONTHS AFTER THE BUSTER CALL
Good job protecting them.
You guys won...
It's a victory for Ohara!
Who is it and what is he doing here?
That's...
Pull it up!
The Giants?!
Why are they doing that?
Do they know
how valuable those books are?!
The books...
What are they gonna do with them?!
It hasn't changed.
Your head is distinctive.
I recognized it at first sight.
It's been a while, Vegapunk.
MONKEY D. DRAGON
LEADER OF THE FREEDOM FIGHTERS (AGE 33)
Dragon!
Your head has enlarged again.
DR. VEGAPUNK
HEAD OF THE PUNK HAZARD LAB (AGE 43)
Enough about that!
Why are you here?!
That's my question, Vegapunk.
I knew the old man Clover.
What? You, too?
Well...
He used to be a rascal
traveling around the world.
The nonsense about him
trying to destroy the world...
is a ridiculous disinformation campaign.
Yeah.
Are you wondering what they're doing?
I can't let them take away
those valuable books!
They're not bandits.
I've already checked them out.
What?
They came from Elbaph.
They know the value of the books.
Their captain is a strange man
with bandages all over his body...
He said, "Ohara saved their legacy
while sacrificing their lives,
and I won't let it be erased
from history."
I'm glad that you
and your World Government people
didn't find out about this
and destroy the books.
Hey, wait! I won't do that...
I thought it was a joke!
I can't believe you finally became
the Government's dog.
After you turned down our invitation
to join the Freedom Fighters.
Don't be a fool!
Even with my wisdom and skills,
what can I make
in a poor army like yours?!
I got it.
You're as honest as always.
The World Government
is a huge organization.
There are people who listen to you too,
especially in the marines.
Don't mistake your target, Dragon.
I know, but...
This incident hit me hard.
Harmless scholars who just questioned
the unreasonableness that is the law
were crushed by violence!
I will build an army that can fight!
But you despised war!
Just you wait, Vegapunk.
I'm gonna change the world!
I won't let Clover's death...
and the will of Ohara go in vain!
Later that year, Dragon teamed up with
Emporio Ivankov...
and Bartholomew Kuma...
to create the Revolutionary Army...
that now rocks the world!
Damn Iva... I didn't know he was a founding
member of the Revolutionary Army!
Luffy's dad is so passionate!
Wait a minute! Did you just say Elbaph?!
I feel like my brain's gonna explode!
Why did Kuma help us?!
I am an officer of the Revolutionary Army.
I have a connection with them,
and I want to help them get out of here.
Why did you modify Kuma?
Vegapunk!
I didn't know Dragon-san and Dr. Clover
had such a relationship!
The books of Ohara certainly
should not be found by the Government...
But I went to Elbaph in secret
out of my own interest...
And I read all the documents.
So...
the mystery of the world
that Ohara unraveled
lives on in my brain
and I've been working on that research.
Can I ask you something?
That strange man
with bandages all over his body...
Listen carefully, Robin!
You're alone now, but you'll
meet friends someday for sure!
That captain of the Giants
who hauled out the books from Ohara...
No one is born into this world
to be alone!
The name of the Giant captain is...
Saul, isn't it?
He is hiding now.
I must keep it a secret from everyone.
Thank you, Vegapunk,
for not letting the battle of
the people of Ohara be in vain.
I'm well versed in all branches of study.
It's the way of a true scholar.
What is it?!
The shoes are moving on their own!
I can't release you guys but follow me.
There's something I want to show you.
SCRAP HEAP, FABRIOPHASE
EGGHEAD
Cool! Guys, look!
I'm like Sanji!
Do you like my invention?
Yeah! You're impressive!
What?! Then he is the real Vegapunk?!
Yeah! But...
What happened to your head?!
It was bigger
and looked like a light bulb!
My head?
It had grown quite long so...
I cut it.
Don't say it like you cut your hair!
Indeed, at the time I met you,
I almost reached the height of a Giant!
I'd heard rumors that it was big...
It was like a balloon.
You cut your head and are still alive.
How is it possible?!
Well, actually I'm...
a Brain-Brain-Brain-Brain...
Ow, ow, ow... I bit my tongue...
I bit... my tongue...
Are you okay, old man?
Well, actually I'm...
a Brain-Brain Fruit user and a Brain-Man!
I can memorize all kinds of knowledge
without limit,
but my brain gets bigger and bigger
in proportion to the data capacity!
A data bank of unlimited capacity
on top of the brain of a genius
with which I was born!
It has grown into the biggest brain
in the world and is still growing!
Still? Is it somewhere else?
What are you talking about?
You cut your head, so you're stupid?
Don't mess with a genius, you little brat!
This apple...
is an antenna!
An antenna?
Look at the highest point of the island!
"Punk Records"
is written underneath the giant egg!
That's my brain storage!
What?!
Isn't it too big?!
Even when I'm away from it,
there's no problem at all
because I'm connected to it
by brain waves through this antenna!
That's awesome!
Are you acquainted with medicine too,
Dr. Vegapunk?!
Of course I am!
What?!
You guys met a girl earlier who identified
herself as Vegapunk, didn't you?
She punched me.
She's one of my clones
and there are six of them on the island!
Are you a ninja?!
Is it Shadow Clone Jutsu?! Nin, nin!
Each of them is an expert
in the fields I require!
Shaka is always calm and good!
01 GOOD (SHAKA)
The evil Lilith
is even willing to plunder!
02 EVIL (LILITH)
An inventor, Edison!
03 THINKER (EDISON)
The wise Pythagoras has an inquiring mind.
04 PYTHAGORAS (WISDOM)
Atlas's job is to be violent.
05 VIOLENCE (ATLAS)
"Eat Poop Sleep." The greedy York!
06 GREED (YORK)
The six of them together
comprise my personality.
But their work output
is six people's worth!
What are you talking about?
Once daily, they synchronize their
experience and knowledge via Punk Records.
Their personalities
and missions are different,
making each experience worthwhile!
You all share the same brain?
It's beyond my comprehension.
Just think of it as us
using the same library.
For example,
if anyone in the world
could have access to my brain,
it would be as if all humankind
had acquired my knowledge!
Furthermore, if all humankind can mutually
update Punk Records continuously...
...we can create a sea of knowledge
that far exceeds my brain!
All humankind can share
the same brain someday!
Does that mean I can study medicine
all over the world?
Of course!
I don't quite get it, but...
But wouldn't it be inconvenient
if ideology were to enter into it?
Good guess, "First Son of the Sea" Jimbei.
But if we worry about such things,
we can't advance science!
That nature of yours is the problem,
Vegapunk!
You're willing to sacrifice everything
for the sake of scientific inquiry!
That's why you
turned my father into a heartless weapon!
Stop, Bonney!
That beam saber is a failure!
Shut up! I've already tested it!
Relax, Bonney! Think about it!
Think how many people will
turn against you if you kill him!
I don't care!
Now change my father back!
If you say no...
Turn off the switch, Bonney!
Are you begging for your life?!
No!
That beam...
What's that?
What?
...attracts a lot of insects!
What's this place?
I'll explain later.
Look at this.
Luffy!
Good! They're all fine!
What are they doing?
Hey! Wake up!
Hey! Bonney!
A great stag beetle!
Cut it out! Why don't you
worry about her passing out?!
The weapon she picked up was a failure
and that saved my life...
But it's no wonder... No wonder...
Bonney wants to kill me.
I think she needs to rest for a while.
Oh yeah, you guys.
I heard you were in the Land of Wano
until recently.
Mm-huh.
Is it true that another dragon appeared
besides Kaido?
Yeah!
It's Momo!
It seems like that person ate a failed
Devil Fruit I left at Punk Hazard.
Oh yeah?
Failed?
That was a Devil Fruit
that I synthesized myself.
I spent 20 years
and a lot of research money
to create it
from Kaido's Bloodline Elements.
But it didn't turn out to be
a fruit of the same composition.
That's why he could transform like Kaido!
It wasn't a failure!
He breathes fire and is strong!
He's a guardian of the Land of Wano now!
So you created that! Impressive!
What was the color?
What was the dragon's color?
Pink.
See?! It's a big failure!
That doesn't matter...
I see. He's a genius and a perfectionist.
Then...
How about this robot?! Move it for us!
Is this your creation?!
No, it's not...
This is the legendary iron giant that is
said to have attacked Sacred Marijoa
200 years ago!
Vegapunk.
I'm here to eliminate you.
How far I have run
Without knowing it, I counted scars
A treasure map in my head all along
Still looking for the future
The real promise
Lies much deeper in my heart
A dream
That no one can catch up with
That's all I hold on to
To you who smiles like the sun
I'll sing the same song as that day
This wish I don't want to forget
Even when I grow up
Until it reaches you
"Dive into the Sea of Information!
The Punk Records Library!"
Hi, I'm Lilith one of the Satellites of
Dr. Vegapunk, the genius scientist!
I'm Edison, also Vegapunk!
In this segment, we'll introduce people
to look out for from Punk Records!
Today we'll introduce this one!
Monkey D. Dragon!
He's the Chief Commander of
the Revolutionary Army!
The Revolutionary Army is
an organization that seeks to dismantle
the World Government.
He's Marine Vice Admiral Garp's son
and Luffy's father.
But they don't look much alike.
He was born on October 5th
and likes bocaditos!
They're like sandwiches.
He apparently saved Luffy's life once, but
Luffy didn't see his face at that time.
He's from Goa Kingdom in the East Blue.
The inequality in his home
was one of the reasons
he founded the Revolutionary Army.
This country is an example of
how the world will be in the future.
There can be no happiness in a world
where the undesirables are thrown away.
Someday I will change the world!
By the way, it seems like he is the one
who saved Sabo in Goa Kingdom.
After the fall of the Donquixote family,
he summoned all leaders
of the Revolutionary Army.
They infiltrated the Holy Land
and declared war
against the Celestial Dragons!
That threw the whole world in tumult!
That's it for today!
See you next time!
The amazing scientific power
of 900 years ago
is revealed in front of the iron giant!
Vegapunk, who is fascinated
by the energy of a faraway antiquity
and who is overflowing
with ideas and ideals.
What lies ahead in the future
that he dreams of?
On the next episode of ONE PIECE!
"The Eccentric Dream of a Genius!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!