(All of us) us, us
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
The end of a dream, the end of the sea
We all have different places we want to go
But first, we need
To make a shining legend out of ourselves
Sparks fly, no limit
This is where it starts
ONE PIECE!!
All of us, I ask you travelers
Are your dreams still pure?
Sleepless cells are shaken and burst
Still, all of us
In the middle of an adventure
All of us, I tell you travelers
No such thing as a pointless fight
When random contexts
Start to make sense on their own
The threads of time are spun back together
The world keeps changing along with us
(All of us) us, us
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
"The World Is Shaken! The Ruler's Judgment
and the Five Elders' Actions!"
While the murder of King Cobra
was kept hidden,
the curtain came down on the Reverie.
He must still be around! Let's catch him!
Yes, sir!
King Cobra!
I...
cannot collapse here!
I must tell Luffy and Princess Vivi...
King Cobra's words!
Don't scare me like that...
Have you found them?
Cobra-sama hasn't returned
from his meeting with the Five Elders...
And we have no idea where Vivi-sama went.
What's going on in Mary Geoise?
I'm worried about
Cobra-sama's condition, too.
I'll search the castle one more time.
Thanks. I'll look for Vivi-sama.
Pell, search from the air.
Yes, sir.
Where are you?
Vivi-sama!
Let me see King Cobra!
We were told not to allow anyone in.
Please leave!
What's going on inside?
Our king is sick!
Cobra-sama!
Somebody!
Has anyone seen Princess Vivi of
the Kingdom of Alabasta?!
This is Princess Vivi! Have you seen her?!
Vivi-sama...
Where did you go?!
King Seki, Princess Comane.
Allow me to escort you to the ship
at the port.
-Hide!
-Yeah.
Jeez! It's just a cat!
Thank goodness.
Be more careful!
I didn't ask you to come with me,
so don't tell me what to do...
You're too loud!
Just leave me alone!
These ones next?
Let's hurry up!
That's a royal family's baggage.
Treat it with care.
Yeah!
Let's go, Wapol!
Hey!
What are we gonna do?!
Let's hide in those boxes.
What?!
It's a good idea, isn't it? Hurry up!
They'll find us! Hey!
Thanks for escorting them.
The marines will take over from here.
You're dismissed.
Thank you. Goodbye.
Now what?
King Tea IV is on board now!
Hurry up with bringing in the luggage!
Yeah!
We managed to sneak in.
It's safe for now...
But what should I do next?
I have to tell the world
what happened at the Reverie!
Shut up!
If you do that,
the Government will kill you!
Or should I turn you over
to marine soldiers?!
Try it.
But just like me,
you don't want to be found, do you?
Damn!
She's right...
Since I witnessed the dark side of
the Government...
I'm doomed!
Why do these things keep happening to me?!
Hey! Keep it down!
Oh, yeah! I'm sure he won't let me down.
Because I have the type of story
that he craves...
A Transponder Snail?!
I didn't know you had it! Can I borrow it?
No!
What a cheapskate!
This is my lifeline!
Ring, ring, ring...
Clank.
Mor-chan! It's me, Wapol!
Oh, it's been a while!
How was the Reverie?!
That's not important!
I bet something happened to you!
Tell me.
I can't talk about it over the Snail!
They'll kill me if they find out!
So I want you to harbor me
in exchange for my story!
All right.
Where are you now?
Hey! What country's ship is this?
The Eigis Kingdom.
Okay. We'll approach the ship
pretending to be researching a story.
Use that chance to get aboard ours.
Don't let anyone see you.
Thanks!
Clank.
This is exciting!
News so big
that a king's life is threatened!
I can't wait to hear it!
So what exactly did you see, Wapol?
I can't say it!
You're the last person
I want to tell about it!
Why don't you go back to your people?!
No. It was CP-0 who captured me.
Even if I meet up with my people,
they'll take me again by force.
So let me use your Transponder Snail!
I have to call my father.
He's always worried about me.
No! You can't do that!
That's the last thing you should do!
Why?! Let me just use it for a bit!
SHIP OF THE TAJINE KINGDOM
(SHIP'S HOLD)
I'm hungry...
SHIP OF THE KINGDOM OF LULUSIA
(SHIP BOTTOM)
Once I get to Lulusia,
everything'll be alright...
I'm counting on you, Sabo-kun!
Live on!
Vivi, Wapol...
and a few other stowaways
lurked on the ships...
that were taking various monarchs
back to their homes.
It didn't take long before the murder
of Cobra, King of the Kingdom of Alabasta,
and the disappearance of Princess Vivi
became known worldwide.
HOLY LAND MARY GEOISE
Sabo is another man with a strange fate.
No one is surrounded by "D"
more than he is.
It's time to put an end
to that Egghead matter...
Ring, ring, ring...
Clank.
Yes, Imu-sama.
I would like to use the Mother Flame
that Vegapunk invented.
Yes, if we don't try it, we'll never know
if that thing is real or not.
Let's figure out what to do with Egghead
based on the results of that experiment.
The testing site should be in areas
with forests rather than at sea...
The Kingdom of Lulusia.
Quite a lot of people live there.
It doesn't matter.
Understood.
The world should be
as the Creators want it to be.
Why did you choose Lulusia?
It's close.
You're right...
We'll make the necessary preparations.
We request your patience.
In Lulusia, there are signs of revolt
among the people.
This will serve as a good lesson
for everyone.
Eventually,
when we have that power at our disposal...
The long battle will come to an end.
One more thing.
Yes.
I want Vivi.
As you wish.
ST. JAYGARCIA SATURN
GODHEAD OF SCIENCE & DEFENSE
ST. MARCUS MARS
GODHEAD OF ENVIRONMENT
ST. TOPMAN WARCURY
GODHEAD OF JUSTICE
ST. ETHANBARON V. NUSJURO
GODHEAD OF FINANCE
ST. SHEPHERD JU PETER
GODHEAD OF AGRICULTURE
MARINE HEADQUARTERS, NEW WORLD
A report for Fleet Admiral Sakazuki!
There are revolts in the Tajine Kingdom
and the Eigis Kingdom
Just crush every last one of them!
Hurry up! Load ammo!
Deploy all the Seraphim!
Yes, sir! We'll launch the Seraphim.
The Marines were extremely busy with
the abolition of the Seven Warlords system
and the uprisings
in various affiliated countries.
However, this was also
the start of the new Marines.
What's going on?!
I can't believe
there's been one revolt after another!
Crocodile showed up
on the Emptee Bluffs Island!
Shoot, shoot!
Sables!
KAMABAKKA QUEENDOM
PEACHY ISLAND, GRAND LINE
As soon as
we arrived at the Kingdom of Lulusia,
King Seki and Princess Comane
got captured...
by the people who were waiting for them.
Shut up and just get me out of here!
I was a stowaway, but they welcomed me.
Well, that's because
you were their best hope.
That's when I saw the newspaper article
for the first time,
and learned that I was framed
for the King's murder.
Unsurprisingly,
people considered me a hero.
I wanted to tell the truth,
but I held my tongue.
Because I felt their growing thirst
for revolution.
Due to the influence of Betty and others,
there were many people in Lulusia
who wanted to join the Revolutionary Army,
and they're the ones I brought here.
What are you gonna do,
you pieces of trash?!
Get killed or fight?!
Choose your own destiny!
That's our Betty.
In the end, I couldn't get an Encryption
Transponder Snail in Lulusia,
so I wasn't able to call you.
But I made an indirect call as soon as
we sailed out, and that was the call.
Dragon-san!
King Cobra's assassin...
isn't me!
I'm sure the Government
eavesdropped on it,
and thought I was in Lulusia.
But in reality, I was already out at sea
with the enlistees.
You were on the call
when it happened, right?
The destruction of the Kingdom of Lulusia?
Yes...
There was panic on board.
So many people left their families behind.
They saw their home island
blown away in front of them!
That must have been tough.
What exactly happened?
A large shadow covered the sky above...
And the next moment, it was already...
A large shadow?
It can't be anything biological
or natural.
Something really dark
was flying over the clouds.
By the way, Sabo,
you mentioned Imu earlier, didn't you?
Yeah.
This may sound rather bizarre to you,
but among the First Twenty
who created this world 800 years ago,
there was a king named Saint Imu
from the Nerona Dynasty.
What?!
Look at this.
We know there is an ability
to make someone immortal in this world...
But this means that
someone has actually used it, right?
It's proof that there's a person out there
who doesn't know death!
Are you saying that's the person I saw?!
Maybe it's just a coincidence
that they have the same name...
But who else would the Five Elders
humble themselves to?
They're the highest authority
among the Celestial Dragons...
who flatter themselves
to be descendants of gods!
One more surprising thing!
If the thing that you saw
destroying the country from the clouds
was a Government weapon,
only Vegapunk
could have made such a thing!
Wait, Iva.
Vegapunk wouldn't make such a blatant tool
for killing people.
I know!
So what if it was an Ancient Weapon?!
If Imu is an ancient, living person,
it makes sense!
Robin confirmed the existence of
the Ancient Weapons.
But if they had it,
why didn't they use it until now?!
And why use it now?
Present day.
A Celestial Dragon has just been executed
in the Holy Land Mary Geoise today.
However,
it will never be reported to the world.
Good riddance-eh.
Because he sided with them,
fools in the lower world
have been pushing their luck recently-eh!
It's all his fault
that we lost our food supply-eh!
The judge was a man who was once active as
a champion on an island called God Valley.
He is now the Supreme Commander of
the Holy Knights.
St. Figarland Garling.
The one executed...
was the man who defended the Fish-Men.
St. Donquixote Myosgard.
Anyone who defends scum
is lower than scum they protect.
How far I have run
Without knowing it, I counted scars
A treasure map in my head all along
Still looking for the future
The real promise
Lies much deeper in my heart
A dream
That no one can catch up with
That's all I hold on to
To you who smiles like the sun
I'll sing the same song as that day
This wish I don't want to forget
Even when I grow up
Until it reaches you
"Dive into the Sea of Information!
The Punk Records Library!"
Hi, I'm Lilith, one of the Satellites of
Dr. Vegapunk, the genius scientist!
I'm Edison, also Vegapunk!
Today we'll introduce this one!
Nefertari Vivi!
She is the princess of
the Kingdom of Alabasta
and Nefertari Cobra's only daughter!
She was born on February 2nd
and likes curry, custard pudding,
and mulukhiyah!
When she learned of
the existence of Baroque Works,
which threatened the Kingdom of Alabasta,
she infiltrated the organization herself
to find out who the mastermind was.
She used the alias Ms. Wednesday.
After she started working with
the Straw Hats,
she returned to the Kingdom of Alabasta,
and together with them, she foiled
Crocodile's plot to overthrow the kingdom!
If we ever meet again some day...
will you call me your friend again?!
Vivi stayed in her beloved homeland, but
her ties to the Straw Hats remain deep!
Later, she was kidnapped by CP-0
in the Holy Land Mary Geoise,
but she managed to escape.
But I'm a little worried that
she'll still be targeted
by a lot of people in the future.
That's it for today!
Now that you've seen it,
donate to our research fund!
See you next time!