(All of us) a-su, a-su
(All of us) us, us
(Dream save us us) a-su, All of us
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
yume no hate umi no hate
The end of a dream, the end of the sea
ikitai basho wa sorezore da
We all have different places we want to go
dakedo hitotsu kagayakeru
But first, we need
densetsu wo buchiagete kara da
To make a shining legend out of ourselves
bachi bachi No limit koko kara ga
Sparks fly, no limit, this is where it starts
ONE PIECE!!
All of us tabibito ni tsugu
All of us, I ask you travelers
sono yume wa mada nigoccha inai ka?
Are your dreams still pure?
nemurenai saibou ga kusugurare hajiketeku
Sleepless cells are shaken and burst
ima mo All of us bouken no tochuu
Still, all of us, in the middle of an adventure
All of us tabibito e tsugu
All of us, I tell you travelers
imi no nai tatakai wa nain da
No such thing as a pointless fight
barabara no bunmyaku ga
When random contexts
ishi wo mochi tsunagareba
Start to make sense on their own
toki no ito ga tsumugi naosareru
The threads of time are spun back together
ore tachi to tomoni sekai kawari tsuzuketeru
The world keeps changing along with us
(All of us) a-su, a-su
(All of us) us, us
(Dream save us us) a-su, All of us
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
"Garp and Kuzan -
A Master and a Pupil's Beliefs Clash"
What is this?
That's impossible...
How could warships get so banged up?
Did they suffer a really powerful attack?
No...
Those are the Battleship Bags.
Commodore Brannew!
Battleship Bags?!
Those are the signs of someone using
the armor of the warships as punching bags.
What?!
Punching bags?!
Punching these warships?! No way!
Who did this?!
Young Vice Admiral Garp.
Vice Admiral Garp?!
It's his decades-long routine
which he continues today.
--He's still doing it?!
--Why are there two?!
The other one belongs to the vice admiral's pupil.
The former Admiral...
...Aokiji.
You can't use your Haki or Devil Fruit powers.
That's the rule of Battleship Bagging.
And they still end up this damaged?
The strength that those heroes have...
It's not something you're born with.
So noisy...
Alley-oop...
Gee...
You interrupted my nap, you little vermin.
I'm gonna crush you!
Do it!
Mr. Sanjuan Wolf was sent flying!
Garp is so scary!
Pull him out already or he'll drown!
What?!
How are we gonna pull that big guy out?!
--He beat that monster with one blow!
--He's unbelievable...
That's our Vice Admiral Garp!
That's what the Legendary Hero
is capable of!
I'm just getting started!
Listen, guys! Get psyched up!
Yes, sir!
Cut the Legendary Hero shit...
How dare you mess up our hideout.
How are you gonna pay for it?
Drunken Spitfire!
Pirate Fireballs!
Ow, it's hot! Stop it!
Are you trying to destroy this Pirate Island?!
If he sees the town messed up like this,
Commodore Teach will kill us!
Why doesn't he flinch at our numbers?!
That geezer is crazy!
Ring, ring, ring...
Clank.
I have a report, Vice Admiral Garp!
The people who were captured,
all our soldiers, and all the injured...
...have escaped the island.
Roger. Good job.
Hibari-chan, stay with me!
Let the frozen ones thaw slowly!
I wonder if Captain Koby is okay...
We can set out anytime!
Okay! We're done here! Let's retreat!
Koby! Grus! Helmeppo!
Yes, sir!
Got it!
Let's get out of here already!
This is indeed a beehive!
Pirates keep swarming out!
I see no end!
Like I said, I can't let you leave.
Garp-san.
I should have left earlier!
I'm gonna die! I can't take it!
Garp-san,
am I not the future of the Navy too?!
Do you still wanna fight, Kuzan?
Watch out for the top members of
the Blackbeard Pirates.
Listen, guys!
All we have to do now is
make it to the sea!
Don't die!
Yes, sir!
Somebody, help!
Oh no!
There was still a kidnapped person left!
I'll help you!
Thank goodness we haven't left yet!
No, fool! Don't go, Koby! It's a trap!
What?
Vice Admiral Garp...
Vice Admiral Garp!
You bastard!
W-Was he invisible?!
Shiryu...
You little hoodlum of Impel Down!
Wow! Shiryu-san did it!
He stabbed Iron Garp and weakened him!
Garp-san!
It's nothing! Just run to the ship!
It's my fault!
Vice Admiral Garp defended me and...
Don't be arrogant, Koby!
His target was me!
How persistent, you shitty geezer...
Garp has been weakened!
That's our Shiryu-san! He's awesome!
Even we can take him down now!
Let's go!
Kill him!
Go, go! The opportunity to get rich quick
is right in front of us!
Bring him down!
Garp has the Three-Crown Bounty,
the same as the admirals!
That's about 3 billion berries!
Kuzan-san!
Move, small fries!
Wait...
Even if his hands and feet are tied,
you guys aren't good enough...
...to kill Garp-san!
Ice Glove!
Garp-san.
Make me your pupil.
My pupil?
Yeah.
I like my freedom.
Just learn from the Navy's instructors.
I've learned all I can from them
so I wanna go to the next level.
Make me your pupil!
Shut up! Get lost!
Ow! That hurts...
Don't use your Haki!
Or you're not truly training.
I don't know how to use it yet.
I'm gonna do this!
Just what does the Navy consider
to be justice?
Ever since Ohara, I can't tell anymore.
My son became a revolutionary!
What?
Dammit!
Kuzan!
What's wrong?
JUSTICE
My grandson says
he wants to become a pirate!
--Whoa...
--I won't allow it!
That's got nothing to do with me!
Kuzan, let's have a snack.
I'm busy. I'm an admiral, remember?
Tea!
Gee!
You trained a troublesome enemy.
You're expelled. My stupid pupil.
Vice Admiral Garp!
Garp-san!
That's pretty good...
Let's defend Garp-san!
Yes, sir!
The chances of you guys
getting away are slim!
This is Beehive!
The more you poke,
the more pirates will swarm out!
If we can get out to sea...
Hibari!
Thank goodness you woke up!
Where's Koby-senpai?!
Sorry that I caused you trouble...
He'll return soon.
I'm glad that you're okay.
Do you think that the ship off the coast
is safe now?
What?
Don't underestimate
my Isle-Isle Fruit power-meow!
What now?!
Why is it shaking?!
What's... that?
The island is moving!
Huh? What's that?
All you see in the newspapers is
"Blackbeard this" "Blackbeard that"...
We wanna make a name for ourselves too!
The headline tomorrow morning
goes like this-meow!
"A young elite unit
led by the famous Vice Admiral Garp...
...attempted to rescue Captain Koby,
the Hero of the Navy!
But the captain of the Fourth Ship of
the Blackbeard Pirates, Avalo Pizarro's...
...terrifying power...
...tragically annihilated them...
...at the Pirate Island!"
No! Don't do it! Everyone's on board!
Even civilians!
Koby...
Don't lose your head...
Justice will always prevail!
How far I have run
doredake hashitte kita noka
Without knowing it, I counted scars
wakaranai mama kizuato kazoeta
A treasure map in my head all along
zutto atama no naka ni aru takara no chizu
Still looking for the future
mirai wo sagashi tsuzuketeru
The real promise
hontou no yakusoku wa
Lies much deeper in my heart
mune no oku no motto oku ni aru
A dream that no one can catch up with
dare mo mina oitsukenai yume
That's all I hold on to
tada hitotsu dakishimete
To you who smiles like the sun
taiyou no youni warau anata e
I'll sing the same song as that day
ano hi to onaji uta wo utau yo
This wish I don't want to forget even when I grow up
otona ni nattemo wasuretakunai
Until it reaches you
kono negai ga todoku made
"Dive into the Sea of Information!
The Punk Records Library!"
Hi, I'm Lilith, one of the Satellites of
Dr. Vegapunk, the genius scientist!
I'm Edison, also Vegapunk!
Today we'll introduce this one!
Kuzan A.K.A. Aokiji!
He is a former Navy admiral!
He uses the Logia type
Chilly-Chilly Fruit...
...which enables him to transform into ice
and freeze anything he touches!
He was born on September 21st
and likes coffee, dairy milk,
and sherry wine!
He once felt threatened
by the Straw Hats' growth
and tried to annihilate them.
If I mess with the others now,
I'd be the senseless one here...
...right, Captain?
He seems to be a man who always honors his word,
even when dealing with pirates.
After the Paramount War, to determine
Fleet Admiral Sengoku's successor,
he fought a duel against Sakazuki.
When he was defeated, he left the Navy
and, to everyone's surprise,
joined the Blackbeard Pirates.
So when Garp came to rescue Koby
from captivity on the Pirate Island of Beehive,
he and Kuzan came to blows.
I'm on the edge of my seat to see
how their battle plays out!
That's it for today!
Oh, now we've got so much money
for the research fund!
So this segment is over for now!
See you!
Avalo Pizarro's giant hand
comes down on the Navy ship!
Leaving the rest to his disciples,
Garp shows the way with a powerful blow.
Accepting his master's wishes,
Koby's true power awakens!
The young fist that lights the future
now rattles Beehive.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Last Lesson! Impact Inherited"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!