(All of us) us, us
(All of us) a-su, a-su
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
(Dream save us us) a-su, All of us
The end of a dream, the end of the sea
yume no hate umi no hate
We all have different places we want to go
ikitai basho wa sorezore da
But first, we need
dakedo hitotsu kagayakeru
To make a shining legend out of ourselves
densetsu wo buchiagete kara da
Sparks fly, no limit, this is where it starts
bachi bachi No limit koko kara ga
ONE PIECE!!
All of us, I ask you travelers
All of us tabibito ni tsugu
Are your dreams still pure?
sono yume wa mada nigoccha inai ka?
Sleepless cells are shaken and burst
nemurenai saibou ga kusugurare hajiketeku
Still, all of us, in the middle of an adventure
ima mo All of us bouken no tochuu
All of us, I tell you travelers
All of us tabibito e tsugu
No such thing as a pointless fight
imi no nai tatakai wa nain da
When random contexts
barabara no bunmyaku ga
Start to make sense on their own
ishi wo mochi tsunagareba
The threads of time are spun back together
toki no ito ga tsumugi naosareru
The world keeps changing along with us
ore tachi to tomoni sekai kawari tsuzuketeru
(All of us) us, us
(All of us) a-su, a-su
(Dream save us us) us, all of us
(Dream save us us) a-su, All of us
A FEW WEEKS AGO
AMAZON LILY, ISLAND OF WOMEN
Stop!
Let's have a lot of fun!
Walk faster!
Stop! Let us go!
I don't know what they'll do to us
once we're taken to the Pirate Island!
I didn't expect Rayleigh to interrupt,
but in the end,
we got some good souvenirs.
Vice Admiral, can't we do anything
about our comrades being taken away?
Are we gonna let our men down?
We haven't gotten permission from above.
We're up against an Emperor of the Sea.
But...
What can I do...
...to save them?
JUSTICE
Captain Koby!
Vice Admiral! He's a SWORD member!
SWORD...
Hey, Koby the Hero!
What do you want?
You want your friends back?
We don't mind an all-out war.
You're now trying to take away
800 Navy soldiers and a warship.
Will you let me trade myself
for their release?
You think very highly of yourself!
But your life is worth it.
Lesson one.
A geezer and a baby are stranded
on an island full of beasts of prey.
You rush in to rescue them alone,
but only one other person can fit on that boat.
What are you gonna do?
FORMER NAVY HQ
Umm... First,
I will get the baby on the boat.
No, but then the old man can't...
What are you waiting for? Hurry up or
you'll all get killed and devoured.
Umm...
Oh, yeah!
Okay! I'll get off the boat
and let the old man and the baby on board!
Then they'll both...
You idiot!
Ouch!
Wrong answer!
Gee. Remember this!
The geezer only has
a short time ahead of him...
TA-DAH!
So abandon him!
What?!
Hey! Vice Admiral Garp!
What did you guys join the Navy to save?
What...
...did you guys join the Navy...
...to save?
"The Last Lesson!
Impact Inherited"
What's going on?!
What the hell is that?!
PRESENT DAY, PIRATE ISLAND OF BEEHIVE
Shoot! Shoot!
Cannonfire does nothing?!
We gotta get away!
Full speed ahead!
I'm not gonna let you escape!
What terrifying power...
If a huge hand like that
comes down on them,
hundreds of soldiers and civilians
will die!
It's impossible! We can't stop it!
Prepare to dive into the sea!
Those inside, go on deck
and protect the civilians!
This is my fault!
Everyone's going to die because of me!
Was I wrong in my decision?
I haven't saved anyone yet!
I can't save anyone!
What should I...
What should I do?!
You guys can...
...save them!
Vice Admiral Garp!
Guys...
Listen.
I'll create an opening!
First, Captain Koby...
Destroy the island monster's hand!
What?! How can I...
Rear Admiral Grus, protect the ship
from the debris of the hand!
Lieutenant Commander Helmeppo,
don't let anyone stand in the way of those two!
Anyone?!
Vice Admiral Garp! But that's...
Decisions must always be
made in an instant!
Jump!
Yes, sir!
Koby and the others are on the move!
It's no use! What can you do without Garp?!
You'll all be sunk into the sea!
There they come!
Helmeppo! Take care of them!
What?! Me?!
You heard what Vice Admiral Garp said!
Damn it! Why is it always me?!
Bring it on!
That's too many!
Too many! Oh, too many!
Hey, Koby! He told you to destroy it.
Do you have a bomb or something?!
No, I don't!
But I gotta figure something out!
Figure something out?!
It's big enough to hold
and crush a warship!
I know!
I won't let you escape, Koby!
Oh, no!
Koby!
Don't let anyone stand in the way of those two!
Oh, come on!
I'll leave you...
CHORE BOY
...the rest!
Go away!
Helmeppo-san!
Don't look back, Koby!
--But...
--You gotta keep going!
Now...
Garp-san, where do you think you're going?
You're heavily injured.
This is just a scratch.
I'm worried about you...
You're too soft!
Garp! Why is he coming this way?!
Wait! Don't you care
what'll happen to the ship?!
Galaxy...
...Divide!
The arm is recoiling!
So this is what he meant by an "opening"?
That made the arm go up!
What are you gonna do, Koby?!
Vice Admiral... Garp!
Why?! I'm not worthy enough to save...
Koby is the future of the Navy!
I won't disappoint you!
Koby!
You bastard!
That's not enough to stop me, Garp!
I'm really pissed off-meow!
Watch closely!
As your men die!
I'll kill them all-meow!
Here it comes again!
You can't save them in time-meow!
Hey, Helmeppo.
Koby progresses quickly
but is often injured.
Koby's injury...
Oh... He told me not to tell you, but...
I'm not as good a fighter as the others,
so 10 times isn't enough!
I have to train myself 100 times
or 200 times harder than them...
...to be a good Navy soldier
who can protect someone!
You fool!
That's enough!
You need to stop now!
Boy... So he's been training by himself
on top of my training?
Yes, he's been doing it every night.
Punching the Battleship Bag...
...with his fists...
...covered in blood.
Gotta make it in time!
Gotta make it!
I gotta make it in time!
Is that...
Koby-senpai!
Captain Koby!
Look! It's Koby!
Is he trying to stop the hand?!
It's impossible!
He's like an ant to that hand!
People call him the Hero,
so that stupid brat is pushing his luck!
Koby-senpai! It's dangerous up there!
Get away, Koby-kun!
Watch as the ship gets smashed
and the soldiers scream as they die!
Even if they dive into the sea,
Aokiji will freeze them!
Serves you right!
People will die because of me.
I gotta destroy it!
If I don't, they'll all die!
I'm not as good a fighter as the others,
so 10 times isn't enough!
I have to train myself 100 times
or 200 times harder than them!
What did you guys join the Navy to save?
Koby!
Too late! Abandon ship!
You guys can save them!
Honesty...
...Impact!
When did he gain such a power?!
That's amazing!
But what should we do about the debris?
I'll protect the ship from the debris!
Glorp Web!
Koby!
Koby! I can't believe you did it!
Helmeppo-san...
I did it...
You're unbelievable!
So unbelievable!
You broke that huge mountain of an arm!
Let's go home, you fool!
Captain Koby!
Helmeppo!
I'm glad that you're alive!
Koby-senpai!
Hibari-san...
I'm glad.
I'm so glad you're okay.
Now all we need to do is
get Vice Admiral Garp on board and go.
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Clank.
This is Garp.
The mission to rescue Captain Koby
is complete.
Vice Admiral Garp!
Thank goodness!
Hurry up and come back to the ship!
Just...
...go ahead and leave Beehive.
What?
What are you talking about, Garp-san?!
I'm gonna be fine.
The top priority is the safety of you all.
Am I right?
No, but...
Prince, turn the ship around...
Our success here...
...will pose a threat to all pirates.
Please let me join the Navy!
I'm happy to do odd jobs or anything like that
if I can become a Navy soldier!
What did you guys join the Navy to save?
It's the future of the people, isn't it?!
In that case, you guys got
more time to live than a geezer!
Take the baby...
...and live on!
Keep going.
You guys are the future...
...of the Navy!
Clank.
Vice Admiral Garp!
Don't ever give a lecture like that!
All lives are equal!
The future of the young people
is limitless!
The next day, newspapers reported...
...the survival of the young naval hero,
Captain Koby,
the disappearance of Vice Admiral Garp,
the Legendary Hero, on the Pirate Island,
and the Emperor of the Sea,
Straw Hat Luffy, barricading himself...
...on the Future Island Egghead.
STRAW HATS
How far I have run
doredake hashitte kita noka
Without knowing it, I counted scars
wakaranai mama kizuato kazoeta
A treasure map in my head all along
zutto atama no naka ni aru takara no chizu
Still looking for the future
mirai wo sagashi tsuzuketeru
The real promise
hontou no yakusoku wa
Lies much deeper in my heart
mune no oku no motto oku ni aru
A dream that no one can catch up with
dare mo mina oitsukenai yume
That's all I hold on to
tada hitotsu dakishimete
To you who smiles like the sun
taiyou no youni warau anata e
I'll sing the same song as that day
ano hi to onaji uta wo utau yo
This wish I don't want to forget even when I grow up
otona ni nattemo wasuretakunai
Until it reaches you
kono negai ga todoku made
ORIGINAL STORY BY EIICHIRO ODA
WEEKLY SHONEN JUMP (SHUEISHA) SERIES
ORIGINAL CONCEPT BY TOMOHITO OSAKI
THE STRAW HAT STORIES
Dear Nami-san,
please keep having wonderful adventures!
The Straw Hat Crew
reunites at Sabaody Archipelago today!