One Dream One Wish
kanaetai nara Over The Top
If you want to make it
come true, Over The Top
ONE PIECE - LAND OF WANO ARC
mitakoto mo nai sekai mezashi
Setting out into the unknown world
araburu namikaze koete
Weathering rough wind and waves
tsukisusumanakya dame sa
ichibannori shitain da
I have to keep going because
I want to get there first
shinpai toka atomawashi
douse shoubu ichika bachika
Worry later since it's
all sink or swim anyway
aite ga dekaku mietara
When your opponent looks daunting
kokoro ga chijinderu shouko
It's a sign that your heart is shrinking
nigeru nante choisu wa nai
Running away is not a choice
ippo soba e chikadukun da
Take one step closer
namaiki tte homekotoba?
Being called insolent's a compliment, right?
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
When things become tough,
that's when you should laugh
atarashii ashita sagashi ni ikitai no nara
If you want to look for a new tomorrow
tobikkiri no jishin wo migaite
Polish your unique confidence
tabi wo shita ashiato ga
Until your footsteps
sou! chizu ni kawaru made
Yes! Become a map
atarashii Horizon hora susunde kita bun
A new horizon, look, how far you've come
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
It's brighter and the
level of difficulty rises
yumeutsutsu de okose Hurricane
Live in your dream and raise a hurricane
saa! chaato kakimidase
Now! Stir up the rankings
One Dream One Wish
yume wa nigenai... zenbu Knock out
Dreams don't run away... Knock everything out
Over The Top
Let go of me!
From the town of leftovers,
Otama has been kidnapped by Shogun Orochi's men.
Big Bro!!
Tama!
Tama!!
A notebook?
There are three Headliners in that town.
Hawkins.
Holdem.
Speed.
How could you tame the savage baboon?!
My men saw you do it!
Don't try to pretend that you don't know!
It must be none other than
a real Devil Fruit power.
Come on...
Spit it out!
To save Otama,
Luffy and the others go into action.
I believe they said you tore
part of your cheek off.
If you're not gonna tell me...
Let's give that a try.
Hey, bring me some pincers!
Yes, sir!
Not that one! The bigger one!
Big Bro Luffy...
Don't do it...!
If you don't want me to, show your ability!
Tama!
"The Yokozuna Appears!
The Invincible Urashima Goes After Okiku!"
Tama!
FRONT ENTRANCE OF BAKURA TOWN
KURI, LAND OF WANO
We're here to save you!
No!
Luffytaro-san!
You can't do that!
Hey!
Stop right there!
Don't start a fuss!
Why?!
There's no record of them
leaving the town.
Hey, who are you guys?!
Everyone in this town is in league with
Otama-chan's kidnappers.
If we make a bigger scene,
it might put Otama-chan in danger.
I see.
What?!
Did you do something?!
That was Haki!
Haki?
Haki of the Color of the Supreme King!
That's a huge lion-dog!
Who owns it?
How do we find the brat named Otama?
The people of the town won't tell us
even if we ask them.
They're all under Orochi's influence.
But there are ordinary people
who don't seem likely to fight.
The townspeople have always been here.
Until 20 years ago,
this was a vibrant castle town.
But one day, Orochi's subordinates
came and seized the houses they liked.
Then everyone except for
the merchants deemed essential...
...was kicked out of the town...
That's the truth behind this Bakura Town.
A sumo wrestler? How did he...?
Something's going on inside the town.
A sumo wrestler came flying out...
So I suppose it's a sumo match.
As expected, is there no one
who can take down Urashima?!
If you can fit into the ring,
I don't care how many there are...
I'm gonna fight you all at once!
Today, we're having
a special exhibition match!
If anyone can take down Urashima,
he'll win the unbelievable sum of 500 Gold coins!
PEACE REIGNS OVER THE LAND
--Those two men at once may pull it off!
--I'll bet on the challengers this time!
Me, too!
Urashima-sama!
Good luck!
Time is up! Hands down...
Ready...
Go!
He's immovable!
You guys are so weak!
The match's over!
Urashima!
Once again, is there no one
who can take down...
...the yokozuna of the
Flower Capital, Urashima!
URASHIMA
A YOKOZUNA OF THE LAND OF WANO'S GRAND SUMO
Another bunch of weaklings-pe.
Again...
Sumo, huh? It should be fun!
The number of wrestlers
who fought against Urashima...
...is 19 now.
But the number of bones that have been
broken is...
10 arm bones.
15 leg bones.
52 ribs.
4 skulls and...
...7 backbones!
It's 88 bones in total
and 4 wrestlers are missing!
Overwhelming!!
His strength is unhuman!
The undefeated monster!
The Yokozuna Urashima!!
Take down Urashima!
I'll bet on you guys!
You can do it, guys!
We have the perfect plan!
We'll get the prize!
--Beat that jerk!
--Urashima-sama!
Oh! Look at this!
Ready...
Go!
Okiku!
I knew you were gonna come!
So you've decided to be my wife, right?!
Excuse me.
There's no way you can hide behind me.
I can't believe it!
There is a woman who is engaged
to be married to Urashima!
How lucky!
She's loved by a yokozuna!
This is big news!
Hey!
Okiku!
My wife!
What?! Urashima-zeki's wife?!
That woman is his wife?!
I wish I were her!
His wife?
No...
As you saw earlier,
it's just his belief I'm going to marry him.
Okiku! I'll have a match
in Bakura Town later-pe!
I'll show you how strong I am
so come see if you're interested!
I have a mind of my own.
I see.
You guys!
We're looking for someone!
She's a little girl named Tama!
Tell me where this town's boss is!
She should be there!
That woman! How frustrating!
She gets to marry a man of wealth!
She's huge but just right for Urashima!
I'd be a better match!
They're not listening...
Okiku came to see me.
Guys, bring her to me!
Yes, sir!
Big Bro!
I didn't know you were good with girls!
I wanna be like you!
No wonder she fell for you!
Okiku!
Okay, we're gonna look for her ourselves!
Let's go!
Lady! Big Bro Urashima wants you!
Come with us!
Who are you fools?! Out of our way!
Kick their asses!
Don't get in our way!
What?!
Nice charge!
I guess the winning technique was
a frontal thrust out...
Come with me, lady!
No... Please stop!
Are you gonna cut up an unarmed naked man?
Ya-hoo!
One, two! One, two! One, two! One, two!
Kiku!
Outta my way!
Hey, Zoro!
How could you let them take her away?!
I'm sorry...
I thought that it wasn't right to...
...slash a naked man.
And...
...she's not just a teahouse waitress.
I (sessha) am...
...a samurai.
Come into my arms-pe!
Hey! She's a girl from the teahouse
in the other town!
With her rank,
it's presumptuous of her to even enter this town!
Is that so?!
Then you gotta kick her out!
She's a vulgar tramp!
Shut up, you commoners!
To us samurai-class,
you fools are all the same, vulgar, lowly bastards-pe!
Your worthless lives...
Whether to spare them or take them...
...is my choosing!
So, Okiku!
Why don't you...
...be...
...mine?!
I (sessha) don't know anyone
who is called...
...a lowly bastard!
Stop your joking.
The only vulgar thing here is your heart.
The yokozuna's topknot!
So cool!
Kiku is so daring!
It's getting exciting!
The yokozuna...
Urashima...
He got rejected by a woman...
...and had his topknot chopped off!
Now we don't have to look for the brat...
This is a quick way to bring their boss!
Okiku!
You...
...betrayed me!
Why did I do that...
...in front of others?!
He's looking like a fierce god!
Okiku!
--Oh, no! That pose is...!
--His Far Bank Slap that sends opponents flying!
Please forgive me, Urashima-sama.
But...
I knew you were the kind of man
who would hit a woman...
Die!
You vulgar, lowly tramp!
Gum-Gum...
...Sumo Slap!
A sumo match between Urashima,
the yokozuna from the Land of Wano, and Luffy.
The enraged Urashima's continuous
slaps rush at Luffy!
But then, Luffy's killer technique
blasts in the heated ring!
In the hard bout that draws
everyone's attention,
which of them will be declared the winner?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Climactic Sumo Battle!
Straw Hat vs. the Strongest Ever Yokozuna!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!