One Dream One Wish
kanaetai nara Over The Top
If you want to make it
come true, Over The Top
ONE PIECE - LAND OF WANO ARC
mitakoto mo nai sekai mezashi
Setting out into the unknown world
araburu namikaze koete
Weathering rough wind and waves
tsukisusumanakya dame sa
ichibannori shitain da
I have to keep going because
I want to get there first
shinpai toka atomawashi
douse shoubu ichika bachika
Worry later since it's
all sink or swim anyway
aite ga dekaku mietara
When your opponent looks daunting
kokoro ga chijinderu shouko
It's a sign that your heart is shrinking
nigeru nante choisu wa nai
Running away is not a choice
ippo soba e chikadukun da
Take one step closer
namaiki tte homekotoba?
Being called insolent's a compliment, right?
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
When things become tough,
that's when you should laugh
atarashii ashita sagashi ni ikitai no nara
If you want to look for a new tomorrow
tobikkiri no jishin wo migaite
Polish your unique confidence
tabi wo shita ashiato ga
Until your footsteps
sou! chizu ni kawaru made
Yes! Become a map
atarashii Horizon hora susunde kita bun
A new horizon, look, how far you've come
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
It's brighter and the
level of difficulty rises
yumeutsutsu de okose Hurricane
Live in your dream and raise a hurricane
saa! chaato kakimidase
Now! Stir up the rankings
One Dream One Wish
yume wa nigenai... zenbu Knock out
Dreams don't run away... Knock everything out
Over The Top
Move out of my way!
I have to tear Okiku into bits...
Otherwise I'll lose face!
Okay! No problem!
Well then...!
Dosukoi!
If you can beat me!
What?!
In order to protect Okiku, Luffy confronted Urashima,
a yokozuna of the Land of Wano's grand sumo.
Meanwhile, captured by Holdem, a Headliner of
the Beast Pirates, Otama was in danger.
Stop chasing after ghosts forever...
The Kozuki were an evil clan...
...that tried to destroy the Land of Wano
two decades ago!
Although his opponent was the
undefeated monster, Urashima,
Luffy didn't give in an inch
and the bout heated up.
And then...
Gum-Gum...
...Giant...
...Sumo Slap!
Dosukoi!
"Luffy Rages!
Rescue Otama from Danger!"
Hey!
Bring the boss of this town!
We're here to take back Tama!
He's...
Hey, take a good look!
It's no mistake.
He's...
They're rebels!
Boss!
We have a group of lowlife rebels here!
The magistrate killer,
Zorojuro, is with them!
Fear not.
I'm on my way.
One of them has a straw
hat on his neck, right?
Y-Yes, sir!
Don't fight them.
You guys are no match for them!
How could you do that to the yokozuna?!
--You're just a lowly bastard!
--I'll teach you a lesson!
Is Tama the brat who
Holdem-sama has captive?!
You want her back?! Bring it on!
I just had a sumo match
and now it's a sword fight?!
Fight them!
Give us back Tama!
He threw it again!
Tama!
What should I do?!
Don't play innocent.
I'm not gonna help you!
I don't know anyone
who is called...
...a lowly-bastard!
Should I... c-cut people, too?
Cut them!
If you wanna save the brat!
Otama-chan...
I want to save her!
Give us back Tama!
If you don't bring her here soon...
You'll all be dead!
Get out of my way!
OKOBORE TOWN, KURI
There's a commotion in the other town...
I'm hungry!
Stop! You're embarrassing yourself!
A man from the Land of Wano must not whine!
I'm hungry!
Don't cry, don't cry.
Otsuru-san!
--Otsuru-san, do you have any Evil-Purging Herbs?!
--What?
My child drank the river water
purely out of hunger!
Oh my!
Come on in!
PARADISE FARM AT THE FAR END OF BAKURA TOWN
It's time to collect!
Put your harvest on the pallet!
S-Sir...
Oh, you want this?
F-Five Silver coins?!
When you're done, go out the back way!
And slink home to Okobore Town!
Please!
This isn't enough to feed my family for a week!
We can't even buy water!
Shut up! Don't complain!
What's the name of your boss?!
Bo... Ho... H-Holdem...
Ho... Ho... Holdem...
"Ball-de-boo"?
Get the firefighters!
Fire! A fire broke out!
Show yourself! Ball-de-boo!
If you harm Tama,
I won't forgive you!
Who is it?! Who is
responsible for this mess?!
What's this smoke?
Holdem-sama, are you okay?!
Yokozuna?!
The one who sent him flying
was the magistrate-killer Zorojuro's ally.
What?!
Where are you, Ball-de-boo?!
Show yourself, Ball-de-boo!
Just come out already!
Big Bro!
So that's him!
He's acting like he owns the place
and it's pissing me off!
It's unforgivable!
Big Bro!
Show yourself! Ball-de-boo!
Bring Tama here!
Ball-de-boo!
It's...
...Holdem!
Ball-de-boo!
Open the gate!
As usual, we have so many kinds of
delicious-looking food today!
That's right, Speed-sama.
Why don't you look it all over?
The food is behind you!
--I can see it!
--What?
Because...
...my range of vision...
...is 350 degrees!
--You're like a horse!
--You think so?
You smile like a horse, too!
SPEED - A HEADLINER OF THE BEAST PIRATES
WITH THE HORSE SMILE FRUIT
The fire bell?
Fire! Fire!
--Clear the way!
--Move! Move!
We, of the group one I-gumi, claim this fire!
This place...
Put out the fire!
This is Holdem's house...
Why has it been destroyed like this?!
It's behind you, Speed-sama!
I can see it.
I have a wide range of vision like a horse.
I thought there was a sumo event today...
What's going on?
Don't keep us waiting!
Ball-de-boo! Give us back Tama!
Ball-de-boo!
I'm right here, boy!
So you're this town's boss...
...Ball-de-boo! Am I right?!
My name is Holdem!
Holdem-sama!
Kick his ass!
You finally showed yourself!
I had no option!
How could you destroy my house
with a sumo wrestler?!
Giant...
...Sumo Slap!
Dosukoi!
Urashima crashed into my house
and it's in ruins!
Who are you bastards?!
Big Bro!
Tama!
Otama-chan!
You guys stand against us...
...because you work under
Shutenmaru the thief?!
You shouldn't have messed
around in Bakura Town!
Shutenmaru?
What are you talking about?
Shutenmaru...
You fools!
Seems like you want this brat back...
But first, don't move!
He can chew her up anytime!
Big Bro...
Tama...
He has a lion in his stomach...
Holdem-sama is talking to
the straw-hat guy now!
A battle could break out at any minute!
Boss! What are your orders?!
I'll be there soon!
I'm in front of Bakura Town!
Captain, Hawkins is at the entrance!
And there was a fire in the town.
The cause of the fire is...
Captain, don't abandon me...
Don't tell me it's him.
Yeah, I see Straw Hat...
Huh?!
Big Bro!
I'll save you now, Tama!
I won't give her back to you!
Idiot!
Those fools...
When Holdem takes a flaming blow,
Otama sees the shadow of the man who she misses!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Taking Back Otama! A Fierce
Fight Against Holdem!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Get ready for the origin of One Piece,
written by Eiichiro Oda!
The One Piece 20th anniversary special program!
"Romance Dawn"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!