One Dream One Wish
kanaetai nara Over The Top
If you want to make it
come true, Over The Top
ONE PIECE - LAND OF WANO ARC
mitakoto mo nai sekai mezashi
Setting out into the unknown world
araburu namikaze koete
Weathering rough wind and waves
tsukisusumanakya dame sa
ichibannori shitain da
I have to keep going because
I want to get there first
shinpai toka atomawashi
douse shoubu ichika bachika
Worry later since it's
all sink or swim anyway
aite ga dekaku mietara
When your opponent looks daunting
kokoro ga chijinderu shouko
It's a sign that your heart is shrinking
nigeru nante choisu wa nai
Running away is not a choice
ippo soba e chikadukun da
Take one step closer
namaiki tte homekotoba?
Being called insolent's a compliment, right?
When things become tough,
that's when you should laugh
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
If you want to look for a new tomorrow
atarashii ashita sagashi ni ikitai no nara
Polish your unique confidence
tobikkiri no jishin wo migaite
Until your footsteps
tabi wo shita ashiato ga
Yes! Become a map
sou! chizu ni kawaru made
A new horizon, look, how far you've come
atarashii Horizon hora susunde kita bun
It's brighter and the
level of difficulty rises
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
Live in your dream and raise a hurricane
yumeutsutsu de okose Hurricane
Now! Stir up the rankings
saa! chaato kakimidase
One Dream One Wish
Dreams don't run away... Knock everything out
yume wa nigenai... zenbu Knock out
Over The Top
Bring the boss of this town!
We're here to take back Tama!
In order to take back Otama
who has been kidnapped,
Luffy, Zoro, and Okiku go into action.
Don't keep us waiting!
Ball-de-boo! Give us back Tama!
I'm right here, boy!
So you're this town's boss...
...Ball-de-boo! Am I right?!
My name is Holdem!
You finally showed yourself!
I had no option!
How could you destroy my house
with a sumo wrestler?!
Big Bro!
I'll save you now, Tama!
I won't give her back to you!
Idiot!
Meanwhile, noticing that there was trouble,
Hawkins and Law...
...were simultaneously heading
to Bakura Town.
Those fools...
"Taking Back Otama!
A Fierce Fight Against Holdem!"
Big Bro!
Tama! I'll save you right now!
Save her?!
How would you save her?! Hmm?!
Don't move!
If you resist,
this brat's body will be chewed up by...
...Kamijiro the lion in my stomach!
KAMIJIRO - HOLDEM'S STOMACH
Otama-chan! We'll save you now!
Let go of Tama, Ball-de-boo!
Or I'm gonna kick your ass!
Like I said, my name is Holdem!
Say it right already!
Big Bro!
Okiku-chan!
Komachiyo!
Just say whatever you like, fool!
I'm not gonna give her back to you!
Why do you want this stupid brat back
so bad?!
I guess that you know about her ability!
I'll hold you guys hostage,
and catch Shutenmaru, too!
Who's that?
Shutenmaru...
Don't play dumb!
He's the head of your thieves brigade!
The robberies at the farm these days...
...are the work of you Atamayama Thieves Brigade,
aren't they?!
Even if it was by sheer dumb luck,
you took down Urashima.
So I bet you're one of his
important subordinates!
What are you talking about?
Luffytaro-san...
Please try to not make him mad.
He's quite angry already!
That's why you shouldn't provoke him anymore!
He's strong, too, but...
...who the townspeople are really afraid of
isn't Holdem himself...
...but a person who has his back.
The Beast Pirates...
...Kaido's right-hand man...
Jack the Drought...
...is the true ruler of Kuri!
Isn't he the one who destroyed Zou?
What? Oh, that guy!
He used poison against that Cat and Dog...
In the end,
the elephant sent him flying, right?
Jack sank into the sea along with his ship!
Didn't he die?
Cat? Dog? Elephant?
Are you talking about animals?
So you know Jack was involved
in a marine accident!
He's most certainly not dead!
He showed up here in Bakura Town
several days ago.
What?!
If you make Holdem mad now
and Jack who is known as a Disaster
comes to retaliate,
this town will be in ruins.
We can't let that happen!
That's not fair!
It's like they're holding
the whole town hostage!
Hey!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
What are you guys talking about
over there?!
What's wrong?
Why don't you try to take back
this little brat?!
But if you move even an inch...
This is what will happen!
It hurts!
Stop it! You bastard!
Ah, the sweet, anguished cries of the lowly!
Don't forget that you tossed that yokozuna
and destroyed my house!
TREASURE
What's going on, Holdem?!
It's Speed-sama's food treasure ship!
It's our grub for today!
I'm starving!
That's a lot of food!
That's food from the Paradise Farm...
It was grown with clean water
so it's non-poisonous.
Why do they get to keep it all?!
Zoro! Could you handle that?!
Okay...
What?
I'll save Tama!
What? What?!
Kiku! I'm sorry but
we've decided to steal it and run.
What? When did you...?
I'm sure it'll piss him off
but it's better than kicking his ass, right?
Hawkins-san!
They're out of our league!
Where's Holdem?
He's in a mess at the
plaza in the 4th district!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
He's not picking up. Holdem.
I need you to stop here, Basil Hawkins!
Who are you?
He's strong...
We're in this isolated Land of Wano
cut off from the outer world,
but he knows our faces...
So I'd better make him disappear!
Now...
...it was fun talking to you but it's over!
From here,
the real fun starts!
I don't care if you happen to
kill one or two of them in the process!
Catch them right now!
Hey, woman!
You remember that
we have this brat as a hostage, right?!
Luffytaro-san... Zorojuro-san...
--Why...
--Look what you've done!
Oh, I see now!
You don't need the brat back, right?!
Then, I'll have her chewed up as you wish!
Go ahead, Kamijiro!
What?!
The brat's gone!
Huh?! When did he get her?!
Kamijiro! What the hell are you doing?!
B-Big Bro?!
Big Bro...
Big Bro!
He's coming this way!
Don't tell me he...
Stop him!
Protect the treasure ship at any cost!
Let's get out of here, Tama!
Big Bro...
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Komachiyo!
You bastard!
Kamijiro!
I'll chop you up with a flaming sword!
No one's ever gotten away
from my Trick Mechanism Sword!
Hell Fire Edge!
I got you! Come on!
You're gonna be our hostage, too!
Don't push your luck!
Is it okay if your friend gets killed?!
Drop your swords now!
Yeah, that's it!
Zorojuro-san...
You stay right there!
I'm gonna beat you to death!
Hey...
I'm not gonna help you.
Don't you care about her?!
I won't let you get away!
Pardon me.
What should I do?
Take care of your side!
Okay!
Dog! This way!
Thank you!
Get us out of town!
What happened to your cheek?
It's nothing.
It was just pulled by some pincers.
Kibi Dango...
You won't be able to pull it out like that...
Pincers?!
Give me a minute!
Stop running!
Big Bro! I'm fine now!
Because you already saved me!
Hm?! Is he coming to attack?!
Roar! Lion Fire!
Big Bro!
Take a look at my Trick Mechanism
Sword's additional force!
Gum-Gum...
...Red Hawk!
Law and Hawkins finally clash!
It's a battle of the brains!
Which one of them will win?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Duel! The Magician and
the Surgeon of Death!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
Get ready for the origin of One Piece,
written by Eiichiro Oda!
The One Piece 20th anniversary special program!
"Romance Dawn"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!