One Dream One Wish
If you want to make it
come true, Over The Top
kanaetai nara Over The Top
ONE PIECE - LAND OF WANO ARC
Setting out into the unknown world
mitakoto mo nai sekai mezashi
Weathering rough wind and waves
araburu namikaze koete
I have to keep going because
I want to get there first
tsukisusumanakya dame sa
ichibannori shitain da
Worry later since it's
all sink or swim anyway
shinpai toka atomawashi
douse shoubu ichika bachika
When your opponent looks daunting
aite ga dekaku mietara
It's a sign that your heart is shrinking
kokoro ga chijinderu shouko
Running away is not a choice
nigeru nante choisu wa nai
Take one step closer
ippo soba e chikadukun da
Being called insolent's a compliment, right?
namaiki tte homekotoba?
When things become tough,
that's when you should laugh
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
If you want to look for a new tomorrow
atarashii ashita sagashi ni ikitai no nara
Polish your unique confidence
tobikkiri no jishin wo migaite
Until your footsteps
tabi wo shita ashiato ga
Yes! Become a map
sou! chizu ni kawaru made
A new horizon, look, how far you've come
atarashii Horizon hora susunde kita bun
It's brighter and the
level of difficulty rises
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
Live in your dream and raise a hurricane
yumeutsutsu de okose Hurricane
Now! Stir up the rankings
saa! chaato kakimidase
One Dream One Wish
Dreams don't run away... Knock everything out
yume wa nigenai... zenbu Knock out
Over The Top
After invading Bakura Town,
Luffy took down Holdem, a
Headliner of the Beast Pirates,
and successfully rescued the kidnapped Otama.
Alright! Let's run!
Kibi Dango!
Get off, you little...
This is Kibi Dango. It's delicious.
Screw that!
I'm not gonna eat a
suspicious dango like that!
Then, through the power
of Otama's Kibi Dango,
Luffy and the others tamed
another Headliner, Speed,
and tried to get out of Bakura Town
along with a treasure ship with a store of food.
That ability...
Chambres!
Meanwhile, around the
entrance of Bakura Town,
Trafalgar Law and Basil Hawkins
were fighting fiercely.
I assume you're not here for vacation
since your allies are also here...
You didn't expect that I knew?
I ran across Straw Hat
and the others earlier.
I bet you wanted to silence me
before it's too late...
Ring, ring, ring...
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Clank.
Holdem-sama was taken down by thieves
and they're on the run now!
We've already reported to Jack-sama!
They crushed Holdem
and now Jack has been notified?!
As you just heard,
all your effort was for nothing.
And of course, Kaido-san will know
what you and Straw Hat's group are doing.
Those fools...
Because of them, we have
the worst possible outcome!
Hey, you guys! Clear the way!
Roronoa-ya!
"The Coming of the Treasure Ship!
Luffytaro Returns the Favor!"
What's your problem, Tra-guy?
Damn you!
What?! Who is that?!
TREASURE
Give us back our food!
Horselina-chan!
Thank you for running!
Here you go!
Neigh-neigh!
Roronoa-ya!
On top of becoming a wanted person,
you drew Jack's attention!
You promised that
you weren't gonna cause trouble!
Sorry...
First of all,
why are you in Kuri?!
You were supposed to be
a ronin in the Flower Capital!
They know each other?
Is everything okay?
No, it's not!
I'm sorry!
I had no choice!
Because I ran into Luffy.
Straw Hat-ya! It's him again!
Horselina-chan!
Do you wanna eat another one?
It's delicious!
Why is even the enemy's Headliner here?
I guess Luffy won her over
while rescuing that brat.
He's doing as he likes...
Hey, where's Straw Hat-ya?
I thought he was with you!
He said he'd be back soon!
FELICITATIONS
Seems like he forgot something!
There it is!
So some people have it!
This will make Tama and the others happy!
Stop it! This water...
...is tribute for Shogun Orochi!
Okay, thank you for this!
What are you doing?!
He's flying!
Zorojuro-san!
We're leaving town!
Alright...
Empty it at Okobore Town!
I wonder if they're doing okay...
Mom! I'm hungry!
Just a while longer.
I'm starving...
What is it?
Th-That's...
...a treasure ship!
There are so many fish!
Food! Food!
A treasure ship is here!
We'll be saved!
It's great!
Guys, hurry up!
It's food!
Can we eat it?!
--Thank goodness!
--We'll be able to survive!
It's delicious!
There are tons and tons of food!
We won't go hungry! It's great!
What a relief...
Everyone's so happy!
Whoa-whoa-whoa, wait!
You fools!
Those aren't leftovers yet!
Stay away from the treasure ship!
You lowly bastards!
You shouldn't be touching that food!
You idiots forgot your place!
You can't go any farther!
You're taking the lowly people's side!
You fools will have to pay for this!
Hey!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
It's water!
It's non-poisonous! Help yourself!
It's been years since we've had
this much drinking water!
Thank goodness! Thank goodness!
I'm Luffytaro!
Tell them that in case someone asks you!
Luffytaro-san, thank you!
Big Bro!
Tama!
Did you get to eat something good?
Not yet!
I was waiting for you!
I see. Then...
Oh?
Tra-guy!
It's been a while!
Straw Hat-ya...
What you're doing is
a rebellion against the Land of Wano...
A rebellion? That's not what this is about!
Here!
It's an apple!
Tama...
I'm paying you back for feeding me.
This is just the start of it!
Look at this meat!
Hey! Guys!
Give me some meat, too!
Meat! Meat, meat!
Meat, meat, meat, meat!
Meat!
Holdem-sama!
The fire is spreading!
Where are the firefighters?!
Holdem-sama! Stay with us!
Please wake up!
Only the lion woke up! It's scary!
That's right...
Monkey D. Luffy, Roronoa Zoro.
And Trafalgar Law.
I don't want to give a
poor account of myself,
but when there are three troublesome guys,
it's too much even for me...
Clank.
TREASURE
It's so delicious!
Good for you, Tama!
Y-Yes!
I don't think I could top
a wonderful birthday like this!
Tama!
Don't set the bar too low!
I'll make it your everyday life!
By the time we leave this country,
I'll make it a place where
you can eat as much as you want!
When we come back to this country,
I'll make it a place where
you can eat as much as you want!
Hm? You don't want that?
What?!
What? What? Whaaat?!
O-Of course...
Of course, I'm happy!
It's just... I'm surprised...!
I see!
Man! You did such a reckless thing!
Now, they'll really come after us!
Get ready for it!
Yeah, we can't cause any trouble!
Okay, guys?!
You're the troublemaker here!
We shouldn't stay here too long.
Let's move on!
Follow me!
We'll go to the ruins of Oden Castle
at the top of the mountain!
Okay, I'll get going!
Yeah!
Thank you!
Alright, take good care of her, Horselina!
I'm Speed, Headliner of the Beast Pirates!
I don't take orders from you, fool!
Servants naturally protect their masters!
Yeah. I'm counting on you!
Why is the Headliner at the brat's mercy?
Big Bro...
Hm? What is it?
I'll never forget...
I'll never forget the taste
of the sweet red-bean soup
and the apple that I had today
for the rest of my life!
Okay!
When I return to Amigasa Village,
I'm gonna give this apple to Master-sama!
Say hi to Grandpa Nose for me!
I promise I'll bring back the dog!
Okay!
Komachiyo!
I want you to help Big Bro!
Oh yeah!
Let me borrow this sword for a little longer!
Without it, I can't call myself a samurai!
You're not using it at all!
Let me see it for a moment... Really!
I'll tell Master-sama so!
Yeah, thanks!
We must get going, Master-sama!
Oh, thank you!
Be careful on the way!
Okay! Well then...!
See you again!
See you!
Tama!
Alright...
Luffy!
We gotta get going, too!
Luffytaro-san!
I've never seen this much food before!
My grandfather became well!
I lived to see my dream come true!
Our child has his energy back!
I've never eaten this much before!
That's good!
Alright then!
Thank you for the treasure ship!
Thank you!
--Come visit again!
--Thank you!
Pirates shouldn't do such a good deed!
It makes me sick!
Oh, we did a good thing!
You stole it.
Guys!
Look after yourselves!
So you didn't become her servant
by eating that dango.
And...
...why are you coming with us?
I-I'm sorry!
I've always wanted to visit Oden Castle!
I can go home after we get there
so I won't give you trouble!
Is it gonna be okay?
Yeah!
Kiku is a good person and she's strong
so it's gonna be fine!
No...
She's hiding something!
By the way, Tra-guy,
why are we going to the castle?
It's not a castle now...
Only the deserted ruins remain.
Why does he wanna go to Oden Castle?
Luffytaro-san and the
others are good people...
But I can't drop my guard yet.
After we separated from you guys,
we made a plan
and were taking action accordingly...
You'll see once you get there.
First,
we'll go meet the ghosts of the Land of Wano.
Ghosts?
You'll be surprised...
Yeah, I was stunned, too...
There, you'll learn...
VASSAL KANJURO
VASSAL RAIZO
VASSAL KIN'EMON
MOMONOSUKE
...an unbelievable truth!
GRAVE OF KOZUKI ODEN
The name, Kozuki Oden, marking
the old grave tells of
a heartbreaking event that happened
in the Land of Wano two decades ago!
The Kozuki Family's name was tarnished
and the
true story of what happened
has been distorted.
When the shocking truth is revealed,
Luffy and the others are
overwhelmed and surprised!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Mysterious Grave Markers! A Reunion
at the Ruins of Oden Castle!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!