One Dream One Wish
If you want to make it come true, Over The Top
kanaetai nara Over The Top
ONE PIECE - LAND OF WANO ARC
Setting out into the unknown world
mitakoto mo nai sekai mezashi
Weathering rough wind and waves
araburu namikaze koete
I have to keep going because I want to get there first
tsukisusumanakya dame sa ichibannori shitain da
Worry later since it's all sink or swim anyway
shinpai toka atomawashi douse shoubu ichika bachika
When your opponent looks daunting
aite ga dekaku mietara
It's a sign that your heart is shrinking
kokoro ga chijinderu shouko
Running away is not a choice
nigeru nante choisu wa nai
Take one step closer
ippo soba e chikadukun da
Being called insolent's a compliment, right?
namaiki tte homekotoba?
When things become tough, that's when you should laugh
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
If you want to look for a new tomorrow
atarashii ashita sagashi ni ikitai no nara
Polish your unique confidence
tobikkiri no jishin wo migaite
Until your footsteps
tabi wo shita ashiato ga
Yes! Become a map
sou! chizu ni kawaru made
A new horizon, look, how far you've come
atarashii Horizon hora susunde kita bun
It's brighter and the level of difficulty rises
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
Live in your dream and raise a hurricane
yumeutsutsu de okose Hurricane
Now! Stir up the rankings
saa! chaato kakimidase
One Dream One Wish
Dreams don't run away... Knock everything out
yume wa nigenai... zenbu Knock out
Over The Top
After rescuing Otama,
Luffy stole a treasure ship with a store of food
and took it to Okobore Town.
It's water!
It's non-poisonous! Help yourself!
I'll make it your everyday life!
By the time we leave this country,
I'll make it a place where
you can eat as much as you want!
And Law is now taking Luffy and the others
to the ruins of Oden Castle.
We'll go meet the ghosts of the Land of Wano.
Ghosts?
You'll be surprised...
Yeah, I was stunned, too...
There, you'll learn...
...an unbelievable truth!
GRAVE OF KOZUKI ODEN
VASSAL KIN'EMON     KOZUKI MOMONOSUKE
VASSAL KANJURO     VASSAL RAIZO
"Mysterious Grave Markers!
A Reunion at the Ruins of Oden Castle!"
Hey, tell me! What do you mean by "ghosts"?!
Zoro!
--You'll see once you get there.
--What?!
Tra-guy! Don't leave me hanging!
In any event,
we'll talk once we get to the top of this mountain
where the ruins of Oden Castle are.
Tsk! You're so mean!
There's someone strong.
Yeah.
Maybe it's Orochi's assassin.
Luffy, you go ahead.
I'll catch up to you after I take care of this.
Thanks.
You think you're hiding well?
I can really feel your thirst for blood.
FLOWER CAPITAL
Alright, everyone, let's start the class.
Today, you'll learn the history of
the Land of Wano!
Yes, ma'am!
Now, everyone...
What is sakoku?
I know!
It means closing a country's doors
to maintain the peace of that country!
--That's correct!
--It's easy!
Next...
KUROZUMI OROCHI
what is kaikoku?
--Me!
--Here!
--Pick me!
--Me, me!
--You there.
--Yes.
It's a very bad action that will let evil people and ideas into a country!
The countries outside want various things
from the Land of Wano.
That's exactly correct!
But, a long time ago,
there were some fools who tried to do just that.
KOZUKI ODEN
It was Oden and the Akazaya Nine!
Wait, I didn't ask for your answer!
Wiggle, wiggle, wiggle, wiggle!
There it is! Her stretchy neck!
You answered without my permission!
What bad kids!
Why couldn't we answer?
Because the Akazaya Nine...
...is a name I don't even wanna hear.
But it's been two decades now.
There was a hero who took down those evil samurai.
It was the Shogun - Kurozumi Orochi!
That's correct!
Orochi Two-Sword Style!
Watch out, Akazaya Nine!
I'll bring you down!
What a horrible education!
It's all falsehoods!
Shogun Orochi saved the Land of Wano
from the bad guys!
That's right.
20 years ago,
all of those bad people died.
And the Land of Wano became...
...the peaceful country it is now!
Orochi-sama is a coward!
K-K-Kyoshiro-dono! What are you saying?!
You're too loud!
Shut up! Idiot!
Don't be scared!
Even if anyone hears it,
I only spoke the truth.
KOROZUMI CLAN'S MONEY CHANGER
NAPPING KYOSHIRO
Booze! Bring me more booze!
Does he have something to do with Orochi?
Napping Kyoshiro...
Maybe I can get some serious information.
20 years ago...
in front of the burning Oden Castle,
Oden's wife uttered these words
before she passed away.
YOU ARE THE MOON UNAWARE OF THE DAWN
"You are the moon unaware of the dawn.
May your purpose be fulfilled
MAY YOUR PURPOSE BE FULFILLED
and cast nine shadows on the night woven of 20 years
20 YEARS
THE NIGHT
NINE SHADOWS
and you shall know the brilliance of the dawn"!
She just said it out of desperation,
but Orochi-sama interpreted in a very specific way!
How did he interpret it?
Orochi-sama...
Go on!
Um...
How did he interpret it?!
Oh, right. Like this.
"I lay a curse on you"!
Like a ghost?!
"20 years later, on a moonlit night,
in order to settle this grudge,
nine samurai will appear as ghosts...
...to kill you."
Which means "to kill Orochi-sama"!
"And they'll open up the Land of Wano"!
This marks the 20th year!
That's why Shogun Orochi is in fear!
Thinking "the ghosts of the Kozuki Clan
might come to kill him"!
I want to fight them!
But what can the dead do?
The samurai of the Kozuki Clan...
GRAVE OF KOZUKI ODEN
VASSAL KIN'EMON     KOZUKI MOMONOSUKE
VASSAL KANJURO     VASSAL RAIZO
20 years ago, we cornered them in the castle...
...and burned them all alive!
There is no castle!
--I said "ruins."
--Oh, yeah.
RUINS OF ODEN CASTLE -
KURI, LAND OF WANO
It's this way. Follow me.
What? Hey, Kiku!
What's wrong with her?
Oh! Come to think of it,
Zoro hasn't returned yet, either.
I thought it was an assassin
but it's a tiger!
Great! Do you wanna fight?
Here we go!
This place is creepy.
It's been abandoned for 20 years.
What are those?
"Kozuki Oden..."?
Look at the other graves, too.
"Kozuki..."
MO
NO
SUKE
Momonosuke is...
That grave belongs to that brat you know.
What?! What are you talking about, Tra-guy?!
It's not just him.
"Raizo"?!
"Kanjuro"?!
"Kin'emon"?!
Why are their graves here?!
Wait a minute, when we were on our way
to the Land of Wano,
I couldn't get in touch with Kin'emon...
KIN'EMON
D-Don't tell me...
...he's dead!
They're dead?
Momo.
Raizo.
Kanjuro.
Kin'emon.
No way...
They can't be dead!
GRAVE OF KIN'EMON
I thought Kin'emon was waiting here...
He's been gone for quite a while.
Gone?!
Maybe he'll come out at night.
He appeared repeatedly last night, too.
That sounds like he's a ghost or something!
What's the meaning of these graves?!
Spit it out, Tra-guy!
Is there something you don't wanna say?!
I'm not the one who should be telling you about it.
Luffy-dono!
What?
Kin!
I'm glad that you're alive!
I'm sorry that I couldn't come to get you...
It's so great that you arrived safely.
I'm afraid I've got the runs pretty bad
and I thought I wouldn't be able to...
...come out from the bathroom tonight again.
But I'm starting to feel a little better.
FOXFIRE KIN'EMON - A VASSAL OF THE KOZUKI CLAN
Well, well, well, it was painful.
He's alive, Tra-guy!
When did I say he wasn't?
--I meant he'd appear from the bathroom at night.
--You misguided me!
Kin-sama!
Kiku!
You were back!
I really missed you!
And it made my body tremble!
Oh, okay...
Honestly! If you were back,
why didn't you tell me?!
I was worried about you!
Don't be a stranger!
I-I'm sorry!
Momonosuke-sama is okay, too?
Yes.
Momo's alive, too, huh?
Oh? Do Kiku and Kin know each other?
--Seems like they're very close.
--What?
Kiku, why are you with Luffy-dono's group?
What?! Don't tell me they're...
Who wants to hear the story
and where should I start?
You're right, Kiku!
They are our strong allies
to help us bring down Orochi!
Luffy-dono and Law-dono!
Whoa!
Hey, Luffy!
You arrived safely!
Momonosuke-sama?!
Luffy, I was just practicing my swordsmanship!
--Good!
--Watch this!
Momonosuke-sama!
I'm glad that you're okay!
Mm-hm. Kiku. It's been a while.
Is Dog Pops here in the Land of Wano, too, Momo?
What? Momo?!
It's rude to speak to Momonosuke-sama
without an honorific!
Oh, that's fine, Kiku.
What? Okay.
Of course, Dogstorm is here, too.
I see.
Then, it's just them left now.
Are we there yet? We walked a lot.
I wonder if Kin'emon and the others are there.
Me, too.
He said to look for castle ruins,
so this mountain's got to be it.
I'm glad that we got in touch with him!
Hey!
Luffy, you're here!
Luffy!
Guys! Get over here!
I'm glad that you're okay!
Garchu!
Luffy!
You're dressed like a samurai! It's cool!
What took you guys so long?!
We were looking for you! Even on the sea bottom!
We found your Vivre Card
so we at least knew you were alive.
Onami!
Momo-chan!
Kin'emon-san, how are you now?
I'm getting by.
Momonosuke-san, you look good.
I thought so, you dirty brat!
So you've returned to the group, Sanji-dono.
Yeah, sorry to make you worry.
Kin-san!
Are these people Luffytaro-san's friends?
What a lovely lady!
Crush, crush, crush...
Hey!
That's enough! Get off of her!
You're rude, Bonekichi!
Leave him alone, Brook!
Right, Momo-chan?
--Onami...
--Momo!
Momo!
They are all Luffy-dono's friends!
The reliable people who will help us!
Momonosuke-sama,
I'm glad that he lightened up like that.
Captain!
Oh, you guys.
How's Bepo doing?
He hasn't come out of the bush yet
because of the runs.
What's wrong with everyone?
Straw Hat-ya.
Let's have a talk inside.
Okay.
We stole safe food from the farm.
So you're the one who did it!
This ruined castle will be our headquarters.
Ouch!
What a messy room!
I'm sorry, everyone...
Luffy-dono! Everyone!
Thank you for coming to the Land of Wano!
Once again, thank you very much!
--Don't mention it!
--Yeah!
First, aside from Momonosuke-sama's identity,
there is another thing that I haven't told you guys.
You guys have so many secrets!
Just tell us everything!
We're not strangers!
--He's right.
--We're friends!
You're totally right... I'm sorry!
But you're not going to believe
what I'm about to say.
What is it? Just say it!
You know Kanjuro and Raizo.
And the three of us here.
The five of us altogether!
As a matter of fact,
we came from the past!
Huh?
What?
The past?
What do you mean by that?
GRAVE OF KOZUKI ODEN
VASSAL KIN'EMON     KOZUKI MOMONOSUKE
VASSAL KANJURO     VASSAL RAIZO
KIN'EMON
KANJURO
RAIZO
MOMONOSUKE
The thing is we came from
the Land of Wano of 20 years ago...
...crossing through time
to the present Land of Wano!
Huh?!
Huuuuuuh?!
Momonosuke's father, Kozuki Oden, was a man who
mesmerized even Whitebeard!
He was aggressive and daring!
The man got out of the Land of Wano
and saw the ends of the world along with the King of the Pirates!
His horrific final moments make Luffy and the others wail!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Legendary Samurai! The Man Who Roger Admired!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!