One Dream One Wish
If you want to make it
come true, Over The Top
kanaetai nara Over The Top
ONE PIECE - LAND OF WANO ARC
Setting out into the unknown world
mitakoto mo nai sekai mezashi
Weathering rough wind and waves
araburu namikaze koete
I have to keep going because
I want to get there first
tsukisusumanakya dame sa
ichibannori shitain da
Worry later since it's
all sink or swim anyway
shinpai toka atomawashi
douse shoubu ichika bachika
When your opponent looks daunting
aite ga dekaku mietara
It's a sign that your heart is shrinking
kokoro ga chijinderu shouko
Running away is not a choice
nigeru nante choisu wa nai
Take one step closer
ippo soba e chikadukun da
Being called insolent's a compliment, right?
namaiki tte homekotoba?
When things become tough,
that's when you should laugh
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
If you want to look for a new tomorrow
atarashii ashita sagashi ni ikitai no nara
Polish your unique confidence
tobikkiri no jishin wo migaite
tabi wo shita ashiato ga
Until your footsteps
sou! chizu ni kawaru made
Yes! Become a map
atarashii Horizon hora susunde kita bun
A new horizon, look, how far you've come
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
It's brighter and the
level of difficulty rises
Live in your dream and raise a hurricane
yumeutsutsu de okose Hurricane
Now! Stir up the rankings
saa! chaato kakimidase
One Dream One Wish
Dreams don't run away... Knock everything out
yume wa nigenai... zenbu Knock out
Over The Top
Luffy came to the ruins of Oden Castle
along with Law,
and found the graves of
Kin'emon and the others.
Why are their graves here?!
Luffy-dono!
What?
Kin!
He was reunited with
Kin'emon and Momonosuke...
...who he parted with at Zou.
Also...
Hey!
Luffy, you're here!
Luffy!
Garchu!
You're dressed like a samurai! It's cool!
Then Luffy and the others were told
a surprising truth by Kin'emon.
The thing is we came from
the Land of Wano of 20 years ago...
...crossing through time
to the present Land of Wano!
What are you talking about?!
Is it true?
20 years ago?! What do you mean?!
How did you get here?!
Oh, I wasn't even born yet!
No way!
Who can do a time leap?
That doesn't make sense! Explain it again!
She's right! Tell us in detail!
Everything that I'm going
to tell you is true!
It's the truth...
...about the Land of Wano!
"A Legendary Samurai!
The Man Who Roger Admired!"
Here is where Oden Castle used to stand...
But it's just a nickname...
It's actually called Kuri Castle!
The people of Kuri truly loved Oden-sama.
That's why they nicknamed it.
Is that Momo's dad?!
That's right!
Our lord, Oden-sama, was
a very daring person.
He was a son of Kozuki Sukiyaki-sama,
a Shogun of the Land of Wano at the time,
but he was free-spirited
and hot-blooded.
He caused violent incidents again and again
and he was eventually banished
from the Flower Capital.
--What?!
--Banished?!
Well... For the young Oden-sama,
the Flower Capital was
too small and too boring.
--Damn you!
--Go to hell!
There was a so-called "lawless area"
in the Land of Wano at that time...
There, criminals and ronin who were
expelled from their hometowns formed groups.
They stole from and mutilated each other
and there was bloodshed every day...
The place was so wild
that even the Shogun family gave up on it.
That was Kuri.
This seems exciting!
The young Oden-sama stepped into that infamous Kuri
of all places!
And...!
Hey, kid! Give us all your belongings!
Help!
Oh! Whoa!
Oden-sama was cool!
Then Kuri's most dangerous man who was
leading the ruffians of the region showed up.
His name was Ashura Doji
and they clashed almost immediately!
He brought Ashura Doji down beautifully.
That wasn't all...
He became the leader of the ruffians.
--Oh, he was quite something.
--He saved Kuri!
On top of that, Oden-sama brought change
to the town!
First, he taught the ruffians to work.
He developed the town, built the castle,
and made the Paradise Farm for everybody.
Kuri became a free and vibrant region
full of laughter
and Oden-sama was finally given
the title of "daimyo of Kuri"
by the Shogun, Sukiyaki-sama.
That's what Oden-sama accomplished
at only 20 years old.
He made a river...
...and built docks.
He connected regions...
...and people.
And then, I...
Right. And...
He was a daimyo who was loved by
the people of Kuri...
But Oden-sama was a freewheeler...
Having so many vassals didn't suit his style.
This is what he kept saying.
Oh! It's so restrictive!
The Land of Wano was a little too small
for Oden-sama...
DUKE DOGSTORM
KING OF THE DAY, MOKOMO DUKEDOM
The good old days...
Yes, that was this beach!
We were washed ashore here
and everyone called us "the talking dog and cat"
and they were afraid of us...
But Oden-sama was different!
You monsters!
Stop!
What did they do to you?!
You fear those who are different
due to your stupidity!
Shame on you all!
I'm sorry...
He was our savior...!
The samurai from the Land of Wano,
who mesmerized Whitebeard
and was admired by Roger!
He was a true hero!
He was our master!
GRAVE OF KOZUKI ODEN
VASSAL KIN'EMON     KOZUKI MOMONOSUKE
VASSAL KANJURO     VASSAL RAIZO
Oden-sama was funny, dynamic, and merry!
GRAVE OF ODEN
His spirit and good nature...
...turned Kuri into a great region.
But now, because of Kaido,
it has become...
It's unforgivable!
Momonosuke-sama!
Father!
Damn Kaido!
Kaido and Kurozumi Orochi...
...secretly joined forces!
And they set Oden-sama up!
The Land of Wano fell to pieces...
...and Oden-sama...
...was labeled a criminal!
KOZUKI ODEN
Okay, let's go back...
Where did they go?
It's a dock.
Oden-sama who was loved by everyone...
Tell us! What happened to Oden?!
He died... as a criminal...
at the Flower Capital!
What?!
You've got to be kidding!
What a sneaky piece of shit! Orochi!
I can't believe it!
That's awful!
The horrific death of Oden-sama...
...happened 20 years ago...
...but for us...
...it was only a few months ago...
Kozuki Oden was a brave samurai...
His final moment...
...still vividly replays in my memory!
What a hero!
It's amazing that you guys made it out of
such a situation.
Yeah...
We no longer had allies,
so from there, we just ran for our lives!
We left the execution ground
and ran straight to Oden Castle!
On our way, Dogstorm and Cat Viper
quarreled with each other
and were caught by Orochi's underlings
so we gave up on them!
Even if any of us might have died,
someone had to get to Oden Castle!
Orochi who was looking to bring down the Kozuki Clan
was taking aim at...
...Momonosuke-sama who was at the castle!
Th-The castle is...!
But Kaido had already made a move
and the castle was on fire.
Damn! You bastards!
I won't forgive you!
Catch them!
Flower Shuriken!
Momonosuke-sama, his younger
sister Hiyori-sama,
and their mother Kozuki Toki-sama
were left behind in the castle.
Mother...
Momonosuke-sama! Hiyori-sama!
Toki-sama!
Come on! Hurry up!
Momonosuke-sama!
I'm glad that you're okay!
Hiyori-sama! Toki-sama!
I'm sorry!
Even though we were there...
we let Oden-sama be...
It was not your fault at all.
But...
Lift your head up.
Toki-sama, it's dangerous here!
Let's get out!
I will stay.
You cannot!
Let's get out of here!
Toki-sama!
Then we will share the
same fate with you here!
Leave... to the future!
The future?
People can never go back to the past...
But you can go forward into the future.
I traveled farther and
farther into the future
by the power of the strange Time-Time Fruit
and finally arrived at the place
where this journey ends.
It was hard to believe,
but rumor had it that Toki-sama was born
way back in the past...
You mean...
...you met Oden-sama.
Yes. That is why I will stay here.
You are determined...
No one can stop you!
If we really go into the future...
We will surely fulfill Oden-sama's dream
and take down Orochi and Kaido!
And we will certainly...
...open up this country!
Please look after Momonosuke.
Mother?
No, I don't want that!
I will stay here with you!
Mother, please don't do that!
Mother! Mother!
Ouch...
Huh?! What the...?!
Am I dreaming?! Where am I?!
Where is the castle?! And the fire?!
Toki-sama! Hiyori-sama!
Where are you, Mother?!
Please stop! Momonosuke-sama!
Mother!
Kin'emon!
Are these our graves?!
And they are old graves!
It was real... Toki-sama's power!
Is that the town in Kuri?
Is this...
the Land of Wano in the future?!
Since we came from the past,
this world after 20 years
was literally unknown.
To learn about the country that had been
completely changed by Orochi
and the others' evil doing,
we walked around.
We saw a row of factories...
And so many smokestacks
that vent black smoke...
Undrinkable water...
Food under strict control...
Daimyo and regions that are destroyed!
Sterile lands!
Kozuki's name is despised
because of all their lies.
This is no longer...
...the Land of Wano that we know!
I thought no one would
fight together with us.
But that was not true.
Even after 20 years,
GRAVE OF KOZUKI ODEN
there are still people who admire Oden-sama
and want to help the Kozuki Clan!
ODEN
The Reversed Crescent Moon lights up the sky!
Guided by two birds and a pit viper, light shines on their way
to take down Kaido!
Samurai! Ninja! The joining of new allies raises
the fighting spirit of Luffy and the others!
Together with their friends
who had dreadful experiences,
a secret operation to bring down
Kaido is finally put into action!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Bringing Down
the Emperor of the Sea! A Secret Raid Operation Begins!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!