One Dream One Wish
If you want to make it come true, Over The Top
kanaetai nara Over The Top
ONE PIECE - LAND OF WANO ARC
Setting out into the unknown world
mitakoto mo nai sekai mezashi
Weathering rough wind and waves
araburu namikaze koete
I have to keep going because I want to get there first
tsukisusumanakya dame sa ichibannori shitain da
Worry later since it's all sink or swim anyway
shinpai toka atomawashi douse shoubu ichika bachika
When your opponent looks daunting
aite ga dekaku mietara
It's a sign that your heart is shrinking
kokoro ga chijinderu shouko
Running away is not a choice
nigeru nante choisu wa nai
Take one step closer
ippo soba e chikadukun da
Being called insolent's a compliment, right?
namaiki tte homekotoba?
When things become tough, that's when you should laugh
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
If you want to look for a new tomorrow
atarashii ashita sagashi ni ikitai no nara
Polish your unique confidence
tobikkiri no jishin wo migaite
Until your footsteps
tabi wo shita ashiato ga
Yes! Become a map
sou! chizu ni kawaru made
A new horizon, look, how far you've come
atarashii Horizon hora susunde kita bun
It's brighter and the level of difficulty rises
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
Live in your dream and raise a hurricane
yumeutsutsu de okose Hurricane
Now! Stir up the rankings
saa! chaato kakimidase
One Dream One Wish
Dreams don't run away... Knock everything out
yume wa nigenai... zenbu Knock out
Over The Top
Luffy stole a treasure ship with a store of food
from Speed,
TREASURE
and took it to Okobore Town.
Sorry to keep you waiting!
It's water!
It's non-poisonous! Help yourself!
It's been years since we've had
this much drinking water!
Thank goodness! Thank goodness!
Everyone's so happy!
I'm Luffytaro!
Tell them that in case someone asks you!
Then, everyone who assembled at
the ruins of Oden Castle...
...were told about a raid operation by Kin'emon.
Our targets are Emperor of the Sea Kaido
and the hateful Shogun - Kurozumi Orochi!
The execution date is two weeks from now!
On the night of the Fire Festival!
We will make a raid...
...on Onigashima where Kaido lives!
"The Strongest Man in the World!
Shutenmaru, the Thieves Brigade Chief!"
Hi!
It's been a while!
I'm sorry but have we met before?
What?! You've got to be kidding!
You haven't forgotten about me,
have you?!
We played together like every day
when we were kids!
Oh... Yeah... I remember...
I-It's been a while...
Yeah, we bumped into each other here for a reason!
Let's have a drink sometime!
O-Okay...
Bye!
What?
Who is that guy?
When did I get this?
Th... This is...
How's everything with you?
Is it going well?
Yeah, if things go well,
I'm gonna be summoned by Orochi soon.
Oh, that'll be nice!
Franosuke, have you obtained
the blueprints of Kaido's mansion?
No, not yet.
That master carpenter is kind of tricky...
What's up with you?
I handed the flyer to
a guy who had the mark of the moon today!
While doing so, I got good news.
--Good...
--...News?
It's the name of the one said to be
the strongest man in the world alive today...
What?
Who is that?
The chief of the Atamayama Thieves Brigade...
Shutenmaru!
GRAVE OF KOZUKI ODEN
VASSAL KIN'EMON     KOZUKI MOMONOSUKE
VASSAL KANJURO     VASSAL RAIZO
Hey, Kin'emon,
I understood your plan.
But there is one thing
that I couldn't quite get.
I know! It's not easy to understand...
...a mature woman's attractiveness!
A-A mature woman's attractiveness...
Yes, I might be... too young to...
understand that...
That's okay, young man!
Someday you'll get it.
Anyway, back to what we were talking about...
You said that Oden brought down Ashura Doji
20 years ago...
Mm-hm...
Then why is he among the allies
that you want us to find?
There are three particular samurai
that I want you to look for!
If we can find them,
they will be a tremendous help!
Kawamatsu.
Ashura Doji.
Denjiro.
They are samurai who used to serve Oden-sama
like us!
That's a legitimate question...
Ashura Doji mended his ways
after being defeated by Oden-sama,
and pledged his loyalty to him...
But...
We heard that now under the name Shutenmaru,
he became the chief of the Atamayama Thieves Brigade,
and is doing wrong again.
Hmmm, a thieves brigade, huh?
By the way...
is he strong?
Yes, perhaps, it is not too much to say
that he is the strongest of all samurai.
As an ally,
no one is more reliable than him.
I see.
Then we definitely need him to be our ally...
You're right!
OKOBORE TOWN
What?!
I can't believe this!
Oh, please!
I thought I could finally eat as much as I want...
TEN (HEAVEN)
SHUTENMARU
CHIEF OF THE ATAMAYAMA THIEVES BRIGADE
Hello!
Do it!
These fools have quite good stuff!
SAKE
Give them back to us!
Luffytaro-san gave...
Luffytaro-san gave them to us!
Shut up!
Mother!
Oh? There's even fruit, sake, and rice!
How impudent!
Give them back to us!
I want my grandson to have them!
Shut up, old man!
Drop dead already...
You're in my way, old bag!
Do you wanna die?!
Tsk!
Who the hell...
...did something like this?
Giving people food and acting like a hero?!
It was just a brief dream for you...
You finally got food,
but it's gonna be taken away by us
and that's it.
There are no samurai
who will stand up for you poor people!
Also, there is no real man left
in this country,
who can lead tough samurai!
The Land of Wano is finished!
Hey, old hag... Even if you live much longer,
all you'll ever see is a cruel reality.
Let me put you out of your misery!
Please run!
Grandma!
I believe in Otoki-sama's words...
She's already dead.
I'm sure the nine samurai will...
...fulfill Oden-sama's wish!
How silly!
They can't fight a war without a leader!
Shutenmaru-sama! That's...
I finally got to meet you...
The head of a thieves brigade...
JACK - A LEAD PERFORMER, ANIMAL KINGDOM PIRATES
A-A-A-A monster!
I know a pirate named Straw Hat Luffy
came around here...
If I say "I don't know," will your attitude change?
Don't push your luck...
Huh?!
We are keeping you alive...
...only because Kaido-san wants to
have you as his subordinate.
I don't have to pay you any respect!
Then, I'm gonna tell you...
My answer to that request is...
...just this!
Oh, Kaido-sama...
He's drinking too much again...
I wonder what'll happen
if he gets drunk this time...
It's scary even to think about it!
I want more sake! Bring some more!
Y-Yes, sir!
S-Sorry to keep you waiting!
Oh, it's unacceptable... Everything that's been going on...
Isn't it?!
Yeah, oh, well, I mean...
Oh, yeah...
Bring them to me...
Th-Them?
Can't you even tell who I'm talking about?!
Don't mess with samurai!
Jack-sama!
Damn you...
Get back!
Shutenmaru and Jack-sama...
...Got into a fight!
We're doomed!
Ever since he died, I...
I was looking for a way to die...
But...
...getting killed by an underling like you
is not it!
Cut the crap!
I...
...should have died!
Living is such a pain in the ass...
J-Jack-sama!
L-Look... The sky!
No way... Why?
He came in person... for what?
I-Is it because of me? Is it?
Did he come to execute me?!
Why, all of a sudden...
Is it gonna rain?
No!
Hey, Straw Hat-ya! Come here now!
What's wrong, Tra-guy?
What the?!
I've never seen this kind of change
in the weather before!
Thank you... You saved me!
Momonosuke-sama!
What?! Momonosuke-sama turned into...
...A-A dragon?!
I will explain to you later,
but his body can now change like this!
Of all things...
the figure of a hateful Dragon!
We're in trouble, Straw Hat-ya.
Move! Out of my way!
No way...
Why...?
Hey, Jack.
Yes, sir...
Bring those brats...
...here now...
A dragon?! What's that?!
Things can't get any worse...
That's...
...Kaido!
Kaido?!
I didn't expect he'd pop up like that!
To put it frankly, we're in danger!
Momonosuke-sama, get ahold of yourself!
So that's...
...Kaido!
Kaido ravages the Land of Wano with his overwhelming power!
In order to stop him, Luffy starts running!
However, mercilessly,
Kaido's blow of anger strikes the ruins of Oden Castle.
Luffy stands by helplessly!
Will the Straw Hats be safe?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Everyone is Annihilated! Kaido's Furious Blast Breath!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!