One Dream One Wish
kanaetai nara Over The Top
If you want to make it
come true, Over The Top
ONE PIECE - LAND OF WANO ARC
mitakoto mo nai sekai mezashi
Setting out into the unknown world
araburu namikaze koete
Weathering rough wind and waves
tsukisusumanakya dame sa
ichibannori shitain da
I have to keep going because
I want to get there first
shinpai toka atomawashi
douse shoubu ichika bachika
Worry later since it's
all sink or swim anyway
aite ga dekaku mietara
When your opponent looks daunting
kokoro ga chijinderu shouko
It's a sign that your heart is shrinking
nigeru nante choisu wa nai
Running away is not a choice
ippo soba e chikadukun da
Take one step closer
namaiki tte homekotoba?
Being called insolent's a compliment, right?
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
When things become tough,
that's when you should laugh
atarashii ashita sagashi ni ikitai no nara
If you want to look for a new tomorrow
tobikkiri no jishin wo migaite
Polish your unique confidence
tabi wo shita ashiato ga
Until your footsteps
sou! chizu ni kawaru made
Yes! Become a map
atarashii Horizon hora susunde kita bun
A new horizon, look, how far you've come
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
It's brighter and the
level of difficulty rises
yumeutsutsu de okose Hurricane
Live in your dream and raise a hurricane
saa! chaato kakimidase
Now! Stir up the rankings
One Dream One Wish
yume wa nigenai... zenbu Knock out
Dreams don't run away... Knock everything out
Over The Top
Shutenmaru, the chief of the Atamayama Thieves Brigade,
made his way to Okobore Town...
...to take away the food
that Luffy delivered to its people.
Jack from the Animal Kingdom Pirates
also appeared on the scene
and they undertook a punishing battle.
Don't mess with samurai!
Then, appearing suddenly from the sky was...
Hey, Jack.
Yes, sir...
Bring those brats...
...here now...
A dragon?! What's that?!
Things can't get any worse...
That's...
...Kaido!
"Everyone is Annihilated!
Kaido's Furious Blast Breath!"
Is that...
...Kaido?!
Kaido is a dragon?!
Yes...
What you see right there is Kaido!
Kaido can...
...transform himself into a dragon!
We're here with you! So don't worry!
BAKURA TOWN
He's not coming this way!
He didn't come to execute me...
OKOBORE TOWN
Where are they?
Those shitty brats...
Otsuru-san!
You'd better run now!
Right...
Okobore Town is around there!
Mm-hm.
Now, why did Kaido come to Kuri
all of a sudden?
I'm sorry, Kin'emon.
To tell you the truth, Straw Hat-ya,
Zoro-ya, and I were identified by them...
What?!
But that's all they know!
They don't know about the plan!
"That's all they know"?!
What the hell are you doing, Law?!
You Straw Hats don't have
the right to blame me!
Oh, I'm sure it was Luffy's fault.
Let me just say, I'm sorry.
Nami-san...
Seems like our captain caused you trouble.
Sorry...
He's probably...
...looking for me and Straw Hat-ya...
The Animal Kingdom Pirates led by Kaido...
...need two key things
to maintain their overwhelming forces.
First, the weapons that Kaido is
getting people to manufacture in this country!
Second, the backdoor trade of
the artificial Devil Fruits called SMILEs...
...which Caesar and Doflamingo were creating!
We destroyed that at its root
which was the factory in Punk Hazard...
...and captured Caesar
who was necessary for SMILE development.
On top of that,
we destroyed the factory...
...in Dressrosa where
Doflamingo, Kaido's important trade partner, ruled.
And we also helped Doflamingo, the buyer,
get locked up and brought him to ruin...
In short,
we picked a fight with Kaido.
So the only ones he's coming after are...
...me and Straw Hat-ya!
Hey, Luffy!
Luffy, wait!
Luffy-dono!
Don't chase! I'll go!
If more of us get exposed,
they'll find out that all the members of
the Straw Hats and the Heart Pirates are here!
They'll start a big hunt!
So think rationally.
They're only seen us so far.
Your plan is still safe!
All right?
Then, what are you two going to do?!
I wish I could let things be...
But Straw Hat-ya has already gotten involved
with the people of this country.
If he lets his emotions take the lead,
it'll spell trouble for the plan.
If all of us aren't there on the execution day,
the alliance is pointless.
I'll take care of it.
Room...
Don't show yourselves at any cost!
Shambles!
Captain!
Damn Luffy...
What did he do while we were apart?
Retreat to the forest,
Atamayama Thieves Brigade!
We don't wanna get involved with him!
I kept hearing that...
...there is a mighty thief
living deep in the mountains of Kuri.
Shutenmaru.
I...
...remember you...
But let's forget about the past!
If you bend your knee to me...
I'll wipe the slate clean between us.
Whoa! Smells like alcohol!
Kaido-san, don't tell me you're drunk!
Idiot! I'm not drunk!
He's drunk!
What are you gonna do, Shutenmaru?
We can't get away! Let's just fight him!
Jack-sama! I'm trying to stop the bleeding
so don't move!
He's so drunk.
He could lose his temper at any minute.
We'd better leave here soon, too...
Right. But...
...the residents of Okobore Town
are a valuable work force in the factories!
It's nice just setting an example,
but if he wreaks havoc senselessly,
they'll all get wiped out along with Kuri...
I am...
I am going to go to Okobore Town, too!
No, you cannot, Kiku!
If you get identified, too,
the plan will be all screwed up!
Well, the fact is...
Kin-sama, I did not tell you
but that's where...
...Otsuru-san lives...
What?!
Why didn't you tell me that sooner, Kiku?!
I am sorry, Kin-sama!
Why don't you go back?!
I will save Tsuru!
No, I am responsible, too!
I cannot believe she did not get remarried to
someone who would protect her!
It has already been 20 years
since I left her!
I am on my way, Tsuru!
Damn! It's still so far away!
Straw Hat-ya!
Tra-guy!
You think the people of Okobore Town are okay?!
Idiot! You see?
When a pirate does a good thing,
this is what happens!
Kaido is coming after us, right?!
Yeah!
Then, I'll stop him!
Supreme Commander Kaido!
Isn't he..
...one of the Headliners?
Supreme Commander! If you're looking for
Straw Hat Luffy and Trafalgar Law...
they're hiding in the ruins of Oden Castle!
Oden Castle?
Hawkins!
Is it true that Straw Hat and Law
are hiding in the ruins of Oden Castle?!
No... I lied to him
in order to stop him from rampaging...
But that's not all.
These days,
maybe because of that particular legend,
some people are saying that they've seen
suspicious lights at the top of the mountain...
Legend?
Is that the one that says the Kozuki samurai
who we exterminated will come back for revenge?
Yes, instead of letting it incite
Shogun Orochi's terror,
we can kill two birds with one stone
by wiping out that abandoned castle.
So huge...
Are we trying to fight him?!
I'm afraid for my life...
But I'm already dead!
My soul left the body before I knew it!
Stop laughing! Don't surprise me!
I wonder if Captain's doing alright...
Oden Castle, you said?!
That brings back memories...
It is indeed a good place to hide.
So that's where they are...
They took SMILE away from me.
LAW AND STRAW HAT'S PIRATE ALLIANCE
Those hateful punks!
I won't let them get away!
He's heading towards the
ruins of Oden Castle!
Oh?
Hey! Isn't he coming towards us?!
No way!
Don't tell me he's noticed that we're here!
What?!
No!
It's impossible to see us from there!
No...
He's coming!
Get away, guys!
Why is he heading that way?!
Don't tell me!
Oh, no! That's...!
Ow, ow, ow...
--We're in trouble, Nami-san...
--What?
Run, everyone!
Blast Breath!
Captain!
Kaido!
Oden Castle has been wiped out in an instant.
It is unknown whether
everyone is dead or alive!
After learning even Otama has been attacked,
Luffy reaches the breaking point
and makes a mad dash for Kaido!
With the memories of his friends in mind,
Luffy's all-out attack blasts!
A blistering battle in which
neither side gives an inch starts!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Finally Clashing! The Ferocious Luffy vs. Kaido!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!