One Dream One Wish
If you want to make it come true, Over The Top
kanaetai nara Over The Top
ONE PIECE - LAND OF WANO ARC
Setting out into the unknown world
mitakoto mo nai sekai mezashi
Weathering rough wind and waves
araburu namikaze koete
I have to keep going because I want to get there first
tsukisusumanakya dame sa ichibannori shitain da
Worry later since it's all sink or swim anyway
shinpai toka atomawashi douse shoubu ichika bachika
When your opponent looks daunting
aite ga dekaku mietara
It's a sign that your heart is shrinking
kokoro ga chijinderu shouko
Running away is not a choice
nigeru nante choisu wa nai
Take one step closer
ippo soba e chikadukun da
Being called insolent's a compliment, right?
namaiki tte homekotoba?
When things become tough, that's when you should laugh
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
If you want to look for a new tomorrow
atarashii ashita sagashi ni ikitai no nara
Polish your unique confidence
tobikkiri no jishin wo migaite
Until your footsteps
tabi wo shita ashiato ga
Yes! Become a map
sou! chizu ni kawaru made
A new horizon, look, how far you've come
atarashii Horizon hora susunde kita bun
It's brighter and the level of difficulty rises
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
Live in your dream and raise a hurricane
yumeutsutsu de okose Hurricane
Now! Stir up the rankings
saa! chaato kakimidase
One Dream One Wish
Dreams don't run away... Knock everything out
yume wa nigenai... zenbu Knock out
Over The Top
Luffy and Kaido finally clashed!
Gum-Gum...
...King Kong Gun!
Thunder Bagua!
What kind of king did you say you'd be?
You little punk!
"A Living Hell!
Luffy, Humiliated in the Great Mine!"
Lock him up!
Oh, y-yes, sir!
Once his spirit gets broken,
we can make him fight for us!
Y-Yes, sir!
Don't even print "pirate" in the broadsheets.
Yes, sir!
I don't want the foolish citizens of this country
becoming curious about the world outside even a bit.
--Yes, sir!
--Let's take him!
Hey, guys! Hold his feet!
Yes, sir!
The Worst Generation...
Screw them.
He's weak as hell!
He's covered with blood!
How disgusting...
--Let's just drag him.
--Yeah.
So you use it, too...
Little punk!
No way!
That's Oden-sama's technique!
Was he able to do it despite being unconscious?!
Who the hell is that brat?!
Kid uses the Color of the Supreme King, too!
We don't need that many...
...Supreme Kings!
I'll get Trafalgar next time.
Let's go back to drinking.
Oh, I'm totally sober now.
A Sea Prism Stone nail?!
I've never heard of it before!
Gee...
Captain!
I wonder if Bepo and the others are okay.
Hawkins-sama!
Did you find Trafalgar?
Well, we looked all over
but he's nowhere to be found!
I guess he's already left town...
Cuff him!
Yes, sir!
Catching Straw Hat alone is enough for now...
But I'll run down Trafalgar Law, too, at any cost!
I won't let him get away!
OKOBORE TOWN
Gorobei-san!
Hey, stay with us!
I will treat you now.
I think that voice belongs to...
I want to apologize...
I want to say sorry to Luffytaro-san...
He took the trouble to bring us food
but it went to waste...
Do not pay that any mind.
I hope he does not feel responsible for
this town being attacked.
Since he is a kind man...
Still beautiful after 20 years!
You have not changed a bit.
But I can only see you again
once I accomplish Oden-sama's dream!
Forgive me for being such a selfish husband!
Is that...
...Ashura Doji!
I-It's...
None of them can be alive...
A massive hole?!
Everyone! Are you okay?!
Everyone!
Okiku!
Don't tell me...
Help us!
A big sinkhole opened up!
Okiku-chan!
We managed to survive!
--Hey!
--We're here!
Thank goodness!
You are all safe!
The sinkhole saved us but...
We're falling!
Everyone!
Oh dear!
Hold on tight!
Thank you!
You saved me!
I managed to rescue the ladies!
Why don't you help us, too?!
We had a close shave!
So at that time, you were all saved by
Shino-chan's technique!
That's right!
At that moment...
Blast Breath!
Ripe-Ripe Enticement Jutsu!
Guard Point!
We survived!
My Ripe-Ripe Enticement Jutsu can
make everything more mature!
Yes! Everything Shino-chan touches rots!
Rots...
Watch your mouth!
Anyway, the situation is...
Oh, yeah!
What happened to Luffy?!
He looked like he wanted to
pick a fight with Kaido!
Prepare yourselves and listen...
How dare he do such a cruel thing!
She's still breathing!
Help her!
Yes, sir. People can see us here
so let's go into the forest!
Who could hurt a little child like this!
Damn Kaido!
Luffytaro's big fight in Kuri...
Special report! Special report!
WANTED FLYER
...Spread across the Land of Wano.
Hm? Is this a broadsheet?
Oh! Luffy!
LUFFYTARO
So he's here in...
WANTED FLYER - LUFFYTARO
Oh, Luffy!
So he's here in...
LUFFYTARO
TOAD OIL
Special report!
Lu...
LUFFYTARO
WASABI
It burns!
Hmmm...
I can't believe a crazy guy like this
appeared in the Land of Wano.
What are you reading?
It burns!
Oh, a samurai named Luffytaro
fought Kaido-sama...
Whoa! That's disgusting, bro!
Don't spew out wasabi sushi!
And you ate too much!
Can you pay for it all?!
Let me see that!
LUFFYTARO
What are you doing, Luffy?!
Beat, beat! Beat the iron flat!
The harder and stronger the weapons we create,
the more the capital will flourish!
Your lives belong to Orochi-sama!
If you wanna live, beat the iron flat!
If you wanna rest, I'll kill you!
Move faster!
Udon, Land of Wano.
UDON, LAND OF WANO
Home to the weapon factories and mines...
... in which prisoners are made to work in forced labor.
Here you go! Poisonous Fish!
What's in this cell anyway?
I don't know... The only rules are...
..."feed Poisonous Fish once a day"
and "remove the bones from the fish"
and that's all.
That means it likes to eat Poisonous Fish?
At first, they fed it Poisonous Fish
as a means of execution.
But whatever's in this cell keeps eating
the Poisonous Fish
and has carried on living up until now!
Is it a shark or a crocodile
or something like that?
Why do we have to kindly remove the bones?
It's a pain in the ass!
That's because...
HEINOUS CRIMINAL
"Heinous criminal"?!
That means we have the newcomer
that everyone's talking about!
What?!
Welcome, Newcomer!
You have a lot of nerve!
Don't think you can survive
after you messed with Kaido-sama!
Get ready!
LUFFYTARO
Come on! Walk faster!
Hey, is he really the guy...
...who fought Kaido-sama in Kuri
and wreaked havoc on a town?!
I think so.
That little guy?!
Yeah, I thought he was at least going to be huge
like the Lead Performers!
Hey, say something!
He's so weak!
Did this loser really challenge Kaido-sama?!
Hey, no taking a break!
Get up already!
Huh? How sharp his eyes are!
That's alright. I'll take time to torture you
so that your eyes will lose their luster!
What's wrong with him?!
He glared at us - prison guards!
I'm gonna teach you what happens
when you defy us!
Die!
My neck!
A fishbone came flying from the cell!
Idiot! Didn't you remove the bones
when you fed it?!
Ouch! My neck hurts!
What is it?! What's in this cell?!
No one knows!
Alright, stay in here!
Until your spirit gets broken
and you bend your knee to Kaido-sama!
--Prepare to be pushed around starting tomorrow!
--We'll give you a hard time!
Alright then!
Just for today, rest up!
It's gonna be hell from tomorrow!
UGH...
Ugh...
URRGH...
Urrgh...
DAMN...
Damn...
I'll get even with you...
I'LL GET EVEN WITH YOU...
KAIDO...
Kaido...
Hm?
HM?
Oh...
OH...
You...!!
YOU...!!
LAND OF WANO ACT ONE - END
To take down Kaido,
the Straw Hats make another move!
Meanwhile, at the Reverie, a major incident occurs!
The tumultuous New World.
At the center of that whirlpool, the Emperor of the Sea Blackbeard
starts moving to become the King of the Pirates!
On the next episode of One Piece! "The Holyland in Tumult!
Emperor of the Sea Blackbeard Cackles!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!