One Dream One Wish
kanaetai nara Over The Top
If you want to make it
come true, Over The Top
ONE PIECE - LAND OF WANO ARC
mitakoto mo nai sekai mezashi
Setting out into the unknown world
araburu namikaze koete
Weathering rough wind and waves
tsukisusumanakya dame sa
ichibannori shitain da
I have to keep going because
I want to get there first
shinpai toka atomawashi
douse shoubu ichika bachika
Worry later since it's
all sink or swim anyway
aite ga dekaku mietara
When your opponent looks daunting
kokoro ga chijinderu shouko
It's a sign that your heart is shrinking
nigeru nante choisu wa nai
Running away is not a choice
ippo soba e chikadukun da
Take one step closer
namaiki tte homekotoba?
Being called insolent's a compliment, right?
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
When things become tough,
that's when you should laugh
atarashii ashita sagashi ni ikitai no nara
If you want to look for a new tomorrow
tobikkiri no jishin wo migaite
Polish your unique confidence
tabi wo shita ashiato ga
Until your footsteps
sou! chizu ni kawaru made
Yes! Become a map
atarashii Horizon hora susunde kita bun
A new horizon, look, how far you've come
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
It's brighter and the
level of difficulty rises
yumeutsutsu de okose Hurricane
Live in your dream and raise a hurricane
saa! chaato kakimidase
Now! Stir up the rankings
One Dream One Wish
yume wa nigenai... zenbu Knock out
Dreams don't run away... Knock everything out
Over The Top
Luffy goes down before the overwhelmingly
powerful Emperor of the Sea, Kaido.
Lock him up!
Oh, y-yes, sir!
Once his spirit gets broken,
we can make him fight for us!
Okiku!
You are all safe!
Anyway, the situation is...
Oh, yeah!
What happened to Luffy?!
He looked like he wanted to
pick a fight with Kaido!
Prepare yourselves and listen...
Special report! Special report!
Oh! Luffy!
Oh, Luffy!
Lu...
WANTED FLYER - LUFFYTARO
What are you doing, Luffy?!
Alright, stay in here!
I'll get even with you...
Kaido...
"The Holyland in Tumult!
Emperor of the Sea Blackbeard Cackles!"
This is Gloom Island in the Grand Line,
the ruins of Muggy Kingdom.
Roronoa Zoro of the Straw Hats
once trained himself here.
Train me as a swordsman!
What are you doing?
That's just embarrassing.
I wanna get stronger!
I don't understand.
You still see me as an enemy.
Then why are you bowing to me
and asking for my guidance?
What's the purpose?
I wanna beat you!
In the old castle near the
lake of this fallen country,
that certain man still lives.
He is a member of the
A WARLORD OF THE SEA
STRONGEST SWORDSMAN IN THE WORLD
Seven Warlords of the Sea and is said to
be the strongest swordsman in the world.
His name is Dracule Mihawk.
DRACULE MIHAWK
A woman crashed into his residence
two years ago.
A member of the Thriller Bark Pirates.
GHOST PRINCESS PERONA
Ghost Princess Perona.
It's ready!
Do you want it?
No.
What?! You're so annoying!
--Get rid of these ghosts.
--Hmph! No way!
I took the trouble to cook it!
I'll eat it all myself!
Today's newspaper?
Moria-sama...
He's... alive...
"Gecko Moria and his zombie
army made a raid"...
He's alive!
Moria-sama is alive! He is!
Look at this! It's so great!
Moria-sama is alive!
Yeah, I read it this morning.
Why didn't you tell me, you fool?!
It's very important to me!
I don't care...
You should! He's my captain!
I thought he died in the
Paramount War two years ago!
I'm really glad!
If Moria-sama is alive,
maybe both Absalom and Hogback
are with him!
I wanna see him! Let's get going!
Oh, yeah...
He let me stay here for quite a long time.
While I was facing the Straw
Hats in Thriller Bark,
I was suddenly sent flying here
by Bartholomew Kuma.
It's already been more than two years.
Moria is a persistent guy.
Just like the zombies he manipulates.
Huh? Did you speak ill of Moria-sama?!
You thankless jerk!
I owe him nothing.
You owe me!
How many times do you
think I cooked for you?!
I cooked more than you.
I helped you with farming, too!
I let you stay here.
You're really annoying!
Fine!
I'm leaving!
Do whatever you like.
There are no hard feelings so that's good.
Be careful on your way.
Too kind!
Damn you! Don't say a nice thing
all of a sudden!
Thank you for everything!
You're such a noisy woman.
But...
...it's perhaps a good
decision to leave here now.
What?
In the Reverie that's still
in session at Marijoa,
a strange topic was brought up.
Meanwhile, this is the
Pirate Island of Fullalead.
It's a paradise for pirates.
Charge!
Where's Absalom?!
Where did you hide him?!
CAPTAIN OF THE THRILLER BARK PIRATES
(A FORMER WARLORD OF THE SEA)
BOUNTY: 320 MILLION BERRIES
GECKO MORIA
Why can't I kill them?!
Where's Absalom?!
I don't know!
You underlings don't know a damn thing!
Where's Blackbeard?!
Where's Teach?! Bring him out!
Don't mess with us!
Didn't you hear what I said?!
I said, "Bring Teach out"!
Teach! Where are you?!
Teach!
Teach! I know it's you!
Where did you hide Absalom?!
Here he comes... Moria.
Where's Teach?!
Tell me!
We won't tell you!
Brick Bat!
Now...!
If you don't wanna die,
tell me where he is already!
Is he there?
Come out!
I'll drag you down from there!
Blackbeard!
It's noisy-meow.
It's Gecko Moria, Pizarro-sama!
The former Warlord of the Sea!
Oh, why did you let him in?
H-He broke in! With his zombie army!
The port is fully destroyed!
What does he want?
CAPTAIN OF THE 4TH SHIP
OF THE BLACKBEARD PIRATES
CAPTAIN OF THE 4TH SHIP OF THE BLACKBEARD PIRATES
"CORRUPT KING" AVALO PIZARRO
He wants to see Commodore Teach!
Seems like he's looking for the invisible man, Absalom,
who came here the other day!
Oh, him!
If you're not coming out,
I'm gonna break in!
Moria-sama!
I'm here!
Is that Absalom?!
Boss! It's me!
Thank goodness! You're alive!
I'm good as new!
After we went separate ways,
we didn't hear from you at all,
so we were worried about you!
I'm sorry, Boss! This island is a paradise!
Because I was having so much fun,
I forgot to keep in touch!
Well if that's the reason, then that's okay!
But...
I shouldn't have done that to them.
Zombies, that's enough!
Go back to the ship!
The Blackbeard Pirates are known for
hunting power-users!
That's right.
Your Clear-Clear Fruit power that
enables you to become invisible.
So many people desire that.
I know that, too...
...very well...
What the?!
Ouch! Damn!
Who is it?!
Where are you?!
Do you know who I am?
Shiryu... of the Rain!
You worked at Impel Down
but defected to Teach!
That's sort of right.
CAPTAIN OF THE 2ND SHIP
OF THE BLACKBEARD PIRATES
SHIRYU OF THE RAIN
Did you like my power?
You became invisible!
That power belongs to Absalom...
No way...
That's right, Gecko Moria.
AN INVISIBLE HUMAN WHO
ATE THE CLEAR-CLEAR FRUIT
I got a useful power.
Damn...
Dammit!
Then, who the hell are you?!
Yip!
Devon!
CAPTAIN OF THE 6TH SHIP OF THE BLACKBEARD PIRATES
DOG-DOG FRUIT, MYTHICAL TYPE
"NINE-TAILED FOX" MODEL
"CRESCENT MOON HUNTER" CATARINA DEVON
Devon-sama!
Don't tell me Absalom is...
He shouldn't have come here
so recklessly!
We still have his dead body.
Do you wanna take it home?
You like dead bodies, don't you?
Damn you guys! I won't forgive you!
How dare you kill my friend!
I'll turn you all into corpses!
Oh, give it a try.
Gecko Moria!
That voice...
Don't corrupt public morals
on this Pirate Island.
Screw you! Show yourself!
No way!
I'm relaxing now.
This is a paradise for pirates!
It's gotta be fun!
You guys!
Do you like to party?!
Then...
come on board my ship!
AN EMPEROR OF THE SEA
COMMODORE OF THE BLACKBEARD PIRATES
BOUNTY: 2 BILLION 247 MILLION 600 THOUSAND
MARSHALL D. TEACH
Moria!
You like to, don't you?!
To party!
Did you read today's newspaper?!
It's never boring!
On the fourth day of the Reverie,
the damn captains of the
Revolutionary Army...
...finally appeared at the Sacred Marijoa
to take back Kuma
and clashed with Navy Admirals -
Ryokugyu and Fujitora!
Meanwhile,
at the Land of Wano
where the monster Kaido lives...
Straw Hat who is much talked about lately
and some other hot-blooded punks gathered.
And chasing them is...
...the crazy Emperor of the Sea - Big Mom!
What do you think will happen?!
It's already begun.
In order to sit on the throne,
the tough ones are crushing each other!
LAND OF WANO - ACT TWO
The turbulent Land of Wano - Act Two starts!
Sangoro, who cooks at a soba
cart where his allies gather,
and the kunoichi Onami
successfully play their parts
and the operation to take
down Kaido gets rolling!
Meanwhile, Luffy's indomitable
fighting spirit is raised up
even more and he creates
a furor along with Kid!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"It's On! The Special Operation to Bring Down Kaido!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!