One Dream One Wish
kanaetai nara Over The Top
If you want to make it
come true, Over The Top
ONE PIECE - LAND OF WANO ARC
mitakoto mo nai sekai mezashi
Setting out into the unknown world
araburu namikaze koete
Weathering rough wind and waves
tsukisusumanakya dame sa
ichibannori shitain da
I have to keep going because
I want to get there first
shinpai toka atomawashi
douse shoubu ichika bachika
Worry later since it's
all sink or swim anyway
aite ga dekaku mietara
When your opponent looks daunting
kokoro ga chijinderu shouko
It's a sign that your heart is shrinking
nigeru nante choisu wa nai
Running away is not a choice
ippo soba e chikadukun da
Take one step closer
namaiki tte homekotoba?
Being called insolent's a compliment, right?
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
When things become tough,
that's when you should laugh
atarashii ashita sagashi ni ikitai no nara
If you want to look for a new tomorrow
tobikkiri no jishin wo migaite
Polish your unique confidence
tabi wo shita ashiato ga
Until your footsteps
sou! chizu ni kawaru made
Yes! Become a map
atarashii Horizon hora susunde kita bun
A new horizon, look, how far you've come
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
It's brighter and the
level of difficulty rises
yumeutsutsu de okose Hurricane
Live in your dream and raise a hurricane
saa! chaato kakimidase
Now! Stir up the rankings
One Dream One Wish
yume wa nigenai... zenbu Knock out
Dreams don't run away... Knock everything out
Over The Top
Devastated by Kaido's reign, the people of
the Land of Wano have no choice
but to live in poverty.
Luffy and the others developed a raid operation
in order to open up the country.
The execution date is two weeks from now!
On the night of the Fire Festival!
We will make a raid...
...on Onigashima where Kaido lives!
However, soon after planning,
Luffy clashed with Kaido.
Gum-Gum...
...Kong Organ Gun!
Thunder Bagua!
Luffy suffered a terrible defeat
and was taken to a prison in the Udon region.
Meanwhile, the injured Otama
was transported to Amigasa Village,
then, Kin'emon and Dogstorm's group
headed to Atamayama...
...to recruit Shutenmaru.
LAND OF WANO - ACT TWO
ATAMAYAMA, KURI, LAND OF WANO
"It's On!
The Special Operation to Bring Down Kaido!"
He's as strong as Dogstorm-sama!
He's giving Dogstorm-sama a tough time...
How impressive.
Why, Ashura?
Why don't you want to use...
...that tremendous power
for the Kuri people that Oden-sama used to love?!
He's dead!
Why did you guys come back here
after all these years?!
We came back to accomplish Oden-sama's dream!
But you-gara have forgotten
what happened to Oden-sama,
and are just wielding your
sword at your own whim!
Shut up!
Don't talk as if you know everything!
If there is something you want to say...
Say it!
Foxfire Style - Fire-Willow Flash
Guys...
That's enough...
Dogstorm!
Ashura!
I thought you were better
than this, Ashura-san!
Kiku!
I've watched the Land of Wano
for two decades since Oden-sama died!
You guys suddenly came back
shouting whatever you like.
I won't listen!
You should be thankful
that I don't rob you blind before I go!
Don't you remember?!
This is how we were even back then!
I was fascinated by that man, Kozuki Oden,
and would risk my life for him as a samurai!
But I've never become a
servant for the Kozuki Clan!
Right?
Momonosuke!
Don't you remember what kind of man I was?!
I won't give up!
I'll make you join us!
Don't assume that everyone will
be thrilled to see the return
of the Kozuki Clan's samurai!
You guys abandoned the country for 20 years!
There is no way to compensate
for all those years!
Are you okay?
Yes...
Let's go.
I am sorry to interrupt you.
Raizo-san!
I was able to locate Luffy-dono.
He is in the Excavation Labor Camp at Udon.
I thought so!
Then, can I count on you to handle that?
Understood!
Otama! Are you awake?!
Master-sama... What happened to me?
You were attacked by Kaido
and these people cared for you!
Oh, I see.
Thank you!
I am grateful!
It was only some light scrapes.
You'll get better soon!
Thanks!
I fainted from fear right away...
so I don't quite remember
how I got attacked...
I only vaguely remember
how Horselina-chan fought desperately...
Where would you like to go,
Master-sama?!
An enemy became that loyal to you?
What an amazing power!
Where are Horselina-chan and Big Bro?!
Are they okay?!
We don't know what happened to Horselina...
Luffy was...
What?!
Big Bro was pretty badly hurt...
and taken to the camp in Udon?!
Oh, no!
Hey, you're wounded!
I'm more worried about Big Bro Luffy
than my wounds!
Don't worry! Luffy is our captain!
Udon is a region in the Land of Wano.
However, these days,
it is mostly used for the Excavation Labor Camp.
UDON, LAND OF WANO
It's a dreadful place where serious offenders
will be forced to do
heavy work until they die,
and no one has ever made it out there.
Here you go!
Every five big blocks of rock you haul
earns you one millet dumpling!
Outta my way!
That bastard...
I'll teach him a lesson soon!
Yum-yum!
It's delicious...
I'm impressed, Sanji...
I mean, Sangoro-kun.
Well, that's because I put more love into it!
Just for you, Orobi-chan!
We have a problem!
Ghosts appear! "A curse on you"!
Ghost sightings at the northern graveyard!
Here's an update!
Hey, paperboy!
Can I get one?
Thank you!
WANTED - HITOKIRI KAMAZO
"Hitokiri Kamazo"?
"There are reports of a killing spree
at the eighth block of district two"!
"The killer is Hitokiri Kamazo"...
You scared me...
It's him!
Once you see him, you're likely to die!
How scary!
What is his true identity?!
WANTED - HITOKIRI KAMAZO
My husband was killed by him, too!
Now, gather 'round! Gather 'round!
The next is Ushimitsu Kozo
who appears at the witching hour!
He's a cool thief who steals from
very rich people and gives money
to the poor living in row houses!
Is he a superhero or a villain?!
What is his true identity?!
If you want to know, buy the broadsheet!
Ah! Ushimitsu-sama!
--I'll take one!
--Yes, thank you!
He's quite popular.
Now, get your own!
It's a broadsheet with some exclusives!
--I'll take one, too!
--Me, too!
The Reversed Crescent Moon!
Who gave me this?
Are they really back?!
The Kozuki Clan!
Hey... Isn't this the work of the ghosts?
Suspicion won't help!
This will start a great fire!
I'm going!
If this was 10 years ago,
I would have fought...
But what are you guys
going to do for weapons?
In this country, if you aren't a samurai,
you can't even carry swords or other weapons.
The kendo halls are all closed
and all martial arts like karate and judo
are prohibited.
Orochi has already destroyed
rebellious elements!
Even if it's with my bare hands,
I wanna fight!
This will be our last chance!
I've been waiting for so long!
I can't help
...trembling with excitement!
I won't give in!
Wait for me, Kaido!
No, we don't need geisha.
Don't let anyone approach this room!
Yes, sir!
Onami.
What a kunoichi needs the
most is a calm heart.
Keep that in mind.
It's time to use...
Wait a minute, Onami. Don't rush.
I like how your youthfulness
gets ahead of you...
But I want you to remember
and enjoy the fact...
...that a mature woman's attractiveness alone
is a weapon.
You are evil indeed...
This is the order sheet for arms and weapons.
You are evil indeed!
Huh? Am I?
Oh, this is a lot!
Is there going to be a war or something?
We don't know what's happening abroad.
We'll just make whatever they want.
You are, oh, evil indeed!
Huh? Am I?
Look closely, Onami.
My eyes are too aged.
You'll be fine!
Just stay calm as you watch.
That head is blocking my view...
Somebody's there!
Who are you?!
--You're too loud, Shinobu-chan!
--Who are you?! Who are you?! Who are you?!
Be quiet!
--Get them!
--There are intruders in the attic!
Who are you?! Who are you?! Who are you?!
I'm scared! I'm scared! I'm scared!
Please be quiet!
Hey, Jack...
The offerings from Kuri are too low.
Now without Doflamingo around,
you know who our next business
partner is, don't you?!
I'm sorry, Big Brothers!
We don't need another burden -
just this idiot Queen is enough.
That's right! Just this piece
of scum King is enough.
Understood, Jack the Stooge?!
And you, Queen!
Why is it taking so long to
break those brats' fighting spirits?!
You moron!
Shut up, you sadistic pervert!
The imprisoned Luffy and Kid!
The two rookies in fierce rivalry ferociously race around!
They stir things up in the camp
where there is supposed to be no hope or future!
Luffy even fights against prison guards
and is sentenced to death in the end!
Will he be able to survive?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Rampage! The Prisoners - Luffy and Kid!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!