One Dream One Wish
If you want to make it
come true, Over The Top
kanaetai nara Over The Top
ONE PIECE - LAND OF WANO ARC
Setting out into the unknown world
mitakoto mo nai sekai mezashi
Weathering rough wind and waves
araburu namikaze koete
I have to keep going because
I want to get there first
tsukisusumanakya dame sa
ichibannori shitain da
Worry later since it's
all sink or swim anyway
shinpai toka atomawashi
douse shoubu ichika bachika
When your opponent looks daunting
aite ga dekaku mietara
It's a sign that your heart is shrinking
kokoro ga chijinderu shouko
Running away is not a choice
nigeru nante choisu wa nai
Take one step closer
ippo soba e chikadukun da
Being called insolent's a compliment, right?
namaiki tte homekotoba?
When things become tough,
that's when you should laugh
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
If you want to look for a new tomorrow
atarashii ashita sagashi ni ikitai no nara
Polish your unique confidence
tobikkiri no jishin wo migaite
Until your footsteps
tabi wo shita ashiato ga
Yes! Become a map
sou! chizu ni kawaru made
A new horizon, look, how far you've come
atarashii Horizon hora susunde kita bun
It's brighter and the
level of difficulty rises
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
Live in your dream and raise a hurricane
yumeutsutsu de okose Hurricane
Now! Stir up the rankings
saa! chaato kakimidase
One Dream One Wish
Dreams don't run away... Knock everything out
yume wa nigenai... zenbu Knock out
Over The Top
Nami and Shinobu who obtained
information on their enemies
were discovered and chased by them,
but they successfully escaped.
Meanwhile, Luffy who has been held captive
by Kaido's subordinates...
...was forced to work at the Excavation Labor Camp in Udon
along with Kid.
You ate all of my food!
Now, it's time for punishment!
"A Great Sensation!
Sanji's Special Soba!"
It's the Special Soba!
Sangoro's Special Soba!
I want to eat it now!
Here! Thank you for waiting!
Oh, it looks good!
It's good! It's insanely good!
Any information on Luffy?
He's in the Excavation
Labor Camp in Udon, right?
It's far from here.
But I bet he'll make it out of there before the big day.
I get to eat Sanji's cooking again!
I'm glad that you came back safely!
I don't care if you like it or not...
Orobi-chan! How does it taste?
Well, it tastes amazing!
Orobi-chan the geisha is more amazing!
Well...
The soba is good
but it's only attracting girls...
Draw in samurai
with something spicy that would go with sake!
What's with that look?!
Don't you wanna recruit more allies, you fool?!
Wait, Franky! Male customers.
Hello!
Excuse us, ladies!
Hey! Don't cut in, guys!
Huh?! What did you say?!
Shut your mouth!
They're the Kyoshiro Family...
What?!
Hey, outta our way!
Your place is thriving, young man!
Yeah, I'm pleased!
Are you guys customers?
If you wanna eat, get in line!
No, we came to ask you...
...who permits you to do business
on this land?
We're the Kyoshiro Family
and this is our turf...
Unless you pay us, you're not
allowed to run a shop here!
KAKU-SAN, KUNI-SAN, SUKE-SAN
KYOSHIRO FAMILY
Oh, is that so?
Those people... Maybe they're...
Do you know something about them?
I went to a man named Kyoshiro's banquet hall
the other day...
Orochi-sama is a coward!
Booze! Bring me more booze!
He was quite an arrogant samurai...
It appears he's the boss of a yakuza group.
And they're probably his underlings.
Hey, can't you hear me?!
I said you gotta pay up!
Why?
Why? Because we can't help you
even if someone comes to attack your shop.
I don't need your help
because I'm strong.
Here, thank you for waiting!
Thanks!
You said you're strong?
Then, try to protect the shop!
Soba!
Hey!
Don't eat soba from this place!
Is she crying or laughing?
Soba!
Oh, no! That pisses Sanji off the most!
Go home, you fools!
The shop is closing for today!
Go, go! He ran out of soba!
Come on! Just go away now!
Don't, Sanji!
Don't make any trouble!
Oh, no! We'd better move!
Hey!
What do you want, you fool?!
I need you to finish your food.
My dear customer...
Huh?! Do you wanna fight, you jerk?!
Hey! Suke! Kaku!
Yes!
Let's beat him up!
Hm?! A fight?!
Go to hell!
You bastard!
Ow, ow, ow...
Damn!
Die!
Ow, ow, ow...
Big Bro!
What?! That soba guy is so strong!
So cool! The soba man!
Sanji! Let me in!
Here we go!
Stop! Dammit!
What are you gonna do to me?!
Franosuke Iron...
...Suplex!
--That carpenter is also...
--But they shouldn't do that!
Now, eat! All of it!
The soba you wasted! Eat it all!
--Here, eat it! Eat up everything!
--Big Bro! Big Bro!
What? Would you like some?!
D... D...
Don't you forget it!
You'll regret this!
Now, wake up, wake up!
Thanks!
Well, I knew it was gonna end up like this,
but was it okay to kick their asses?
Maybe we shouldn't have messed with them...
There was a long line
but now, literally no one's here...
This is right about the
time some bad ass appears.
She's the girl who had her soba knocked over.
She's a weirdo,
crying and laughing at the same time.
Hm? Wait a sec...
What is it?
I saw her before somewhere...
All right!
I made a lot of money!
I didn't think I'd sold so much!
What do you want?
Hey, does that medicine heal
any kind of wound?
What? Oh, yes!
This will stop bleeding and pain!
Anything can be remedied with this toad oil!
That's wonderful!
I met her at the shrine.
I'm sorry to cause you trouble earlier...
There was still some soba left!
Please have some!
Whoa! Thank you!
It...
I-It's delicious!
TOKO - A CHILD FROM THE CAPITAL
Oh, yeah? That's good!
It's good!
It's really good!
Seeing you makes me smile!
Oh, yeah?!
I don't know why but I'm happy!
Oh, yeah! Listen!
The Special Soba really has a good reputation
so I wanted to eat it no matter what...
But I was stunned when I saw the big line!
There were way more people than
for the toad oil which works really well, right?
Yeah, there were!
And I was in line for a long time
so I'm already late for work.
Work?
Do you work?!
Uh-huh! I worked hard
and managed to save enough money to buy the soba,
but it was knocked over so I was sad!
Now I'm happy!
This is the best soba I've ever had!
Oh, yeah?! You like it that much?
Thanks!
Anyway, what's your name?
My name is Toko.
But say it with an "O" at the front!
TOKO
"O"?
OTOKO
O... toko-chan?
OTOKO (MALE) ?
Oh! It's "Otoko"!
I'm not otoko (male).
But my name is Otoko!
I'm a girl but my name is Otoko!
Isn't it funny? Isn't it amusing?
Otoko! Otoko! Otoko!
People always say it's easy to remember!
Uh-huh! Yeah! I'm sure I won't forget!
That's a good name!
Yeah, it is!
So cool!
Oh, it was delicious.
Thank you!
Okay! Come back again!
Uh-huh!
Oh, no! I'm really late! Very, very late!
Oh, yeah!
I'll be passing through this street later!
Today, we have the Oiran's procession!
Oiran?!
Toko-chan, by any chance,
are you a Kamuro?
That's right. I'm a Kamuro!
It's already started!
I have to run! Bye-bye! See you!
The Oiran's beautiful
so please enjoy!
See you!
Oh, boy, she's so funny!
Toko-chan's cheerful. Very cute!
The much-talked-about Oiran's procession
will pass through here!
Oiran?
OIRAN
Kamuro?
KAMURO
An Oiran is...
Where did you emerge from,
you paper-lantern hag!
Ma'am!
Who did you call a wrinkled
paper-lantern hag?!
I'll illuminate your hide, you little snot!
An Oiran is, in a sense, the top idol of the Land of Wano!
A superstar!
Uh-huh! Uh-huh!
There is only one Oiran in the country now!
The chosen woman's name is Komurasaki!
A dream woman for men!
A role model for women!
Very sophisticated!
And her beauty could destabilize the country!
The gods themselves couldn't
sully her nobility!
That's who the Oiran, Komurasaki, is!
No way!
There's no such woman in the world!
If you don't believe me,
see for yourself!
There! You hear that?!
The cheers for her
and the sound of exciting music.
The Oiran is in procession to Orochi Castle!
Today, they have the Shogun's banquet
at the castle!
The girl from earlier is a Kamuro,
a child attendant for an Oiran.
Hmmm, I see!
Orobi, I have good news for you!
So I ran around the Flower Capital!
For me?!
Congratulations!
What?!
You've been summoned to the castle, too!
It's your desire to meet
Shogun Orochi-sama, right?!
Yes!
Wow! That's our Robin-chan!
Now, let's go home and get ready!
Yes! I can't wait!
No slacking off!
UDON, WANO
Hey, straw hat guy!
You're really something!
Which family are you from?!
It felt good yesterday!
All they talk about is you guys in every cell!
Leave me alone...
Don't say that.
Everyone here likes you so much!
Pfft! He's so unfriendly...
Straw hat man!
Thank you very much for saving
my useless life yesterday!
OLD MAN HYO - A LONGTIME PRISONER
I had to beat him anyway
so don't mention it.
Oh, yeah. You can have these!
If you're hungry, you can't even work!
Oh, no! Please don't!
A good-for-nothing like me can't accept those!
Oh, come on, just keep them.
Goodbye!
I-I'll use them wisely!
Thank you! Thank you!
What a funny guy!
Luffy-dono!
Raizo! How did it go?!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Um... The key to the Sea Prism Stone cuffs...
I found it, but, um...
It's under tight security.
In addition to a guard,
they keep it in a Sea Prism Stone box!
But...!
I'll steal it at any cost.
Please give me a little more time.
Okay! I got it!
All right!
In front of the Straw Hats who
are on an undercover operation,
Komurasaki, Wano's most beautiful woman and an Oiran,
walks through in procession.
Her gorgeous appearance! That amorous look!
However, behind the beauty, she
is hiding her true identity!
A storm of flowers sweeps
through the Land of Wano!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Luxurious and Gorgeous!
Wano's Most Beautiful Woman - Komurasaki!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!