One Dream One Wish
If you want to make it come true, Over The Top
kanaetai nara Over The Top
ONE PIECE - LAND OF WANO ARC
Setting out into the unknown world
mitakoto mo nai sekai mezashi
Weathering rough wind and waves
araburu namikaze koete
I have to keep going because I want to get there first
tsukisusumanakya dame sa ichibannori shitain da
Worry later since it's all sink or swim anyway
shinpai toka atomawashi douse shoubu ichika bachika
When your opponent looks daunting
aite ga dekaku mietara
It's a sign that your heart is shrinking
kokoro ga chijinderu shouko
Running away is not a choice
nigeru nante choisu wa nai
Take one step closer
ippo soba e chikadukun da
Being called insolent's a compliment, right?
namaiki tte homekotoba?
When things become tough, that's when you should laugh
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
If you want to look for a new tomorrow
atarashii ashita sagashi ni ikitai no nara
Polish your unique confidence
tobikkiri no jishin wo migaite
Until your footsteps
tabi wo shita ashiato ga
Yes! Become a map
sou! chizu ni kawaru made
A new horizon, look, how far you've come
atarashii Horizon hora susunde kita bun
It's brighter and the level of difficulty rises
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
Live in your dream and raise a hurricane
yumeutsutsu de okose Hurricane
Now! Stir up the rankings
saa! chaato kakimidase
One Dream One Wish
Dreams don't run away... Knock everything out
yume wa nigenai... zenbu Knock out
Over The Top
Luffy is being forced to work at the Excavation Labor Camp
shackled with the Sea Prism Stone cuffs.
If you're hungry, you can't even work!
I-I'll use them wisely!
Thank you! Thank you!
Meanwhile, Sanji and the others who were trying to
recruit samurai for the upcoming battle...
...faced the Kyoshiro Family.
Don't eat soba from this place!
Franosuke Iron...
...Suplex!
An Oiran is, in a sense, the top idol of the Land of Wano!
A superstar!
Uh-huh! Uh-huh!
There is only one Oiran in the country now!
The chosen woman's name is Komurasaki!
A dream woman for men!
A role model for women!
Very sophisticated!
And her beauty could destabilize the country!
"Luxurious and Gorgeous!
Wano's Most Beautiful Woman - Komurasaki!"
Komurasaki the top Oiran is in procession!
Oh, Komurasaki-sama!
Look this way, Oiran!
KOMURASAKI
Ah! Oiran!
Oiran! So beautiful!
Whoa! Komurasaki-sama!
Oh! She's dazzling!
Too dazzling to lay eyes on!
I'm sorry I'm late!
Hey! Toko!
You made me worry.
Big Sis, I'm sorry!
Now, get to work.
Okay!
Oiran! Ah! Look this way!
Komurasaki...
EXCAVATION LABOR CAMP
UDON, LAND OF WANO
It's you again!
You work so hard.
Mister!
Just how many dumplings
are you trying to earn, mister?
I'm not gonna give you any!
Cut it out! Caribou!
Don't be so mean... We're friends.
WET-HAIRED CARIBOU
CAPTAIN OF THE CARIBOU PIRATES
BOUNTY: 210 MILLION BERRIES
Wet-Haired Caribou of the Caribou Pirates.
This ill-famed atrocious pirate and Luffy...
...met in the Sabaody Archipelago.
While attempting to take down the Straw Hats,
he raided the Sunny on her way to the Fish-Man Island
but failed!
After arriving at the Fish-Man Island,
he carried on doing evil,
but he was defeated by Luffy and Pekoms.
Later, he reached the New World
and tried to worm his way through everything.
He discovered a new way of life there.
But he was defeated by Drake
who appeared unexpectedly.
He was sent to the Land of Wano
and was forced to work as a prisoner
at the Excavation Labor Camp in Udon.
Mister!
Give me some, too!
Millet dumplings for the needy!
No way! Work!
That's too cruel!
These Sea Stone Prism cuffs...
I heard they made them less powerful
so that prisoners could work.
But I'm quite paralyzed...
Push yourself harder!
You're so harsh, mister.
If you give me dumplings,
I'll be your henchman.
I've been here way longer than you,
so I know more things than you do, you know.
Mister, you'll do it, right?
Shut up!
You're gonna do the jailbreak thing, right?
--Come on, tell me!
--Go away!
I beg you!
Don't touch me!
Take me with you!
A soba cook beat you?
SAKYO, FLOWER CAPITAL
That's right! He was quite strong!
He overpowered the three of us...
I'm gonna be busy today.
I'm invited to Shogun Orochi's banquet...
Contact Queen...
Let him...
...send assassins.
But it'll cause an uproar...
--I don't care!
--Yes, sir!
Orochi-sama...
The Oiran is heading this way now.
Good...
Komurasaki...
Today, I'm gonna make her mine!
Komurasaki-sama!
Komurasaki the top Oiran!
Here she comes! Komurasaki-sama!
It's the Oiran's procession!
Isn't she here yet?!
There are tons of people here.
I wonder how beautiful she is.
Can't wait! Komurasaki-chan!
KOMURASAKI
I hate... that bitch...
Komurasaki!
Komurasaki...!
I think they're looking for trouble!
H-Hey!
I've got to...
...kill that bitch!
I'll get kicked out of the city...
It's all over!
If I'm gonna die anyway...
I'll kill her, too!
Whoa-whoa!
What are you up to?!
Don't do it, guys!
--Komurasaki!
--You're in the way!
Move!
Stay away from the Oiran!
Komurasaki...
Now, sing more! Dance!
NEARLY A YEAR AGO
I'll buy out everyone's contract
once you become my favorite courtesan!
I have tons of money, you see?!
If you're rich, you can get whatever you want!
I want to be with you forever...
What?
With an old geezer like me?!
If I have to live as Orochi-sama's puppet,
I would rather you bought out my contract...
But the ransom on me is
an enormous amount of money...
So it is an impossible dream...
If even just this conversation
comes to Orochi-sama's knowledge...
You must not lose heart!
If that is what you want,
I, Bingoh, will stake my manhood
and make it happen!
Really?
Even if it's a lie, I'm still happy...
You don't have enough money to pay me back?!
I'm sorry!
Are you taking me for a fool?!
You think crying will help?!
I'll take your house as collateral for the loan!
Here, Komurasaki.
I've never seen a large amount of money like that!
Komurasaki, this is an advance payment
to buy you from the pleasure hall.
It's not enough yet but keep it for me.
Then, let me enter it in the ledger...
Not necessary!
What kind of fool distrusts the woman he loves...
Your word is good enough.
Bingoh-sama...
I cannot wait till you take me with you.
Don't cry...
Alright!
I will organize a funeral for you.
And I will lend you money for it
and for living expenses.
Stop crying already!
You need to pay me back double!
It's your own fault for being too naive!
Here is your money!
No... That is a lot!
But...
What's wrong?
To tell you the truth, someone else
recently bid to buy me...
What?!
I must hurry!
I need more and more money to buy her...
Is there anything that I can sell?
I sold my storehouse, Komurasaki!
I'm so happy...
Enough, already!
I'm sick and tired of you!
I'm going back to my parents' house!
Do whatever you want!
I'm on my way... Komurasaki!
I even abandoned my family!
Oh, no, your health...
Buying medicine is a waste of money...
I'm fine.
Once I get what I want,
I'm going to be the happiest person in the world.
I dream of... a life with you...
every night, too...
Oh... Komurasaki...
I got all the money...
I no longer have a house!
Let's live as we like together
starting from zero!
This is the final 500 Gold coins...
With this, I can buy your contract, Komurasaki!
What?
I'm sorry. The Oiran is sick today...
Oh, no!
Hand this to her at any cost.
I'll come back again...
Komurasaki...
Komurasaki!
I'll rescue you from the pleasure hall!
Let's live together!
You really did it!
Way to go! You old pervert!
Oh, guys!
Stop laughing and get Komurasaki for me...
She'll live with me in happiness!
Idiot! Stop dreaming!
Do you have enough money
to liberate her?
Of course! Komurasaki has it!
I asked her to keep it for me!
Oh, Bingoh-san.
Oh, Komurasaki! Tell them the truth!
They have no idea how serious our relationship is
and are saying whatever they like!
Huh?
You said you were giving me the money,
didn't you?
What?!
I spent it all.
Thank you.
That old man really thought
Komurasaki-san fell in love with him!
Who's that old fart?
What?
Komurasaki...
B-Boss Kyoshiro!
So...
...you're the old man who's been hanging
around Komurasaki these days...
Hanging around... Th-That's not true!
Komurasaki, you're joking, right?
I really sacrificed everything!
I don't have anything now!
I threw away everything I had for you!
Oh, no...
How many of these guys has it been now?
You're interfering with our business
by crying out here, old man.
If you're done, leave!
You lecherous old geezer!
Stop!
Stop...
I'm leaving!
I'm leaving so stop!
Komurasaki...
Komurasaki the top Oiran...
...is in procession!
KOMURASAKI THE OIRAN
WANO'S GREATEST COURTESAN
Komurasaki-sama!
So pretty!
So splendid!
Oh, how gorgeous...
Too bright! My eyes!
Komurasaki!
I turned my house, family,
and everything into money!
Give me back the money I entrusted to you!
You thief!
Asking for your gift back?
How pathetic you are...
To me, men are like dogs who bring me money.
Without it, you're worthless.
Now you guys can't get away!
Don't give us trouble,
you penniless fools!
People who can't make money
have no right to live in the Flower Capital.
In the name of Shogun Orochi,
we'll expel you from the city!
Please don't!
Outside the city,
we can't even have a human life!
Damn! Go to hell!
Komurasaki!
I... don't like...
...poor people.
They can only count on themselves.
Zoro's strange wanderings
with a sycophant named Tonoyasu creates turmoil!
After catching a dealer cheating,
they face Wano's worst criminal group, the Kyoshiro Family!
To pay back his debt for sushi, Zoro makes a big bet!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Tale of Chivalry! Zoro and Tonoyasu's Little Trip!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!