One Dream One Wish
If you want to make it come true, Over The Top
kanaetai nara Over The Top
ONE PIECE - LAND OF WANO ARC
Setting out into the unknown world
mitakoto mo nai sekai mezashi
Weathering rough wind and waves
araburu namikaze koete
I have to keep going because I want to get there first
tsukisusumanakya dame sa ichibannori shitain da
Worry later since it's all sink or swim anyway
shinpai toka atomawashi douse shoubu ichika bachika
When your opponent looks daunting
aite ga dekaku mietara
It's a sign that your heart is shrinking
kokoro ga chijinderu shouko
Running away is not a choice
nigeru nante choisu wa nai
Take one step closer
ippo soba e chikadukun da
Being called insolent's a compliment, right?
namaiki tte homekotoba?
When things become tough, that's when you should laugh
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
If you want to look for a new tomorrow
atarashii ashita sagashi ni ikitai no nara
Polish your unique confidence
tobikkiri no jishin wo migaite
Until your footsteps
tabi wo shita ashiato ga
Yes! Become a map
sou! chizu ni kawaru made
A new horizon, look, how far you've come
atarashii Horizon hora susunde kita bun
It's brighter and the level of difficulty rises
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
Live in your dream and raise a hurricane
yumeutsutsu de okose Hurricane
Now! Stir up the rankings
saa! chaato kakimidase
One Dream One Wish
Dreams don't run away... Knock everything out
yume wa nigenai... zenbu Knock out
Over The Top
At the Flower Capital, Komurasaki the Oiran
was making her way to Orochi Castle,
to attend the Shogun's banquet.
Her beauty captures people's hearts,
however, in the shadows,
there are some who hold grudge against her.
To me, men are like dogs who bring me money.
Without it, you're worthless.
I... don't like...
...poor people.
"A Tale of Chivalry!
Zoro and Tonoyasu's Little Trip!"
Dice in.
Now, place your bets!
Evens!
We've got a bet on even numbers!
Anyone for odds?!
Odds!
We've also got a bet on odds!
Now, place yours!
Odds!
Evens!
Last call, everyone!
Here we go!
Five and one, it's evens.
Wow!
People often say that
it all depends on the roll of the dice...
But you're special, mister!
You're lucky and on a winning streak!
There.
That's for the sushi.
Thanks for paying for it on the boat.
Wow! This is more than I paid, mister!
Don't worry. I'll win more.
Man!
We just stopped by
to take shelter from the rain!
If I stay with you, I'll never go hungry!
All right!
You're the coolest man in the Land of Wano!
I think the sake will taste good tonight.
Zoro went missing?!
NIN
Come on! He always does that!
Haven't you seen him in the Flower Capital?
No, I haven't!
SOME DESERTED VILLAGE, KURI
He is as free as the clouds.
I guess it's not so bad to be unconventional...
I will just trust everyone and wait here!
If I get to eat yummy stuff,
guarding the food storage isn't so bad.
You're right!
Guys, don't push it too far.
It's fine now. They left.
Carrot, don't just take carrots...
Why?! These carrots are
sweet and delicious!
Okay, so we could sneak inside pretty easily
thanks to your hole-digging skills...
Okay, I guess we got enough.
Let's go back!
Not yet! You still have an important task.
Oh, yeah!
--Leave it where it can easily be found.
--Okay!
"The Atamayama Thieves Brigade was here.
Shutenmaru."
Do you think the beautiful Oiran is a good excuse
for coming to work late, Kid Fra?!
No, Boss!
I'm sorry!
Well, but I couldn't believe
there was such a pretty woman!
I know how you feel!
But it could've affected my honor, you fool!
MINATOMO
A LEGENDARY MASTER CARPENTER
WHO BUILT KAIDO'S MANSION
Yes! I'm so sorry!
I wasn't going to bring dishonor
to the name of Minatomo, the legendary master carpenter!
Since you work 10 times more than anyone else though,
I don't mind if you ditch work sometimes.
If you show me the blueprints of the mansion on Onigashima,
I'll work 10 times more...
I mean, even 100 times more!
Oh, yeah.
About the blueprints of the mansion on Onigashima
that you've asked me for repeatedly...
Those... Um...
Oh, this is just a wipe...
Oh, please!
About those...
I remembered...
I pawned them about 10 years ago!
What do you think I've worked under you
week after week for?!
Ouch! Damn you, stop it, Kid Fra!
You jumped on your master carpenter!
Who do you think you are?!
You piece of wood!
You're driving me crazy!
Take this! Franosuke Rocket Launcher!
You're fired! Get out of here, you idiot!
Gladly!
I no longer have business here!
PAWN
A pawn from 10 years ago? Blueprints?
But we rarely take those...
Oh, maybe those!
What? Do you have them?!
Oh well, of course, they were forfeited...
I wonder who bought such a thing.
Hmmm, who was it?
Um...
Oh, yeah!
It was Kumagoro from the tenement,
who said he'd study them. No doubt about it!
KUMAGORO FROM THE TENEMENT
Who's that?!
Kumagoro!
Blueprints?
Oh yeah, I certainly had them once,
but I fell behind in rent
and they were taken away by Kobei-san, the landlord.
KOBEI, HIS LANDLORD
Who the hell?!
ROOMS AVAILABLE
Kobei!
Oh, the blueprints.
Those were good, so I gave them to my favorite geisha.
Kisegawa-chan.
--Do you know her?
--No!
KISEGAWA, HIS FAVORITE GEISHA
I didn't know what to do with them
so I used them as a dish mat, but then Tokijiro-san...
All right, who is that?
TOKIJIRO
I had them!
But Rakuda-san said they could be sold for quite a price
and took them away!
RAKUDA
What? Rakuda (Camel)? An animal?
I'm Rakuda!
Man, because of the blueprints,
I had a terrible time!
Some guy made off with them!
He was hiding his face
but he said he came from Kuri.
Kuri?!
Um...
Oh, I'm sorry. It's sea bream.
Is that how sea bream always looks?
Thank you for shopping with us!
Franosuke-dono!
You are looking good.
I am! By the way, what are you selling?!
What? I'm peddling fish.
You're sticking out!
Kids are surrounding you!
Anyway, you were in a big hurry earlier.
Is anything wrong?
Oh, yeah! Sticking out is nothing!
I have an even bigger problem!
The guy I was looking to get the blueprints from
didn't have them!
Check the swords over there next.
What?! The blueprints of Kaido's mansion
must be here in Kuri?!
Yeah! I ran all over the capital
but I couldn't find them!
I don't know what to do now!
Sorry to cause you trouble.
Franosuke-dono, support the other missions
in the capital!
Got it!
Clank.
Hmm... Who would want the blueprints of
Kaido's mansion?
Could it be...
Duke-sama! Kin-san!
Hey!
Whew!
We stole so much.
Food... And weapons from the factory!
Nice work. Did you leave the note?
Yes, of course!
THE ATAMAYAMA THIEVES BRIGADE WAS HERE
SHUTENMARU
But is it okay?
Because of that note,
Ashura Doji could be attacked by the Animal Kingdom Pirates.
That is what we want.
Being attacked will infuriate him.
This way, we can goad him
into fighting the Animal Kingdom Pirates.
Otherwise, his spirit will never be ignited again!
When I think of the pain he suffered for two decades,
it feels like it's a little too high-handed...
I know!
But by fair means or foul,
we definitely need him to take down Kaido!
We need Ashura Doji's help!
Now, place your bets!
Odds!
Wow! You're extremely unreserved!
Mister!
We've got a bet on odds!
All set.
Here we go!
Four and two, it's evens!
Oh, you lost!
Well, gambling is all about luck!
You sometimes lose.
Next round, dice in.
Now, place your bets!
All my remaining bets...
...on evens...
Wow! You're going for the gamble of a lifetime!
How cool, mister!
Evens! We've got a bet on evens!
All set.
Here we go!
One and two, it's odds!
Oh! You lost again...
No-Sword Style...
Dragon Twister!
Oh?! That's a cheat!
They're so uncool.
Guys! Come out!
Oh, you can offer cool hospitality, too.
Guys! Get him!
One-Sword Style...
Dragon Quake!
Wow! Everyone collapsed
without so much as a cut!
Whoa, wait a minute, mister!
As they say, there are evens and odds in this world.
Both good and evil come in turn.
Let's put an end to this here!
Okay?!
Now, manager,
there was an objection to the last game.
So how about giving this gentleman
what he won up to that point?
Damn! Take it!
Don't ever come back!
RUINS OF KIBI, LAND OF WANO
Oh, I was so scared! Were you, mister?!
Could you shut up?
Wow! How kind of you to say that!
You subtly care about my voice.
How nice. Thanks!
Oh, sorry for not introducing myself sooner,
my name is Tonoyasu.
Everyone calls me "Sycophant Yasu."
Nice to meet you!
Gee, you're enticing
even when you don't speak!
You stud!
Girls won't leave you alone, mister!
Why are you following me?
At the gambling house earlier,
I realized.
"If I follow this man,
everything will be alright"!
But normal people don't mess with those men.
They're underlings of the Kyoshiro Family,
the terrifying yakuza group from the capital.
Oh, that was so staggering!
If I were a woman,
I'd go weak in the knees!
What's the matter, mister?!
That looks familiar.
Oh-ho, you are incredibly perceptive!
What you see in the distance is the Flower Capital!
And before that,
there is Ebisu Town aka Okobore Town!
That's my hometown!
Ebisu... Sounds like it's wealthy.
Why is it named Ebisu, you wonder?
You'll see once you get there!
You guys don't want us to open up the country, either!
Right?
Because you're looking to buy weapons to fight pirates,
from pirates.
It's really strange...
Isn't it?!
Now without the broker, Doflamingo aka Joker,
you guys lost your cover,
so you have no choice but to deal with us directly...
I know you are anxious
so we can take unfair advantage...
But you're already making unreasonable demands.
The Land of Wano is fully self-sufficient!
Everyone seems happy, right?
If there is something we need,
that would be greater power!
This time, we only asked for a warship...
But next time, we want Dr. Vegapunk!
That's impossible!
I didn't ask if it's possible or not!
The Celestial Dragons? The Navy?
You know we're not afraid of them, don't you?
Even if you attack us all at once,
you can't defeat us.
Because Kaido is backing me up!
No one can stop me!
Open the gate!
Komurasaki the top Oiran has arrived!
So you have a little sister, Momo-kun?
Hey, Tama!
You're being rude!
Who do you think I am?!
You're Momo-kun.
Forget it...
Yes, I have a little sister.
If she is alive, she would be 26 now.
There were people who saw my mother dying,
but no one said Hiyori died.
So I truly believe she is alive somewhere!
I hope you can see her.
No, I won't see her!
Once Orochi knows her identity,
he will go after her!
I will only see her once we win the fight!
KOZUKI MOMONOSUKE
SON OF THE LATE DAIMYO OF KURI, LAND OF WANO
Luffy and Kid are incarcerated.
When the two rookies are about to clash, a fearful singing voice
echoes over the rough sea around the Land of Wano!
It belongs to Emperor of the Sea Big Mom!
Kaido and Big Mom start a fierce fight over Luffy!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A State of Emergency! Big Mom Closes in!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!