One Dream One Wish
If you want to make it
come true, Over The Top
kanaetai nara Over The Top
ONE PIECE - LAND OF WANO ARC
Setting out into the unknown world
mitakoto mo nai sekai mezashi
Weathering rough wind and waves
araburu namikaze koete
I have to keep going because
I want to get there first
tsukisusumanakya dame sa
ichibannori shitain da
Worry later since it's
all sink or swim anyway
shinpai toka atomawashi
douse shoubu ichika bachika
When your opponent looks daunting
aite ga dekaku mietara
It's a sign that your heart is shrinking
kokoro ga chijinderu shouko
Running away is not a choice
nigeru nante choisu wa nai
Take one step closer
ippo soba e chikadukun da
Being called insolent's a compliment, right?
namaiki tte homekotoba?
When things become tough,
that's when you should laugh
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
If you want to look for a new tomorrow
atarashii ashita sagashi ni ikitai no nara
Polish your unique confidence
tobikkiri no jishin wo migaite
Until your footsteps
tabi wo shita ashiato ga
Yes! Become a map
sou! chizu ni kawaru made
A new horizon, look, how far you've come
atarashii Horizon hora susunde kita bun
It's brighter and the
level of difficulty rises
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
Live in your dream and raise a hurricane
yumeutsutsu de okose Hurricane
Now! Stir up the rankings
saa! chaato kakimidase
One Dream One Wish
Dreams don't run away... Knock everything out
yume wa nigenai... zenbu Knock out
Over The Top
In order to take down Emperor of the Sea Kaido
who is reigning over the Land of Wano,
Luffy and the others
determined to make a raid.
Will they be able to avenge the late Oden
and open up the country?!
The date is set for the night of the Fire Festival
on Onigashima!
So you have a little sister, Momo-kun?
Yes, I have a little sister.
If she is alive, she would be 26 now.
I hope you can see her.
No, I won't see her!
I will only see her once we win the fight!
"A State of Emergency!
Big Mom Closes in!"
Hey yeah! Hey yeah! Hey yeah!
Hey yeah!
Okay, here we are!
Hey! I'm back!
EBISU TOWN
So this is like an "Okobore Town"
of the Flower Capital...
Yasu-san!
Oh, you're back, Tonoyasu!
Yasu-san, now you're back
but we still don't have any food!
I'm so hungry!
I'm starving to death!
How come they're so cheerful?
Wow!
Mister, you're quick to notice!
Everyone looks joyful, right?!
It's slightly different
from Okobore Town in Kuri.
Amongst all the species,
only humans can laugh!
Yeah!
If that's true, why not laugh, laugh?
Why not laugh, laugh?
Pardon us!
Orochi-sama!
Don't be reserved! Raise your heads!
Now, what's for dinner tonight?
Yes! It's all ready!
Bring it here!
Oh!
We slaughtered the chickens
we bred in the beautiful environs of Orochi Farm,
and boiled them lightly...
No! I don't feel like chicken!
Yes, sir! We'll discard them!
Take it away!
Next!
Fresh delicious vegetables...
--I don't want them!
--Yes, sir!
We'll throw them out!
Next!
We've got nice and fatty saury.
I like saury!
And tuna sashimi!
Yeah! Tuna is the best! Tuna!
And we have a variety of selected sake
from across the Land of Wano...
I got it!
Yes, you should have a variety of sake!
But how about women?
Of course, we've got women!
Good! Good!
Mom, I'm hungry!
Me, too!
My tooth fell out
from a lack of nourishment!
You have no food to chew with it anyway!
Now, Tonoyasu, who is this ronin?
One, two, three.
He has three swords belted on!
You're right! Three swords!
And they're all long swords!
Are you trying to be funny?!
Whoa-whoa! I admire this gentleman!
Oh, no! I feel bad for you
for having some strange guy follow you around!
No, I'm the world's greatest sycophant!
At one point, he was worried about my voice
because I talked a lot.
"Shut up."
That's what this kind gentleman said to me!
Right, you stud?!
I see! But look at him.
He has a scary look!
Gee, young man.
Don't look so scary...
Smile like this!
Something good has happened
even to this trashy Ebisu Town!
You mean that man came to town?!
Yes, Ushimitsu Kozo came to town again!
That's great!
Uhimihu?
Yeah, he always comes by
when we're in trouble!
But we don't even know who he is...
He appears at the witching hour,
and steals money
from rich, evil people in the capital...
MONEY BOX
He leaves the money
at poor tenements and disappears.
I wonder who he is.
Thank goodness, thank goodness!
Fortune comes in by a merry gate!
So we bought a treat together!
Oh! What kind of treat?!
It's this!
You see?
This is it!
Please have a cup!
You should have some, too!
It's clear water!
We bought it with the gift of money!
No, I shouldn't...
Don't worry!
This water is clean,
so you won't have a stomachache!
Yasu-san brought you here,
so you must be a good man!
Don't be shy!
Go ahead and drink!
Everyone has the right to have some!
Delicious water!
Clear water!
Delicious water! Clear water!
Isn't it good?!
It seeps into every fiber of your being, doesn't it?!
There, you have a cold look again!
Smile, or fortune won't come to you!
In this country,
we call everyone's smiling face...
..."Ebisu gao," mister!
That's why this place is called Ebisu Town!
Poverty won't get us down!
Crying won't cure your poverty!
So, why not laugh, laugh?
Why not laugh, laugh?
I can't wait anymore! Let me see them!
Please wait, my Lord!
Oh, yeah... Pretty ones!
A-Are they good enough?
So... gorgeous!
This is great! Let's have a banquet now!
Drink!
Dance!
Sing!
Don't hold back!
KUROZUMI OROCHI
SHOGUN OF THE LAND OF WANO
Are you new?
Yes...
You're quite beautiful.
But I don't see the most important one!
What's going on?!
Yes, sir!
I'm here...
Oh, Komurasaki! I missed you!
Me, too...
My Lord...
Oh... D-Did you?!
Did you?!
Tra-guy... What brought you here?
You're unwelcome here...
State your business or leave.
It's an emergency.
Hide somewhere, Black-Leg-ya.
Is it about the fight earlier?
If they come back, I'll beat them again.
That's not it.
Some guys who know our faces
are on their way!
Is it Hawkins?
It wouldn't be so bad if it was just him...
The strongest six among the Headliners
are called the Tobi Roppo...
And two among them...
Two?
One is Page One from the Tobi Roppo!
PAGE ONE - ONE OF THE TOBI ROPPO
ANIMAL KINGDOM PIRATES
Tobi Roppo... Page One...
The other one is X. Drake
from the Tobi Roppo.
Drake...
He's from the Worst Generation...
Page One.
Why do we have to do this?
X. DRAKE - ONE OF THE TOBI ROPPO
ANIMAL KINGDOM PIRATES
To set an example, I guess...
It's important to show
what'll happen to someone who messes with...
...the Animal Kingdom Pirates
in the Land of Wano.
Now...
Why are you here?
Hawkins...
I came looking for some guy...
You'll get more than what you bargained for
from this job, Drake...
Komurasaki, come here!
No...
I am not worthy of it.
It's all right! Come on.
Come a little closer!
Yes, sir!
Guys, you can come in now!
Do you fancy everything?
Yeah! Kyoshiro, you guys should drink, too!
Then, we will have some...
Everyone, the Fire Festival is coming up!
Let's have a pre-party!
Go ahead and enjoy it!
This is the Land of Wano!
I know It's just like heaven!
Eat and drink as much as you want!
Mister, have you thought about
my offer from earlier?
If you're gonna break out,
take me with you!
I'd do anything!
If you and I join hands,
there'll be nothing to be scared of!
Shut up! Why don't you team up with Jaggy?!
With Kid?
No way. His reputation is not so good.
Did you know that he tried
to take down Big Mom?!
But rumor has it that he had his arm torn off
by her subordinate,
not even by her, and he escaped!
Rumor? You're such a pathetic loser.
No, I heard it from a trusted source, mister.
Who is that trusted source?
I've never tried to take down Big Mom!
K-K-K-Kid!
I injured one of her Sweet Generals,
and took what I meant to take!
B-B-B-But your arm...
I'd already lost my arm before that,
in the battle against the Red-Hair Pirates.
Any other questions?!
No.
Then, let me tell you something!
You listen to this, too, stupid monkey!
What?!
I'm the one who'll take down Kaido
and win glory!
No, I am!
What?!
Where's Bonekichi?
He said he's already snuck in.
Then, we must go, too.
Yeah.
You're okay now!
This is also what a mature woman's capable of!
You saved me. Thank you!
Ripe-Ripe Enticement Jutsu!
Now, dance!
Drink!
Eat! Don't be shy!
Oh, I feel lighter without flesh
to weigh me down.
I mean, I don't have any flesh.
Because I'm a skeleton.
It's only vain to tell a
skull joke to myself...
Let's start searching!
A strangely reinforced door...
I smell something here.
I don't have a nose though.
What are those dolls?
Pone... gliff?
Kaido-sama, I'm here to report!
Aboard a giant ship,
approaching from southeast!
She really came! That old bag!
Fire away!
Let her be swallowed by the sea so we're rid of her!
We're already prepared to attack!
Don't let her enter the country!
But there is a problem...
They're charging forward
being hauled by carp!
What?!
Why do they know how to
climb up the waterfall?!
Well... The Big Mom Pirates have a reputation
for their ability to collect information...
Shut up! I don't care!
We knew they were coming!
Just sink them!
That old bag! I'm sure she
remembers that I warned her...
If you come, I'll kill you, Linlin!
I won't let you get away, Straw Hat...
Glaring sharp fangs!
Giant feet that crush everything!
Page One's roar echoes!
When Sanji hears the hard-working
people's screams,
heedless of his own pride and safety,
he stands in Page One's way!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Capital in an Uproar!
Another Assassin Targets Sanji!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!