One Dream One Wish
kanaetai nara Over The Top
If you want to make it
come true, Over The Top
ONE PIECE - LAND OF WANO ARC
mitakoto mo nai sekai mezashi
Setting out into the unknown world
araburu namikaze koete
Weathering rough wind and waves
tsukisusumanakya dame sa
ichibannori shitain da
I have to keep going because
I want to get there first
shinpai toka atomawashi
douse shoubu ichika bachika
Worry later since it's
all sink or swim anyway
aite ga dekaku mietara
When your opponent looks daunting
kokoro ga chijinderu shouko
It's a sign that your heart is shrinking
nigeru nante choisu wa nai
Running away is not a choice
ippo soba e chikadukun da
Take one step closer
namaiki tte homekotoba?
Being called insolent's a compliment, right?
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
When things become tough,
that's when you should laugh
atarashii ashita sagashi ni ikitai no nara
If you want to look for a new tomorrow
tobikkiri no jishin wo migaite
Polish your unique confidence
tabi wo shita ashiato ga
Until your footsteps
sou! chizu ni kawaru made
Yes! Become a map
atarashii Horizon hora susunde kita bun
A new horizon, look, how far you've come
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
It's brighter and the
level of difficulty rises
yumeutsutsu de okose Hurricane
Live in your dream and raise a hurricane
saa! chaato kakimidase
Now! Stir up the rankings
One Dream One Wish
yume wa nigenai... zenbu Knock out
Dreams don't run away... Knock everything out
Over The Top
Hey yeah!
Okay, here we are!
Hey! I'm back!
In this country,
we call everyone's smiling face...
..."Ebisu gao," mister!
Why not laugh, laugh?
What are those dolls?
Pone... gliff?
I'm the one who'll take down Kaido
and win glory!
No, I am!
What?!
It's an emergency.
Hide somewhere, Black-Leg-ya.
--If they come back, I'll beat them again.
--That's not it.
Some guys who know our faces
are on their way!
The strongest six among the Headliners
are called the Tobi Roppo...
--And two among them...
--Two?
One is Page One from the Tobi Roppo!
The other one is X. Drake
from the Tobi Roppo.
Why do we have to do this?
"The Capital in an Uproar!
Another Assassin Targets Sanji!"
Everyone, the Fire Festival is coming up!
Let's have a pre-party!
Destroy everything!
She really came! That old bag!
Fire away!
Let her be swallowed by the sea so we're rid of her!
Eat and drink as much as you want!
They broke through the third defense line!
Focus fire!
Drink more!
Eat more!
This is the Land of Wano!
If you come, I'll kill you, Linlin!
Zeus! You should come back to me!
Wait for me, Straw Hat!
Luffy-dono.
Raizo!
That's too loud!
Something wrong?
No, I have good news.
Otama is better.
Oh! She is?!
Great...
So Tama is fine now...
Thank you for letting me know!
Okay, I'll come back again.
Yeah.
Ya-hoo!
They broke through the seventh defense line!
Everyone at the final defense line,
get ready to fire!
Stop them at any cost!
Napoleon!
Fire!
Ikoku Sovereignty!
The image has been cut off!
Switch to a different camera already!
Jeez...
What?!
They broke through the final defense line
and are now climbing up the falls!
Whaaat?!
Go!
Those fish are climbing up the falls!
It's unbelievable... Lick.
Dammit! What are you doing, you idiots?!
Don't let them set foot on the island!
But we have no troops
at the top of the falls!
And they're all extremely strong!
We don't have time to bring out weapons
that could take them down!
Don't get panicky...
Kaido-sama!
Damn Linlin.
She even brought her brats with her.
All of you get your shit together!
This'll be an all-out war!
We don't have to sit here and wait for them.
Hmph! What's taking them so long
to handle a ship?!
KING - DRAGON-DRAGON FRUIT, ANCIENT TYPE
PTERANODON MODEL
I'll go!
We're reaching the top!
We're almost there!
Here I am, Kaido!
What's that?!
Is that King?!
Is that a Pteranodon?!
Shoot!
How pathetic!
We're arriving in the Land of Wano!
Now, let's go kill Straw Hat!
He's still here!
No way!
Oh, no!
King! You little...!
I won't let you set foot in the Land of Wano!
Dammit!
Mama!
Hmph! Get swallowed up by the sea.
That's our King-sama!
That piece of shit is just flying in the sky
looking for attention!
Oh?
W-What do you want from me?!
This is...
...a soba shop, right?
PAGE ONE - DRAGON-DRAGON FRUIT, ANCIENT TYPE
SPINOSAURUS MODEL
Where's Sangoro?
I-I don't know! Help me!
Well, then...
Call out for Sangoro!
Hurry up, Franosuke!
Hey, why do we have to run?!
They're after Sangoro the soba cook!
Together with that soba cook,
you took down a member of the Kyoshiro Family!
Sorry! Couldn't help it.
They're linked to Orochi.
That's why they sent out the Animal Kingdom
Pirates' Tobi Roppo to get revenge!
Oh, no! The enemy?! Damn!
Thank goodness. It's you guys.
It's not safe here. This way!
Okay!
Let's get out of here for now.
The situation is bad.
It doesn't matter what triggered this.
If one of you gets caught and
your true identity is revealed,
it's gonna be quite messy.
They'll start searching
for the rest of the crew!
Oh, no! Nami-san and Robin-chan
are in danger!
It's still fine if it's just you guys!
But if they find out
you're even involved with the Kozuki Family,
this vengeful plan of 20 years
will be ruined!
No!
Even if you get caught and tortured...
What...
Don't tell them about the
samurai and the Minks.
Keep quiet and...
...let them kill you!
You're terrible!
Luffy wouldn't say such a thing!
I'm more practical.
It's fine as long as
they got no idea who we really are, right?
Well, then...
Why don't we fight hiding our faces?!
Well, um...
Best to avoid fighting for now.
Don't act like you're our captain!
If I get caught...
I'll spill everything to get away!
Screw you!
Then I'll protect you at any cost!
--Yay!
--What a lovely friendship!
It's a lady!
SOBA SHOP
--Oh, shoot!
--Is someone already after us?!
Stop! We have nothing to do with this!
We serve soba, but we have nothing to do with
Sangoro the soba cook!
How could you destroy our shop?!
Without it, we can't stay in this city!
If you wanna hold it against someone,
blame it on the fool named Sangoro.
Tell me about other soba shops!
Otherwise, call out for Sangoro!
He's an idiot who messed
with the Kyoshiro Family!
If you two resist...
I'll eat you, too!
Sangoro!
Hey!
Sangoro, show yourself!
That's enough.
Sangoro!
Maybe it's no use.
If he's a coward, he'll never show himself!
Sangoro!
Oh, I wanna eat something sweet next!
They're using trickery!
Our top priority should be on running!
Sanji!
How...
...could I do that?!
Hey, wait, Sanji!
Stop! We have nothing to do with him, either!
Then, call out for him!
Everybody!
For Sangoro the soba cook!
I'm...
...here!
Diable Jambe!
Concasser Crush!
That's him...
He's...
...Sangoro of the Special Soba!
So you're the soba cook.
You finally showed up...
You gave me trouble.
Um, this is Page One.
I found the target at the sixth block of district two!
Roger! We'll be there as soon as we can.
You can't escape now!
A dinosaur power-user...
You asshole...
What are you doing, Sangoro?!
Stop it!
If Drake and Hawkins come, it'll be all over!
I know.
But...
...he doesn't know who I really am.
So no one will find it out
and I won't get hurt!
I can beat this fool in an instant.
It'd be nice to have more allies...
But it would also be nice
to have fewer enemies.
Stop talking gibberish!
Guys, move ahead!
What?
It's fine as long as...
...I keep my identity secret, right?
A jet-black Raid Suit and a skull belt!
On his feet are devices that accelerate
him to the speed of light!
Wearing a cape with the number 3 on it,
a new hero appears in the Flower Capital!
Shouldering the people's expectations,
he fights the Animal Kingdom Pirates!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Dashing! The Righteous Soba Mask!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!