One Dream One Wish
kanaetai nara Over The Top
If you want to make it come true, Over The Top
ONE PIECE - LAND OF WANO ARC
mitakoto mo nai sekai mezashi
Setting out into the unknown world
araburu namikaze koete
Weathering rough wind and waves
tsukisusumanakya dame sa ichibannori shitain da
I have to keep going because I want to get there first
shinpai toka atomawashi douse shoubu ichika bachika
Worry later since it's all sink or swim anyway
aite ga dekaku mietara
When your opponent looks daunting
kokoro ga chijinderu shouko
It's a sign that your heart is shrinking
nigeru nante choisu wa nai
Running away is not a choice
ippo soba e chikadukun da
Take one step closer
namaiki tte homekotoba?
Being called insolent's a compliment, right?
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
When things become tough, that's when you should laugh
atarashii ashita sagashi ni ikitai no nara
If you want to look for a new tomorrow
tobikkiri no jishin wo migaite
Polish your unique confidence
tabi wo shita ashiato ga
Until your footsteps
sou! chizu ni kawaru made
Yes! Become a map
atarashii Horizon hora susunde kita bun
A new horizon, look, how far you've come
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
It's brighter and the level of difficulty rises
yumeutsutsu de okose Hurricane
Live in your dream and raise a hurricane
saa! chaato kakimidase
Now! Stir up the rankings
One Dream One Wish
yume wa nigenai... zenbu Knock out
Dreams don't run away... Knock everything out
Over The Top
Robin infiltrated Orochi's Castle,
but was attacked and caught
by the Oniwabanshu.
She's gone?!
Where did she go?
Meanwhile,
Shogun Orochi was having a big banquet
along with many of his subordinates.
Oh, how pleasant!
Oh, Orobi the new girl!
Where have you been?!
Come closer!
Oh, yes!
Komurasaki!
You're so mean...
Don't pout, don't pout, Komurasaki!
How cute! You're very, very cute!
At Kuri Beach,
Chopper and the others bumped into...
Big M...
I'm gonna kill her right now!
Who...
...am I?!
"Pandemonium!
The Monster Snake, Shogun Orochi!"
What was I doing here?
Are you hurt? Let us treat you!
Are you all right?!
Chopperemon!
She doesn't seem like herself...
Chopperemon?!
We shouldn't get mixed with her!
If we do...
Give it to me!
Wedding cake!
We'll get killed!
Hey, do you know who I am?
I don't remember a thing...
I know your name!
You do?!
Don't tell her!
Um... Bi... B-B-B...
Big...!
Chopperemon?!
I-It's Olin! Olin!
Your name is Olin!
Olin?
Olin...
It's a lovely name!
That is not the name you told us.
I don't wanna remind her of anything!
Thank you. You're so kind.
When you see someone in trouble,
you help!
Chopperemon is a doctor!
Oh, is he?!
My name is Tama!
I'm hungry...
You must always crush your enemy
with overwhelming force!
What's happening is more than just
some of your underlings getting beaten.
Kyoshiro.
Some strangers snuck into the capital!
Listen, guys!
Since I have you together, let me say this again!
This year marks the 20th year
since Kozuki Oden died!
His wife, Toki said there would be retaliation
this year!
Oden's legacy persists!
That ghost story again...
We don't remember Kozuki...
Right, Komurasaki?
Do you remember how unusually strong
Oden's retainers, the Akazaya Nine, were?!
Their leader, Kin'emon, is a bright guy!
They've come back to the Land of Wano after 20 years
and are preparing!
They will come!
To cut off my head!
We have already buried a bunch of people
who were related to Oden...
Is he still scared of Kozuki?
Kaido has already taken an enemy down,
but the yokozuna and Jack's men
got attacked in Kuri!
A soba cook in the capital,
and a ronin from a post town
attacked some yakuza!
Maybe they were all on Kin'emon's orders!
Foxfire Kin'emon and the Akazaya samurai...
I cannot wait to face them!
I will cut them down with a single stroke!
You are dependable, Kyoshiro!
Oden died! Before my eyes!
But his son Momonosuke is still alive!
The body of that brat was never recovered
along with others!
The Kozuki Clan hasn't died out yet!
They're aiming to revive the Kozuki Clan!
Of course, they are going to
chop off Kaido's head, too...
They will definitely come!
No one will chop off Kaido's head!
How cowardly can he be?!
You're drinking too much!
If he hears that,
your head will be cut off!
Otoko-chan, take this one next!
Okay!
Hey, I'm out of sake!
Yes, we'll be right with you!
Can you take it to him?!
Yes!
Listen up, guys! This is the year!
Remember Toki's last words!
Do not drop your guard!
He's too scared.
How pathetic.
When will he stop believing that bullshit poem?
"You are the moon unaware of the dawn."
Here we go again... It ruins the taste of sake.
"May your purpose be fulfilled
and cast nine shadows on the night woven of 20 years
and you shall know the brilliance of the dawn"!
You know what it means!
20 years later, on a moonlit night,
in order to settle the grudge,
nine samurai will appear as ghosts...
They will... kill me...
...and open up the Land of Wano!
Orochi believes in the prophecy quite firmly...
Even so, his subordinates don't care...
No wonder.
He's so delusional.
Oden and the Akazaya members are all dead!
I don't even remember them.
What a coward.
We will not let them do as they like!
That is why we cannot lower our guard...
Who is it?! Idiot! Stop it!
This voice... Oh, please no!
You can't laugh! Stop it!
Who is it?!
Do not tell me you laughed at me!
Otoko-chan!
Because everyone is taking him for a fool!
That's enough! Go away!
I can't stop! I'm sorry!
--It's a child!
--She's the Oiran's attendant!
Stop her!
Otoko-chan!
I know I shouldn't laugh!
How obnoxious!
I am the Shogun!
Stop her!
The grudge from 20 years ago...
Do you think I am...
Do you think I am afraid of it?!
I am the victor!
My Lord!
I defeated Oden!
Please! Stop it!
Don't do it!
Oiran!
She's unreliable!
That black-hearted woman
can't do anything!
My Lord!
She is just a little child.
Stay out of this, Komurasaki!
My Lord... Please forgive her!
Did you laugh at me?!
Squirt!
She's prone to laughter!
She means no offense!
We can't stop him anymore...
Give up on her!
My Lord! She's just a child!
Have mercy!
Listen to what I say!
Stop laughing!
Otoko-chan!
Komurasaki...
Why...?
Why did you hit me?
Apologize, Komurasaki!
Bow until your forehead sinks into the floor!
I will not!
I will never abase myself before anyone!
How dare she!
When I know I am right,
I do not need to give an inch!
Hey, Komurasaki...
I was going to...
...make you the Shogun's wife...
If you want a weak woman,
go ahead and cut me up!
I am a samurai's daughter!
Shut up!
I will not live in disgrace!
You are impertinent...
You're just some whore!
Do not act like you know
a damn thing about samurai!
Orochi-sama...?!
He transformed.
Komurasaki...
SNAKE-SNAKE FRUIT, MYTHICAL ZOAN TYPE
(MODEL: YAMATA-NO-OROCHI)
What a waste...
It's a shame to lose that beauty!
I do not want to chew up your head!
Apologize!
If you plead for your life,
you will get a lighter sentence!
What are you waiting for?!
Apologize from the bottom of your heart!
You are the Shogun...
You should learn to let things go...
They say whoever falls in love loses out.
What?!
I...
...will not beg for my life!
She's provoking him...
Stop! Komurasaki!
Komurasaki!
Damn you!
Orochi-sama, why are you attacking us?!
How rude!
Huh? You're the lady from the soba shop?!
Otoko-chan!
I'm glad that you're okay.
That magic user! Where did she go?!
Give up now!
How could you fool us?!
I found that woman!
Don't let her get away!
Please stop, Orochi-sama!
Help!
All right, Komurasaki!
As you wish,
I will kill you with my own hands!
The Oiran!
Komurasaki-dayu!
This is it!
Prepare yourself!
You damn specter!
Go away!
I am going to haunt you! I am going to curse you!
This is...
...pandemonium!
Komurasaki's determination can't be destroyed
even by Orochi's fangs!
She sees imminent danger,
but this samurai's daughter won't back down an inch!
Kyoshiro closes in to kill her!
Life, pride, and schemes... What will be the outcome?
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Flower Falls! The Final Moment of the
Most Beautiful Woman in the Land of Wano!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!