One Dream One Wish
kanaetai nara Over The Top
If you want to make it
come true, Over The Top
ONE PIECE - LAND OF WANO ARC
mitakoto mo nai sekai mezashi
Setting out into the unknown world
araburu namikaze koete
Weathering rough wind and waves
tsukisusumanakya dame sa
ichibannori shitain da
I have to keep going because
I want to get there first
shinpai toka atomawashi
douse shoubu ichika bachika
Worry later since it's
all sink or swim anyway
aite ga dekaku mietara
When your opponent looks daunting
kokoro ga chijinderu shouko
It's a sign that your heart is shrinking
nigeru nante choisu wa nai
Running away is not a choice
ippo soba e chikadukun da
Take one step closer
namaiki tte homekotoba?
Being called insolent's a compliment, right?
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
When things become tough,
that's when you should laugh
atarashii ashita sagashi ni ikitai no nara
If you want to look for a new tomorrow
tobikkiri no jishin wo migaite
Polish your unique confidence
tabi wo shita ashiato ga
Until your footsteps
sou! chizu ni kawaru made
Yes! Become a map
atarashii Horizon hora susunde kita bun
A new horizon, look, how far you've come
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
It's brighter and the
level of difficulty rises
yumeutsutsu de okose Hurricane
Live in your dream and raise a hurricane
saa! chaato kakimidase
Now! Stir up the rankings
One Dream One Wish
yume wa nigenai... zenbu Knock out
Dreams don't run away... Knock everything out
Over The Top
Listen to what I say!
Stop laughing!
Otoko-chan!
Komurasaki...
I will never abase myself before anyone!
Hey, Komurasaki...
I was going to...
...make you the Shogun's wife...
If you want a weak woman,
go ahead and cut me up!
I am a samurai's daughter!
Shut up!
I will not live in disgrace!
You are impertinent...
You are just some whore!
Do not act like you know
a damn thing about samurai!
Komurasaki...
Apologize!
If you plead for your life,
you will get a lighter sentence!
I...
...will not beg for my life!
Komurasaki!
Damn you!
All right, Komurasaki!
As you wish,
I will kill you with my own hands!
"The Flower Falls! The Final Moment of
the Most Beautiful Woman in the Land of Wano!"
The Oiran!
Komurasaki-dayu!
This is pandemonium!
Get ready!
Komurasaki!
Daikoku!
If you ninja are here, stop the Shogun!
Save the Oiran!
He's free.
Nothing is tying him down.
More importantly,
we're currently dealing with an invader!
An invader?!
Orobi-san is an invader?
Oh, yeah! I've never seen her before...
Hey, lady, please save the Oiran.
That's impossible!
I don't even know if I can save you
since you made the Shogun mad!
Help me!
It's a curse of death!
What's going on over there?!
Fujin! Raisin! What are you doing?!
I-It's a specter!
Gasha-dokuro creatures really do exist!
A curse on you!
What?!
Ghost!
Otoko-chan!
A curse on you!
Robin-san, glad to see you fine!
Bonekichi, you're a hero! Thanks!
I'm awesome, right?
Keep it up!
Let's make it out of here!
Are they the specter's allies?!
Mil Fleurs!
Gigantesco Mano!
--How could you!
--Damn you!
This is it!
G-Gasha-dokuro...
Let me guide you to the land of dead.
Young lady!
Go away!
No!
Robin and even Brook...
What should I do?!
There's no point in hiding now.
INSIDE THE CASTLE - IN THE ATTIC
Let's go!
Okay, Shinobu-chan!
Onami!
Thank you, Shinobu-chan.
Don't mention it, Onami!
Who's that?! A ninja?!
Hey lady! You were called Shinobu just now,
weren't you?!
You're...
...Hanzo?!
So you're alive! You man-seducing...
...sexy kunoichi.
Shinobu the Man-killer!
How did you know?
No, you're not her.
Forget it!
That's me!
Ninpo: Ball-Crusher!
Is that a type of ninjutsu?!
This is why... you're
called... the Man-Killer...
Is that what it means?!
I-I can't move...
Ninpo: Paralysis Jutsu!
What?! You made that part up!
We must get going!
--Let's go, Onami!
--What?
Sexy Ninpo!
Rot Garden!
Why did Hanzo fall down from the attic?
Who are those two kunoichi?!
--What's going on?!
--The banquet room is a mess!
Whoa, Onami-san!
A curse on you!
Why?!
Onami!
I came as back-up!
Where are you?! Komurasaki!
There you are!
Kyoshiro?!
You should not have done that, Komurasaki...
Are you prepared?
I am.
What?
Wait a minute, Boss Kyoshiro!
You should not have done that, Komurasaki...
Are you prepared?
I am.
O... Oiran...
Big Sis...
Kyoshiro-dono, why did you do that?
The most beautiful woman
in the Land of Wano...
It's heartrending!
Komurasaki...
Why did you do that, Kyoshiro?!
Did I tell you to kill her?!
You bastard...
It is...
...the mercy of a samurai for Komurasaki...
No matter who does it,
rebelling against the Shogun is a grave offense.
That's the iron rule.
He did it to show his loyalties?!
Kyoshiro has gone too far...
Give that kid...
...to me!
I will chew her to death!
If you did not laugh at me,
she would not have died!
Brat!
Hand her over, Orobi!
And who the hell are you?!
Robin!
Come on, Zeus!
Hey! Did you summon me, Nami?
I'll give you a Weather Egg.
Yeah?!
A curse on you...
This is no time for us
to be chased by a ghost!
A curse on you...
Why isn't it attacking?!
A curse on you!
Oh, no! He noticed!
It's time for me to go...
Come out and fight!
There is trouble in the banquet room!
Capture the invaders
and get rid of the specter!
Stop the rampaging Orochi-sama!
Everyone, on the floor!
Ninpo!
Lightning Blast!
What the hell?!
You're pretty young,
but that was quite a ninpo!
That was close!
Only you could've done it, Onami!
NEXT MORNING
EXCAVATION LABOR CAMP, UDON
You're full of energy even in the morning,
straw-hat man...
Go eat your breakfast already!
Let's get to work!
I'll be thanking you when I use these...
Don't mention it!
Oh, yeah. Hasn't he gotten up yet?
We have a problem!
An inmate, Eustass Kid, escaped!
What?!
AT THE SAME TIME
OKOBORE TOWN, KURI, LAND OF WANO
This is sweet red-bean soup.
Go ahead, Olin-san, try it!
Whoa! It smells good!
Thank you!
So good!
It's delicious!
This soup tastes good and sweet!
I'm glad that you like it.
I'm sorry, Olin-san, but
that's all we have...
I wish I could have more.
But you fed me even though you're poor.
Thank you, Tsuru-san.
Is she that strong?
Yeah, more than you'll ever know...
Then I want her to rescue Big Bro
who is being held captive at Udon!
What?!
Oh, that's a good idea!
It's not so simple!
She'll never listen to us!
Let's go, Chopperemon!
Let's go!
Are you sure?
Once she gets her memory back, we'll be screwed!
It's better than just waiting here!
I want to go! This is the chance!
Um...
What is it, lovely Chopperemon?
Paw.
O-Okay...
I'm hungry...
I wanna eat more...
I can't help but be scared!
We need your help. Olin.
What?!
Let's go to Udon together!
Udon? That's where I'm going?
That is right!
I heard that Udon's Lead Performer
likes sweet red-bean soup!
Yeah, yeah! They have tons of red-bean soup!
I lied before I knew it...
If there's no red-bean soup,
she'll kill me!
There's tons of red-bean soup there?!
Let's get a move on!
Taking down Kaido!
That goal gives Luffy indomitable fighting
spirit and he makes a heroic move!
In that hellish camp where guards
act mercilessly and atrociously,
there is only one man who
Luffy became close to!
The emotional bond they share that was born in hell
will blow up a storm!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Bond Between Prisoners!
Luffy and Old Man Hyo!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!