One Dream One Wish
If you want to make it
come true, Over The Top
kanaetai nara Over The Top
ONE PIECE - LAND OF WANO ARC
Setting out into the unknown world
mitakoto mo nai sekai mezashi
Weathering rough wind and waves
araburu namikaze koete
I have to keep going because
I want to get there first
tsukisusumanakya dame sa
ichibannori shitain da
Worry later since it's
all sink or swim anyway
shinpai toka atomawashi
douse shoubu ichika bachika
When your opponent looks daunting
aite ga dekaku mietara
It's a sign that your heart is shrinking
kokoro ga chijinderu shouko
Running away is not a choice
nigeru nante choisu wa nai
Take one step closer
ippo soba e chikadukun da
Being called insolent's a compliment, right?
namaiki tte homekotoba?
When things become tough,
that's when you should laugh
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
If you want to look for a new tomorrow
atarashii ashita sagashi ni ikitai no nara
Polish your unique confidence
tobikkiri no jishin wo migaite
Until your footsteps
tabi wo shita ashiato ga
sou! chizu ni kawaru made
Yes! Become a map
atarashii Horizon hora susunde kita bun
A new horizon, look, how far you've come
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
It's brighter and the
level of difficulty rises
yumeutsutsu de okose Hurricane
Live in your dream and raise a hurricane
saa! chaato kakimidase
Now! Stir up the rankings
One Dream One Wish
yume wa nigenai... zenbu Knock out
Dreams don't run away... Knock everything out
Over The Top
Are you prepared?
I am.
No matter who does it,
rebelling against the Shogun is a grave offense.
That's the iron rule.
"The Bond Between Prisoners!
Luffy and Old Man Hyo!"
This is...
...the five-colored rice! Must be Shinobu!
"Wait you at the dried-up well"...
Are they there?!
I am glad that you are all alive!
I did not think that you ran all the way to the region of Ringo
to hide from the pursuers...
Orochi's men will not pursue this far.
I didn't expect the famous Oiran,
Komurasaki, to be killed.
Mm-hm. That has thrown the Flower Capital
into an uproar.
I mean,
all she did was speak against Orochi.
How could he be so quick to kill a woman like that?!
I'm scared of samurai...
The man who cut Komurasaki
was Napping Kyoshiro.
Kyoshiro...
I have never heard that name...
20 years ago, the greatest yakuza boss
in the Land of Wano was...
...Hyogoro the Flower.
What a colorful name.
Boss Hyogoro who values
honor and helps the weak,
would never handle the situation
in such a cruel way.
Napping Kyoshiro... How horrible that man is.
Maybe we shouldn't take Otoko-chan
back to Kyoshiro's brothel...
Even though she made the Shogun mad,
I don't think Kyoshiro will
chase after a child...
But he even killed the most
popular woman in his brothel.
I'm worried...
Let's go back to the Flower Capital...
It's cold, isn't it?
It's so warm! Thank you, Shinobu-chan!
Everyone, if we're going
back to the Flower Capital,
let's take a bath to rest our weary bones.
Since I'm just bones.
Yeah. It's so nice to warm ourselves up at a bathhouse
in the Flower Capital while doing research.
A bath sounds good!
Yeah. We wanna refresh ourselves.
We have to wear disguises.
The hot water and drinking water are managed by Orochi.
In the Flower Capital,
every single aspect of life is controlled.
Before that, Orobi-dono,
I would like to hear the information you've collected so far...
It's a shame... All I've
found out so far is...
...what time Orochi will wake up
on the day of the battle,
the offerings that they
will take to Onigashima,
Kaido's favorite food and organization chart,
the number of
his soldiers and weapons...
So efficient!
By the way, I discovered a Ponegliff!
It wasn't a red one though...
You sure?!
You surely have luck with stones, Bonekichi!
It was in a basement room
with a reinforced door.
It was a strange room with wooden puppets.
Then, the Road Ponegliff that'll lead us the way to Raftel,
might be on Onigashima as I thought.
Onigashima, huh?
Mm-hm. With so much information,
we can say the mission was quite successful...
Thank you...
It is all because of your support.
Now, Orobi-san, Onami-san!
Let's go to a bathhouse
for healing and to see panties!
--You can't come since you draw attention!
--What?!
Come on!
Breaking news!
The biggest icon in the Flower Capital,
Komurasaki the Oiran,
...was cut down by Boss Kyoshiro
at Shogun-sama's banquet!
You can find out more in here!
KOMURASAKI, THE TOP OIRAN, DIES
Komurasaki-chan!
How could this happen?!
EBISU TOWN
Why so mournful?!
You barely met her only once.
The death of such a beauty is the world's loss,
idiot!
The funeral will be held tomorrow.
You're so insensitive!
The Raid Suit...
Do you think Orobi and the others got caught?
I'm worried.
Should I try to contact them by Smail?
What do you think, Sanji?
The ability to become invisible...
I guess I have to try it there...
Hey, Sanji!
In the women's bath!
Oh, yeah, you're right!
Speaking of which, Tra-guy,
isn't there anything about Udon? About Luffytaro?
Yeah, it's about time he loses patience
and starts rampaging!
You're right! Can't wait to see him again!
There is no article on Straw Hat-ya...
Wait...
Eustass-ya?!
What?! Did you say "yuya (bathhouse)"?!
Is it the women's bath?!
Oh, I mean, so he's here
in the Land of Wano?!
Since his ally Hawkins is here,
it's no wonder that he's here, too...
SERIOUS OFFENDER, KID, ESCAPES
But he was held in the prison at Udon...
Then, he escaped.
--Escaped?!
--Hey, what about Luffy?!
I guess something more
will take place in Udon...
By the way...
is there a bathhouse?
--Damn you! This is not the time for that!
--You're not listening at all!
You fool!
Hey, wait!
What is it?!
I'm worried. Bepo and the others went scouting
and haven't come back yet...
I hope we won't have any more trouble.
Oh, gee. Lick.
Of all places, Mama fell out of the ship
on the top of the waterfall!
We can't go back there
since King is defending by air...
It's already miraculous that
the Queen Mama Chanter didn't roll over...
...after falling from that height...
Hey! All we can do is wait?
Yes, for now.
Once we fall off the ship,
we power-users will be paralyzed...
No! Then, Mama sank into the sea?!
Don't worry!
This is also a miracle...
Mama's Vivre Card shows she's alive!
Great! She's alive!
But then, where is she?!
That means she probably was hauled up
by the Animal Kingdom Pirates and is being held captive!
By Kaido's group? That complicates things...
Mama and Kaido used to be crewmates,
but now they're called Emperors of the Sea
and became enemies that are competing with each other...
He'll kill her for sure.
What?! What's gonna happen to us then?!
Lick!
The Big Mom Pirates will become...
...the Perospero Pirates?! Lick!
Hey! What are you talking
about, Big Bro Peros!
The next captain will be Katakuri!
We value seniority! Lick!
Don't be a fool! Quality matters!
The eldest son should lead!
Do you want me to summon a genie?!
I'm gonna do it now!
Stop it!
Don't assume Mama'll die!
Don't think of her as a commoner, you fools!
Big Mom?!
Yes, she is a very strong
person from overseas!
This animal called Sharkodile is
pretty calm and sweet!
You hit the animal two times to tame it!
Wait! I do not understand why you have to go to Udon
with that Big Mom person?!
With her help, we will save Big Bro!
I-I do not understand!
Just come back, Otama!
Fill me in on the details!
Kin'emon-dono told me
to guard Momonosuke-sama tightly!
It will be all right, Master-sama!
As a kunoichi, I will protect Momo-kun
at any cost!
W... W...
Who is a kunoichi?!
You are not even half-fledged yet!
Do not be ridiculous
and get back here already, Otama!
Hitetsu-dono! We are already on our way...
What?! No! Okiku-dono!
Head back now!
Say hi to Komachiyo and the others!
Clank.
Hey, considering Hitetsu is worried,
maybe we'd better go back...
We will save Big Bro, Chopperemon!
Right, Olin-san?!
By the way, I heard you
say "Big Mom" earlier...
That sounds awfully familiar...
Never mind, Olin! You're Olin!
Right, Olin?!
Olin, Olin, Olin!
You're so cute, Chopperemon!
Anyway, the people in Okobore Town
were all nice...
They don't know me
and I don't even know who I am,
but that woman treated me to
the sweet and delicious red-bean soup...
That talking hat hasn't spoken at all,
so did he lose his memory, too?
Now I remember...
I wanna eat the red-bean soup again...
Don't look at me when you say that!
I couldn't help it because you're so cute
I could eat you up...
I'm not food!
You are working hard, Momo-kun!
I am at the center of this battle!
I must stay sharp!
Sunacchi!
Oh, sorry! I am sorry!
By the way, what is "Sunacchi"
that you have been yelling?
Sunacchi is a word that gives you energy!
Sunacchi!
Sunacchi! Sunacchi!
You are right! I got a lot of energy!
Yeah? Great!
Sunacchi! Sunacchi! Sunacchi!
Stop, both of you!
What, Kiku?
Where did you learn that word?
It's what they yell in
a sword fight overseas!
I learned it from Zorojuro!
He said it's a good-luck word to uplift your spirit
when you lose courage...
Then, I forbid you to say it!
What?! Why?!
It could be just a coincidence,
but there is the same battle cry in an old dialect from Kuri.
It is not appropriate for you to say.
--What?! Come on!
--No!
It is a word that gives you energy...
No means no!
I'm hungry. Aren't we at Udon yet?
I'm too hungry so I...
Don't look at me drooling like that!
The fact is, Olin-san,
the Udon region is still a long way from here...
Is that right?!
This is a rough map of the Land of Wano.
The Land of Wano has six regions
divided by a river,
and each region has a different climate.
At the far west, is the region of Kuri.
KURI
We met on the beach near
Amigasa Village in Kuri...
AMIGASA VILLAGE
ATAMAYAMA        OKOBORE TOWN
BAKURA TOWN
Bakura Town used to be a
castle town of Oden Castle.
Otsuru-san was in Okobore
Town right next to it.
That's where I had the red-bean soup!
And Atamayama is where Shutenmaru is based.
Now, where is Udon?
If you head east from Kuri,
you'll find the region of Udon.
UDON
We are heading for the
Excavation Labor Camp there.
UDON
EXCAVATION LABOR CAMP
Big Bro! We will rescue you at any cost!
Alright! Suna...
Oh! Sorry!
The region of Kibi is a wasteland.
Fujiyama is at the center
of the Land of Wano.
FLOWER CAPITAL
At the foot of it, is...
...the great-extravagant Flower Capital.
Its prosperity is purchased with
the sacrifice of the commoners.
EBISU TOWN
The hateful Orochi is responsible for it.
I have to make it right!
Suna...
I am sorry!
East of the Flower Capital,
RINGO
NORTHERN GRAVEYARD
is the snowy region of Ringo.
I think Brook is in the Northern Graveyard!
The region of Hakumai has port towns.
HABU PORT     HAKUMAI
And located directly in
south of the Land of Wano...
ONIGASHIMA
...is Onigashima!
Where we plan to attack!
We have to recruit allies
from across the country.
--Mm-hm!
--First, let's save Big Bro!
Luffy is indispensable for us!
Udon is so far away...
After I saw the map, I got hungrier.
Like I said, stop looking at me and drooling!
That tool is too heavy to
be used by one person...
Old man, let me help you!
No, straw hat man!
You don't have to help me!
It's nothing!
Straw hat man, thank you.
I'm not doing it for you.
I'm doing it for myself!
I'm gonna become stronger
and get out of here at any cost!
I can do this, too!
All right!
Hey! Old man!
You okay?!
Take these.
You're too hungry to work, right?!
Straw hat man...
Thank you for these again, straw hat man...
Go eat dumplings now!
Thank you very much, straw hat man.
Thank you very much!
He's a funny old man.
Now...
How disgusting!
Hey, you!
I need to ask you something.
What is it?!
ALPACA-MAN - A GUARD (A GIFTER)
ALPACA SMILE FRUIT
As you may know, the prisoner
Eustass Kid escaped!
I bet you know something.
It stinks!
I haven't eaten this much for a long time...
Ever since that straw hat
man came, I've been blessed.
If you're hungry, you can't even work!
Not just once - he's
saved me so many times...
Thank you, straw hat man!
I'm gonna...
I'm gonna eat them with appreciation.
Hey!
Let me have some!
Those dumplings look delicious!
DAIFUGO - A VICE WARDEN (A HEADLINER)
SCORPION SMILE FRUIT
I mean,
don't you have something
to do with Kid's escape?!
You guys were talking so often!
His spit stinks...
Stinks?! Are you messing with me?!
Don't forget that you have
the Sea Prism Stone cuffs!
But it's only a matter of
time before he gets caught!
His jailbreak was not well-planned.
Foolishly he still has the
Sea Prism Stone cuffs on...
So he'll get caught soon
and face the consequences!
Stop it! Your spit really stinks!
Don't tell me you're messing with me?!
Do you wanna go over the rules again?!
The first offense, your arms will be cut off!
For the second, your legs!
And for the third, you're sentenced to death!
Idiot!
You guys shouldn't mess with us!
Stop hurting Old Man Hyo!
You're killing him!
Are you messing with me?
No, we're not...
I'm doing this for your sake as well!
You prisoners are getting the dumplings
for your work, right?
What if there's someone...
...who doesn't even work to eat them
and uses tickets he got from someone else?
Since you guys work hard,
can you forgive a cheater like that?
--Of course you can't!
--My...
--Rules are rules. If someone can't follow them, he has to die!
--...precious millet dumplings...
Don't you think so?
Dumplings...
The rule says you can only eat
what you earn by working.
If you can't work, just starve to death!
Don't you agree, old man?!
Hey, are you trying to get away like that?!
Now, you can't even work,
so how did you get so many food tickets?!
Who gave them to you?
Dumplings...
My precious dumplings...
You greedy old man!
So delicious!
What are you doing?!
You have no right to eat anything!
Don't eat dumplings if you don't work!
Spit them out! Spit them out, shitty old man!
Please stop!
I won't spit them out...
Straw hat man, you gave me these dumplings...
I will never... ever...
...waste them!
There! You've got to see this, too!
Old man! Why?!
It serves him right!
That's what you'll get if you mess with us!
Keep that in mind!
Now, spill it with dumplings!
What idiot has been giving you the tickets?!
I ate them!
How much do you wanna mess with me?
I won't go easy on you.
I'll make you say your accomplice's name,
and kill you both!
Luffy takes down the Headliner guard
and climbs up the wall
in order to break out.
However, a funky singing
voice suddenly echoes around!
To the sound of enthusiastic cheers, Queen, a supreme officer
of the Animal Kingdom Pirates, begins the show!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Lead Performer! Queen the Plague Emerges!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!