One Dream One Wish
If you want to make it come true, Over The Top
kanaetai nara Over The Top
ONE PIECE - LAND OF WANO ARC
Setting out into the unknown world
mitakoto mo nai sekai mezashi
Weathering rough wind and waves
araburu namikaze koete
I have to keep going because I want to get there first
tsukisusumanakya dame sa ichibannori shitain da
Worry later since it's all sink or swim anyway
shinpai toka atomawashi douse shoubu ichika bachika
When your opponent looks daunting
aite ga dekaku mietara
It's a sign that your heart is shrinking
kokoro ga chijinderu shouko
Running away is not a choice
nigeru nante choisu wa nai
Take one step closer
ippo soba e chikadukun da
Being called insolent's a compliment, right?
namaiki tte homekotoba?
When things become tough, that's when you should laugh
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
If you want to look for a new tomorrow
atarashii ashita sagashi ni ikitai no nara
Polish your unique confidence
tobikkiri no jishin wo migaite
Until your footsteps
tabi wo shita ashiato ga
Yes! Become a map
sou! chizu ni kawaru made
A new horizon, look, how far you've come
atarashii Horizon hora susunde kita bun
It's brighter and the level of difficulty rises
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
yumeutsutsu de okose Hurricane
Live in your dream and raise a hurricane
Now! Stir up the rankings
saa! chaato kakimidase
One Dream One Wish
Dreams don't run away... Knock everything out
yume wa nigenai... zenbu Knock out
Over The Top
This animal called Sharkodile is
pretty calm and sweet!
Wait! I do not understand why you have to go to Udon
with that Big Mom person?!
With her help, we will save Big Bro!
I'm hungry. Aren't we at Udon yet?
I'm quite hungry so I...
Don't look at me drooling like that!
Thank you, straw hat man!
I'm gonna...
I'm gonna eat them with appreciation.
Hey!
Let me have some!
Those dumplings look delicious!
Don't you have something to do with Kid's escape?!
You guys were talking so often!
His spit stinks...
Stinks?! Are you messing with me?!
Don't forget that you have the Sea Prism Stone cuffs!
The rule says you can only eat
what you earn by working.
If you can't work, just starve to death!
Don't you agree, old man?!
Hey, are you trying to get away like that?!
Now, you can't even work,
so how did you get so many food tickets?!
Who gave them to you?
Dumplings...
My precious dumplings...
But it's only a matter of time before he gets caught!
His jailbreak was not well-planned.
Foolishly he still has the Sea Prism Stone cuffs on...
So he'll get caught soon
and face the consequences!
Stop it! Your spit really stinks!
Don't tell me you're messing with me?!
Do you wanna go over the rules again?!
The first offense, your arms will be cut off!
For the second, your legs!
And for the third, you're sentenced to death!
Idiot!
You guys shouldn't mess with us!
What are you doing?!
You have no right to eat anything!
Old man! Why?!
It serves him right!
That's what you'll get if you mess with us!
Keep that in mind!
Now, spill it with dumplings!
What idiot has been giving you the tickets?!
I ate them!
How much do you wanna mess with me?
I won't go easy on you.
I'll make you say your accomplice's name,
and kill you both!
"A Lead Performer!
Queen the Plague Emerges!"
UDON
EXECUTIVE TOWER IN THE EXCAVATION LABOR CAMP
What do you want?!
I found this.
A kani (Crab)?
It's not a kani, it's a kagi (key)!
If a prisoner escapes, it will be your fault!
Thanks-kani!
Put it away in the safe now!
Jeez! We are taking the trouble of
keeping the keys to the power-user prisoners' cuffs...
...safe in the Sea Prism Stone box,
so it is very important for you guards to stay sharp.
If the power-users release themselves
from the Sea Prism Stone cuffs
and stage a rebellion,
our heads will roll!
I'm sorry-kani!
By the way, you don't look familiar...
Kani!
--An intruder!
--Get ready to die!
I obtained the keys!
RAIZO OF THE MIST - AKAZAYA NINE (A NINJA)
Seems like you can only walk sideways.
Since you are a crab!
Ninpo: Flower Shuriken!
I will take the keys, but I will not take your life!
Now, goodbye!
Nin, nin, nin...
Spit it out already!
Who gave you the food tickets?!
Tell me or I'm gonna kill you!
I won't tell you even if it means death!
You little punk...
He acts up to the cause of justice
and helps the weak...
...without yielding to fools...
He has such chivalrous spirit,
and I have to honor that with my own chivalrous spirit
or I'll disgrace myself!
Old Man Hyo...
Now, kill me!
Meeting him makes me nostalgic for a bygone era.
I am Hyogoro the Flower!
After so long, my heart is filled with joy
and my stomach is full!
This is a land of samurai!
There used to be...
...a bunch of men like him!
You guys killed them all!
Hey!
Stop! Luffytaro!
You know what'll happen to you
when you talk back to guards, right?!
Kill me, you fool!
What did you say?! Say it again!
I said that you guys are irrational fools
who use unreasonable violence!
You moron!
But...
...we couldn't defeat you fools...
There, you said it again...
I'm gonna kill you!
Stop! If you hit a guard...
They execute you on the spot,
Luffytaro!
Old man!
Hey! No! Don't do it!
Stop...
No... Don't...
...making me cry...
Daifugo-sama!
Whoever attacks a guard
will be executed immediately!
We saw it this time! There can be no excuses!
--Kill him!
Kill him! Kill him! Kill him!
Solitaire-sama! The keys have been stolen!
Someone stole the keys
to the Sea Prism Stone cuffs!
What are you doing, you fools?!
Did someone see who did it?!
SOLITAIRE - A VICE WARDEN (A HEADLINER)
EXCAVATION LABOR CAMP, MONKEY SMILE FRUIT
A man with a big face-kani!
He told me to put a fake key into the safe.
I was fooled-kani!
I can only walk sideways
and he took advantage of that,
and stole them-kani!
You fool!
You're useless as a guard!
He must still be in the tower!
Search high and low, even in the attic!
This is a ninja's true worth!
I got the keys!
--Stop!
--An intruder!
A shadow?!
Stop, you prowler!
Who would stop in a situation like this?!
Makibishi!
It took a little too much time...
Luffytaro-dono, wait for me!
It's time to escape!
All I need to do now is run stealthily!
Queen-sama!
Queen! Queen! Queen! Queen!
A Lead Performer, Queen-sama, is here!
Let us open the gate!
Kill him! Kill him! Kill him! Kill him!
Why is it so noisy inside?
It's heartbreaking...
But this time, he can't get away!
I won't forget you, Luffytaro!
This is finally it for Old Man Hyo, too!
You did great, straw hat man!
Why are you talking like it's over?!
Let's get out of here!
It's no use! Don't resist!
You're weakened by the Sea Prism Stone -
what can you do?!
Shut up... If you wanna fight,
bring it on!
You go next!
Damn! I'll kill him!
What's going on with that prisoner?
Why can he fight without any difficulty?
Following regulations, all power-users wear
the Sea Prism Stones to allow them just enough to work.
He should only be able to do the bare minimum...
Are you saying that I'm still no match for him?!
No, that's not what I meant!
He's running out of breath...
Warden!
The Sea Prism Stone is working!
But he has extremely strong willpower!
BABANUKI - A WARDEN (A HEADLINER)
EXCAVATION LABOR CAMP, ELEPHANT SMILE FRUIT
It troubles me...
...that you seem to be able to
violate the law of physics!
I'm in training now,
to become stronger, even a little bit,
by the time I'm released from these!
You have no future,
so why do you bother?!
Why don't you be my sparring partner?!
You should know your place!
Take this! The elephant's sneeze!
Elephant's Marchoo!
Straw hat man, are you alive?!
Damn, he's strong!
Warden Babanuki!
Queen-sama is already here!
What?!
Why didn't you tell me sooner?!
If Queen-sama's showtime has already begun,
I'll kill you!
I'm sorry!
Damn! If I could use at least Haki...
Komurasaki-tan...
She's so cute!
I'm excited!
She's too good for Orochi!
Komu-tan... Komu-tan...
Oops.
It's showtime.
We'll stop by the brothel later!
Roger!
When should we tell him that Komurasaki's dead?
We can't tell him! He'll kill us!
Here we go!
Zoom, zoom, zoom, zoom
If I get thinner, I'll be too popular
So I don't get thinner - that's my kind of...
...funk!
I may look chubby, but it's all muscle
I can sing and dance - that's my kind of...
...funk!
I'm excited!
Thanks for waiting!
You pieces of crap!
QUEEN THE PLAGUE
A LEAD PERFORMER OF THE ANIMAL KINGDOM PIRATES
Bounty: 1.32 BILLION BERRIES
Climb on my back!
Oh, okay.
All right.
Let's hear it one by one, Babanuki.
Ranking what troubles you the most recently!
Number three!
Eustass Kid escaped.
What?!
Number two!
The keys to the Sea Prism Stone cuffs
have been stolen.
What?!
And number one!
Straw Hat Luffy is on the run.
Whaaat?!
Chase him, you idiot!
Wano's special mixed bath! Nami and
Robin's sexiness catches everyone's eye while they bathe!
Meanwhile, Luffy fights against heavy odds
and Queen gives him a dreadful sentence!
Luffy and Old Man Hyo's deadly challenge begins!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Climb up! Luffy's Desperate Escape!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!