One Dream One Wish
If you want to make it
come true, Over The Top
kanaetai nara Over The Top
ONE PIECE - LAND OF WANO ARC
Setting out into the unknown world
mitakoto mo nai sekai mezashi
Weathering rough wind and waves
araburu namikaze koete
I have to keep going because
I want to get there first
tsukisusumanakya dame sa
ichibannori shitain da
Worry later since it's
all sink or swim anyway
shinpai toka atomawashi
douse shoubu ichika bachika
When your opponent looks daunting
aite ga dekaku mietara
It's a sign that your heart is shrinking
kokoro ga chijinderu shouko
Running away is not a choice
nigeru nante choisu wa nai
Take one step closer
ippo soba e chikadukun da
Being called insolent's a compliment, right?
namaiki tte homekotoba?
When things become tough,
that's when you should laugh
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
If you want to look for a new tomorrow
atarashii ashita sagashi ni ikitai no nara
Polish your unique confidence
tobikkiri no jishin wo migaite
Until your footsteps
tabi wo shita ashiato ga
Yes! Become a map
sou! chizu ni kawaru made
A new horizon, look, how far you've come
atarashii Horizon hora susunde kita bun
It's brighter and the
level of difficulty rises
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
Live in your dream and raise a hurricane
yumeutsutsu de okose Hurricane
Now! Stir up the rankings
saa! chaato kakimidase
One Dream One Wish
Dreams don't run away... Knock everything out
yume wa nigenai... zenbu Knock out
Over The Top
Nin, nin, nin...
This is a ninja's true worth!
I got the keys!
Having obtained the key to Luffy's cuffs,
Raizo raced to meet him.
Meanwhile, Luffy and Old Man Hyo
who dodged the attack of the guards...
...were trying to break out of
the Excavation Labor Camp.
Thanks for waiting!
You pieces of crap!
Climb on my back!
Oh, okay.
And number one!
Straw Hat Luffy is on the run.
Whaaat?!
"Climb up!
Luffy's Desperate Escape!"
Damn!
That was close!
It's impossible, straw hat man!
You'll never know until you try!
Hey, come on!
You pieces of crap!
Catch him already!
We're almost there!
Maybe, he can...
Does he really think
he can get out of here?!
Come on! Get back here!
I'm sorry, old man.
We fell quite far down...
No, don't be sorry!
He's not dead yet!
Guys, get out of my way!
Babanuki-sama!
I'll take care of them!
Elephant's Marchoo!
Luffy-dono!
I have good news!
The key to your cuffs...
Look! I got it!
Luffy-dono?
Isn't he here?
Are you okay, old man?
Y-Yes, I think so...
I'll make you understand
that escape from Udon is impossible!
Go!
Go to hell!
You can't get away from me this time!
How annoying!
Leave them to me!
It's him again!
Elephant's Marchoo!
Old man!
Give up now!
Damn! I feel weak!
Tsk. You gave us so much trouble...
I got something to tell you two!
EBISU TOWN
No, don't worry at all!
You can use the empty house all you want!
If you're Zorojuro-san's friends, feel free!
Thanks.
No, no, you see,
people are dying of hunger one after another.
So there are a bunch of empty houses!
You really don't have to worry!
What's so funny?
He laughs a lot.
All you can do is laugh
when you're this hungry!
Anyway, you just missed meeting Zorojuro-san!
Where did he go?
Well, he suddenly rushed out of here!
He said his sword got stolen!
I don't know how far he's gone...
It's highly likely that he got lost
and can't find the way back.
As always...
By the way, why isn't Blackleg-ya with us?
Yeah, I haven't seen him for a while...
That fool!
The ability to become invisible...
I guess I have to try it there...
By the way...
is there a bathhouse?
Don't tell me...
...he's already gone to...
BATH
BATHHOUSE
A BATHHOUSE, FLOWER CAPITAL
It's so relaxing!
So this is how a bath is in the Land of Wano.
But isn't it a little too hot?
Well, we think it's cool...
...to endure it and say something like,
"Today's bath is a bit too chilly, isn't it?"
I can't relate to that...
Say, Shinobu-chan.
I've been thinking...
What's that low entrance way?
Oh, that's called a Pomegranate Gate.
They put the wooden piece low so that
the bath won't get too cool and the steam won't escape.
Oh, I see. Thank you for your explanation.
By the way, Orobi, do you get hot easily?
Don't you wanna bathe in the hot water?
I'm not comfortable soaking in a tub
in a public bathhouse.
If anything happens...
You're as cautious as a ninja!
Magic users such as me and Orobi
get weaker when we soak in water.
But don't worry! No enemies will come.
The enemies aren't here but...
Look at that. Should I charge them?
I can't believe...
...it's a mixed bath!
Yes, it is.
Aren't you familiar with
a mixed bath like this?
Well, I know...
...that those men can't
take their eyes off of me,
but it can't be helped!
Young men are all...
--Hey, move!
--Old woman, you're in the way!
Get out of the way!
Move! Move! Move!
Ninpo!
NINPO
Ball-Crusher!
BALL-CRUSHER
That hurts!
Let's move on to the washing area.
When you get warmed up enough,
you ask Sansuke to wash your back.
Who's Sansuke?
He's Sansuke.
That's what we call the person
who washes our backs at a bathhouse.
Why an octopus?
Well, he has eight limbs.
He's suited to the job.
That's not the point.
All right.
Grab one of these.
Oh, okay.
Kyoshiro is scary.
I don't know what he's thinking.
Of course you don't. He's a yakuza.
What're you talkin' about, you idiot?!
The Land of Wano's yakuza are
supposed to be the commoners' allies.
Young people may not know it,
but there used to be...
...a great yakuza boss named
Hyogoro the Flower.
Is that the person Kanjuro was talking about?
20 years ago, the greatest yakuza boss
in the Land of Wano was...
...Hyogoro the Flower.
That's true.
If Boss Hyogoro the Flower were here,
he could've united the samurai at once.
To be honest, I don't think
we can recruit 5,000 troops in a week like this.
Maybe 500, at most.
Hmm... Is he that great?
Yeah!
He was the most influential man behind the scenes
in the Land of Wano 20 years ago,
and the great boss who had complete control
over the Flower Capital underworld.
He was also trusted by
the bosses of the other five regions,
and nice even to commoners.
He was a real chivalrous yakuza
who had both power and magnetism.
Oden-sama had respect for him, too,
since he was young...
Then, if we can find him...
It's been over 20 years.
Rumor has it that...
...he refused to be subordinate to the Kurozumi Clan
and was killed by Orochi!
In contrast, Fukurokuju
who leads the Oniwabanshu
that supported the Kozuki Clan
with Boss Hyogoro the Flower...
...chose to serve Orochi.
I worked for him at that time,
but I couldn't take it so I ran.
So I became their enemy!
I see...
You're...
...Hanzo?!
So you're alive! You man-seducing...
...sexy kunoichi.
That's why he knew you!
Shinobu-chan, you're so cool!
I kind of am!
I miss him...
Boss Hyogoro...
He's become a part of history now...
Stop making me repeat myself...
I said if you join our pirate group,
Kaido-san will pardon you for everything!
Shut up! I refuse!
Talk about bad timing!
Luffy-dono!
I have the key!
It brings back memories,
doesn't it, Hyogoro?!
You were approached quite feverishly
by Kaido-san and Orochi back then.
The legendary yakuza became
such a malnourished old man,
and he will die a miserable death!
What? Did he say Hyogoro?!
No way! That small Old Man Hyo?!
I don't care about myself,
but have mercy on this young man!
I'm begging you!
Please!
What should I do?
Okay, I got an idea!
I came up with something exciting!
Luffy-dono...
I cannot believe it...
You really look exactly like you did back in those days.
Who is it?!
Is anyone there?!
It is me, Raizo...
Is Momonosuke-sama alive?
Don't tell me you are...
...Kawamatsu?!
K...
Kawamatsu?!
Is it...
...really you?!
You are alive!
Yeah... I am glad that I was able to put up with
all that rotten fish for 13 years.
Let me see your face, Kawamatsu!
I can't. I am chained!
What?!
When will the fight be?
Nine days from now, on the
night of the Fire Festival!
Chopping Kaido's head off
during the festival to pay tribute to him is a great idea!
I am sorry, Raizo,
but could you get me out of here first?!
Of course I will! I will
get to it right away!
In order to set you free,
I guess I need the key to the
cage and the key to the cuffs.
Yeah, I do not know if they will open
since they are rusted.
There's someone at the forbidden cell!
Who is that?!
That's the guy!
Solitaire-sama!
We found the key thief
from the Executive Tower!
Don't let him escape!
Oh, no!
Smoke Escape Jutsu!
--He disappeared!
--He must be a ninja!
Find him!
Now, leave the key thief to the others and...
...bring the thing here!
All right.
We'll execute the fools!
Yes, sir!
Hey! Come this way!
Here we go!
It's Queen-sama's Special Device Performance!
The Sumo Inferno!
Queen! Queen! Queen!
Queen!
Sumo?
What the...?!
This collar is the same as the ones
I just put on you guys!
Imagine this stone pillar is you!
If you leave the ring with that thing on...
How scary!
If you leave the ring,
the sharp blades will be ejected as you saw,
and your head will get cut off in an instant!
Damn! It's just like the
Celestial Dragons' collar!
Of course, it's not designed to be taken off by force
so it's no use!
I can't remove it!
You'll be fine as long as you keep winning
sumo matches!
But stepping out of the
ring means instant death!
You guys are a tag team!
If both of you fall out of the ring, the execution is complete!
But if you ever change your mind
and wanna join our group,
only Straw Hat will be released!
On this side, we'll use weapons,
fight in numbers, and have no collars!
We'll deploy as many people as we want.
So I'll do you one favor!
I'll remove your Sea Prism Stone cuffs!
What? Whaaat?!
I went through a lot of trouble!
Then, this is not the key
for Luffy-dono's cuffs!
Yay!
You're a really nice person!
This means you're letting us out!
Aren't you forgetting about the collar?
I put something worse on you!
Oh, yeah!
Wait a minute!
If we fight as a tag team,
I'll give Straw Hat-san trouble!
Could you at least execute us separately?!
Hey, Balloon!
Balloon?!
Straw Hat-san!
If I kick your ass...
will you let us out of here?!
What did you say?!
The worst-ever deathmatch, the Sumo Inferno!
Its deadly rules force its unarmed
challengers to fight Kaido's armed troops
who come attacking fiercely
from every direction!
In this hellish situation,
Luffy launches an offensive to survive!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Dead or Alive! Queen's Sumo Inferno!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
...