One Dream One Wish
kanaetai nara Over The Top
If you want to make it come true, Over The Top
ONE PIECE - LAND OF WANO ARC
mitakoto mo nai sekai mezashi
Setting out into the unknown world
araburu namikaze koete
Weathering rough wind and waves
tsukisusumanakya dame sa ichibannori shitain da
I have to keep going because I want to get there first
shinpai toka atomawashi douse shoubu ichika bachika
Worry later since it's all sink or swim anyway
aite ga dekaku mietara
When your opponent looks daunting
kokoro ga chijinderu shouko
It's a sign that your heart is shrinking
nigeru nante choisu wa nai
Running away is not a choice
ippo soba e chikadukun da
Take one step closer
namaiki tte homekotoba?
Being called insolent's a compliment, right?
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
When things become tough, that's when you should laugh
atarashii ashita sagashi ni ikitai no nara
If you want to look for a new tomorrow
tobikkiri no jishin wo migaite
Polish your unique confidence
tabi wo shita ashiato ga
Until your footsteps
sou! chizu ni kawaru made
Yes! Become a map
atarashii Horizon hora susunde kita bun
A new horizon, look, how far you've come
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
It's brighter and the level of difficulty rises
yumeutsutsu de okose Hurricane
Live in your dream and raise a hurricane
saa! chaato kakimidase
Now! Stir up the rankings
One Dream One Wish
yume wa nigenai... zenbu Knock out
Dreams don't run away... Knock everything out
Over The Top
BATH
BATHHOUSE
That's true.
If Boss Hyogoro the Flower were here,
he could've united the samurai at once.
Hmm... Is he that great?
Yeah!
He was the most influential man behind the scenes
in the Land of Wano 20 years ago,
and the great boss who had complete control
over the Flower Capital underworld.
He was also trusted by
the bosses of the other five regions,
and nice even to commoners.
He was a real chivalrous yakuza
who had both power and magnetism.
Here we go!
It's Queen-sama's Special Device Performance!
The Sumo Inferno!
Queen! Queen! Queen!
Queen!
You'll be fine as long as you keep winning
sumo matches!
But stepping out of the ring means instant death!
You guys are a tag team!
If both of you fall out of the ring, the execution is complete!
But if you ever change your mind
and wanna join our group,
only Straw Hat will be released!
Wait a minute!
If we fight as a tag team,
I'll give Straw Hat-san trouble!
Could you at least execute us separately?!
Hey, Balloon!
Balloon?!
Straw Hat-san!
If I kick your ass...
will you let us out of here?!
What did you say?!
"Dead or Alive!
Queen's Sumo Inferno!"
My stomach hurts!
He said he's gonna kick my ass!
You crack me up.
Queen-sama! He'll understand once it starts!
He doesn't realize how unreasonable its rules are!
He has no idea that
he's got no chance to survive!
You're right!
Then, get ready and enter the ring, guys!
Deathmatch! Deathmatch!
Deathmatch!
Th-There are too many of them...
On top of that, all of us have weapons.
You guys are unarmed!
Now do you realize that you're gonna die soon?!
Deathmatch! Deathmatch!
Deathmatch!
Rest in peace... Old Man Hyo... Straw Hat...
Lock eyes with your opponents!
Don't look away!
Observe what happens to those
who disobey us in this place!
Ready...
I'm sorry, straw hat man...
I put you through this...
Stay close to me.
Go!
Watch this, damn prisoners!
This is what'll happen to you
if you disobey guards!
Who's next?!
They're not even a good enough warm up!
Whaaat?!
Don't tell me he's...
So he uses the Color of the Supreme King...
You...
I guess this is gonna be interesting...
Pleasures, enter the ring!
It's been uproarious since he came...
In any case, don't let Boss Hyogoro die.
I'm counting on you, Luffytaro.
I feel refreshed!
A BATHHOUSE, FLOWER CAPITAL
We can have tea upstairs.
Let's go see then.
It's a raid!
A Headliner of the Animal Kingdom Pirates - Hawkins!
Nobody move!
What do you want from a bathhouse?
Oh, a bathhouse is perfect for this
because everyone's naked
and we can see everything.
Drake, what are you doing? Get inside.
My duty is to take down the fool
called Soba Mask.
Take care of those chores by yourselves.
What should we do, Shinobu-chan?!
I think they know about us.
They came for us.
It's no fair!
People are defenseless here!
Shall we fight?
That's the last resort.
Mature women don't use weapons carelessly...
Hide behind me.
It's time to show
the power of the enticing sexy body!
Everyone, line up
and show us your ankles!
What?!
If you have a Reversed Crescent Moon
tattooed on your ankle, we need you to come with us!
All of those people who are in the tub
must come out, too!
I can't believe it.
How does he know?!
--Go check.
--Yes, sir!
Was the plan leaked?
Someone's hiding there!
Come out!
Nami! I'll back you up if something happens.
No, I didn't mean to hide!
I'm just an ordinary customer...
You are...!
--Dynamite!
--Oh, my! That body is a national treasure!
How deadly!
I can't believe it!
That's very powerful, Nami-san!
Happy punch!
What?!
What the...
He's the guy from yesterday.
Soba Mask!
Nami-sa...
The shape of Nami-san's body
was like a magnificent mighty river flowing...
Sanji! Why is he here?!
What is he wearing?!
You've got to be kidding!
Drake!
Soba Mask?!
He was inside all along!
Hey! Where is Soba Mask?!
What?!
Where...
Why didn't you tell me that
you're sensitive to naked women?!
I'm not...
Drake...
You're from the North Blue, aren't you?
So are you... Why are you asking?
Then you know him, don't you?
Germa 66's...
...Stealth Black!
Everyone from the North Blue knows
the story of Sora, Warrior of the Sea...
Germa... Is he the real thing?
Stop running!
The search is not over...
This is our chance to escape!
I won't let you!
You bastard!
You can't attack women!
An acceleration device?!
Even a flotation device...
Stealth Black!
You're a member of the evil army.
Why are you helping people?!
Stealth Black!
Don't call me that!
I'm Soba Mask!
You're Germa. Cut the crap!
Go to hell, Germa 66!
Soba Mask!
Is it Stealth Black's transmission device?!
Hang on tight!
--He's flying!
--Chase him!
Only Stealth Black could've done it!
I'll take him down next time!
Sanji-kun, what is this all about?!
It's a long story! I'll tell you later!
Aren't you losing too much blood?
I could die happy right now!
Let's get to Ebisu Town!
Usopp and the others will be there!
You're not okay, are you?!
It's not a big deal...
Anyway, it's not a good thing
that they know about the ankle tattoo!
Yeah, I wonder how they found that out...
Before I went to the bathhouse,
I heard more bad news.
Bepo and the others were captured!
What?
The Animal Kingdom Pirates are looking to
lure Tra-guy using his friends as bait.
I'm sure he'll go rescue them.
He may not look it, but he cares about his friends.
We must stop him for now!
Or the Flower Capital will be in chaos!
What were you doing at such a serious time?
Go!
--What are you waiting for?!
--I wanna see Straw Hat's blood splattered already!
What's wrong with him?
Since I had the Sea Prism Stone cuffs on for so long,
I feel so much lighter!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Gatling!
My technique got stronger, too!
I'm not getting tired at all!
Let's get rid of the old man first!
Go to hell!
Straw hat man...
I'm sorry to give you so much trouble...
Please pay no mind to a dotard like me
and fight with all your might!
Fighting with all my might isn't enough.
What?
I feel like I still need something more...
No...
No... This isn't good enough...
He's still...
Gum-Gum...
...Kong Organ Gun!
Thunder Bagua!
...out of my reach!
Oh, yeah!
That's it!
LAND OF WANO
Meanwhile, in Ringo
on the east side of the Land of Wano...
RINGO, LAND OF WANO
I will help myself to that weapon!
I still have to collect more...
There you are.
You stole my sword, didn't you?
It is not your sword...
I've already taken the great sword - Shusui
back to where it belongs.
That is a treasure which was stolen from the
legendary samurai of the Land of Wano - Ryuma's grave!
I know!
Then, shut up and go away!
Otherwise, I will swipe those two swords
on your waist, too!
Are you a weapon collector?
What are you gonna do with all those?
We happen to need a lot of weapons, too,
so the timing is excellent...
Your weapon collection...
I'm gonna take the whole thing!
I will bring you down instead,
you damn mountain bandit!
I'm sorry if I confused you.
I'm...
...a pirate!
Zoro and Gyukimaru get in a fierce sword fight over
the great sword Shusui.
During the severe fight,
Zoro comes to know the secret behind Shusui.
However, at the same time, another assassin appears
in a spray of snow as a new crisis hits Zoro!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Gyukimaru! Zoro Fights a Duel on Bandit's Bridge"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!