One Dream One Wish
kanaetai nara Over The Top
If you want to make it
come true, Over The Top
ONE PIECE - LAND OF WANO ARC
mitakoto mo nai sekai mezashi
Setting out into the unknown world
araburu namikaze koete
Weathering rough wind and waves
I have to keep going because
I want to get there first
tsukisusumanakya dame sa
ichibannori shitain da
Worry later since it's
all sink or swim anyway
shinpai toka atomawashi
douse shoubu ichika bachika
When your opponent looks daunting
aite ga dekaku mietara
It's a sign that your heart is shrinking
kokoro ga chijinderu shouko
Running away is not a choice
nigeru nante choisu wa nai
Take one step closer
ippo soba e chikadukun da
Being called insolent's a compliment, right?
namaiki tte homekotoba?
When things become tough,
that's when you should laugh
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
If you want to look for a new tomorrow
atarashii ashita sagashi ni ikitai no nara
Polish your unique confidence
tobikkiri no jishin wo migaite
Until your footsteps
tabi wo shita ashiato ga
Yes! Become a map
sou! chizu ni kawaru made
A new horizon, look, how far you've come
atarashii Horizon hora susunde kita bun
It's brighter and the
level of difficulty rises
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
yumeutsutsu de okose Hurricane
Live in your dream and raise a hurricane
saa! chaato kakimidase
Now! Stir up the rankings
One Dream One Wish
yume wa nigenai... zenbu Knock out
Dreams don't run away... Knock everything out
Over The Top
Who's next?!
They're not even a good enough warm up!
You stole my sword, didn't you?
It is not your sword...
Are you a weapon collector?
What are you gonna do with all those?
We happen to need a lot of weapons, too.
Your weapon collection...
I'm gonna take the whole thing!
I will bring you down instead,
you damn mountain bandit!
I'm sorry if I confused you.
I'm...
...a pirate!
"Gyukimaru!
Zoro Fights a Duel on Bandit's Bridge!"
I wanna eat the red-bean soup already...
Hey, haven't we reached
the place called Udon yet?
Chopperemon!
I'm hungry.
Don't look at me drooling like that!
It won't be long, Olin-chan!
Once we get to Udon,
we'll save Big Bro Luffy.
And then...
...we'll eat...
...the red-bean soup!
Otama-chan, do you like it, too?
Yeah, I love it!
I was treated to it by Otsuru-san
on my birthday!
My mouth slowly filled with
the sweetness of the red-bean paste...
My taste buds were truly dancing!
I know!
Red-bean paste is the best!
Yes! Yes! Absolutely!
Uh-huh! Uh-huh!
Red-bean paste! And a rice cake!
I've never had such a soft and delicious thing
in my life!
I know, I know!
A white rice cake shines
like a living frog's eyeball!
What?!
A frog's eyeball?
Olin-chan, that's a little freaky.
Oh, yeah? Just by thinking about it,
I can't help drooling.
I'm not edible!
I can't wait to have the red-bean soup!
They are getting quite excited
talking about the red-bean soup.
It's no good.
What should I do?
Once she finds out there's no red-bean soup,
the shock might bring back her memories,
and she'll return to herself!
Straw Hat!
Instead of saving him,
we'll put Luffy in harm's way!
What should I do?!
What am I supposed to do?!
--Bring me more red-bean soup!
--Yes, sir!
Luffytaro wins!
You did it, Luffytaro!
Gee... You took down all the Pleasures.
That's not it.
What's not it? You won again!
Well, Rayleigh was doing it effortlessly.
Rayleigh?
Yeah.
Luffy.
When you use the Haki of the Color of Arms,
imagine you're wearing invisible armor.
At that moment, Rayleigh sent the elephant flying
without touching it.
The first Haki he showed me was
a very high level one.
If I can use that...
Gum-Gum...
...Grizzly...
...Magnum!
I can take down Kaido!
It's taking too much time!
If you let me do it,
the execution will be done in no time!
You don't really understand
how the Sumo Inferno works!
Look!
The length of the fight
and the number of opponents.
Those are the toughest elements in fights.
He'll lose his spirit and energy little by little
and die miserably.
"The execution will be done in no time"?!
Don't be silly.
That's not exciting at all!
I want a refill!
Again?! You've already had
so much red-bean soup!
Screw you!
Red-bean soup is like oxygen to me!
Here you go.
No one else can have it!
My red-bean soup! It's my favorite!
Oh, my soup!
Send my opponent flying
as if I'm wearing invisible armor!
Straw hat man, what are you...
All right!
I wanna practice! Bring it on!
As you wish!
Your next opponents are...
...the Gifters!
I won't miss any secret talk.
Bat Smile Fruit!
Bat-man!
The beautiful leg.
I'm a swift runner!
Gazelle Smile Fruit!
Gazelle-man!
We're the Gifters!
Oh, no! There are two Gifters!
They kidnapped Tama, didn't they?
How dare you mess with Holdem-sama
and Bakura Town!
You can't get away with it!
Great! They're perfect sparring partners!
Lock eyes with your opponents!
Ready...
Go!
Beautiful Leg Spin Kick!
All right!
How dare you!
It was just an ordinary punch.
I'll do it right this time!
That wasn't it!
Luffy.
It's invisible armor.
Invisible...
...armor!
Gum-Gum...
...Bullet!
The winner is Luffytaro!
This Straw Hat is quite strong!
Hmmm... That wasn't it.
What?
I'm not supposed to touch them.
I wish I could try something more.
Oh, well!
All right!
Next!
Bring it on!
I met Ryuma.
Don't lie to me!
You met Ryuma?!
How could I believe such nonsense?!
Well, the soul belonged to
someone else I knew.
Stop talking gibberish!
How could you know Ryuma?!
Ryuma is a great swordsman
who was said to cut any opponent in an instant!
You do not know how valuable
the great sword Shusui is!
Shusui is the Land of Wano's treasure!
It belongs to Ryuma!
A long time ago, when the Land of Wano
was recognized as the Land
of Gold by other countries...
Gold? What are you talking about?
Unguarded!
Pirates around the world wanted gold.
Nobles tried to rule
the Land of Gold - the Land of Wano!
He showed those enemies from overseas
how formidable he was...
and burned the Land of Wano's samurai
in their minds!
That is who Ryuma is.
There are so many legends related to him
as a swordsman.
One of them...
...says that he slayed a dragon
that appeared above the capital!
After his death, he was laid to rest in a temple
with the great sword Shusui...
...as this country's God of the Blade.
Shusui is a national treasure!
Okay. I understand.
But it has nothing to do with me!
I'll take back Shusui!
I don't feel comfortable
with just two swords.
I think I have overestimated you.
Shusui is a Black Blade!
In other words, it was forged
through the battles that Ryuma fought!
I was only trying to figure
out if you were a punk
with no backbone who just wanted to have it!
"Forged"?
Oh, yeah, I was wondering about that...
Don't tell me that Black Blades are...
Help!
Unguarded!
You bastard...
Don't try your best to catch me off guard!
Catching people off guard is the only way to
win deadly battles, so that is all I am trying!
Somebody, help!
Someone is trying to kill us!
Oh, there's a samurai!
Hey! Help us!
Are they serious or just fooling around?
I can't tell!
Swordsmen, please help!
Blood?
I guess they're not joking.
Hold it right there!
Unguarded!
Why don't you wait?!
Hey, you, take a hint!
Our duel is not over!
I'll fight you! But could you wait?!
You are the murderer - Zorojuro, right?
A WANTED PERSON IN THE FLOWER CAPITAL
HITOKIRI KAMAZO
Zorojuro, why would you
wanna help that woman?
Why do you wanna slash a woman?
I'm only trying to kill that brat
who won't stop laughing.
Don't worry, Toko.
Hitokiri Kamazo.
You're a street slasher
who randomly kills people in the capital.
But you're actually an assassin working for Orochi
while disguised as an outlaw!
Otherwise, why would you want to kill Otoko?
You address the Shogun, Orochi-sama,
with no honorific.
Who are you?
Samurai-sama, please help us!
Well, of course, I'm not gonna just stand here
and watch a kid and a woman get killed...
I will give you anything you want!
Sake and food would be nice...
You got it!
All right! Deal!
No problem. I've been told that I can kill
as many as I want if they get in my way.
I often get in trouble afterwards
when I slay someone who has a boss.
Don't worry!
You'll be the one dying!
He's quite strong!
Now you're getting serious.
Against the two formidable opponents,
Kamazo and Gyukimaru, Zoro wields only two swords!
The fierce scramble drives him into a corner!
Facing the worst crisis ever without Shusui,
he risks his life and takes the chance of a lifetime!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Big Turnover! The Three-Sword
Style Overcomes Danger!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!