One Dream One Wish
kanaetai nara Over The Top
If you want to make it
come true, Over The Top
ONE PIECE - LAND OF WANO ARC
mitakoto mo nai sekai mezashi
Setting out into the unknown world
araburu namikaze koete
Weathering rough wind and waves
tsukisusumanakya dame sa
ichibannori shitain da
I have to keep going because
I want to get there first
shinpai toka atomawashi
douse shoubu ichika bachika
Worry later since it's
all sink or swim anyway
aite ga dekaku mietara
When your opponent looks daunting
kokoro ga chijinderu shouko
It's a sign that your heart is shrinking
nigeru nante choisu wa nai
Running away is not a choice
ippo soba e chikadukun da
Take one step closer
namaiki tte homekotoba?
Being called insolent's a compliment, right?
kitsui toki hodo warattoke
When things become tough,
that's when you should laugh
atarashii ashita sagashi ni ikitai no nara
If you want to look for a new tomorrow
tobikkiri no jishin wo migaite
Polish your unique confidence
tabi wo shita ashiato ga
Until your footsteps
sou! chizu ni kawaru made
Yes! Become a map
atarashii Horizon hora susunde kita bun
A new horizon, look, how far you've come
mabushisa to nanido ga joushou
It's brighter and the
level of difficulty rises
yumeutsutsu de okose Hurricane
Live in your dream and raise a hurricane
saa! chaato kakimidase
Now! Stir up the rankings
One Dream One Wish
yume wa nigenai... zenbu Knock out
Dreams don't run away... Knock everything out
Over The Top
The first Haki he showed me was
a very high level one.
Help!
Now you're getting serious.
"A Big Turnover!
The Three-Sword Style Overcomes Danger!"
Feels like I'm missing something...
EXCAVATION LABOR CAMP, UDON
No, no!
This isn't good practice at all!
Practice?
Hey, Balloon!
They're not good enough!
Don't you have someone stronger?
You can fight me if you want!
That bastard... He's pushing his luck!
I think you still don't understand
the situation you're in.
Hell hasn't been unleashed yet.
Straw Hat!
I'm hungry-bear!
If I defeat Straw Hat,
can I get the prisoners' dumplings all to myself-bear?
BEAR-MAN - A GIFTER
BEAR SMILE FRUIT
Yes, you can. Rock the place up!
That's my Queen-bear!
I became 100 times more motivated-bear!
What?!
You're so greedy!
I won't let you have the dumplings!
This time, it's a bear Gifter...
He's quite pretty...
Let's go-bear!
Bear!
Those punches...
...aren't working at all-bear!
Straw hat man!
Outside he looks pretty,
but he's still a bear!
They say that bears' claws are
powerful enough to sever human bodies!
Be careful!
Your body's...
...tough.
So what-bear?
This is more like it...
Because Kaido's body is even tougher!
Shut up!
Bear!
Without laying a finger...
Send him flying!
Damn, when I try to use force,
I can't help hitting them!
What have you been...
...up to?
Forget it.
Let's move on!
Next!
Oh, Dogstorm!
Where have you been?
What's the matter, Kin'emon?
We have a huge problem!
AN ABANDONED VILLAGE, KURI
KIN'EMON AND MINK MUSKETEERS
They found out about
the flyer with the symbol and the moon tattoo?!
Yes, and now it's a big mess!
What should we do, Duke-sama?!
We were handing them out covertly...
I do not know how it leaked...
We wrote it in the coded symbol
in case it fell into unintended hands.
But they somehow know the link between
the ankle tattoo and this flyer.
Now in the capital,
I heard our allies are getting caught
by Kaido and Orochi's underlings.
You're under arrest! You're under arrest!
Stop resisting, you rebel!
I found the flyer!
Easy!
He's got the moon tattoo, too!
Those who have the mark on their ankles
are rebels!
If anyone sees it, let us know!
Rumors spread quickly...
Everyone in the capital already knows about it.
We shouldn't take our time
patrolling bathhouses now.
You're lucky.
What do you mean by that?
You're Germa. Cut the crap!
Go to hell, Germa 66!
Soba Mask!
Is it Stealth Black's transmission device?!
Hang on tight!
Only Stealth Black could've done it!
I'll take him down next time!
It wasn't just my fault.
You also let them get away.
Oh? Oh, boy!
This is...!
On the night of the Fire
Festival... Habu Port...
And the Reversed Crescent Moon,
the symbol of rebellion!
Komurasaki-dayu!
Boss Kyoshiro...
Komurasaki's wake has been canceled.
If so many upset people like them pour in,
there might be an accident...
A BROTHEL, FLOWER CAPITAL
I think the funeral tomorrow will be
even more crowded...
--May she rest in peace!
--Komurasaki-dayu!
--Komurasaki!
--Komurasaki-sama!
Quite a lot of people
hold a grudge against you,
so please be careful.
They don't know what they're talking about...
Kyoshiro!
KYOSHIRO SLASHED KOMURASAKI TO DEATH
There was no other way...
The one who'll suffer the biggest loss...
...is me.
Certainly.
Orochi-sama is frustrated.
I guess that it's because of this.
Komurasaki!
Orochi-sama... has not
come out of his room...
It cannot be helped.
His love interest, Komurasaki, was killed in front of him.
On top of that, there is this.
This symbol points to a rebellion
against Orochi-sama and Kaido-sama.
The fire suggests the Fire Festival.
The two birds indicate twilight.
The habu snake implies Habu
Port, the rendezvous point.
That means some people will raid Onigashima
on the night of the Fire Festival?
But we found out beforehand, so all we need to do
is find the rebels and keep them under control.
And we will teach them the hard way
who reigns over the Land of Wano.
Stop, you two!
Nothing will be solved by arguing!
EBISU TOWN
We're friends!
Let's talk!
I don't have anything to talk to you about!
Hey, what's up, kids?
It seems like you're having fun!
They're fighting!
Fighting? That's not good...
Here, you can have this,
so go someplace else.
--Yay!
--Thank you, Yasu-san!
I'm not gonna give up on my crew!
I'll go save them!
Are you out of your mind?
It'll be like you're turning yourself in!
Our allies who wanna take down Orochi
are getting caught one after another...
...ever since your crew messed up!
What do you mean?!
That little bear and the others...
...definitely told them about our plan!
Bepo and the others would rather die than talk!
Don't underestimate them!
Wait! That's exactly what
the enemies want, Tra-guy!
You can't tell me what to do, Blackleg-ya!
Both of you, simmer down.
You're the one who needs to cool your head!
You've got to...
You've got to trust your friends!
You're the most untrustworthy person I know!
Happy punch!
What?!
What the...
He's the guy from yesterday.
Soba Mask!
Nami-sa...
The shape of Nami-san's body
was like a magnificent mighty river flowing...
Sanji! Why is he here?!
What is he wearing?!
You've got to be kidding!
I didn't see anything at all...
How did you get punched
to end up looking like that?
Are you trying to run?!
You must eliminate those who got caught!
To silence them!
What did you say?!
That's what we do in the ninja world!
You're scary, Shinobu!
We're not doing this for fun!
For two decades...
For 20 years, we've been waiting for this!
If we fail now, there
won't be another chance!
Stop it, Shinobu!
Kan-sama...
Things do not always go the way you want!
I can relate to your frustration!
But without help from these people
who miraculously have the same purpose as us,
we cannot fulfill Oden-sama's wish!
Excuse me, thank you!
I heard your voice outside!
You all have good voices!
Hey, who are you?!
Oh?
Whoa! You're so beautiful!
Are you a goddess?!
Stop it!
Would you like to come in?
Oh, thank you.
Hey!
Don't tell me...
...you're Shinobu-chan?!
Kanjuro-kun!
Oh, I see, I see!
Then this is the real thing!
This is what everyone's
talking about in the capital!
I got excited!
Will the decisive battle start soon?!
Unguarded!
I can't pull it out!
I'll make use of this for now...
Three...
...swords?!
Three-Sword Style!
Purgatory...
...Onigiri!
How strong...
Damn... Not before the decisive battle!
S-Samurai-sama!
Luffy tries to elevate his ability to use
the Color of Arms as tough enemies keep assail him!
With this deadly training,
he pushes himself ahead to take down Kaido!
And Zoro is taught a stunning
truth by the woman he saved,
and gets to the core of
the incident 20 years ago!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Zoro, Stunned! The Shocking
Identity of the Mysterious Woman!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!