Hey, Balloon!
They're not good enough!
Don't you have someone stronger?
You can fight me if you want!
Unguarded!
I'll make use of this for now...
Purgatory...
...Onigiri!
How strong...
S-Samurai-sama!
Without laying a finger...
Send him flying!
Forget it.
Let's move on!
"Zoro, Stunned!
The Shocking Identity of the Mysterious Woman!"
EXCAVATION LABOR CAMP, UDON
Come on, come on! Kick their asses now!
I wanna join a sumo match myself!
Gross!
You idiot!
I told you that you'd get killed
if you mess with us!
Oh, the spit guy from earlier!
Not just Alpaca-man!
I'm Madillo-man! A Gifter who ate...
the Armadillo Smile Fruit!
MADILLO-MAN - A GIFTER
ARMADILLO SMILE FRUIT
Oh, your body looks so tough!
Perfect for my training!
You fool!
The bullets that are loaded in these
are made of the Sea Prism Stone!
Straw Hat!
Since you're a power-user,
go ahead and curl up in a ball!
Just like an armadillo!
You guys are finished!
They're finished?
Why can't he see? They're
not finished at all!
To set an example for other prisoners,
I'll take my time torturing you!
First you, old man!
We'll begin with you, you worthless shit!
Old man!
Go right, crouch down, and jump!
What?!
Go to hell!
--Run!
--Okay!
Go right!
Crouch down!
--And...
--Damn you!
Jump!
What?!
Ow, ow, ow...
Damn, damn, damn, damn, damn, damn!
Good job, old man! Keep it up!
What the...
Can you foresee the future or something?
Screw you!
No one can do that!
What did you actually do?!
What?!
I can't get him! Dammit!
U-Unbelievable...
Old man! Go left next!
--What?!
--You fool!
Left!
Dammit, that old shit!
Take this!
Left! Left! Left! Left!
You fool!
Damn, you little shit!
Stop moving!
Right there!
You can't take me down with guns!
Y-You bastard!
I have no other option!
Go to hell!
Without laying a finger, send him flying!
That's not it.
That's just the normal Color of Arms...
Damn!
Arma-Defense!
This isn't it...
Again, this is just the
normal Color of Arms...
What?! You're not gonna hit me?!
Alpaca Fencing!
Hey! Which way should I go next?!
Straw hat man!
All right! Stop right there!
What?!
It's easier this way!
I'm sorry!
Let's do it, Alpaca-man!
Okay!
Put me down!
I don't wanna give you any more trouble!
No, actually, the heavier the better!
What?!
For my training!
FLOWER CAPITAL
RASETSU TOWN, FLOWER CAPITAL
PRISON
RASETSU PRISON
RASETSU TOWN PRISONERS' QUARTERS
AKA: PUBLIC CELLS
I didn't expect to see this
many ruffians in here!
People, have a good look at them!
These are the faces of the fools
who want to rebel against Orochi-sama and Kaido-sama!
Get your ass in there already!
I feel sorry for you guys!
Your plot has already been revealed...
It's a complete failure.
Fukurokuju-dono, wait!
What makes you think that
this ankle tattoo is the symbol of rebellion?!
This is just a popular design!
We have nothing to do with any kind of rebellion!
Cut it out!
Then, how do you explain about this flyer?
The Reversed Crescent Moon
at the center of the flyer...
I assume it is a symbol pointing to a rebellion
against Orochi-sama...
It looks just like your tattoos.
It is an order from Orochi-sama.
Just shut up and stay in there!
We're in big trouble...
Will everyone think...
...that we told them about the plan?
Don't worry...
I know Captain will believe us...
Alpaca Fencing!
You bastard!
What's wrong?! Finish it up already!
Alpaca-man! Madillo-man!
Just take them down!
Are you trying to help us
by carrying the old man, Straw Hat?!
Okay! Bring me more!
Y-Yes, sir!
You fool!
You're already playing into our hands!
Take this, Straw Hat!
--Let's use a combination technique!
--Okay!
Madillo Spin!
Alpaca Fire!
Oh, they've merged together!
Here comes the combination technique!
Great! Go get them!
Just keep it up!
Hey! Bring more!
Yes, sir!
Kaido's body is far tougher than this!
That wasn't it! I can't do it right!
What?!
You sent them flying.
Wasn't that good enough?
No, it wasn't, old man!
Every time you hit someone,
you've been saying, "That wasn't it" this whole time.
What are you trying to do?
What am I trying to do? I'm training myself!
I have to become strong!
What? Training yourself?!
Despite being in the middle of a deadly show,
is he training himself?!
I wanna throw a punch that will send my enemies flying
without touching them!
That way,
I think I can break Kaido's tough scales!
NORTHERN GRAVEYARD, RINGO
Sword...
Sword!
You are...
You surprised me!
Please do not get up yet.
It is not good for your wound...
She's right! You don't need to get up yet!
Where am I?
Thank you very much for
saving our lives earlier.
Thank you!
But you got badly injured in return...
I really don't know what to do
to repay you...
I got hurt because I suck.
You guys have nothing to do with it...
Where did he go?!
He still has Shusui!
No, you cannot go out
with such a grave wound!
Ouch!
The wound is on that side, idiot!
I am sorry!
Gee...
Goodbye!
Do not go! Your wound has not yet healed!
Ow, ow, ow, ouch!
I said my wound is right there!
Why can't you see?!
I-I am so sorry!
Ow, ow, ow...
Uh, um, are you okay?
Don't touch me!
You're gonna be fine, Samurai-san!
You'll get better soon!
I stole this toad oil
ointment in the capital...
I mean, I bought it!
You stole it...
N-No, I bought it.
Well, I don't care either way.
Toad oil is amazing!
If you apply it to a sword-cut,
it'll just go away!
Toad oil, huh?
Well, I hope it'll work!
Say, Samurai-san!
Stay with us!
Well, at least until the wound heals,
you had better stay here...
You got something to eat?
Yes! Do you want some now?!
Would you like to have more?
Gyukimaru?
Oh, yes.
Everyone knows him in the capital.
Gyukimaru on Bandit's Bridge.
I've already taken the great sword - Shusui
back to where it belongs.
That is a treasure which was stolen from
the legendary samurai of the Land of Wano - Ryuma's grave!
We do not know where he lives,
but the warrior monk shows himself
whenever an armed person tries to cross the bridge.
So I can always meet him there?
Then there's no need to hurry...
I wonder who that Gyukimaru is,
but first, who are you two?
That Grim Reaper was after your lives...
The thing is we made
the Shogun of the Land of Wano angry...
The Shogun, huh?
Oro... Oroshi?
No, Orochi.
You made him angry
so he sent that assassin after you?
Yes, if one makes him angry,
they must die in the Land of Wano.
Say, Samurai-san!
My name is Toko!
TOKO
If you say it with an "O,"
it's Otoko (Male), but I'm not male!
OTOKO
Isn't it funny?
No, not really.
What? What?!
Everyone says it's funny!
Why don't you think so?!
I don't know.
You are attired as a samurai from the Land of Wano,
but you are from overseas, aren't you?
You don't look like a bad...
A bad per...
A bad person.
--Say it smoothly!
--I am sorry!
Samurai-san, you look scary!
But you're a really nice person
because you saved us!
Um...
I will tell you a secret,
but you must keep it...
What is it?
I want to find my older brother!
We were separated 20 years ago...
He might be in the Land of Wano now!
His name is...
Kozuki Momonosuke.
I'm his sister...
My name is Hiyori!
Luffy keeps on fighting,
seeking to learn the way to strike a blow against Kaido!
Ryuo is the name of the Land of
Wano's Haki! To share its essence,
Old Man Hyo challenges a formidable enemy!
When Old Man Hyo's all-out punch roars,
Luffy breaks new ground!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Get the Hang of It! The Land of Wano's Haki - Ryuo!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!