Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Catch the wind
kaze ni nore
Don't give up, if I'm determined
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
I'll never turn back
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
Laugh on through troubled waters
waraitobase aranami
Shout it out, to save
your spirit from breaking
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Your friends are there for you
nakama ga irun da
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Even when the darkness
tries to tear you apart
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Come on, brave it out
hora Brave it out
It's going to be all right
daijoubu sa
Strong bonds will break through
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
The flag that called forth oaths
chikai atsumeta hata
Keep fighting on
tatakai tsudukete iku
Stay true to yourself
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Seize it, dreamin' on
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
I can't lose, I'll never run away
makerarenai nige ya shinai
Transcend meetings and
partings and keep going
deai wakare koe ikou
They're all treasures
zenbu takaramono
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Raise your fist
ko wo agete
Um...
What is it?
I want to find my older brother!
We were separated 20 years ago...
He might be in the Land of Wano now!
His name is...
Kozuki Momonosuke.
I'm his sister...
My name is Hiyori!
"Get the Hang of It!
The Land of Wano's Haki - Ryuo!"
Momonosuke's...
...sister?!
I thought so!
I am glad that I gathered
my courage and said it!
I kind of took a chance.
You know my brother, don't you?!
And he is okay, right?!
Wait! Calm down!
I need to organize my thoughts.
These days, people are talking about
the return of the Kozuki Clan.
At the same time, a strong and kind samurai
from overseas is here.
So I thought he might be my brother's ally!
Or are you an enemy who is after my brother?!
I'm his ally.
First of all, I'm his ally.
I am so relieved.
Do you know if Kin'emon is alive?
Are Kanjuro, Raizo,
and Kikunojo all with him?
Kikunojo?
Oh, you mean Kiku?
Yeah, but wait...
Something has me wondering.
Are you really Momo's sister?
Let me explain.
I see.
You're right.
Momo from 20 years ago
appears to be 8 years old,
and you're supposed to be his younger sister,
but you aged 20 years and you're now 26...
Yes.
By the way...
Is it okay for her to hear all of this?
It's okay! Because I already knew!
It was a secret between Big Sis and me!
Otoko is one of the few close friends
who knows my true identity.
Her cheerfulness sustains me day-to-day...
20 years ago, I was still
a little girl like her...
...but I will never forget
what happened that day.
Leave... to the future!
Mother, please don't do that!
Mother! Mother!
I didn't know what was going on
and I was confused.
In the blazing fire,
my brother and the others
disappeared right before my eyes...
On the same day, I lost my father, Oden,
and even my mother...
That day, I suddenly lost everything.
I was told that my brother would come back
20 years later,
but I could not hold out hope for
such an uncertain thing...
I did not have the will
to live all those years.
Why didn't they make you cross through time
with the others?
In case something happened
either to my brother or to me,
they did not want the
bloodline of Kozuki to end.
That's too cruel...
But my father's retainer,
Kawamatsu the Kappa
supported me emotionally with patience and raised me.
Kappa?!
Indeed.
It is hard to believe that those creatures exist,
but he takes great pride in being one...
On the day that the castle burned,
we were surrounded by the enemy,
but we escaped from the moat
through a drainage channel without being seen.
Princess! Please be patient!
After losing my father, mother, and brother,
I lost my voice from shock,
but he always cheered me up.
Princess! This is the Kappa Dance!
Come on!
Kappappa, kappappa, kappappa and pa!
Kappappa, kappappa...
Go ahead and eat, princess.
You are hungry, too, aren't you?
No, I have a little indigestion...
That's why it's growling...
Please... Please eat at least half.
No, no, I found a grilled fish
swimming in the river earlier.
A grilled fish in the river?
That's right.
I filleted it and ate it already.
He did not eat much himself,
but he tried to feed me...
Thanks to kind Kawamatsu
protecting me with all his soul,
I gradually began to laugh again.
Where's he now?
I think when I was about 13,
we were separated...
But Kawamatsu is a strong samurai,
so I am sure that he is waiting for
the day of the great battle.
I want to see him as well as the others...
Big Sis! I want to see a kappa, too!
Kappa, kappa, kappappa!
Uh-huh!
Zorojuro-san.
Who else is there preparing
for the great battle?
Well...
What?!
The doggy and the kitty are there, too?!
Yeah.
I heard that they were both dead,
so I thought I would never see them again!
Maybe Cat Viper hasn't arrived
at the Land of Wano yet...
What are you doing?
I am very, very happy...
You're funny, Big Sis!
But I will not cry!
Because I am a samurai's daughter!
If the doggy and the kitty will be there,
it's possible that all members of the Akazaya Nine
could come together!
I don't know...
Kin'emon.
Kanjuro.
Raizo.
Okiku.
Dogstorm.
Cat Viper.
AKAZAYA NINE
All we know is those six and Momonosuke.
We haven't met the other three yet.
Those three are Kawamatsu
who I told you about,
KAWAMATSU   DENJIRO
Denjiro, and Ashura Doji.
ASHURA DOJI
I do not know where they are
or if they are safe...
But everyone is talking about this flyer
in the capital now,
so I bet they will show up!
Is that the flyer we handed out
to the rebels?
Yes.
Thanks to the uproar,
information has spread very fast and that's a good thing,
but it's obviously unfavorable for us...
...that the rendezvous spot leaked out
and our allies have been caught.
I wonder what's gonna happen.
It will be all right.
I believe so.
Well...
Too many captains sink the ship.
I'm gonna stop fretting...
That's right!
Before anything else, I want you to get well!
Now, get some rest.
Yeah, you don't have to tell me...
Otoko, this is miracle!
I am so happy!
My brother is alive!
I'm happy for you, Big Sis!
I'm so happy!
Toko, this is great!
Can't they shut up?
I can't sleep...
But he is 8 years old!
That's so strange!
He is still a child.
I guess Kin'emon and the others
have not changed since 20 years ago, either.
I wonder how I will react when I see them.
Maybe I better not see them
before the great battle.
I should not interfere
with a samurai battle...
What do you think, Otoko?
Oh, no! I have to get more wood!
I wish we had at least one comforter...
That wasn't it! I can't do it right!
What?!
You sent them flying.
Wasn't that good enough?
No, it wasn't, old man!
I wanna throw a punch that sends enemies flying
without a touch!
That way,
I think I can break Kaido's tough scales!
A punch that sends enemies flying
without a touch?
Yeah. I won't know if it works
until I actually try.
But I saw it before...
Both Rayleigh...
...and that battle-axe guy...
...used the same Haki of the Color of Arms.
How is theirs different from mine?!
Haki must be a foreign concept.
Do you know anything?!
In the Land of Wano, there is a concept of power
that will cover your blade via your body.
A good sword will cut even iron
when you need it to,
but when you don't,
it won't even cut a sheet of paper.
It's all up to the swordsman!
Old man.
You fool! Are you stepping
forward to get killed?!
Straw hat man.
Watch as I show the skill
that I used to hone through sword fights.
Old man!
Straw hat man! Give me directions!
Okay!
Don't forget that you suspected my crew.
How can people who don't trust each other
fight together in a deadly battle?!
Hey, wait! Tra-guy!
Tra-guy left in a rage.
Is he going to come back?
Damn Shinobu! How could she say that?!
But you know why Shinobu-chan grew impatient!
Kaido took over her country
and screwed up her life.
But she has endured it
and waited 20 years to fight back!
I know.
But even if Bepo and the others told them about the plan,
I wouldn't blame them.
Because you'd do so, right?
I think you'd talk, too.
Torture, huh?
Over in three seconds.
That's too short!
Go away!
I don't need you lowly
shits to take care of me!
What's this? Yelling in Ebisu Town
that is always filled with laughter?
You must be that monster - bean-washing hag!
Stop it!
They're new here! They fled the capital
and arrived yesterday.
What are you looking at?!
Go away!
Fled the capital?
Yeah.
Only people who are loyal to the Shogun
and earn money can live in the capital.
I heard that those men were
doing pretty bad things.
Bad things?
First...
--...the underling, Bungoh...
--You little shits!
He set fires throughout the town
every night.
But he didn't get punished
because he paid off officials.
BUNGOH - AN ARSONIST
An arsonist?!
Why bother paying off officials
to start fires?!
Someone was making money off of it...
He's a lumber dealer
who sold lumber for rebuilding houses.
His name is Bongoh.
BONGOH - A LUMBER DEALER
What?!
There's more to it.
The other man exploited mourning people
who lost their family members in the fire,
and charged them an outrageous price.
He's a priest and undertaker named Bingoh.
BINGOH - A PRIEST AND UNDERTAKER
Wait a minute!
Don't tell me those three were...
That's right. Bingoh, Bongoh, and Bungoh
were in cahoots.
I thought so.
That's terrible!
Right, but no matter how
much crime they committed,
they bought off officials,
so they escaped arrest.
They pretended to be good people,
but they're actually the
worst kind of people.
Those ruffians didn't receive
any divine punishment?!
But the funny thing is...
...all three of them fell in love with
the incredibly beautiful Komurasaki the Oiran...
...who died yesterday!
All three of them spent tons of money on her
and went broke!
So the gods really watch over us!
Those are the rumors!
That's a good story.
But that's too specific to be rumor.
It must be a true story.
In that case, that Oiran knew who they were
and tricked them.
Well done!
Who is Komurasaki?
Oh! Them!
Yeah! I remember!
They were making a scene
at the Oiran's procession!
Yasu-san provided them a place to live
and took care of them,
but they still act arrogant
and are out of control.
Tonoyasu is such a caring man.
He even took care of those vermin!
Straw hat man! Give me directions!
Okay!
He'll swing down his right sword full force!
I got it!
You damn geezer!
He knocked him back!
Old man...
Old Man Hyo took the Gifter down!
Alpaca-man!
That dotard...
I thought he had one foot in the grave.
But he's still pretty young!
Could Old Man Hyo actually be...
...the famous Hyogoro the Flower?!
Straw hat man...
If this is something that you want to do,
maybe I can help you a little bit.
Teach me!
That's exactly it!
To master Ryuo and break out of the labor camp,
Luffy lets his fighting spirit burn even more!
Meanwhile, other prisoners who wish to rebel against Orochi
and Tonoyasu join the raid operation!
More allies to take down Kaido come together
and the road of hope starts opening!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Tonoyasu! Ebisu Town's Most Loved!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
...