Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Catch the wind
kaze ni nore
Don't give up, if I'm determined
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
I'll never turn back
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
Laugh on through troubled waters
waraitobase aranami
Shout it out, to save
your spirit from breaking
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Your friends are there for you
nakama ga irun da
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Even when the darkness
tries to tear you apart
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Come on, brave it out
hora Brave it out
It's going to be all right
daijoubu sa
Strong bonds will break through
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
The flag that called forth oaths
chikai atsumeta hata
Keep fighting on
tatakai tsudukete iku
Stay true to yourself
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Seize it, dreamin' on
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
I can't lose, I'll never run away
makerarenai nige ya shinai
Transcend meetings and
partings and keep going
deai wakare koe ikou
They're all treasures
zenbu takaramono
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Raise your fist
ko wo agete
Please tell Kin'emon-kun and the others!
That we'll fight along with you at any cost!
Kin'emon... kun?
I'm glad to see you two, too...
Now, it's getting busy!
Hey, wait!
There are tons of people
who won't last the week before the great battle!
So if you'll excuse me!
I guess you're pretty exhausted, officer.
I'm hungry, too.
What?!
I'll repeat myself over and over again
until you believe me.
I am the great thief Ushimitsu Kozo
who created turmoil in the Flower Capital!
Oh, shut up! If you're really him,
why did you appear around midnight?!
Don't laugh! You're taking me for a fool!
You won't get out of here alive!
He is...!
Move!
I see. No wonder we did not notice...
"Shaking the Nation!
The Identity of Ushimitsu Kozo The Chivalrous Thief!"
Big news! Big news!
The great thief Ushimitsu Kozo...
FLOWER CAPITAL
...who caused trouble
in the Flower Capital...
...finally got caught!
No way! I can't believe it!
His number is finally up...
Special report! Special report!
There's big news!
Ushimitsu Kozo?
Orochi-sama.
Orochi-sama,
there is something that I want you to know...
It's about Ushimitsu Kozo
who we caught yesterday...
Oh, shut up!
None of you can understand the pain of
losing a beloved woman!
About the Oiran, Komurasaki's death,
my sympathies are with you...
But with all due respect,
Kyoshiro's move was wise.
If he let someone
who stood against you walk away,
it would have undermined
your authority and reputation.
Orochi-sama!
I do not care about Ushimitsu Kozo!
There is no other woman as beautiful as Komurasaki
in the world!
Can't you see that?!
It is so great to see you, Orochi-sama!
Please listen to me.
Ushimitsu Kozo was not
just another petty thief!
Ushimitsu Kozo, the cowardly burglar
who caused trouble in the Flower Capital...
He is a hero-wannabe, small-time
crook who gives away
the money and goods he steals to poor people.
We are holding him at the Prisoners' Quarters
in Rasetsu Town,
but the truth is his identity is...
What?!
He is...
H-He is... alive?!
No way... I cannot believe it!
He is...
So you are from the Kurozumi Family.
Why didn't you tell me?
He is... He is...
Lord! Lord!
What should we do about Ushimitsu Kozo?
Why do you need to ask?
Execute him! And show it to public
to set an example!
Illuminate the Light-Scrolls across the Land of Wano
immediately!
The Light-Scrolls are already prepared.
Kyoshiro!
Today, Komurasaki's funeral will be held
in the Flower Capital.
We are expecting a crowd of people
and it will be chaotic...
That is why we have already prepared.
That's my Kyoshiro!
What shall we do?
Okay! This is what we are going to do!
We will let Ushimitsu Kozo
follow Komurasaki to the grave!
To accompany her!
Oh!
What a pity to lose the two biggest stars of the capital
at the same time!
Only you could come up
with such a nice idea...
I will be there, too!
I will witness his execution to the end!
I need a palanquin now!
EXCAVATION LABOR CAMP, UDON
That's a lie!
Stop making bad jokes
so early in the morning, Kaido-san!
It's not a joke!
Word came from the Flower Capital.
Komurasaki died!
She died!!
If you think it's a lie,
hook up your Light-Scroll Snail!
No way! No...
No!
Komurasaki-tan!
Hey!
He found out that Komurasaki died!
I'm sure that he'll be in
a bad mood for a while.
We're in trouble. What should we do?
Hey, balloon!
Come out already!
Shut up! No time for that now!
Hey, balloon!
Can we start today's sumo match already?!
Hurry up!
Did you idiots gain weight from yesterday?!
No, we didn't! It's just your imagination!
--O-Okay.
--Hey!
--Forget it!
--Should we tell him that the red-bean soup is all gone?
No way! Another shock could drive him mad!
I agree!
But I wonder where the red-bean soup went...
That is why I told Luffy-dono
not to eat too much...
Eating up all the soup in the pot
was too much.
How can an idiot like him survive?
Let's just have the sumo match!
Come on! Dosukoi!
This is no time for dealing with a fool!
I have to find out the truth!
Hey! Let me see the Flower Capital now!
Get the Light-Scroll Snail ready!
The Light-Scroll Snail has been set up!
Connect it to the Flower Capital!
Is it a Video Transponder Snail?
What? That must be the Flower Capital.
ATAMAYAMA, KURI
I can't believe they are attacking Atamayama!
Screw them!
Shutenmaru, this is it for you!
This is my revenge!
I'll make you pay!
Damn you Atamayama Thieves Brigade.
How dare you steal all
of my food and weapons!
THE ATAMAYAMA THIEVES BRIGADE WAS HERE
SHUTENMARU
H-Holdem-sama...
I won't forgive you, Shutenmaru!
I'll smash you fools to pieces!
That's hysterical! What can you do?!
W-What should we do?
I didn't expect stealing food and weapons
would cause this much trouble...
Duke-sama! Kin-san!
Hey!
Whew!
We stole so much.
Food... And weapons from the factory!
Nice work. Did you leave the note?
Yes, of course!
THE ATAMAYAMA THIEVES BRIGADE WAS HERE
SHUTENMARU
Are we responsible for this?!
Don't panic!
This is part of Kin-san's plan...
Watch closely!
Okay!
Not just the food and the weapons!
--You coward!
--What?!
Don't play innocent!
Look at me!
Your subordinate made such a ruckus in Bakura Town
and messed me up!
Gum-Gum...
...Red Hawk!
What?! What are you talking about?!
I had nothing to do with that!
Are you pretending that you don't know?
All right.
Let's just sort it out!
Take this Trick Mechanism Sword's attack!
One more!
Your cheap trick won't work on me!
Yeah? Then, I'll increase the heat!
Kamijiro!
Look at this fire!
I told you that your cheap trick won't work!
Fight me fairly!
Haven't you noticed yet? Look around you!
You see? The fire has
spread in all directions!
Why would I even bother
fighting you head-on?!
I'm here to destroy Atamayama!
What?!
Our Atamayama...
Forget about Holdem for now!
Let's retreat!
Yes, sir!
Don't let them get away!
Wait!
That's enough...
Shutenmaru's hideout has been destroyed!
They no longer have a place to hide.
This is the end of the
Atamayama Thieves Brigade!
Too late! The fire's spreading too fast!
It's impossible to extinguish
it, Shutenmaru-san!
Damn Holdem!
Let's go to Bakura Town!
Bakura Town?!
Kaido's army will come after us!
So what?!
I'll kick all of their asses!
No way... This can't be happening...
We didn't plan for this...
Let's notify Duke-sama.
AN ABANDONED VILLAGE, KURI
I see... I feel sorry for Ashura Doji.
Mm-hm... But we did it for the greater good.
It cannot be helped.
Let's go to Bakura Town!
Our plan is foiled
and we do not know what to do yet...
But for the time being, we need Ashura to be
hostile towards the Animal Kingdom Pirates.
Because we definitely need him!
NORTHERN GRAVEYARD, RINGO
Maybe Nami-san and the others
have come back.
I'm back...
What?!
Who are you?! What is this?!
W-W-What's going on?!
Oh, Brook... What's up with you?
Why are you here?
Zoro-san!
You're almost making my eyes pop out!
I mean, if I had eyes to begin with!
I'm sorry to interrupt you!
Hey, you got the wrong idea! Come back in!
What? Oh, okay... If you say so...
Whoa, how beautiful!
I'm sorry, but may I see your panties?
A ghost!
Wait! He's safe!
I'm hungry. A curse on you!
I'm scared!
Kin'emon-san told me to
stay here and say that to people...
Oh, that's why...
...there are so many offerings out front.
Well, I can't believe that
you're Momonosuke-san's sister!
You're as lovely as the Oirans!
Of course! Because she's an Oiran!
It must be so nice to have someone like her by your side.
I wish I were you!
I was just sleeping, but she...
I'm sorry! I thought you were really cold...
But I always make men drool
whenever I sleep alongside them!
Did you like it? Well, I know you loved it!
--You're pretty straightforward...
--Yes!
Anyway, I wonder where
Nami-san and the others are...
They went to a bathhouse yesterday,
so I tried to go meet them, but I couldn't find them...
Oh, by the way, the Flower Capital is
in total chaos now!
Today is the funeral of Komurasaki-san the Oiran,
the most beautiful woman in the Land of Wano...
On top of that, Ushimitsu Kozo the great thief
who spread the money he stole to the poor got caught,
and that's causing a fuss, too!
Ushimitsu Kozo got caught?! No way!
But it's true.
Look, it's written in the broadsheet.
He'll be executed in the capital today...
And they found out his identity.
USHIMITSU KOZO GOT CAUGHT
I think he's popular in Ebisu Town...
You said Ebisu Town?!
Yes. And his name is, um...
...Yasu-something...
Tonoyasu?!
Yes, that's the name!
Toko!
Hey! What's the matter?!
Wait, Toko!
Thank you for saving us yesterday!
We will not forget your kindness!
Wait, you fool!
You couldn't protect her yesterday!
What?! I've just come back!
Please wait! Hey!
Daddy...
Hey, let's go!
Oh, you came to escort me?
That's very generous.
N-No way...
That man is...
Where do you think you're going?!
Your life is in danger!
Let go of me!
I've got to go!
Hey! Get yourself together!
Let go of me!
What's going on?!
Toko!
He'll be executed!
Let go of me!
He'll be killed!
He's my father!
Toko...
What did you say?!
Seems like it will be a lovely day
in the Flower Capital today...
The time for Tonoyasu's
execution is approaching.
The Straw Hats clear away unassailable guards
and rush to stop the execution.
Will Tonoyasu share the fate of the cherry blossoms?!
The truth behind his smile will be revealed!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Straw Hats Run! Save the Captive Tonoyasu!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
...