Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
kaze ni nore
Catch the wind
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
Don't give up, if I'm determined
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
I'll never turn back
waraitobase aranami
Laugh on through troubled waters
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Shout it out, to save
your spirit from breaking
nakama ga irun da
Your friends are there for you
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Even when the darkness
tries to tear you apart
hora Brave it out
Come on, brave it out
daijoubu sa
It's going to be all right
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Strong bonds will break through
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Have the courage to take a step forward
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
chikai atsumeta hata
The flag that called forth oaths
tatakai tsudukete iku
Keep fighting on
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Stay true to yourself
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
Seize it, dreamin' on
makerarenai nige ya shinai
I can't lose, I'll never run away
deai wakare koe ikou
Transcend meetings and
partings and keep going
zenbu takaramono
They're all treasures
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Have the courage to take a step forward
ko wo agete
Raise your fist
What?!
He is...
H-He is... alive?!
Ushimitsu Kozo got caught?! No way!
But it's true.
Look, it's written in the broadsheet.
He'll be executed in the capital today...
And they found out his identity.
I think he's popular in Ebisu Town...
You said Ebisu Town?!
Yes. And his name is, um...
...Yasu-something...
Tonoyasu?!
Where do you think you're going?!
Your life is in danger!
Let go of me!
I've got to go!
Hey! Get yourself together!
Let go of me!
What's going on?!
Toko!
He'll be executed!
Let go of me!
He'll be killed!
He's my father!
Seems like it will be a lovely day
in the Flower Capital today...
Daddy!
"The Straw Hats Run!
Save the Captive Tonoyasu!"
FLOWER CAPITAL
How could this have happened?!
Komurasaki-sama!
What I wouldn't give to see her once more!
This isn't the Oiran procession
I wanted to see...
Where are you taking her?!
She rebelled against Orochi-sama.
We'll cremate her at the Prisoners'
Quarters in Rasetsu Town.
As soon as you arrive, Orochi-sama,
we will execute him as an offering!
Mm-hm, I will be there soon!
Hearing his dying scream...
...will heal the pain of losing Komurasaki
a little bit.
Today is a great day!
UDON
Where is Komurasaki-tan?!
I don't see her anywhere.
They're still transporting her.
What's that place on the screen?
That's the Prisoners'
Quarters in Rasetsu Town.
Many criminals are held there,
though not as many as here.
PRISONERS' QUARTERS, RASETSU TOWN
FLOWER CAPITAL
Raise the post.
It's beautiful...
Oden (stew) wouldn't be "oden"...
if it wasn't boiled!
EBISU TOWN
Tonoyasu's been caught?!
What the hell is going on?!
I can't believe Tonoyasu-san
is Ushimitsu Kozo!
Ushimitsu Kozo...
The great thief who steals money and goods
from the rich,
and gives them away to the poor and the weak
every night...
Thief?
That old geezer?
Ushimitsu Kozo...
I heard people talking about him
in the Flower Capital.
What is this all about?
I thought he was a saint.
Tonoyasu-san!
Why's everyone laughing?
Your friend's been strung up!
Is Tonoyasu-san really Ushimitsu Kozo?
Even if it's true,
that's not what's really important.
I remember! That hairstyle...
Tonoyasu is a fake name.
Who is he?
BAKURA TOWN, KURI
Seems like something exciting is
happening in the Flower Capital...
Turn on the Light-Scroll Snail!
Let's look for Ashura!
What is that?
No way... That's...
He is alive!
Do you know him?
Yeah, I know him pretty well.
That gentleman...
...used to be one of the Daimyo who served
under the Kozuki Clan along with Oden-sama...
His real name is...
...Shimotsuki...
Yasuie-dono!
The Daimyo of Hakumai! Yasu the Hedgehog!
He was very austere and never smiled!
I didn't realize
because he's nothing like he used to be!
Stop the execution!
--I'm from Hakumai!
--I'm glad to see you again...
Untie him, damn you!
Yasuie-sama!
People did not forget me yet?
That makes me happy.
HAKUMAI, LAND OF WANO
This Hakumai is the only region in the Land of Wano
that has a legitimate port.
Some visitors wish us
well, others wish us harm.
That is why...
...we need to be an unassailable army.
SHIMOTSUKI YASUIE (LATER KNOWN AS TONOYASU)
DAIMYO OF HAKUMAI
They are definitely the strongest samurai
in the Land of Wano...
Want some?
Stop fooling around, Oden.
How long are you going to hang out at my place?
You are the son of the Shogun!
I got kicked out of the castle.
I do not know if there is still a blood tie.
Everyone is saying...
...that Oden will not be the heir
to Kozuki Sukiyaki...
Yasuie will become the Shogun.
You idiot!
Ouch!
What are you doing?!
Don't take silly talk like that seriously.
You are the true successor
of the Kozuki Clan!
Sukiyaki-sama kicked you out
because he loves you!
Try to live up to his expectations.
Yasu-san.
I would rather go out to the sea!
Why doesn't this country allow that?
The isolation policy is just annoying!
Shut up!
Say whatever you like
after becoming a real samurai.
You are hurting me!
How dare you keep punching me.
Who do you think I am?
You are still a nobody...
Just a hoodlum.
Yasuie-sama!
It is no use, everyone!
Orochi will not let me go!
First, I want to apologize to everyone
about two things!
Then I want to say one thing
to the stupid Orochi!
Toko!
After I say those things,
I can leave for kingdom come, laughing.
Daddy!
Yasuie-sama!
The next hit will be a killing blow.
I will read the charges of the accused.
Last night, he committed a
theft in the Flower Capital.
He has fallen dreadfully.
He is the former Daimyo of Hakumai
who makes a living as a male geisha!
His name is Shimotsuki Yasuie!
For the heinous crime of rebelling against
the Shogun Orochi-sama in the past,
as an offering to the
Oiran Komurasaki's grave,
we hereby sentence him to dishonorable death.
Now, according to his statement,
he was Ushimitsu Kozo
who caused a disturbance to the public...
That was a lie.
What did you just say?
I said it because I wanted to get all the attention
if I die anyway!
I'm sorry that I lied.
I'm no hero like that!
Yasuie-dono...
Why did he tell such a lie?
The sorrow from Komurasaki's funeral
has been directed to Yasuie's execution.
Drake-san! The people of Ebisu Town
are charging into the Flower Capital.
What?!
I guess he is a bigger
figure than we imagined.
Yasu-san, don't die!
Yasu-san!
If we lose you,
who else will support us?!
Don't enter this town without permission!
Go back to Ebisu Town, you beggars!
Yasu-san!
These small actions won't draw the attention of
the Animal Kingdom Pirates.
Yasu-san, hold on!
The residents on the main street
are raging!
In the west district, too!
It's one thing after another!
Orochi-sama's decision to broadcast the execution
through the Light-Scrolls could backfire.
Keep an eye on other areas, too.
Shogun-dono is such an idiot,
I feel sorry for his subordinates!
Now, everyone!
Look at the beautiful Flower Capital!
The view of the Land of Wano is magnificent!
For generations, this scenery was developed by
the Kozuki Clan and the common people.
We take pride in it.
Hurry up!
Faster!
He's started talking shit!
You cannot take the credit
for that, you fool!
Kurozumi Orochi!
Do you hear me, Orochi?!
There used to be immense forests
and fields with vegetation.
Rivers!
Villages!
And you are just contaminating them
with dirt of greed!
You're nothing but vermin!
That bastard!
Yasuie-dono...
How impressive.
Old man.
Daddy!!
Entrusting the Land of Wano's future to the Straw Hats,
Tonoyasu dies with a smile on his face!
The people of Ebisu Town grieve,
but Zoro sees them laughing hysterically!
When he learns the truth behind their smiles,
he becomes furious!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Zoro's Fury! The Truth About the Smile!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
...