mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
kaze ni nore
Catch the wind
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
Don't give up, if I'm determined
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
I'll never turn back
waraitobase aranami
Laugh on through troubled waters
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Shout it out, to save
your spirit from breaking
nakama ga irun da
Your friends are there for you
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Even when the darkness
tries to tear you apart
hora Brave it out
Come on, brave it out
daijoubu sa
It's going to be all right
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Strong bonds will break through
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Have the courage to take a step forward
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
chikai atsumeta hata
The flag that called forth oaths
tatakai tsudukete iku
Keep fighting on
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Stay true to yourself
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
Seize it, dreamin' on
makerarenai nige ya shinai
I can't lose, I'll never run away
deai wakare koe ikou
Transcend meetings and
partings and keep going
zenbu takaramono
They're all treasures
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Have the courage to take a step forward
ko wo agete
Raise your fist
First, I want to apologize to everyone
about two things!
Then I want to say one thing
to the stupid Orochi!
I will read the charges of the accused.
Last night, he committed a
theft in the Flower Capital.
He has fallen dreadfully.
He is the former Daimyo of Hakumai
who makes a living as a male geisha!
His name is Shimotsuki Yasuie!
For the heinous crime of rebelling against
the Shogun Orochi-sama in the past,
as an offering to the
Oiran Komurasaki's grave,
we hereby sentence him to dishonorable death.
Look at the beautiful Flower Capital!
The view of the Land of Wano is magnificent!
For generations, this scenery was developed
by the Kozuki Clan and the common people.
We take pride in it.
Hurry up!
Faster!
He's started talking shit!
Do you hear me, Orochi?!
There used to be immense forests
and fields with vegetation.
Rivers!
Villages!
And you are just contaminating them
with dirt of greed!
You're nothing but vermin!
That bastard!
"Zoro's Fury!
The Truth About the Smile!"
Damn Holdem!
How dare he set fire to my hideout!
Where are you?! Come out!
Holdem!
Is that...
Yasuie-sama, don't go too far!
You won't be able to turn back!
There is another thing...
...that I want to apologize for.
About the flyer with the symbol
that went around recently...
It has been 20 years
since the name Kozuki perished.
Now I cannot gather enough soldiers
to seek my revenge,
and I feel bad about the Kozuki Clan...
So I made the flyer!
What?!
The symbol does not mean anything.
That is...
...just a prank!
What?!
What's this all about?!
There you are, Ashura!
Oh, Kin'emon! Dogstorm!
I can't believe it!
Look!
It seems like Yasuie-sama is alive!
Yeah, I just found out, myself.
It has become quite a spectacle.
20 years ago, Oden died,
and Orochi asked the four remaining Daimyo
including me...
...if we would serve under Kurozumi...
...or fight them.
What a laugh!
You had a great debt to Oden!
But you seized the position of Shogun
by a cunning trick.
It was unacceptable!
Daimyo and people from every region
drew their swords without hesitation,
but the monster named Kaido
got in the way of their retaliation,
and the Land of Wano was consumed in flames.
I did not wish to, but I survived
and lived secretly in Ebisu Town,
but I did not want to just live on
and die a natural death.
So, channeling my inner child,
I came up with
the flyer prank idea and gave it a shot.
Please forgive me!
But Orochi was a bigger
coward than I thought...
He got flustered and
jailed the innocents who
had the moon tattoo which
was a popular design!
What?!
It's all in Orochi-sama's mind?!
What should we do?! We caught so many!
What?!
Does that mean they aren't even rebels?!
Yasuie-sama!
Get out of our way!
Neigh!
Orochi-sama! Now I see it!
Damn Yasuie!
I will fill you with bullets!
Here he comes...
Orochi, it has been a while!
Do you have any last words, Yasuie?!
Orochi! Let's see...
Do you want me to recite the curse
that binds your heart?
"A man of such small caliber...
...shall never know the taste of oden
for as long as he shall live!"
A MAN OF SUCH SMALL CALIBER SHALL NEVER KNOW
THE TASTE OF ODEN FOR AS LONG AS HE SHALL LIVE
It's getting interesting!
I guess he's a good guy...
Yes, he's very loyal to others!
Oden-sama and Yasuie-sama were
just like sworn brothers...
No way!
Yasuie-dono!
Daddy!
Wait, Toko!
Momo!
Why don't you take a break?
This is nothing!
The great battle is approaching!
What's wrong?!
The raid operation that we were preparing for
was somehow totally exposed.
What?!
We thought it was all ruined, but...
I think Yasuie-dono is trying to
get us out of trouble all by himself!
This is it for me.
You know what to do, Kin'emon...
Akazaya samurai!
And the future Shogun, Momonosuke!
Your plan is now reset!
To your allies who are
captured in Rasetsu Town,
I gave a new rendezvous point.
It is not much, but that is
all I can do with my life!
Is he trying to sacrifice himself
to keep our plan alive?!
Yasuie-dono!
Thank you!
No matter what the cowardly Orochi yells,
his soldiers will not listen to him anymore...
I'm sick of the Shogun's paranoia!
Stop! Someone'll hear you!
Daddy!
Yasu!
For 20 years, no one could
chop off Kaido's head!
But this time...!
Cover your children's eyes!
The last Daimyo who served under Kozuki...
I mean, Ebisu Town's happy-go-lucky guy...
...will cross over to the other side!
Yasuie!
Let's sing as I go!
Here we go!
Yasuie!
Let's sing as I go!
Here we go!
Shoot!
Invade Onigashima!
Avenge your lord!
I shall await the good
news in the other world!
HAKUMAI, LAND OF WANO
Why did you try to steal this much money?
Oden-sama is running short!
Why don't you just kill us already?!
Hedgehog!
Oden... He took on such strange followers...
Guys!
You can have all the
money you tried to steal!
What?!
Wait a minute, Yasuie-sama!
Then Hakumai will face
financial difficulties!
I do not care...
More importantly, untie them!
What?!
Guys, you can use this, too!
Take it!
More money?!
You've got to be kidding!
This must a trap!
Yasuie-sama, enough is enough!
Do you like Oden?
Of course, we do!
We're deeply indebted to him!
That's right!
I see...
In that case, use this money...
...for fixing yourselves up, learning manners,
buying books, and getting an education!
Having hoodlums like you as retainers
will bring shame on Oden!
He will eventually...
...become the Shogun of the Land of Wano!
Those who support him must be
the best samurai in the Land of Wano!
Needless to say,
you must protect your lord.
And become the capital's...
I mean, eventually become
this Land of Wano's guardian angels!
Understood?!
Yasuie-dono!
Daddy!
Otoko...
Are you tired, Toko?
Yes, Daddy!
Okay, okay!
I'll give you a ride on Daddy's shoulders!
There you go!
Here we go!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Forgive me, Otoko...
For leaving you behind...
Daddy!
Daddy! Daddy!
Okay! Cease fire!
Yasu!
Yasu-san!
They're the lowly beggars from Ebisu Town!
Kick them out of the capital!
Yasu-san!
Yasuie-sama!
D-Daddy!
Daddy!!
Da... ddy...
Yasu...
Is Yasuie finally dead?
Yasuie-sama...
What's going on here?
What's...
...happening?
Somebody died...
What's so funny about it?!
My dad died!
You little...
Please wait!
They're all... crying...
What?!
The people from Ebisu Town
are always smiling...
...because even when they're hurt or sad...
...they can't let it show on their faces.
All facial expressions other than a smile
were taken away from them...
...and now, all they can do is laugh!
Because of what Kaido and Orochi
brought here...
It's a fruit called Smile!
The Straw Hats shake with rage
against the merciless Orochi.
But now, Orochi points
his gun at a new target!
In this desperate situation,
everyone's favorite duo finally strikes out!
Flying sparks and a flash of light!
With smoke and flames,
they blow up a storm over the Flower Capital!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Toko's Tears! Orochi's Pitiless Bullets!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
...