mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
kaze ni nore
Catch the wind
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
Don't give up, if I'm determined
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
I'll never turn back
waraitobase aranami
Laugh on through troubled waters
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Shout it out, to save your spirit from breaking
nakama ga irun da
Your friends are there for you
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Even when the darkness tries to tear you apart
hora Brave it out
Come on, brave it out
daijoubu sa
It's going to be all right
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Strong bonds will break through
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Have the courage to take a step forward
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
chikai atsumeta hata
The flag that called forth oaths
tatakai tsudukete iku
Keep fighting on
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Stay true to yourself
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
Seize it, dreamin' on
makerarenai nige ya shinai
I can't lose, I'll never run away
deai wakare koe ikou
Transcend meetings and partings and keep going
zenbu takaramono
They're all treasures
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Have the courage to take a step forward
ko wo agete
Raise your fist
D-Daddy!
Daddy!!
Somebody died...
What's so funny about it?!
My dad died!
They're all... crying...
What?!
The people from Ebisu Town are always smiling...
...because even when they're hurt or sad...
...they can't let it show on their faces.
All facial expressions other than a smile
were taken away from them...
...and now, all they can do is laugh!
Because of what Kaido and Orochi
brought here...
It's a fruit called Smile!
"Toko's Tears!
Orochi's Pitiless Bullets!"
Daddy!
The Smile fruit is more than just an artificial Devil Fruit?
Yasuie-dono!
Tonoyasu got...
Damn! We were too late!
How could not I recognize him
until he was tied up there!
What a blunder.
I should commit seppuku...
Yasuie-sama!
Tonoyasu-san...
Yasuie-sama...
He died!
W-What's going on here?!
The people from Ebisu Town
loved him so much.
Why are they laughing?!
Orochi has a sick sense of humor...
They must be crazy!
They're laughing at
the execution of their former Daimyo!
Orochi's so cruel...
Yasuie-dono...
I can't believe he was alive until today...
So the enemy knew about our raid plan.
That is why you... Yasuie-dono...
You sacrificed yourself...
...to keep the plan safe?!
There must be a reason, right?
It doesn't matter who he was...
No one in this world deserves to be laughed at...
...as they die!
That's probably because of the Smile.
You can find some of those people
who can only laugh here, too...
Dogstorm, Kin'emon...
Do you guys know about the Smile fruit?
I should have... told you earlier...
The smiling faces of Ebisu Town's people...
...are merely masks.
Masks that can't be taken off...
...for the rest of their lives!
A few years ago, Kaido and Orochi...
...started importing some kind of artificial fruit...
...in exchange for the weapons
that are made in this country.
Smile fruit?!
When you eat that horrible fruit,
the sea will hate you and you'll lose the ability to swim,
but in return, you'll gain the ability of an animal
and it'll make you ferocious.
It's an artificial Devil Fruit, right?
We destroyed the factory
that was making them.
Yes, Kin-sama told me about it...
But tons of them had already been
brought into the country.
Kaido's objective was to make his subordinates stronger
like ferocious beasts with that fruit,
and build the world's greatest pirate group!
But there is always a catch to
something that's too good to be true.
The success rate of that artificial strength enhancer
was about 10 percent...
If 10 people ate that fruit,
only one of them would gain the ability.
The other nine won't see any improvement
and will face only the consequences.
Of course, they won't be able to swim again.
As the side effects of the defective chemicals,
they won't be able to express their sorrow or anger.
They'll only be able to laugh...
What?!
The key ingredient of the Smile is
SAD that Caesar was making, right?!
That has a terrible side effect like that?
Kaido doesn't care about his subordinates' safety.
He just wants strong soldiers.
The combatants of the Animal Kingdom Pirates
are grouped into three categories.
Those who haven't eaten and are waiting
for a chance to gain an animal ability...
...are the Waiters!
The tough ones who obtained animal abilities
from a one-in-ten chance...
...are the Gifters!
The laughing fighters who ate the fruit,
but failed to gain abilities...
...are the Pleasures!
Then as if they mock those unlucky ones
who couldn't gain any ability,
they named the artificial fruit
after those soldiers' facial expression.
Namely, a "Smile"!
So that's where the name "Smile" came from.
Even if it's artificial,
I thought it was a weird name for a Devil Fruit...
That's horrible!
Wait!
The tragedy only begins there!
Orochi took notice of
those failed Smiles that were bitten once.
They still harbored bad side effects,
so they could produce more Pleasures.
No...
In the town of leftovers outside the Flower Capital,
people were dying every day and crying out in hunger.
And Orochi couldn't stand it,
so he mixed those failed Smiles in
with the leftovers from the capital.
There are apples! They're still fresh!
Everyone, let's share!
These will be great!
After the first few times,
anyone would figure out...
...what kind of fruit it is!
But the townspeople...
...couldn't hold back their hunger!
That is how Ebisu Town
where everyone is smiling and cheerful...
...was made.
The tragic town where everyone looks happy,
but they cannot even grieve over the death of their parents...
So...
...please do not blame... those laughing people...
Amongst all the species,
only humans can laugh!
Yeah!
If that's true, why not laugh, laugh?
Daddy...
Daddy!
That was...
...Shogun Orochi's heaviest sin...
He made people's lives miserable...
...and even forbade them to grieve!
If...
...this is not hell...
...then what is?!
Zorojuro-san!
You got the death you deserved, Yasuie!
Ya...
Yasu-san passed away...
I cannot believe how impudent he was
to survive in my Land of Wano.
You were so rude, Hedgehog!
No, I mean, Sewer Rat!
That is right, everyone!
Shimotsuki Yasuie, Hakumai's former Daimyo
that you loved has died!
Send him off with the sound of your laughter!
This is the Land of Wano!
The cheerful Land of Wano!
It is just like heaven!
Laugh! Laugh more!
Toko?
Toko!!
No, Toko! Come back!
Daddy...
Daddy! Daddy!
Daddy!!
Daddy!
I have good medicine!
That girl! She came to eat soba...
Otoko-chan!
I guess she's Tonoyasu's daughter!
What?!
Daddy, come back!
This medicine will heal your wounds.
It's called toad oil
and it works super well!
You'll be fine...
I'm sorry, Otoko!
No! That medicine is...
Hiyori-san!
Please, Toko! Come back!
Daddy!
There you are, you damn brat!
Get out of my way!
I see... So you are Yasuie's daughter!
That explains why you are so rude!
If you... If you...
If you...
...did not laugh like an idiot at that time,
Komurasaki would not have had to die!
You little shit!
Daddy! Daddy!
Both you and your father are driving me crazy!
Come back, Daddy!
I will execute you!
Go to hell! You little shit!
Otoko, run!
I do not want to lose you as well!
Disappear from my sight!
Those are...
The wanted man who killed the magistrate!
WANTED - ZOROJURO
And the soba cook who stood against the Kyoshiro Family!
WANTED - SANGORO
To take down their formidable enemy,
the Straw Hats keep fighting!
Sanji bravely fights back against fierce attacks
from Drake of the Worst Generation.
In anger, Zoro takes a slice
at Kyoshiro who stands in his way!
Thunder roars and each of the Straw Hats shows
their great technique!
Will they be able to
break through Orochi's encircling forces?!
On the next episode of One Piece! "The Straw Hats Step In!
An Uproarious Deadly Battle at the Execution Ground!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!