Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Catch the wind
kaze ni nore
Don't give up, if I'm determined
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
I'll never turn back
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
Laugh on through troubled waters
waraitobase aranami
Shout it out, to save
your spirit from breaking
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Your friends are there for you
nakama ga irun da
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Even when the darkness
tries to tear you apart
hora Brave it out
Come on, brave it out
daijoubu sa
It's going to be all right
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Strong bonds will break through
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Have the courage to take a step forward
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
chikai atsumeta hata
The flag that called forth oaths
tatakai tsudukete iku
Keep fighting on
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Stay true to yourself
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
Seize it, dreamin' on
makerarenai nige ya shinai
I can't lose, I'll never run away
deai wakare koe ikou
Transcend meetings and
partings and keep going
zenbu takaramono
They're all treasures
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Have the courage to take a step forward
ko wo agete
Raise your fist
That is right, everyone!
Shimotsuki Yasuie, Hakumai's former Daimyo
that you loved has died!
Send him off with the sound of your laughter!
Daddy!!
Daddy! Daddy!
There you are, you damn brat!
If you... If you...
If you...
...did not laugh like an idiot at that time,
Komurasaki would not have had to die!
You little shit!
I will execute you!
Go to hell! You little shit!
Otoko, run!
Disappear from my sight!
"The Straw Hats Step In!
An Uproarious Deadly Battle at the Execution Ground!"
Th-They are...
...Zorojuro the magistrate killer
and Sangoro the soba cook!
Those fools...
I knew they couldn't hold back!
This is gonna be trouble.
But we can't really blame them!
Yeah, they did a good job saving Otoko!
Zoro! Sanji!
How dare you interfere with her execution!
More friends of the rat have appeared!
Yasuie's daughter...
That accursed brat is a serious criminal!
Hey, samurai! Go ahead and kill everyone
who interferes with the execution!
Yes, sir!
Hey, aren't they pointing
their guns this way?!
Oh, no!
Run, you idiots!
Get them!
I'm sorry, but I have no time for you.
Neither do I!
Well then, go away, Browgoro!
"Browgoro"?
It's Sangoro!
You go away, Mossjuro!
"Mossjuro"?!
Your head looks like a moss ball!
What?!
Do you want me to chop you up
before Orochi?!
Shut up! Then I'll kick you to death
before Kaido!
What did you say?!
Daddy!
Otoko... Thank goodness she is okay!
Is he... Zorojuro-san's friend?
Yes, he is.
He's our friend, too.
His name's Sangoro the soba cook.
Sangoro-san... the soba cook?
The Straw Hat Pirates' Roronoa Zoro,
and the other one is...
...Vinsmoke Sanji...
So the Straw Hats are really here
in the Land of Wano...
I can't believe that
they showed their faces so brazenly.
Hey!
Do you have a problem with
the way we appeared?!
Yeah, do you?! And...
...don't ever call me Vinsmoke, okay?!
Well then, I'll just finish you off!
Shoot!
That damn ronin...
Next! Get ready!
Shoot!
Take Otoko and run already!
No, not yet!
He needs to be...
That rat is behaving impertinently...
Take care of her!
What?! H-Hey!
Is he going to attack?!
Fight him! Fight him!
That ronin is going to attack me!
Run, Browgoro!
How could that lowly bastard be so rude?!
I gotta cut you myself!
Hey, Moss!
Don't rush into a fight on your own!
Prepare to fire!
Oh, damn!
Shoot!
Hey! Stop, you idiot!
Tonoyasu sacrificed himself for what?!
Whoa, wait a minute, mister!
As they say, there are evens and odds in this world.
Both good and evil come in turn.
Let's put an end to this here!
Okay?!
In this country,
we call everyone's smiling face...
..."Ebisu gao," mister!
That's why this place is called Ebisu Town!
Poverty won't get us down!
Yasu...
Could it be that he is Akazaya's soldier?!
Come on, you samurai! Protect me!
720-Pound Phoenix!
Who is that man?!
Boss Kyoshiro...
He repelled Zoro's sword attack?!
I think he was the one who cut Komurasaki...
It's Boss Kyoshiro.
So, he is the boss of the hoodlums
who caused that trouble at my soba shop?!
Lord, you are too careless.
You should not come to the execution ground
with such poor security.
Yeah, you are right...
And that ronin...
He was really going to kill me!
Hey, Moss! What are you thinking?!
Chill out!
X. DRAKE
DRAGON-DRAGON FRUIT, ALLOSAURUS MODEL
A surprise attack from one so big?!
Take this!
Prepare to fire!
Well, well. This is going
to be a scene of bloodshed.
What should we do?
Are we gonna stand here and just watch?
When it comes to this,
we gotta fight, too!
Wait a minute!
That will ruin the whole plan!
And if we get involved with this,
we can no longer stay in the capital!
Even so, we can't let them expose Yasuie-sama's body
to public view!
We must take it away somehow!
You are right, but...
Let's split up.
Where should we meet?
I'll help fight, too!
No, wait! Now is not the right time for
Oden-sama's allies to show themselves.
That's right. Shinobu-chan and Kanjuro,
head out discreetly.
But...
It's our crewmembers who created this mess,
so we'll take care of it!
Thank you!
Let's go, Shinobu!
Leave it to Onami-dono!
Take Shogun-sama to the castle!
You know what to do! Kill them!
Kill every single person
who rebels against me!
I won't let him go!
Shoot!
Do it!
All right!
Bulletproof?!
What's up with that carpenter?!
Strong Right!
Who are they?!
Who in the world are they?!
Oh, there he is!
No! He stole Yasuie-sama's body!
What's going on here?!
Don't worry!
I won't let them desecrate his body!
Oh, no!
Is that?!
Oh! Usohachi! Thanks! You saved me!
On top of that ladder! Aim!
Whoa-whoa! A sniper getting sniped
is too much irony!
Mil Fleurs!
Gigantesco Mano Spank!
Thanks, Orobi!
Another one appeared!
She was...
...the geisha from that time...
I knew she was a magic user.
The enemies are strong. Surround them!
Onami!
Leave them to me!
Thunderbolt Tempo!
Outta my way!
I think not!
In that case...
I'll cut you!
Outta my way!
I think not!
In that case...
I'll cut you!
I am the Shogun's dog.
Zorojuro-san... Kyoshiro...
You need to get out of the capital!
But what about Toko?!
She'll be fine because
she's with the strong man named Sangoro!
Poele A Frire Spectre!
Let's wrap this up and get out of here!
Okay!
Special Attack Atlas Comet!
Mil Fleurs, Gigantesco Mano!
Weapons Left!
Tornado Tempo!
All soldiers! Fight them! Fight them!
Rebels are rioting in Rasetsu Town!
According to the Shogun's command,
it does not matter if they're dead or alive!
Feel free to kill them!
Go, guys!
Kick their asses!
--Way to go!
--Hey, straw hat man.
Are those your crew
that the Light-Scroll Snail is showing?
What? I think I've been told
to keep it a secret...
Well, who cares...
Go!
--There! Do it, do it! Take them down!
--This is no good...
Zorojuro! You can do it!
Hey, Straw Hat!
That green-head is your friend?
That's Zorojuro, the serious criminal
who killed a magistrate, right?
Like I said, I don't know him!
It's too obvious!
How interesting!
Of all people, he's trying to kill Orochi!
That scum deserves to be chopped up!
Do it!
But he's up against Kyoshiro
who is quite tough.
What, Babanuki?
It's getting exciting now. I'm sure this can wait.
But a criminal has just arrived
from the Flower Capital...
From the Flower Capital?
Who came now?!
The criminal will arrive soon.
Through that gate.
HITOKIRI
SERIOUS CRIMINAL
Who's that?
He's a useless piece of garbage who couldn't fulfill a mission
assigned by the Shogun at the Flower Capital.
We have a message from Orochi-sama
saying you can punish him as you like!
We brought Hitokiri Kamazo!
So you're Kamazo...
I've heard so much about you.
And there's one more!
Okay, stop!
I have a report!
While we were escorting Kamazo here,
we caught another crook!
The escapee, Captain Kid!
Jaggy!
Didn't you know?!
All jailbreakers are to be executed immediately!
Yes, death penalty!
You came back so quickly!
By the way, how did you catch him?
Well, it was so easy!
This fool came towards us
yelling something,
so I shot him a couple of times,
but he didn't even try to run and here we are!
Maybe he forgot that
he has some Sea Prism Stone cuffs on!
Kid! You're so dumb!
He took the trouble of escaping,
so why did he surrender himself?!
Hey, stop!
I said stop!
I remember how you didn't
like the way you laugh...
You even stopped laughing
out loud at some point...
Everyone who mocked your laugh
would be nearly beaten to death by you!
Please... stop...
You started wearing a mask to hide your face
at some point...
That's the person I knew...
What happened to you?!
After we got separated,
what did Kaido do to you?!
Or did Orochi do something to you?!
Where's everyone else?!
Answer me!
Hey, answer... Please!
Killer!
What?! That's him?!
Straw hat man, do you know him?
Yeah...
Alright, Straw Hat...
I'm glad I got a chance to meet you.
But next time we meet,
I won't show any mercy.
Hmm, okay.
But...
...I'm going to find the One Piece!
Hey, Kid! What're you
just standing there for?!
You know, Killer...
On our journey up to this point,
we've been laughed at and ridiculed
whenever we mentioned getting our hands
on the One Piece.
And each time that happened,
I slaughtered everyone who laughed.
But what lies ahead is a sea of death
for those who don't got the guts to mention it.
Let's meet again in the New World!
Let's go, men!
Is that the masked guy who was with Jaggy?!
Jaggy must've tried to save him...
How cruel...
He was forced to eat the Smile fruit
and was given a mask of laughter that he can never take off...
Damn Orochi... How could
he do such a thing...
What did they do to change you completely?!
Who did this to my buddy?!
Where's my crew?!
Dammit!
Hey, balloon.
Straw hat man?
Hey, balloon!
What do you want, Straw Hat?!
Why are you yelling?
Come on, let's just start the sumo matches!
Come on!
If Luffy dies, Kid and Killer
will be freed from torture!
Queen, who toys with people's lives,
resumes the Sumo Inferno!
Bearing responsibility for their fate,
Luffy is as determined as ever and gives it all he has!
He finally faces off against Queen!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Luffy's Determination! Win Through the Sumo Inferno!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!