mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
kaze ni nore
Catch the wind
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
Don't give up, if I'm determined
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
I'll never turn back
waraitobase aranami
Laugh on through troubled waters
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Shout it out, to save your spirit from breaking
nakama ga irun da
Your friends are there for you
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Even when the darkness tries to tear you apart
hora Brave it out
Come on, brave it out
daijoubu sa
It's going to be all right
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Strong bonds will break through
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Have the courage to take a step forward
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
chikai atsumeta hata
The flag that called forth oaths
tatakai tsudukete iku
Keep fighting on
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Stay true to yourself
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
Seize it, dreamin' on
makerarenai nige ya shinai
I can't lose, I'll never run away
deai wakare koe ikou
Transcend meetings and partings and keep going
zenbu takaramono
They're all treasures
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Have the courage to take a step forward
ko wo agete
Raise your fist
Those fools...
I knew they couldn't hold back!
This is gonna be trouble.
But we can't really blame them!
How dare you interfere with her execution!
More friends of the rat have appeared!
Yasuie's daughter...
That accursed brat is a serious criminal!
Hey, samurai! Go ahead and kill everyone
who interferes with the execution!
Take care of her!
What?! H-Hey!
720-Pound Phoenix!
Thunderbolt Tempo!
Outta my way!
I think not!
In that case...
I'll cut you!
I am the Shogun's dog.
I remember how you didn't like the way you laugh...
You even stopped laughing out loud at some point...
Everyone who mocked your laugh
would be nearly beaten to death by you!
Please... stop...
Who did this to my buddy?!
Hey, balloon!
Straw hat man?
What do you want, Straw Hat?!
Why are you yelling?
Come on, let's just start the sumo matches!
Come on!
"Luffy's Determination!
Win Through the Sumo Inferno!"
Sangoro!
Leave Otoko to me!
Thanks, Usohachi!
I'll leave the dinosaur to you!
Yeah! I'll take care of it!
Two-Sword Style!
Tower Climb Return!
Diable Jambe!
Concasse!
Zorojuro's so strong!
He's a good match for Boss Kyoshiro!
You better stop, ronin.
Who is he?!
Seems like fortune favors me.
OROCHI'S ONIWABANSHU
SHOGUN OF WANO PERSONAL NINJA FORCE
Orochi's Oniwabanshu is here!
We know who you are.
Roronoa Zoro from the Straw Hat Pirates.
Hawkins was right. It seems like
all members of the Straw Hats are here in the Land of Wano.
All we need is one of you. I do not care who it is.
Your capture and subsequent torture will tell us your purpose!
Let's go!
Yes, sir!
Sorcery?
Ninpo!
Hell Biwa!
That's just a damn gun!
Toko!
Don't worry!
Please flee the capital now!
I'll take care of them!
Soul King!
Sooouuul!
A curse on you!
It appeared again!
Gashadokuro!
That's it, Bonekichi!
That woman...
She was with Zorojuro.
Fujin, Raijin.
Yes, sir!
Chase that woman.
What a great view.
Now,
go to...
...hell!
They both ate the Devil Fruit.
Water torture must be agonizing.
Don't mess with me!
You son of a...!
Do you have a problem?
Oh, yeah. I came up with an exciting game.
Thank you for waiting, you damn fools!
The Sumo Inferno...
...is back on!
I knew you were coming.
Trafalgar Law.
Captain!
Captain, I'm sorry!
Us getting caught really put you in a bind!
What did you do with our polar bear?
With your ability,
you can get them out in an instant.
What kind of fool would keep all the hostages
in one conspicuous place.
I'll put you in that jail, too.
Don't push your luck.
Didn't you learn anything?
Did you?
You can't take me down.
Ouch!
Shachi!
I have four lives now.
You can only cut me up
after you've killed...
...the three from your own crew.
Yes. That's good.
Diable Jambe!
Concasse!
You've surely got the Vinsmoke's blood in your veins.
I told you not to mention that name again!
You also disguised yourself as Soba Mask, right?
Who knows.
I guess I'm only popular with dinosaurs.
You really want me to cook a meal out of you?
You'd better not think
that I'm as weak as that guy.
Nasty ingredients always make the cooking more fun.
That's the voice...
...of a beauty!
She's getting attacked!
Diable Jambe!
Extra Hachis Hash!
She needs help.
I'll be there soon... for you!
Zorojuro-san!
You're protecting her!
So she's your ally!
Why are you getting chased?!
I'm sorry! I tried to hide my face, but...
Moss knows that beautiful woman?!
That bastard!
His bounty is... lower than mine!
The Sumo Inferno...
...is back on!
But we have a new rule.
The moment you step out of the ring,
you'll be killed by the spikes in those collars!
That hasn't changed.
But the new rule is...
...as long as you guys are alive,
those two will be submerged in the water.
Which means only when you and that old geezer...
...die,
will we pull them out of the water.
Don't be ridiculous!
They have nothing to do with me!
Yeah, that's probably true...
But then, why do you seem a bit upset?
Is it because you two are rivals
from the same generation?
Well, you could always sacrifice your lives
for them immediately.
No matter how notorious or how many
hundreds of millions of berries a bounty is,
all humans...
...will drown in a mere five centimeters of water.
Now, the game begins.
Then,
why don't you enter the ring?!
I'll kick your ass and end this!
Who do you think you're talking to?
Don't push your luck!
You bastards!
Straw hat man!
Hey.
You punk.
I don't see how you can be so hopeful.
Do you really think you can get out of here alive?
Do you think you can beat us?
You fools are gonna die!
One by one!
Shut up!
When it comes to where I die...
...I'll do the choosing!
Hey! What was that noise?
Hey, what's wrong?!
Hey, respond!
Queen-sama!
We lost contact with the guards outside!
At last, I made it!
Red-bean soup!
An emergency occurs! It's out of control!
Big Mom rampages about looking for red-bean soup
and finally breaks in on the Sumo Inferno!
Queen and Big Mom!
Facing those two monsters, Luffy is driven to the wall!
However, an unexpected turnaround
happens at the chaotic Inferno!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Storm Has Come! A Raging Big Mom!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
...