mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
kaze ni nore
Catch the wind
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
Don't give up, if I'm determined
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
I'll never turn back
waraitobase aranami
Laugh on through troubled waters
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Shout it out, to save
your spirit from breaking
nakama ga irun da
Your friends are there for you
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Even when the darkness
tries to tear you apart
hora Brave it out
Come on, brave it out
daijoubu sa
It's going to be all right
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Strong bonds will break through
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Have the courage to take a step forward
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
chikai atsumeta hata
The flag that called forth oaths
tatakai tsudukete iku
Keep fighting on
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Stay true to yourself
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
Seize it, dreamin' on
makerarenai nige ya shinai
I can't lose, I'll never run away
deai wakare koe ikou
Transcend meetings and
partings and keep going
zenbu takaramono
They're all treasures
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Have the courage to take a step forward
ko wo agete
Raise your fist
Two-Sword Style!
Tower Climb Return!
Soul King!
Sooouuul!
A curse on you!
It appeared again!
Gashadokuro!
Diable Jambe!
Extra Hachis Hash!
I have four lives now.
You can only cut me up
after you've killed...
...the three from your own crew.
Meanwhile, at the Excavation
Labor Camp in Udon...
Who do you think you're talking to?
Don't push your luck!
You bastards!
"The Storm Has Come!
A Raging Big Mom!"
I did not expect...
...that the Flower Capital would be in such turmoil
after Yasuie-dono's execution...
I know how Zorojuro-dono
and Sangoro-dono feel...
It can't be helped.
Let's go beat the hell out of Holdem!
Yeah!
Wait a minute, Ashura!
I have something to tell you.
THE ATAMAYAMA THIEVES BRIGADE WAS HERE
SHUTENMARU
OUTSIDE OF BAKURA TOWN, KURI
Is that true?
Yes, it is all true.
We provoked Holdem...
I mean, I did.
It was my order.
I told them to steal food and weapons
from Holdem,
and make it look like Atamayama
Thieves Brigade did it.
That is why Holdem became mad
and attacked your clan.
You really use any means.
Don't you, Kin'emon?
Because of that, Atamayama
was destroyed by fire!
I told you that your cheap trick won't work!
Fight me fairly!
Haven't you noticed yet? Look around you!
Our Atamayama...
Kin'emon!
Did you try to entrap us?!
Stop, Ashura! We are deeply sorry!
I did it because I wanted to motivate you...
I was driven by that thought!
But...!
I am so sorry, Ashura!
I should have come to you like this instead!
I was justifying my actions
in the name of our lord,
and I did not have much time,
so I could not help but use such a drastic measure...
But I was completely mistaken!
20 years is a long time!
The world itself would change,
let alone people's minds!
I have never thought about it!
No, I tried not to see it!
But I realized there were still unchanged minds
and unshakable beliefs left in this country!
When I saw Yasuie-sama...!
Our plan is still safe!
Yasuie-sama misled the enemy for us
at the risk of his life!
The mark on the ankles of
those who were captured by Orochi...
Those samurai know the best
that the moon tattoo is not just a popular design!
On the night of the Fire Festival,
we will raid Onigashima!
Those samurai in the capital
will be released because of what happened,
and I am sure they will join us!
In order to take down Kaido and Orochi,
we definitely need you!
Will you please fight
together with us, Ashura?!
Twenty years...
You'll never understand the
weight of the past 20 years.
Follow me...
There's something I want to show you!
EXCAVATION LABOR CAMP, UDON
Hey! What was that noise?!
It was from outside of the gate,
but we just lost contact with the guards...
Red-bean soup...
Red-bean soup!
Save Big Bro at any cost!
Go for it, Olin-chan!
No, no, don't try too hard!
Red-bean soup!
There is no way that they
have that soup here.
If Big Mom finds out,
the shock might bring back her memories...
And we'll be killed!
This is none other than the Excavation Labor Camp.
It's sturdier than I expected.
Even if it is Big Mom, isn't it impossible to
break the thick steel gate?!
What?!
Red-bean soup!
That's it, Olin-chan! Keep going!
No, that's enough!
Don't keep going like that!
Red-bean soup!
Red-bean soup...
Red-bean soup!!
She did it!
Olin-chan, you're so strong!
Oh, no, she did it...
What's going on?
We're under attack!
The front gate has been destroyed!
No way!
Who did such a thing?!
Accursed invader! I'll teach you a lesson!
Prepare yourself!
Sniff, sniff... Sniff...
Hey, where do you keep that
delicious red-bean soup?
Lick.
Can't you hear me?! I said red-bean soup!
This is it! I'm gonna die!
I'm definitely gonna die!
What's happening?
The intruder has broken
through the second gate!
Now approaching the third gate!
What?!
The third gate is...
What the...?!
That's...
Is there red-bean soup here?
What the...?!
Bi...!
Big Mom?!
What?! Am I dreaming?!
--Big Mom...
--That's Big Mom!
What? Is it delicious?
Why is she here?!
I heard that her ship was sunk!
I'm hungry!
I-I can't believe...
...that she destroyed the steel gate!
That old bag is too dangerous!
Just like Kaido-san,
Big Mom is the Emperor of the Sea...
What brought her here to Udon?!
Red-bean soup...
Red-bean soup!
Hm? Red-bean soup?
Otama-chan! Come quickly!
I smell red-bean soup!
Olin-chan is calling me!
Let's eat it together!
What?!
Let's go eat red-bean soup now!
Why is there red-bean soup here?!
I told that deadly lie
at the risk of my life!
And the gate has been opened.
I thought how to get inside
would be a problem...
Now, we can rescue Big Bro!
Momo-kun, let's go!
Y-Yeah! Let's go save Luffy...
No!
Otama-chan and Momonosuke-sama,
you must hide and wait outside.
What?! How come?!
It is obviously too dangerous for you
beyond this point, Otama-chan.
And Momonosuke-sama,
you must not be spotted at any cost.
Hmmm... If you say so...
Okiku, you don't want them to know
that you're alive, either!
You are right!
Thank you for your advice!
I will disguise myself with this!
This is...
...perfect!
No one will ever know who I am!
Why do you samurai think
those cloth face coverings are so convincing?!
Chopperemon-san!
Udon is reined over by...
...the Animal Kingdom Pirates'
Lead Performer, Queen!
Let's be careful!
Nice...
Red-bean soup smells great,
doesn't it?
Red-bean soup?
It's really delicious, isn't it?
Red-bean soup!
Red-bean soup?!
Queen-sama!
Red-bean soup! Red-bean soup!
Where is it?! Red-bean soup!
Oh, no! We're in big trouble!
Hey, old bag! Did you say red-bean soup?!
I did! Give it to me already!
Whoa-whoa, you'll get it soon.
I heard that I could eat a lot of it here,
so I came all the way!
Screw that!
Who told you such nonsense?!
You can eat a lot of it?
Did you come to steal it
knowing that it's my most favorite?!
Hey, wait, you fools!
Pull them out first!
While you're talking idly,
Jaggy and the other guy will drown!
This is not idle talk!
Damn! He's totally losing it!
He's starting to transform!
Red-bean soup is like oxygen to me!
It keeps me alive!
You're gonna fight?!
Please wait, Queen-sama!
If you fight Big Mom over food,
you'll end up in big trouble!
Too late! We can't stop him now!
DRAGON-DRAGON FRUIT, ANCIENT TYPE
BRACHIOSAURUS MODEL
I just heard a tremendous noise...
I'm scared!
But Big Mom paved the way for us!
Red-bean soup!
Hey, we're in a terrible situation.
We've already run out of red-bean soup...
What should we do?!
You're right.
We have a great amount of red-bean soup here.
But it's all mine!
You can't even have a drop of it, old bag!
Red-bean soup...
Olin is a nicer version of Big Mom,
so she might be bullied
or hurt by Queen!
I see... So you've got red-bean soup.
Don't ever say red-bean
soup in front of me again!
Go away, old bag!
What?!
Just give me...
...red-bean soup...
...already!
What?!
Olin-san!
Queen-sama!
Her strength is not of this world!
Here comes Big Mom!
She takes down the Supreme Officer Queen
and fiercely attacks Luffy over red-bean soup!
He gets thrown out of the ring
and his collar is about to explode and kill him!
Will he be able to survive?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Grudge Over Red-bean Soup!
Luffy Gets into a Desperate Situation!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
>>>>oakislandtk<<<<<
www.opensubtitles.org