Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Catch the wind
kaze ni nore
Don't give up, if I'm determined
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
I'll never turn back
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
Laugh on through troubled waters
waraitobase aranami
Shout it out, to save your spirit from breaking
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Your friends are there for you
nakama ga irun da
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Even when the darkness tries to tear you apart
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Come on, brave it out
hora Brave it out
daijoubu sa
It's going to be all right
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Strong bonds will break through
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Have the courage to take a step forward
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
chikai atsumeta hata
The flag that called forth oaths
tatakai tsudukete iku
Keep fighting on
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Stay true to yourself
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
Seize it, dreamin' on
makerarenai nige ya shinai
I can't lose, I'll never run away
deai wakare koe ikou
Transcend meetings and partings and keep going
zenbu takaramono
They're all treasures
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Have the courage to take a step forward
ko wo agete
Raise your fist
Oh, Big Mom is...!
Guys!
Bring me 100 percent pure
Sea Prism Stone cuffs and chains!
Yes, sir!
Do something more!
Inject 100 shots of tranquilizer for savage animals!
Let's take the old bag to Kaido-san!
Hurry up!
Advance at full speed! To Onigashima!
They're gone...
I wish Big Mom and the balloon
were still here to fight...
Oh, yeah. He freed himself.
I've always been free!
Hey! Tell them everything, straw hat kid!
That there is still hope!
That there is one last chance
to take down Kaido!
It's not a beast that's held in that cell.
"If we keep feeding him fish
that are contaminated with industrial wastewater, he'll die."
That's what Orochi-sama ordered 13 years ago,
he meant it as an execution...
We couldn't disobey Orochi-sama's order,
so we kept him alive,
but he should have been executed
before anyone else.
In that cell, we're holding...
...a member of the Akazaya Nine!
"Start Fighting Back!
Luffy and the Akazaya Samurai!"
Here it is!
There he is! That's him!
Oh, no!
So you're the man with the big face!
SOLITAIRE - A VICE WARDEN (A HEADLINER)
EXCAVATION LABOR CAMP, MONKEY SMILE FRUIT
Solitaire-sama!
You bastard! Who are you?!
So you stole the keys
to the Sea Prism Stone cuffs!
The truth is shrouded in mist!
I'll shred you to pieces and unseal your lips!
Damn you!
Even if you're a legendary samurai,
you're no better than a baby with those cuffs.
No, be careful.
He might be hiding something more...
What's the matter?
If you have something, use it!
--I guess you ran out of fishbones...
--Let's go!
You're so damn agile!
You're using six swords,
so here's what I do...
Ninpo: Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Nin, nin, nin!
Can you guess which one is the real me?
No matter how many there are,
I'll cut them all up!
I beat the Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Go to hell!
What?!
Nice try!
Now, I must be going.
Ninpo: Smoke Escape Technique!
Where is he?!
Where did he go?!
--H-He is...
--What should we do?!
Babanuki-sama's orders are clear.
We should kill him!
Okay!
NINPO
Ninpo: Flying Squirrel Technique!
FLYING SQUIRREL TECHNIQUE
Oh... Oh, no!
The intruder got out!
Don't let him get away! Go!
Yes, ma'am!
Kawamatsu!
Here is the key to the cuffs
and your sword!
W-What was that?
Just in time, Raizo...
Oh, I missed it so much...
My precious sword.
Sotomuso!
You men...
Do you like sumo?
Kawamatsu-san!
I'm on my way!
Ready...
Go!
Yagura Ryuo!
What was that?
If your feet leave the ground,
you lose!
You are still very strong, Kawamatsu!
That technique...
I am so glad!
Damn you!
Just like swimming in the rapids of a great river!
People call it Kappa Style!
River of Retribution!
RIVER OF RETRIBUTION
Were the poisonous fish delicious?
No, their awful taste made me want to vomit
and they ruined my stomach...
But I stayed alive for 13 years!
In comparison to my lord's disappointment,
whatever pain I felt paled!
I have been waiting all this time!
Kawamatsu the Kappa has just joined the fight!
YOKOZUNA KAWAMATSU
A VASSAL OF THE KOZUKI CLAN
Kawamatsu-san!
Oh, Kiku!
You have not changed a bit!
I am so happy to see you again alive!
Raizo! You, too!
Kiku! When did you get here?!
What's going on?!
Who's that guy with a giant face?!
He's an intruder!
He stole the keys to the cuffs and the sword!
Hey! Don't just stand there!
Catch them now!
Yes, sir!
Why did you guys come back?!
Kawamatsu-san!
Are you all right?
I am sorry...
I feel like throwing up everything that I had the last 13 years...
Get the Plague Rounds ready!
We've got to finish them off!
Everyone, prepare to fight!
Count on us!
Are you guys ready?!
Hey! Go away! Let go of me!
Leave Luffytaro-san alone!
Otherwise, we must fight you!
That is right!
Luffy!
It's you guys who should leave us alone!
Don't get us involved!
Even if we're pathetic or go hungry,
we can live on as long as we submit to them!
Guys! Is that really what you want?!
Kiku! Raizo!
HYO
Oh! Old man!
What? Don't tell me you're Boss Hyogoro!
Uh-huh... Anyway, Kiku and Raizo!
Let everyone know who you are!
There are people who got their spirits broken and
people who actually fought and have been beaten up.
If you want to encourage them,
you must take off those cloth face coverings!
How true!
Hyogoro-dono!
You are right.
We must win their trust first!
If we do not reveal our identities,
we are no more than ghosts...
No way... That mask...
I thought he died at Oden Castle...
The most beautiful swordsman
in the Land of Wano...
Kikunojo of the Fallen Snow?!
What?! Are you a man?!
I am a woman at heart...
That mask is scary!
And that's...
...Fukurokuju's rival ninja,
Raizo of the Mist!
And he's a samurai and the most formidable
sumo wrestler ever, Yokozuna Kawamatsu!
And that old man next to them
really is who we thought! The real Hyogoro the Flower!
If so...
who is Luffytaro?
Anyway, they're all amazing!
What?! What about me?!
I thought you guys died 20 years ago!
We dare say...
We are alive like this!
Then, you're really...
really the Akazaya samurai?!
Yes, as you can see!
We'll save you at any cost!
Trust us!
Uh-huh!
Uh-huh! Uh-huh!
This is exactly like Orochi-sama's absurd story!
We must let Kaido-sama know somehow!
No...
Now that you've seen us,
we need you to keep your mouth shut.
He must be Fukurokuju's underling!
I wonder if he'll ever stop following us.
I don't know. That guy's so pesky.
But I'll get him next time.
It's that simple.
How's the old bag?
Sir! Thanks to the tranquilizers,
she's sleeping like the dead!
Good! If we can take her to Kaido-sama,
everything will be...
W... What's that?
No way! We injected 100 shots of
tranquilizer for use against savage animals!
She woke up!
Oh?
Such gracious hospitality!
Hey, stop running!
Hey, you!
Bring me red-bean soup!
Huh? Screw you!
The red-bean soup is all mine!
Why would I wanna give it to you?!
And you fell asleep again?!
EXCAVATION LABOR CAMP, UDON
Take them down!
Ninpo: Flower Shuriken!
Heavy Gong!
Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
Take the Plague Rounds!
What?!
The Plague Rounds aren't hitting him!
Daifugo-sama!
Idiot! I told you that it doesn't matter who they hit!
Stop!
Please stop!
How could those bastards do that
to the starving prisoners!
I can't forgive them
for using a virus as a weapon!
Oh, no! I won't let you get in
Daifugo-sama's way!
--Let's do it, Chopper!
--Okay!
Gum-Gum...
Heavy Stamp!
Leave my allies alone!
That is right!
It's a demon!
Kappa Style!
Yorikiri!
Ninpo: Lightning Shuriken!
Use it! Luffy-dono's friend!
Friend... you said?!
One of them should be the right key!
Hey...
I can't take them off without your help...
Give me a hand!
Or do you wanna laugh to death here?
You actually recognize me now,
don't you?
Get up. Uncuff me using those keys.
Killer!
It can't get any worse!
The random shooting of the Plague Rounds continues
and all hell breaks loose in the Labor Camp.
Even after being infected,
Luffy risks his life trying to stop the prisoners' riot!
He must awaken their fighting spirits!
Luffy's holler for victory echoes across the Land of Wano!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"We're Here to Win! Luffy's Desperate Scream!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
...