Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Catch the wind
kaze ni nore
Don't give up, if I'm determined
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
I'll never turn back
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
Laugh on through troubled waters
waraitobase aranami
Shout it out, to save your spirit from breaking
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Your friends are there for you
nakama ga irun da
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Even when the darkness tries to tear you apart
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Come on, brave it out
hora Brave it out
It's going to be all right
daijoubu sa
Strong bonds will break through
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Have the courage to take a step forward
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
chikai atsumeta hata
The flag that called forth oaths
tatakai tsudukete iku
Keep fighting on
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Stay true to yourself
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
Seize it, dreamin' on
makerarenai nige ya shinai
I can't lose, I'll never run away
deai wakare koe ikou
Transcend meetings and partings and keep going
zenbu takaramono
They're all treasures
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Have the courage to take a step forward
ko wo agete
Raise your fist
People call it Kappa Style!
River of Retribution!
RIVER OF RETRIBUTION
Were the poisonous fish delicious?
No, their awful taste made me want to vomit
and they ruined my stomach...
But I stayed alive for 13 years!
In comparison to my lord's disappointment,
whatever pain I felt paled!
I have been waiting all this time!
Kawamatsu the Kappa has just joined the fight!
I thought he died at Oden Castle...
The most beautiful swordsman
in the Land of Wano...
Kikunojo of the Fallen Snow?!
Fukurokuju's rival ninja,
Raizo of the Mist!
And he's a samurai and the most formidable
sumo wrestler ever, Yokozuna Kawamatsu!
And that old man next to them
really is who we thought! The real Hyogoro the Flower!
We'll save you at any cost!
Trust us!
Hey! Go away! Let go of me!
It's you guys who should leave us alone!
Don't get us involved!
Even if we're pathetic or go hungry,
we can live on as long as we submit to them!
Guys! Is that really what you want?!
Use it! Luffy-dono's friend!
Friend... you said?!
Get the Plague Rounds ready!
We've got to finish them off!
Everyone, prepare to fight!
Count on us!
Are you guys ready?!
Take the Plague Rounds!
Please stop!
How could those bastards do that
to the starving prisoners!
"We're Here to Win!
Luffy's Desperate Scream!"
Stop!
Ninpo: Lightning Shuriken!
Demon's Hand, Saint's Heart...
Evil-Slashing Wave!
Kappa Style!
River of Retribution!
Use it! Luffy-dono's friend!
Friend... you said?!
One of them should be the right key!
Come on! Come on! Come on! Come on!
Shoot! Shoot! Shoot! Just keep shooting!
Damn!
I got shot!
It burns!
Help me! It's spreading!
Stay away from me!
Shoot! Shoot! Shoot! Just keep shooting!
Ow, ow, ow, ow...!
Dammit! They're only targeting the prisoners!
Oh, yeah! I forgot to mention.
Regarding the name of the plague...
A high fever spreads from
the spot where you got shot...
--Burning pain over the entire body!
--Ahhh!
Blood sprays out!
And you suffer and wriggle around...
...and pass that pain to random people!
Help!
--No!
--It's excruciating!
Don't!
Look at that!
That's how you end up if infected!
They look like plants
that are dried-out and rotten.
--Help me...
--No! Go away!
That's...
Queen-sama's masterpiece!
This strange plague is called Mummy!
Go!
You guys are now human weapons
that can bring down the enemies with just a touch!
Don't spread the virus!
Guys, don't move!
I'll figure something out!
I promise I'll cure you!
You guys should fight, too!
Or should I consider you rebels?
Damn...
Dammit...
--Gee...
--I don't wanna fight...
They're not gonna stop!
As it turns out,
all of Udon is against us!
Get out of here!
If you guys hadn't appeared...
this wouldn't have happened!
Even if you guys really are...
...the Akazaya samurai
who were supposed to have died 20 years ago,
you'll never win!
Kaido...
The giant flying dragon...
And the Animal Kingdom Pirates...
No one has chance against them!
Look at this!
A mere weapon made by
one of Kaido's underlings...
...can pose a threat like this!
The devastating power!
That's right!
If a stranger like you hadn't appeared,
we could've just carried on with our daily lives
in Udon!
We didn't have to go through this!
No, Luffytaro-san! Don't touch them!
Stop, you guys!
No way! He exposed himself voluntarily?!
Is he stupid?!
Stop this.
You're gonna die!
What are you doing, Luffytaro-dono?!
Straw hat man!
A threat?!
Devastating power?!
It's not...
...affecting me at all!
Don't lie!
Get away from them now!
Luffy!
The samurai that I know are all very strong...
But you guys...
...got your spirits shattered!
Your daily lives?!
You just do as you're told
and get your measly dumplings...
You're given enough to keep you from dying
and you call that living?!
Wake up!
You guys are nothing but...
...slaves!
Big Bro and the others are fine!
Is he really fine?!
I'm from overseas! What's wrong with that?!
A stranger's not allowed to save this country?!
I made a promise...
...to my friend Tama...
...who gave me her food...
...that I'll make this country
a place where she can eat as much as she wants!
It's so yummy!
This soup is so delicious!
Tama!
Don't set the bar too low!
I'll make it your everyday life!
By the time we leave this country,
I'll make it a place where
you can eat as much as you want!
Big Bro...
If I can't...
...fulfill that promise, this country will be...
...an eternal hell!
I heard about Oden!
What an incredible guy!
But 20 years ago,
the day that he got killed by Kaido,
this country came to a standstill, right?!
We're here to win against Kaido!!
We don't need allies standing in our way!
So make a decision now!
Do you wanna side with us...
...or Kaido?!
Are you serious?
You'd still...
...give us a chance?
He got them...
He has a way of capturing people's hearts!
Oh, no...
Their minds are wavering...
But if I land a shot
right in the middle of those unguarded fools now,
it'll raise havoc,
and turn the tide again!
These 200 Plague Rounds' worth of virus
will be scattered...
...with this Plague Shot!
Take this! A big chunk of Elephant's Marchoo!
Chief Warden, don't tell me that's...
No! Don't do it!
Hey! Babanuki is going to fire something!
What?!
Too late!
Elephant's Marchoo!
What?!
What? What? What?
I did it because I saw a terrible future.
Babanuki-sama!
Chief Warden!
How...
...formidable he is!
Take care of the rest.
Count on us!
Hey, wait! Guys! Remember?!
What'll happen if you mess with the guards?!
The first offense, your arms will be cut off...
We know, but we don't care.
We've decided to rise in revolt!
Pay for what you've done to us all these years!
--Let's do it.
--Yeah.
Eight days before the great battle...
unbeknownst to the enemy's main army...
UDON HAS BEEN CONQUERED
Udon has been conquered!
You did it! Straw hat man!
You brought an incredible helper...
Kin'emon!
He wants to take back the Land of Wano from Kaido!
Luffy's unyielding disposition becomes
Momonosuke and the prisoners' hope and inspiration!
After 20 years of pain and humiliation,
will Luffy and his allies come together?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Warriors' Dream! Luffy's Conquer of Udon"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
...