mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
kaze ni nore
Catch the wind
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
Don't give up, if I'm determined
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
I'll never turn back
waraitobase aranami
Laugh on through troubled waters
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Shout it out, to save
your spirit from breaking
nakama ga irun da
Your friends are there for you
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Even when the darkness
tries to tear you apart
hora Brave it out
Come on, brave it out
daijoubu sa
It's going to be all right
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Strong bonds will break through
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Have the courage to take a step forward
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
chikai atsumeta hata
The flag that called forth oaths
tatakai tsudukete iku
Keep fighting on
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Stay true to yourself
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
Seize it, dreamin' on
makerarenai nige ya shinai
I can't lose, I'll never run away
deai wakare koe ikou
Transcend meetings and
partings and keep going
zenbu takaramono
They're all treasures
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Have the courage to take a step forward
ko wo agete
Raise your fist
A stranger's not allowed
to save this country?!
Eight days before the great battle...
...Luffy and the others had conquered Udon
unbeknownst to the enemy's main army.
"Warriors' Dream!
Luffy's Conquer of Udon!"
We're free!
Yeah!
Defeat Kaido!
One, two, hurrah!
You guys can't back down anymore.
Luffy... Where did he go?!
Luffy!
Killer...
You're so reckless!
Hey!
Are you gonna fight Kaido again?
Do you wanna join us?
No way!
Look what happened to my buddy...
Thank me for not killing
you right here and now!
I'm sick of forming alliances.
I won't believe anyone.
Let's go, Killer.
To take back our crewmates.
We're gonna go our own way!
Look what 20 years can do.
It is very hard to keep
believing in a hopeful dream.
They could not wait more than 10 years...
They became impatient
and went to Onigashima...
And they all died!
What happened?!
It's been 10 years!
10 YEARS AGO
We've grown so old.
If we wait for 20 years,
we'll get even weaker!
Are you asking us to wait for those people
whose return isn't guaranteed?!
Believe in Toki-sama's words...
Believe in them!
Kin'emon will come back!
Along with Momonosuke-sama!
We have nothing to eat
since we don't submit ourselves to Orochi.
Disease will kill us before a fight does!
It's Kaido's army!
Why did you destroy the well?!
Shut up!
We can't take it anymore, Shutenmaru!
Let us go and take down Kaido...
and Orochi!
I don't wanna just grow old
and die without doing anything!
No! Your death will be senseless!
You have no chance unless you form a big army
under Kozuki's banner!
We can't take it anymore!
Let us at least die holding our swords!
If we die, we wanna die as samurai!
Don't stop us!
--Let us go!
--Please!
You men, calm down!
Risking your lives now will not change a thing!
Why?!
We're not cowards like you!
That's right!
We'll choose how we die ourselves!
--Let us go!
--Please!
Let us have our revenge!
All that you've borne will have been in vain!
If you go now, you cannot avenge Oden-sama!
You all know that!
Remember? When we were kids...
We used to shout out that word
and test our courage.
In the end, placing too much value on yourself
makes people cowards!
Sunacchi!
Su-rrender your na-me and be as a chi-ld.
Take the leap without thinking!
That's what the word means!
Raise your voice! Sunacchi!
Sunacchi!
Stop it!
If we die, we wanna die as samurai!
Sunacchi!
Why did it have to take 20 years?
We will know once this is over!
There must be a meaning to it!
I have no reason to distrust Oden-sama.
Hey, guys!
Eight days from now...
On the night of the Fire Festival,
in the name of Kozuki,
we will raid Onigashima...
...to take the pirate Kaido
and the Shogun Orochi's heads!
Those of you who are determined,
follow me!
Yeah!
Of course we will, Chief!
We've been waiting for this day for so long!
Ashura!
You guys have not changed
since that day, right?
We were the same age at that time, but now that
we've lived 20 years longer, we are stronger than you!
Right, doggie?!
Yes, you are right!
Shut up, you old farts!
Do not get in our way!
You squirt!
Whoa-whoa, stop!
No one can stop a fight among the Akazaya members!
UDON
A pirate?!
The straw hat guy is a pirate
just like Kaido?!
Yes, he is, but he is different!
We can't trust him!
We know he'll betray us!
Of all people, why did you bring a pirate?!
Well, the world is big
and there are many different kinds of pirates...
That man is crucial for
us to bring down Kaido!
--How can we trust him?!
--We need a good explanation!
Oh, no. We are missing something.
They came to their senses, but...
First of all, is it true
that you came from 20 years ago?
Raizo-san, you always looked
older than your age.
So we can't tell
if you've actually aged 20 years or not!
You might not mean to,
but you are hurting my feelings!
Where did the straw hat man go?
Tama, you shouldn't have come this far.
It's dangerous.
I'm sorry, Big Bro.
But I'm glad that you're okay!
Yeah...
--He is barely alive.
--What?!
Big Bro, show some guts!
Don't touch him!
I'll find an antibody soon!
You shouldn't have pretended
that it wouldn't affect you!
It must be painful!
Why didn't you think it through?!
Say sorry to me!
I'm sorry.
It's painful.
Help me!
Just wait!
We thank them! But now that we know they're pirates,
we won't join with them!
Wait! Then we can't take down Kaido!
Straw hat man is trustworthy!
Pirates are all the same to us!
We don't need pirates!
Kick them out!
Luffy may be stupid but he is quite special.
I could not have done something like that.
Momo, you are...
...a real idiot...
...and a coward...
...and a weakling...
...and a wimp...
You're so helpless.
Shut up! You are so rude!
You have no business talking to me like that!
Momo-kun, don't hit him!
What are you, a chicken?
I am Kozuki Momonosuke...
Kozuki Oden's son!
Then go, Momo!
Kick them out!
We won't trust pirates!
Go now!
S-Stop, you fool!
Are you going to kill me?!
Who do you think they're waiting for?
They're waiting for you!
Don't tell me that's...
Momonosuke-sama!
Thank goodness you're alive!
Oh, yeah...
What we were missing was...
...a dream.
What lies ahead of this battle!
It is not me...
I think what everyone is seeing
is my father...
The great shadow of Kozuki
that protected the Land of Wano!
I-I cannot do it...
I cannot!
I want to bring down Kaido!
Momonosuke!
Do not be afraid, Momonosuke...
Do not be afraid, Momonosuke!
E-Everyone, listen...
Everyone!
Listen up!
What happened at Oden Castle that day...
I went on a journey searching for allies
along with Kin'emon and the others.
But I strayed from them
and was floundering about helplessly in a dangerous place.
I could not come back without the help of
Luffy and the others who I met along the way...
I am not strong enough yet.
But I will avenge everyone at any cost!
Even through difficult times,
I could carry on without giving up...
...because of one wish.
To realize that, I need like-minded allies...
I need the help of you all
who are living in the Land of Wano!
We all share one wish!
Take back the Land of Wano!
Everyone... For the last 20 years,
thank you for waiting for us!
I am the heir to the Daimyo
of the Land of the Wano...
...Kozuki Momonosuke!
Now is the time to rise up!
Yeah!
I am relieved to know that
Momonosuke-sama's grown up strong.
There is some place I urgently need to go.
I promise I will join you all before the battle!
Okay. See you then!
Orochi has a plan!
The Shogun's scheme drives
the Straw Hats into a corner
and destroys the plot to
take back the Land of Wano!
But to counteract this, Zorojuro, the swordsman, rises up!
He will punish the vice-ridden world!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Orochi's Hunting Party! The Ninja Group vs. Zoro!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!