Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Catch the wind
kaze ni nore
Don't give up, if I'm determined
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
I'll never turn back
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
Laugh on through troubled waters
waraitobase aranami
Shout it out, to save your spirit from breaking
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Your friends are there for you
nakama ga irun da
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Even when the darkness tries to tear you apart
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Come on, brave it out
hora Brave it out
It's going to be all right
daijoubu sa
Strong bonds will break through
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
The flag that called forth oaths
chikai atsumeta hata
Keep fighting on
tatakai tsudukete iku
Stay true to yourself
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Seize it, dreamin' on
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
I can't lose, I'll never run away
makerarenai nige ya shinai
Transcend meetings and partings and keep going
deai wakare koe ikou
They're all treasures
zenbu takaramono
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Raise your fist
ko wo agete
There's no time to lose!
Let's take the old bag to Kaido-san!
Hurry up!
Set sail!
"Tension Rises in Onigashima!
Two Emperors of the Sea Meet?!"
EBISU TOWN
All right. We'll leave it to you.
Count on me!
I will take it upon myself...
...to lay Yasuie-sama's body
to rest in Kuri.
Please take extra care.
Of course...
We owe a great debt to Yasuie-sama, too...
There is another thing...
...that I want to apologize for.
About the flyer with the symbol
that went around recently...
It has been 20 years
since the name Kozuki perished.
Now I cannot gather enough soldiers
to seek my revenge,
and I feel bad about the Kozuki Clan...
So I made the flyer!
The symbol does not mean anything.
That is...
...just a prank!
What?!
But Orochi was a bigger coward than I thought...
He got flustered and jailed the innocents
who had the moon tattoo which was a popular design!
Damn Yasuie!
I will fill you with bullets!
Orochi!
Do you want me to recite the curse
that binds your heart?
"A man of such small caliber...
...shall never know the taste of oden
for as long as he shall live!"
A MAN OF SUCH SMALL CALIBER SHALL NEVER KNOW
THE TASTE OF ODEN FOR AS LONG AS HE SHALL LIVE
Yasuie!
Thanks to Yasuie-sama,
our long-cherished wish has not been crushed...
We cannot have a massive funeral,
but we at least want to lay him to rest
in the same ground as Oden-sama.
Please...
Take good care of him!
We're counting on you!
--Please!
--Thank you!
We're all set!
Let's go, Nami! Kanjuro!
Okay!
Hey, wait for me! Let's get going!
Goodbye, everyone!
Safe travels!
LAND OF WANO
At a dock on the way from the Flower Capital to Kuri...
WANTED
USOHACHI      OROBI      PENGUIN
At this very moment, to catch the serious criminals
who tried to kill Orochi-sama and run,
NAMI THE KUNOICHI
FRANOSUKE THE CARPENTER     SHACHI
we've set up checkpoints
all around the Flower Capital!
Everyone, show your faces!
What should we do?
I knew that they wouldn't let us get away
so easily.
We must take that boat
if we wanna go to Kuri.
We have to come up with a plan
to pass through.
USOHACHI   OROBI
All right, go!
Next!
What?!
A curse on you!
Th-They're haunted by a ghost!
Y-You can pass through...
We managed to make it...
How's Otoko-chan?
She must be exhausted from crying,
she's sleeping in my arms.
To be honest,
I don't know what to say to her...
Daddy!!
Daddy!
Bonekichi, I'll take her.
You have no body warmth.
How dare you!
It's not true, right?
SOUTHWEST PART OF KURI
It has been a while since the last time
we walked side by side like this...
Come to think of it, it is true.
It was just days ago to me.
Ashura.
What is there to see at a place like this?
There is something that I want to show you.
Th-Those are...!
Don't tell me!
Ships?
Ships!
I'm speechless! Ashura!
They need to be fixed up a little bit...
But I brought them here from
ports across the country that were destroyed by Kaido.
We have enough to transport
thousands of warriors to Onigashima!
You are quite dependable!
My opinion of you has improved!
Yes, mine, too.
You were not so attentive before.
I did not spend 20 years sleeping!
I will ask Franosuke-dono to do maintenance later.
It has been a long, tough road
to get to this point...
But the day of the raid is within our sight!
EXCAVATION LABOR CAMP, UDON
That wasn't right...
What are you doing, Luffy?!
You still need to be resting!
Go back now!
Everyone's preparing, right?
What?
I need to master that technique, too.
What technique?
It's Ryuo.
If you need intensive training,
I'll be your sparring partner.
Hit me without holding back!
Okay!
What?! Are you gonna be okay?
Allow Haki to flow... inside my body!
Wow!
That's Ryuo?
At that time, the straw hat man...
...certainly used Ryuo!
I assume that Kawamatsu the kappa is so strong...
...because he uses Ryuo so well.
Once the straw hat man masters it,
I am sure it will help him in the fight against Kaido.
One more time!
Okay!
RINGO
I cannot believe it took years...
...just to get some ordinary deep-fried tofu...
I cannot possibly think that
that one is still waiting for me.
You did not learn anything and you came back.
The last time,
we had some unwanted interference.
I bet you don't like leaving it unsettled, either.
Then I will have the rest of your swords, too!
Two-Sword Style...
720-Pound Phoenix!
I have more weapons than you!
Who are you anyway?
An enemy or an ally?!
Who are you?!
Why are you ripping off weapons
from people who cross the bridge?!
Give me back my sword!
Don't waste your life over a sword!
Zorojuro-san...
I will not give it back to you!
I will give you any sword but that one!
That sword Shusui that you had was
the Land of Wano's stolen treasure!
What? Shusui?!
When it was taken away,
the whole tragedy began!
Because of that,
our God of the Blade became enraged,
and each region was defeated one by one!
In the end, the country was taken over!
What god?
You blasphemer!
Stop fighting!
What are a samurai and a monk fighting for
in the remote countryside like this?
It is funny that both of you have
no intention of killing each other...
A Fish-Man?
Kawa... matsu...
Kawamatsu?! Is that you?!
How do you know my name?!
ONIGASHIMA
You did such a crappy job! Damn you, King!
I'm sure I knocked the ship off of the waterfall...
Big Bro Queen, why did you bring her here?
Shut up! What could I do
in Udon where communication was cut off?!
King!
I'm willing to forget what you did to me,
so why don't you join us?!
We have all kinds of people living in our country
except for three.
One of them might have dwindled and disappeared
over time...
But you're alive.
I refuse!
What a shame.
Then, why don't you uncuff me?
What do you mean by "then"?!
We won't, you old bag!
How inflexible...
Hey, did you know?
A long time ago, Big Mom and Kaido-sama were
members of the same pirate group!
Uncuff her.
What are you doing?
Kaido-sama?!
You're finally here, Linlin...
Kaido.
Hey, you! He told you to uncuff me...
What?!
No, no, he must be kidding...
Uncuff her!
Kaido-san!
I haven't seen you for decades...
Napoleon!
Yes, Mama!
I'm glad that you're back to your usual self!
I'm shy with strangers,
so I didn't know what to do.
I told you I'd kill you if you came...
What kind of fool would march to their own death?!
With the bosses of the underworld on his side,
Luffy gets all fired up!
Meanwhile, Kawamatsu and Hiyori finally see each other again,
but Orochi's army comes to attack!
Swords flash! Zoro and Kawamatsu!
With their strong determination to protect Hiyori,
They brandish their precious swords!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Hiyori's Confession! A Reunion at Bandit's Bridge!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!