Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Catch the wind
kaze ni nore
Don't give up, if I'm determined
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
I'll never turn back
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
Laugh on through troubled waters
waraitobase aranami
Shout it out, to save your spirit from breaking
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Your friends are there for you
nakama ga irun da
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Even when the darkness tries to tear you apart
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Come on, brave it out
hora Brave it out
It's going to be all right
daijoubu sa
Strong bonds will break through
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
The flag that called forth oaths
chikai atsumeta hata
Keep fighting on
tatakai tsudukete iku
Stay true to yourself
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Seize it, dreamin' on
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
I can't lose, I'll never run away
makerarenai nige ya shinai
Transcend meetings and partings and keep going
deai wakare koe ikou
They're all treasures
zenbu takaramono
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Raise your fist
ko wo agete
Kappa Style!
Two-Sword Style!
River of Retribution!
RIVER OF RETRIBUTION
Rhino Cycle!
RHINO CYCLE
Kawamatsu-sama...
Hey, wait! Are you running away again?!
Damn you! Give me back my Shusui!
That bastard's wounded but not giving up...
Anyway, if I follow these blood stains...
Give me back my sword now!
What's this place?
More importantly, where did he go?!
"Its Name is Enma!
Oden's Great Swords!"
The samurai went after the giant warrior-monk...
I wonder who that warrior-monk is...
Anyway, Kawamatsu,
I am so glad that you are alive!
I am so grateful that you care about me...
Your Majesty! Step back!
Damn Kaido... He is still tenaciously hunting for
the remnants!
Hey, look!
They've been beaten...
Fill him with bullets!
Kappa Style!
Yorikiri!
Kawamatsu!
--Kawamatsu!
--Your Majesty!
Kawamatsu... Are you okay?!
Do not worry!
More enemies may be on the way.
Let's get away from here.
You are right...
Get on! It is hard to walk here.
Hey! I am no child, Kawamatsu!
Oh, yeah?
Well adults do not get all pouty like blowfish.
Hey. How could you!
This really brings back memories.
I cannot believe
that I get to walk with you again.
There is so much I want to talk to you about,
but first, why are you here?
After you disappeared,
I made my way here on mundane business...
Just as with the neighboring Hakumai,
this northern region of Ringo,
RINGO
HAKUMAI
was governed by the Shimotsuki Clan,
that was famous for their toughness.
The Daimyo's name was Shimotsuki Ushimaru-sama.
He was a master swordsman
who was always seen in the company of a fox.
A fox?
However, just like other regions,
Ringo was destroyed by Kaido.
Your Majesty, do you know
Ringo's tradition of Eternal Graves?
Yes, I heard corpses are placed in caskets
and they don't decompose for centuries due to the cold.
That is correct.
And grave markers are supposed to be swords.
People in Ringo are given swords
when they are born.
They will grow up with them
and keep them into old age.
When they die, the swords they carried
become their grave markers.
The people are with their swords for eternity.
That is why those graves are called
the Eternal Graves.
But since some of them are known as great swords,
graverobbing is a continual problem.
That is how this region, Ringo, is...
Let me tell you what happened
when I came here 13 years ago...
I was determined that if I cut my belly,
I would do it in this region...
Your Majesty, please be safe!
Damn! Is it a monster?!
How creepy!
We'll get the weapons next time! Run!
Is this the curse of the samurai from Ringo?!
How annoying!
Why can't they let me die in peace?
It is you!
Yes. I have met you once before!
You are Onimaru, aren't you?!
The name of that Koma Fox was Onimaru.
He was a companion of Shimotsuki Ushimaru-sama,
the late Daimyo of Ringo.
Is this...
Have you been protecting this all by yourself?!
For more than five years
since Ringo was destroyed,
Onimaru had been fighting by himself against grave robbers who came to steal
weapons from the Eternal Graves.
Come on. You do not have to be afraid.
I am your ally.
You are injured...
Onimaru!
Stay with me!
You are up!
Here is your food!
Foxes like fried tofu, right?
What is the matter?
If you do not eat, that wound will not heal.
If you die,
you cannot guard your master's grave.
Take a bite.
Come on. Try it.
Well, I have a stomachache.
I think I ate too much.
It does not matter!
Come on! Don't be shy!
Do you like it?!
Onimaru! Do not make a scene.
Forgive me! I know what you want to say!
Let go of me!
How could I explain it to you?!
I do not want to disturb the sleep of the dead!
But I must do this now!
Toki-sama, it's dangerous here!
Let's get out!
I will stay.
Toki-sama! We will protect you
as long as we breathe!
Leave... to the future!
People can never go back to the past...
But you can go forward into the future.
13 years from now,
there will be a big battle again!
Listen! I am sure that there will be a day
when samurai across the country stand up in high spirits!
When that happens,
we will definitely need tons of swords!
On the battlefield, we will pick up the swords of
our comrades who die in front of us...
...and advance!
The spirits living in those swords will make samurai stronger
and better able to defeat enemies!
This is still a battlefield!
Listen, Onimaru!
The battle between the Animal Kingdom Pirates
and the Land of Wano is not over yet!
It is still too early to lay these swords to rest!
Until that day comes...
we cannot let those robbers have the swords!
Instead, I will collect all of them
and hide them!
I understand...
...this is the only role...
...that I have been given!
Your Majesty...
Hiyori-sama!
I could not protect Hiyori-sama...
So...
...this is the least I can do!
I have to keep myself busy with something
or remorse will torment and kill me...
If you are hungry,
bite off this arm already and take it!
I will not stop robbing tombs!
SHIMOTSUKI USHIMARU
Onimaru...
What?!
What has gotten into you?
Did you understand what I said?
All right, Onimaru! I will join you!
Thus, Onimaru and I
joined forces to protect the graves
and collect the swords.
All right! Another day to rob the graves!
It is freezing today!
If it goes on like this,
we will have no place to sleep...
Let's dig a hole to hide them.
I am hungry...
If I sell one or two of those swords in the capital,
I will earn money
to buy enough food for a while...
Onimaru?!
I am just joking!
An army marches on its stomach....
This is for the greater good! Forgive me!
I am back, Onimaru!
I got some food!
Here is your favorite, fried tofu!
There is a money-making opportunity
in a place like this?!
Bingoh, are you sure?
I checked up on it.
The Eternal Graves are a treasure-trove!
We can steal as many swords as we like. Look!
Across that bridge is the main part of Ringo.
What is it?!
Leave, you robbers!
Lowlifes like you cannot have any sword!
--Screw you! Let's do it, Bungoh, Bongoh!
--Yeah!
Onimaru!
Who are you, you bastard?!
Do you want to know my name?
Let's see...
Hey!
I got an idea!
My name is...
...Bandit's Bridge's...
...Gyukimaru!
Now, leave your weapons and go!
Gyukimaru?! Is it a coincidence?
That warrior-monk has the same name...
And a short time later, I went to the capital
to get food,
but for a certain reason,
I was not able to return.
FRIED-TOFU
People of the capital, I am sorry...
--You're under arrest!
We caught him! You fried-tofu robber!
Stop resisting!
This is the gravest blunder of my life...
Forgive me, Onimaru...
And you were held captive
for 13 years?
That was a complete failure.
So you came here to see that fox today?
No, I am sure that Onimaru must have given up on me
since I never returned.
It has been 13 years already...
I do not think he is still here.
Zorojuro-san!
What happened to that warrior-monk?
He opened this door and disappeared.
He opened the door?
This place is...
What is he thinking?
Do not tell me that is the path to the underground space
that we created...
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Clank.
Hello? Is that Kin'emon?!
Oh, Kawamatsu!
I am glad that you are alive!
We have a lot to catch up on,
but I need to tell you something first.
You know that we conquered Udon, right?
Yes, about that,
I has told by Raizo that thanks to Luffytaro-dono,
the number of soldiers on our side was increased.
But I bet you do not have enough swords.
That is exactly right!
We have been contemplating what to do about it!
Damn Orochi!
He has been taking away people's swords
all across the country for the last 20 years!
I thought so...
But do not worry!
Even if you get thousands of soldiers,
I can provide as many swords as you need!
What?! Truly?!
Send some people
to the location I am about to share with you!
All right! I will do so immediately!
Clank.
But how...?
Onimaru did this?
But only humans can do this...
Then who did it?
Kawamatsu-sama...
I fulfilled... my duty...
Good luck!
Seems like there are enough weapons for the samurai.
Yes...
Now what's left to do is
to take back my Shusui...
That bastard... Where did he go?
Zorojuro-san!
If your sword is the real Shusui,
give it back to the Land of Wano!
I told you! That's mine!
I will give you a replacement!
A sword that was handed down to me
from my late father...
Enma the famed blade!
Enma...
It is a legendary sword
and the only weapon that ever injured Kaido!
I will give it to you...
The blade that cut Kaido...
Enma...
It's the battle of the Emperors,
Kaido and Big Mom!
While it rages to unexpected levels,
Apoo of the Worst Generation and the Numbers,
a group of giant creatures, arrive in Wano!
Another strong one joins Kaido's invincible army,
putting Luffy and his clan in a tighter spot!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A New Alliance?! Kaido's Army Gathers!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!