mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
kaze ni nore
Catch the wind
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
Don't give up, if I'm determined
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
I'll never turn back
waraitobase aranami
Laugh on through troubled waters
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Shout it out, to save
your spirit from breaking
nakama ga irun da
Your friends are there for you
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Even when the darkness
tries to tear you apart
hora Brave it out
Come on, brave it out
daijoubu sa
It's going to be all right
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Strong bonds will break through
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Have the courage to take a step forward
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
chikai atsumeta hata
The flag that called forth oaths
tatakai tsudukete iku
Keep fighting on
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Stay true to yourself
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
Seize it, dreamin' on
makerarenai nige ya shinai
I can't lose, I'll never run away
deai wakare koe ikou
Transcend meetings and
partings and keep going
zenbu takaramono
They're all treasures
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Have the courage to take a step forward
ko wo agete
Raise your fist
There you are.
You stole my sword, didn't you?
I met Ryuma.
Don't lie to me!
Stop talking gibberish!
A long time ago, when the Land of Wano
was recognized as the Land
of Gold by other countries...
Gold?
Unguarded!
Pirates around the world wanted gold.
Nobles tried to rule
the Land of Gold - the Land of Wano!
He showed those enemies from overseas
how formidable he was...
and burned the Land of Wano's samurai
in their minds!
That is who Ryuma is.
Who are you anyway?
An enemy or an ally?!
I will not give it back to you!
I will give you any sword but that one!
That sword Shusui that you had was
the Land of Wano's stolen treasure!
What? Shusui?!
When it was taken away,
the whole tragedy began!
Because of that,
our God of the Blade became enraged,
and each region was defeated one by one!
In the end, the country was taken over!
But how...?
Onimaru did this?
But only humans can do this...
Then who did this?
Kawamatsu-sama...
I fulfilled... my duty...
Good luck!
"A New Alliance?!
Kaido's Army Gathers!"
A week before the raid on
Onigashima where the great battle
is planned to take place on
the day of the Fire Festival,
the samurai have gotten their
hands on tons of swords.
Zorojuro-san!
If your sword is the real Shusui,
give it back to the Land of Wano!
I told you! That's mine!
I will give you a replacement!
A sword that was handed down to me
from my late father...
Enma the famed blade!
Enma...
It is a legendary sword
and the only weapon that ever injured Kaido!
The blade that cut Kaido...
Enma...
No, Hiyori-sama!
You cannot give away a
memento from Oden-sama!
My father, Kozuki Oden, was...
...a Two-Fullsize-Sword Style swordsman.
Before he got executed by
that hideous man, Orochi,
my brother Momonosuke and little me...
...were each entrusted with one of the two swords
that our father used.
My brother got...
...Ame-no-Habakiri.
AME-NO-HABAKIRI
I got...
...Enma.
ENMA
They are both made by the great swordsmiths
who were once famous in the Land of Wano.
They are fine swords.
That is why you cannot give
it away, Your Majesty!
You cannot let a dubious man like him...
...use Oden-sama's sword!
Kawamatsu...
I know how you feel,
but do not be rude to the man
who saved my life.
It is the God of the Blade, Ryuma's, sword.
I do not know how Shusui
ended up in your hands.
Well...
I guess Moria stole it...
But...
...when it was stolen,
the whole nation was crestfallen because it is...
...a sacred treasure.
Please offer Shusui to this country.
If you give me a replacement, then...
All right.
But I'm bonded to him because we fought a battle
even though it was against his corpse!
I'll return Shusui...
In exchange,
let me visit Ryuma's grave afterwards.
He is really delusional!
Is he okay?!
Your Majesty!
The Flower Capital...
This is commonly known as the Public Cells
where prisoners are displayed.
PRISON
RASETSU PRISON
RASETSU TOWN PRISONERS' QUARTERS
AKA: PUBLIC CELLS
Rasetsu Town Prisoners' Quarters.
The samurai who are held captive there
for rebelling against the Shogun Orochi...
...have not been released yet.
Yasuie threw dust in the enemies' eyes
and saved the raid plan by risking his own life.
However...
What's going on?!
We're not rebels!
The flyers we had were just
a prank by Yasuie-sama!
The Moon Tattoo was just a popular design!
How could you be so scared...
...as to imprison us who are all innocent
and put us on display in a place like this?!
It's disgraceful to be seen as rebels!
Let us go already!
Hey!
Damn...
What can we do?
INSIDE RASETSU TOWN PRISONERS' QUARTERS
What happened to your alliance?
I thought you formed an alliance
with Kid and Apoo...
We were set up...
Scratchmen Apoo was
under Kaido's wing all along...
The monstrous Kaido said to me...
"If you wanna become my subordinate,
I'll welcome you."
He's always looking for strong soldiers...
To make the most powerful
army in the world...
My chances of victory in that situation
were zero percent.
My chances of successful escape
My chances of survival by obeying
were 40 percent.
I had no choice.
But Kid and Killer weren't like me...
They challenged him
and kept fighting
until they couldn't move an inch.
Kaido won't kill people like that.
He'll try to break their spirit
and crush them into obedience.
But I don't think Kid will give up...
So he'll be killed.
I feel sorry for Kid's crewmembers.
They've been told to do this and that
if they wanna save their captain.
Which means Orochi uses them as he likes.
The Four Emperors of the Sea
are a different kind of creature from us.
They don't comprehend reason!
The alliance between you and Straw Hat
seems to be going well...
You two came to the Land of Wano together...
And now,
have you changed your mind?
Don't question me!
If you're plotting to let me escape...
I'm it.
SIX DAYS UNTIL THE RAID ON ONIGASHIMA
Six days until the raid on Onigashima.
That's Kaido's skin!
EXCAVATION LABOR CAMP, UDON
Remember your setback!
Remember that you couldn't beat him by force!
Thunder Bagua!
That iron sheet looks soft like konnyaku...
FIVE DAYS UNTIL THE RAID
Five days until the raid!
Ring, ring, ring...
Clank.
This is...
...Kin'emon!
There is a change in the symbol on the flyers
that you people have with you.
Add two lines on the habu snake's stomach!
AMIGASA VILLAGE, KURI
That is...
...Yasuie-sama's message!
Two lines...
Two lines?!
I got it!
WEAPON PREPARATION UNIT, UDON
Only Yasuie-sama could come up with it!
SWORD TRANSPORT UNIT, RINGO
I see...
Okay! I got it!
YAKUZA COMMAND UNIT, KIBI
Use the lower half of your body more!
SHIP MAINTENANCE UNIT, ITACHI PORT, KURI
Otherwise, it won't be good enough to
sail through rough waters to Onigashima!
Yes, Boss!
--Come on, use your lower body!
--Two lines on the habu's stomach?
I see!
I understand, Kin'emon-dono!
Mm-hm. I am glad you do.
Is it Kin'emon?
I'll make sure to fix up all the ships!
Super...
...count on me!
--Leave it to us!
--Let's give it our all!
Count on us!
Tell everyone about the change in the symbol!
Thank you.
I'm impressed.
The people from the Land of Wano can figure out
the meaning of the additional lines instantly.
Now what does it mean?
Two dashes on the habu snake...
Babu?!
You cannot understand it
if you do not know the names of the ports in Land of Wano.
ITACHI PORT
Itachi (Weasel) Port.
NEKO PORT
Neko (Cat) Port.
Kaeru (Frog) Port.
KAERU PORT
Mogura (Mole) Port.
MOGURA PORT
Tokage (Lizard) Port.
TOKAGE PORT
And Habu Port.
HABU PORT
Every port in the Land of Wano
has a name that sounds the same as an animal.
First, with the symbol of a habu snake,
we implied that Habu Port
is the rendezvous point.
HABU PORT
Now, two sets of limbs are added.
The body is a bit too long,
but adding limbs to a habu snake makes it a lizard.
Tokage (Lizard) Port is in Udon.
TOKAGE PORT
By changing the rendezvous point
from Habu Port to Tokage Port,
even quick-witted enemies
won't be able to get in the way of our plan.
Yasuie-sama...
...must have considered every possibility
and taken steps early on for us!
We were already indebted to him,
but we caused him trouble until the very last.
A true samurai must make use of this opportunity
or it will bring shame.
I remember what Yasuie-sama once told us...
"You guys must become the Land of Wano's...
...guardians!"
He was really something...
Yasuie-san.
We still have a few challenges,
but thanks to you all,
the number of our allied soldiers is increasing
just as we had hoped.
We still have no idea
what happened to Denjiro,
but we have seven of Kozuki's retainers!
EVENING SHOWER KANJURO, AKAZAYA NINE
KIKUNOJO OF THE FALLEN SNOW, AKAZAYA NINE
KAWAMATSU THE KAPPA, AKAZAYA NINE
DOGSTORM, AKAZAYA NINE
ASHURA DOJI, AKAZAYA NINE
FOXFIRE KIN'EMON, AKAZAYA NINE
RAIZO OF THE MIST, AKAZAYA NINE
It's quite impressive.
It's no longer just a dream
to have 5,000 troops.
Yeah! It's wonderful!
Are you going to keep chit-chatting?
It's a waste of time.
Okay, let's start the discussion of the plan!
We will take Kaido and
Orochi's heads at any cost...
...to avenge the late Oden-sama!
Scratchmen Apoo is arriving
at the Land of Wano!
Check it out!
Incidentally...
there are actually two ways
to enter the Land of Wano.
One is...
...the risky way of being hauled by carp!
Shake it up, baby!
The other is...
...to break the waterfalls open
and pass through a cave.
Needless to say, without Kaido and Orochi's permission,
you can't pass through it safely.
MOGURA PORT
At the end of the cave lies Mogura Port.
Sailors and cargo are moved to a gondola there
to be pulled up.
When they rise out of the end of the tunnel,
HAKUMAI
they'll find themselves in Hakumai.
Hello, Kaido-san?
We've arrived at Hakumai.
ONIGASHIMA
Oh, you guys took the trouble
to come back for the party, too?
Of course, we did!
It's the annual Golden Festival!
I don't wanna be left out!
We'll throw a bigger party than ever!
That's great!
Let's do that!
W-W-What are they?!
O... O...
Onigashima...
The Numbers of Onigashima!
Let's run now!
Or they'll eat us!
I guess the Numbers came back...
What?!
I hate them because they're messy drinkers!
Let's have another!
On the night of the Fire Festival,
we'll have the greatest party ever!
Yes, it's gonna be an anniversary.
What the...
They became friends
after trying to kill each other?
--Hey, listen up, guys!
--What is it?
We, Animal Kingdom Pirates...
and the Big Mom Pirates...
Let me stand up.
...decided...
...to form...
...an alliance!
What?
What?!
First, we dominate the world together!
Then we'll go back to killing each other!
Cut in two with a single stroke!
Zoro struggles with Enma that draws out Haki!
Meanwhile, Luffy tries hard to master Ryuo!
As everyone rouses themselves,
the recruitment of allies is almost over!
Finally, the day comes!
With the fate of the Land of Wano
on the line, the Straw Hats and
Akazaya make desperate efforts!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Ticking Down to
the Great Battle! The Straw Hats Go into Combat Mode!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!