Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Catch the wind
kaze ni nore
Don't give up, if I'm determined
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
I'll never turn back
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
Laugh on through troubled waters
waraitobase aranami
Shout it out, to save
your spirit from breaking
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Your friends are there for you
nakama ga irun da
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Even when the darkness
tries to tear you apart
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Come on, brave it out
hora Brave it out
It's going to be all right
daijoubu sa
Strong bonds will break through
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
The flag that called forth oaths
chikai atsumeta hata
Keep fighting on
tatakai tsudukete iku
Stay true to yourself
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Seize it, dreamin' on
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
I can't lose, I'll never run away
makerarenai nige ya shinai
Transcend meetings and
partings and keep going
deai wakare koe ikou
They're all treasures
zenbu takaramono
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Raise your fist
ko wo agete
On the night of the Fire Festival,
we'll have the greatest party ever!
Yes, it's gonna be an anniversary.
--Hey, listen up, guys!
--What is it?
We, Animal Kingdom Pirates...
and the Big Mom Pirates...
Let me stand up.
...decided...
...to form...
...an alliance!
Tokage (Lizard) Port is in Udon.
TOKAGE PORT
By changing the rendezvous point
from Habu Port to Tokage Port,
even quick-witted enemies
won't be able to get in the way of our plan.
Yasuie-sama...
...must have considered every possibility
and taken steps early on for us!
We will take Kaido and
Orochi's heads at any cost...
...to avenge the late Oden-sama!
"Ticking Down to the Great Battle!
The Straw Hats Go into Combat Mode!"
Is it really...
AMIGASA VILLAGE, KURI, LAND OF WANO
...true?!
Yes, it is true.
Hiyori-sama is alive?!
Yes, she is.
I am worried to death about Otoko...
but still, Kawamatsu,
I am not going to meet everyone now.
People should not get
emotional before battles.
Together with everyone else,
please save the Land of Wano!
Your Majesty! You should not do that!
Raise your head!
That little devil said such a polite thing?!
She really grew up!
Kawamatsu! Since you were in prison,
I imagined something bad had happened to her,
so I could not ask you!
Where is she now?
Is she with a bodyguard?!
Do not worry. She is in a secure location.
Anyway, that is great!
That is really great!
She is alive...
Big Bro!
Hiyori!
Dropkick!
Zorojuro!
Did you save her?
Thank you!
She is a bit rough,
but she is actually a bit weak,
and cries a lot, so she is quite a handful.
Hey, Momo.
You still think it's just like the old days?
She is now 18 years older than you.
Dropkick!
A dropkick from someone
18 years older than me?!
That is not good...
That beautiful lady who was with you
at that time...
...was Momonosuke's sister?!
W-What?
Momonosuke-kun!
Is there anything you want?
Don't suck up to her brother, idiot.
Sangoro-dono.
Enough fooling around.
Kawamatsu! They are ready!
Are you sure about this?
Yeah.
We have already come to an agreement...
I see.
Then I will hold my tongue.
Hitetsu-dono!
Take this first.
This is Kitetsu II which was confiscated
from Luffytaro-san at Udon.
Oh! Thanks!
That big-stomached brat!
He took it without permission.
Kitetsu!
I knew it was one of the famed blades.
Hark! My name is Tenguyama Hitetsu!
I am a swordsmith from the Land of Wano!
For two decades,
I have been awaiting the day that
I can hand back these swords to
Momonosuke-sama and Hiyori-sama!
These were Oden-sama's precious swords.
Ame-no-Habakiri that can slice heaven in two!
And Enma that can even cut
through the bottom of hell!
Both counted among the 21 Excellent Grade Swords
along with Shusui.
Momonosuke-sama, what would you like to do
with my masterpiece?!
W-Well...I am not ready yet!
Not that I am scared of it,
but I want you to keep it for now.
And that Enma is yours!
First, I must tell you that the only person
who was able to manage Enma in this country...
...was Kozuki Oden
and no one before or since!
Try cutting one of those trees.
Zoro-dono.
I am going to say this frankly out of kindness,
but if I were you,
I would not take it.
The whole cliff has been cut off!
Look at Zorojuro's arm!
Damn...!
Give it back!
That's Enma!
It will suck out the owner's Ryuo
as it pleases,
and cut more than needed.
If you were a regular swordsman,
you would have dried up and collapsed by now...
Impressive!
What do you want to do?
Do you want other swords?
No, I'll take this!
Enma, huh?
Once I get used to it,
I'm gonna be even stronger, right?
He is a fool!
Gear Four!
Bounce-Man!
EXCAVATION LABOR CAMP, UDON
King Kong Gun!
That wasn't good.
Yeah, you're straining yourself too much.
What?! That wasn't good?!
Keep working hard! We don't have time!
Make it strong enough
to carry a hundred thousand people.
THREE DAYS UNTIL THE RAID
We're not expecting that many.
Idiot! We want as many allies as possible.
Let's make a bet on
how many people will come!
Orobi-dono.
Do you know how big the enemy's military force is?
According to what I heard,
the Animal Kingdom Pirates have
about 20 thousand troops.
The Shogun Orochi has
about 10 thousand companions.
That means there'll be 30 thousand enemies
at Onigashima on that day.
There are no commoners to get in the way,
so they have a geographical advantage.
Even with the blueprints of the mansion.
And all we have is about four thousand.
It is not going to be an all-out war,
but we are hugely outnumbered.
Nevertheless,
we have no other option than the raid plan!
We must execute it!
Luffy...
Are you okay?!
Luffy! We must get going!
Sorry. Could you wait a little longer?
Can you master it in time?
Ryuo?
Yeah, I'll master it in time at any cost!
Settle down!
Momo, don't you have to train yourself?
Oh, yeah. Remember you once told me
the word "Sunacchi"?
Yeah.
You said it's a good-luck word
to uplift your spirit.
Right.
But Okiku told me not to say it.
I just learned it from an old man in my village
a long time ago,
but I've never said it even once.
What?!
Hey!
TWO DAYS UNTIL THE RAID
Master-sama!
Otama!
I was worried about you!
Chopper! Luffy!
Nami!
Ring, ring, ring...
Clank.
This is Kin'emon.
What is the military potential in each region?!
How many allies did you recruit?
The fire of rebellion is still burning.
I have a bunch of lively allies!
We are ready.
Kin'emon-dono.
Kibi!
Hakumai!
Ringo!
Udon!
We have 200 additional troops in total!
Really?!
Yay!
Now we have 4,200 troops!
I have not heard from Law-dono yet...
Who cares if he calls or not?
Well, he's pretty strong!
Big Bro trained so hard
that he's not waking up.
Hey, officer!
There'll be a festival soon.
We wanna participate.
RASETSU PRISON
No, you can't! Knock it off!
Damn! This will be our last chance!
Everyone will fight to the death!
I know those who were caught in the capital
are frustrated,
but there is nothing we can do.
Even their families who protested
got caught.
That is where our toughest samurai are...
But we are running out of time.
Everyone!
Thank you for your work!
Use the remaining time for
travel and preparations.
Roger!
See you at the rendezvous port!
Momo-kun.
Here, take this.
A braided hat...
You braided it for me?
Uh-huh!
I made one for everyone.
ONE DAY UNTIL THE RAID
Thank you.
Now, Luffy-dono.
We are leaving now.
We must get there before anyone.
Okay!
Our ship, the Sunny is docked here.
Don't get caught!
What?!
We have never dropped our guard!
I am counting on you guys!
Yeah, leave it to us!
See you at the port!
Yeah!
There are countless smokestacks
in this country,
and even more unfortunate laborers.
--Do you think it's true?
--What?
Yasuie-sama...
...covered for the Akazaya samurai.
Did you hear that rumor?
--What?
--That flyer...
...wasn't Yasuie-sama's prank,
but it was actually a real signal for the raid, I heard.
Don't make us feel hopeful.
Remember what happened to the Kozuki Clan
20 years ago.
Even if Kin'emon and the others are alive...
their spirits must have been broken.
They'll never stand up again!
This country is so isolated.
No one'll come to help!
Besides, no one can stand up against Kaido!
Now, silently setting out,
are seven Akazaya samurai, one ninja
and one important personage.
They step on the dried-up land
which crunches like frost in winter.
The sun shines high up in the sky.
There are some dark clouds,
but the shadows of the nine...
...who are in fact not ghosts
and who intend to avenge their
lord after two decades...
...are clearly seen on the ground.
Once we win the battle,
let's build nicer tombs.
YASUIE
PEDRO
That Kitetsu looks different now.
It seems like he met a good owner.
Kitetsu III which you wield is my craft.
Is that so?!
Squirt.
Hiyori-sama gave you Enma,
which I'm guessing fits oddly
comfortably in your hand, doesn't it?
It follows the same logic of cursed swords.
The weak cannot handle them.
But the biggest reason why it fits comfortably in your hand
is, in a twist of fate,
...that Wado Ichimonji and Enma
were crafted by the same person!
The legendary swordsmith,
Shimotsuki Kozaburo.
More than half a century ago,
he illegally departed from this country.
Hiyori-sama might have given you the
memento from her father
because she recognized that sword.
Enma has not been
forged into a Black Blade yet!
Its rank can be raised depending on you.
I'll do it!
Is all well in Udon?
Yes, everything is fine.
Oh, so that was a false report!
Yes, this is Udon. Nothing has changed here.
We'll keep watch on prisoners.
--Well then.
--Clank.
What an untrustworthy fool!
But as long as I have this information,
it's more than enough.
"Changed from Habu Port to Tokage Port.
Kozuki Hiyori is alive somewhere
in the north," huh!?
Just you wait, Kaido!
Gather 'round!
The sky is clear and cherry blossoms flutter
in the Flower Capital!
The day of the Fire
Festival has finally come!
Meanwhile, in the shadows, the battle
that might sway
the fate of the world is about to begin!
LAND OF WANO ACT TWO - END
We have big news!
The One Piece manga that will be in
the January 4th edition of Weekly Shonen Jump
marks our one thousandth chapter!
CONGRATULATIONS!
1,000TH MANGA CHAPTER
Thanks for everything
and please keep rooting for us!
Conspiracies boil!
The raging waves of time are drawing near!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Big News! An Incident That Will Affect the Seven Warlords!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
THANK YOU!
WE'RE FRIENDS FOREVER!