Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Catch the wind
kaze ni nore
Don't give up, if I'm determined
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
I'll never turn back
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
Laugh on through troubled waters
waraitobase aranami
Shout it out, to save
your spirit from breaking
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Your friends are there for you
nakama ga irun da
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Even when the darkness
tries to tear you apart
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Come on, brave it out
hora Brave it out
It's going to be all right
daijoubu sa
Strong bonds will break through
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
The flag that called forth oaths
chikai atsumeta hata
Keep fighting on
tatakai tsudukete iku
Stay true to yourself
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Seize it, dreamin' on
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
I can't lose, I'll never run away
makerarenai nige ya shinai
Transcend meetings and
partings and keep going
deai wakare koe ikou
They're all treasures
zenbu takaramono
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
ko wo agete
Raise your fist
I am worried to death about Otoko...
but still, Kawamatsu,
I am not going to meet everyone now.
People should not get
emotional before battles.
Together with everyone else,
please save the Land of Wano!
First, I must tell you that the only person
who was able to manage Enma in this country...
...was Kozuki Oden
and no one before or since!
I am counting on you guys!
Yeah, leave it to us!
See you at the port!
Yeah!
Just you wait, Kaido!
ISSHO
SEA AREA AROUND THE ENTRANCE OF THE NEW WORLD
I'm just a newcomer
picked through the International Military Draft,
but since being appointed as a Navy admiral,
there is something I want to do.
The Navy.
The Seven Warlords.
The Four Emperors.
What do you think will happen to
the balance of power?
I don't know. Who can
tell before we upset it?
That vicious pirate was approved as a king of a country
under the Seven Warlord system
and allowed to reign over this island
by none other than...
...the World Government!
What I want to destroy is...
...the system.
We no longer need the
Seven Warlords of the Sea!
"Big News!
An Incident That Will Affect the Seven Warlords!"
MARIJOA
The World Conference known as the Reverie.
It's a grand conference of 50 representative kings and queens
held every four years,
representing more than 170 countries
that are affiliated with the World Government.
The Reverie was dismissed
in a state of great confusion as always,
and all the representatives went home.
Then...
...a week later...
Gee... I'm finally home-jamon...
RYUGU CASTLE, RYUGU KINGDOM, FISH-MAN ISLAND
Boy... The surface world is so far above...
Um, thank you for escorting us!
Luffy-sama's grandfather-sama!
Well, don't mention it.
It was a pretty long trip, huh, Neptune?
You must be tired!
I'm exhausted-jamon.
Garp, stay here with us and rest well.
Well, maybe I'll have a cup of tea,
but considering the situation,
I can't stay here that long...
The Reverie always triggers big incidents.
When 50 countries gather,
a simple "Let's get along" won't do.
Each country has tons of
problems of their own.
Large and mighty countries
just quietly stare at each other,
and let their proxies bicker...
To them, resources and technologies
are a weapon.
They say that all countries are equal,
but that's just lip service.
Wealth and poverty and religious differences,
won't allow them to be equal...
Even if they shake hands,
they step on each other's foot with a grin.
I wonder how many leaders there are
who can speak for their
citizens and for other countries...
The round table must be weeping...
You're right.
The conversations among the leaders were explosive.
We're no exception, but quarrels between countries
can't be solved so easily.
If there is a long history,
the conflict must have deeper roots.
Even if there is a disagreement,
as long as no blood is spilled, I call it peace.
But what happened this time is no good!
It's a bit late to mention this,
but there's actually one thing
that I haven't told you about.
Right after the Reverie was dismissed and we set off,
an incident occurred,
and I received the report aboard ship.
We the Navy will do our best to resolve it,
but please don't be afraid of...
JUSTICE
...the surface world as well as humans!
What happened?
Garp, what kind of report did you receive?
It's an incident concerning Alabasta Kingdom.
Alabasta Kingdom...
Vivi-sama!
Before all of this transpired...
At the World Economic Journal
right after the Reverie was dismissed...
Wow! It's incident after incident!
Can't believe this many
things happened at once.
Listen! Come up with the
greatest heading ever!
Sir, which one should make the front-page?!
Listen! Someone has died!
The big obituary sells papers!
--Then, that'll be the headline...
--No, wait!
The resolution they passed is also good.
But a murder attempt makes
you excited as well!
That's right!
Okay, let's have two front pages!
The back page will have the same format as the front!
Okay!
Sir!
Express mail from the Government.
A check, huh?
Oh, that's a lot!
I see. It's an order to
manipulate information.
But for which case?
Hushing up this incident?
I can't do that!
Throw this back in their faces!
Hey, what's wrong?
No, no, no...
Do what you're told, Morgans!
The secret agency, Cipher Pol?!
You must obey orders
from the World Government.
Don't move!
Don't underestimate "Big News" Morgans!
When did he sneak in?!
Sir! Members of Cipher Pol are
the Government officials!
I know!
Guys, it's dangerous to stay here.
Let's relocate!
I may be a miser,
but I'm first and foremost a journalist!
Sometimes I spin lies and make people dance.
I'm a DJ of words!
I decide what to publish!
Mr. Morgans!
You got a call from King Wapol of Drum Kingdom...
King Wapol?
What does he want?
Well, sounds like he has information to leak.
What?!
What's going on?
A special report?
Don't worry...
It's gonna be okay...
In addition to the incident that
the Government failed to hush up,
the decision of the leaders made at the Reverie
and the incident that occurred there...
...became known throughout the world in a flash
and stunned people.
Wait! What is this all about?!
That can't be true!
It's just a story in the World Economic Journal, right?
REVOLUTIONARY ARMY'S GENERAL HEADQUARTERS
KAMABAKKA KINGDOM
It's the WEJ!
That bird president must've written nonsense!
I'm sure of it!
It's Sabo! That's impossible...
I don't buy it!
Calm down!
First, we must confirm the facts.
But all of them are out of contact...
How can we confirm?
This isn't true, right?
Sabo-kun...
ROYAL ESCORT SHIP, GOA KINGDOM
My lady!
He was in Marijoa?!
B-Big Bro-sama?!
What happened to Makino?
--The bar is closed today.
--What?!
There was so much news in the world...
I could use a drink.
Sabo-kun...
I just found out that he was alive...
Tell me it's not true!
Sabo!!
UNDERSEA PRISON IMPEL DOWN
I never get bored with this world!
It's getting interesting!
Hey, guys!
Let's set sail!
Rather than just watch as the Navy takes it,
I'll take it for myself!
Now, back to the current action...
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
OUTSKIRTS OF EBISU TOWN
Ring, ring, ring...
Clank.
It's me, Koby.
Hold on a second.
--I can't speak to you here.
--Okay.
Oh, yeah! "Sea"!
"Fog"!
As always, you're conscientious...
Well, it's a rule...
Oh, yeah! Listen!
There's something that I need to report...
...to you, Captain!
X. DRAKE - CAPTAIN OF "SWORD"
NAVY HQ TOP SECRET SPECIAL FORCE
What?! Is that the situation out there?!
Yeah, it's too much to handle...
Even with all Navy soldiers in the world...
So just as we planned,
the Navy won't get involved with what's going on over there.
They don't have enough soldiers...
I think that's fine.
The Land of Wano is not affiliated with the World Government.
Now, about Big Mom arriving at Onigashima...
Yes.
Kaido and Big Mom have had a vendetta
for so long...
The Navy is expecting those two pirates
to ruin each other.
Yeah, I guess.
As we expected,
Kaido and Big Mom were at each other's throats...
But they joined hands!
W-W-W-W-What do you mean?!
As for Straw Hat Luffy,
there's been no word of a breakout.
The situation is at a standstill.
And there's one more thing.
This is unpleasant,
but I saw Cipher Pol Zero in the capital
the other day.
What?! Why are they in the Land of Wano?!
I hope I'm wrong,
but that must mean the World Government is
doing business...
...with this Land of Wano
which is reigned over by a pirate.
When I was made aware,
I became stunned...
...for a few minutes.
By the way, where are you now?
Yes.
To capture Pirate Empress, Boa Hancock...
we're heading towards the Island of Women!
Oh, my...
Those ships coming towards us
crossing the Calm Belt are...
...a Naval fleet?!
Margaret!
What is going to happen?!
That news that spread across the world...
They should've gotten rid of that damn thing
a long time ago!
It was a mistake to team up with pirates...
They're evil!
For those who think all pirates are bad...
Those Government dogs will finally go away!
Screw that Pirate Empress, Hawk-Eye,
and Clown!
They're nothing but looters!
And for those who hate looters,
it's good news...
But I thought they did great
in the Paramount War!
The Reverie made the decision?!
I think the Navy will go into action
immediately...
Is it gonna be okay?
They were one of
the three great powers in the world!
For those who knew
how they did in the Paramount War,
and those who are concerned about
losing the balance of the three great powers,
it's a truly alarming situation.
One of the news stories
on the latest Reverie,
that stunned the people across
the world the most was...
...the abolition of the Seven
Warlords of the Sea system!
The Seven Warlords of the Sea
are officially recognized pirates.
While they're allowed to loot,
the Government uses them as deterrents
against other pirates.
The composition of the Seven Warlords
has changed repeatedly with the times.
Crocodile.
He collided with the Straw Hats
over Alabasta Kingdom.
He was trying to take over the kingdom,
but he was defeated by Luffy
and expelled from the Seven Warlords.
The man who replaced Crocodile
and joined the Seven Warlords...
...was Marshall D. Teech.
However, after achieving his aim,
he announced his resignation.
"First Son of the Sea" Jimbei
who was opposed to the Paramount War
and became antagonistic to the Navy.
He, too, declared his resignation.
Gecko Moria.
This man who once got in the Straw Hats' way
was also summoned for the Paramount War.
However...
after the war, he was attacked off guard
by an order from high up in the Government.
and was expelled.
Heavenly Demon Don Quixote Doflamingo...
At the same time he governed
Dressrosa as its king,
he was trafficking an artificial Devil Fruit, Smile,
as an influential underground broker.
However...
he lost the battle over the kingdom
against Luffy
and the others and his
Warlord title was revoked.
And Trafalgar Law.
He allied with the Straw Hats to take down Doflamingo
and was stripped of his title.
The four pirates who reign supreme
as if they're emperors.
The Four Emperors.
The Navy Headquarters
that is trying to contain them.
NAVY
And the Seven Warlords of the Sea.
These three great powers
have kept the peace in the world.
FOUR EMPERORS       NAVY
SEVEN WARLORDS OF THE SEA
However...
there are two kings who took
enormous losses from the Warlords.
King Nefeltari Cobra of Alabasta Kingdom,
and Riku Doldo III of Dressrosa Kingdom.
They stood up for
the abolition of the Seven Warlord system.
And after a heated debate at the Reverie,
a large majority supported the proposition
and it was passed.
Therefore, the Seven Warlords of the Sea
naturally forfeit all of their rights,
and their connections with the World Government
are cut off.
That means...!
EMPTEE BLUFFS ISLAND, NEW WORLD
Buggy!
You're just another pirate!
That's not fair, you fools!
A decision was made without telling us
and since we're no longer useful, you'll arrest us?!
You have no sense of justice whatsoever!
You being outwitted by Crocodile and Doflamingo
is none of my business!
Don't take it out on me!
We've got the whole coast surrounded!
What should we do?
My whole life plan has been screwed up!
Oh?
The Navy's supposed to be on our side,
but we're surrounded!
What should we do, Mommy?!
Mommy!
RUINS OF MUGGY KINGDOM, GLOOM ISLAND
Surrender yourself now! "Hawk-Eye" Mihawk!
Surrender yourself!
KUJA
Snake Princess, we have a problem!
Your title as a Warlord of the Sea
has been stripped away!
Granny Nyon!
There are Navy ships off the coast!
What?!
They've already gone into action?!
Don't panic!
Snake Princess!
I think they're...
...forgetting something!
This is no good, Chairman Buggy!
Should we run?!
Of course, we'll fight them in a flashy way!
Show some guts!
You fools!
That's our Chairman Buggy!
BUGGY THE GENIUS JESTER, BUGGY'S DELIVERY CHAIRMAN
A FORMER WARLORD OF THE SEA
Buggy! Buggy! Buggy! Buggy!
Seems like they're not on our side anymore!
It's so unforgivable...
Weevil! I give you approval
to take them down!
Really?! Then...
I'm gonna kill them!
EDWARD WEEVIL, WHITEBEARD JR. (SELF-PROCRAIMED)
A FORMER WARLORD OF THE SEA
In the name of Whitebeard!
I feel a tremor of excitement...
It's been a long time...
DRACULE MIHAWK, "HAWK-EYE"
A FORMER WARLORD OF THE SEA
...since I was the one being chased.
We became the Seven Warlords of the Sea...
BOA HANCOCK, PIRATE EMPRESS
A FORMER WARLORD OF THE SEA
...because we were strong!
I'm counting on you, you guys!
While you're doing that...
I'll get the hell out of here...
Kaido and Big Mom!
Does that mean the vicious Rocks pirate
group which
once ruled the whole sea is back?!
The legend that Luffy's grandfather Garp
once allied with
the King of the Pirates is now revealed!
The balance of power is lost!
No one can resolve the confusion now!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Legendary Battle! Garp and Roger!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!