Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Catch the wind
kaze ni nore
Don't give up, if I'm determined
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
I'll never turn back
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
Laugh on through troubled waters
waraitobase aranami
Shout it out, to save your spirit from breaking
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Your friends are there for you
nakama ga irun da
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Even when the darkness tries to tear you apart
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Come on, brave it out
hora Brave it out
It's going to be all right
daijoubu sa
Strong bonds will break through
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
The flag that called forth oaths
chikai atsumeta hata
Keep fighting on
tatakai tsudukete iku
Stay true to yourself
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Seize it, dreamin' on
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
I can't lose, I'll never run away
makerarenai nige ya shinai
Transcend meetings and partings and keep going
deai wakare koe ikou
They're all treasures
zenbu takaramono
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Raise your fist
ko wo agete
The Reverie always triggers big incidents.
Even if there is a disagreement,
as long as no blood is spilled, I call it peace.
But what happened this time is no good!
It's a bit late to mention this,
but there's actually one thing that I haven't told you about.
Right after the Reverie was dismissed and we set off,
an incident occurred,
and I received the report aboard ship.
We the Navy will do our best to resolve it,
but please don't be afraid of...
...the surface world as well as humans!
Wait! What is this all about?!
"Fog"!
As always, you're conscientious...
Well, it's a rule...
Oh, yeah! Listen!
There's something that I need to report...
...to you, Captain!
X. DRAKE - CAPTAIN OF "SWORD"
NAVY HQ TOP SECRET SPECIAL FORCE
Therefore, the Seven Warlords of the Sea
naturally forfeit all of their rights,
and their connections with the World Government
are cut off.
That means...!
EMPTEE BLUFFS ISLAND, NEW WORLD
Buggy!
You're just another pirate!
That's not fair, you fools!
A decision was made without telling us
and since we're no longer useful, you'll arrest us?!
You have no sense of justice whatsoever!
You being outwitted by Crocodile and Doflamingo
is none of my business!
Don't take it out on me!
We've got the whole coast surrounded!
What should we do?
Of course, we'll fight them in a flashy way!
Show some guts!
You fools!
That's our Chairman Buggy!
BUGGY THE GENIUS JESTER, BUGGY'S DELIVERY CHAIRMAN
A FORMER WARLORD OF THE SEA
Buggy! Buggy! Buggy! Buggy!
Seems like they're not on our side anymore!
It's so unforgivable...
Weevil! I give you approval to take them down!
Really?! Then...
I'm gonna kill them!
EDWARD WEEVIL, WHITEBEARD JR. (SELF-PROCRAIMED)
A FORMER WARLORD OF THE SEA
In the name of Whitebeard!
I feel a tremor of excitement...
It's been a long time...
DRACULE MIHAWK, "HAWK-EYE"
A FORMER WARLORD OF THE SEA
...since I was the one being chased.
Granny Nyon!
There are Navy ships off the coast!
What?!
They've already gone into action?!
Don't panic!
Snake Princess!
I think they're...
...forgetting something!
We became the Seven Warlords of the Sea...
BOA HANCOCK, PIRATE EMPRESS
A FORMER WARLORD OF THE SEA
...because we were strong!
It's getting interesting!
"A Legendary Battle!
Garp and Roger!"
NAVY
You must be happy, Issho...
The abolition of the Seven Warlords of the Sea
was what you all really wanted...
I was against it, but the leaders' decision
can't be reversed.
Dammit, how can everyone be so naive?!
Justice comes with a price...
And there's no escaping it?
You can't understand
because you've never been one of them...
The world where innocent weak people
get ignored...
...is worthless!
Hurry up! Keep moving!
Hurry!
The Seven Warlords of the Sea are no more.
Let's believe in the SSG,
the Navy's Special Science Group...
The balance of power in the world
is about to change drastically!
Just how it'll change is unknown!
I heard that Kaido and Big Mom
will team up in the Land of Wano...
What?!
ISSHO
Does it mean the return of Rocks?!
Don't speak of it
like it's legend or something!
It's all true...
and a disaster that menaces us
despite how busy we are at the moment!
What?! Two Emperors of the Sea joined forces?!
--No way!
--Of all times, now?!
To be precise, we got information
that they'll team up in the days ahead...
They haven't done any harm so far
and we don't know their purpose or how to deal with it yet.
The only thing that connects those two...
...is the legendary Rocks Pirates.
But there isn't much information about them, either...
Big Mom and Kaido have hated each other
for a long time...
I didn't expect such a thing would happen.
Sengoku-san, what are Rocks Pirates?
Oh, yeah.
You are too young to know about them...
The Rocks Pirates were a gang of unique characters
who gathered together...
...around just one money-making scheme
on the Pirate Island of Fullalead ages ago.
They were all so violent,
they even battled to the death on board their own ship.
Its members were, first, Captain Rocks...
Whitebeard in his younger days!
Big Mom!
And Kaido!
Those three used to be on board
the same pirate ship.
What?!
--N-No way!
--I-I can't believe it!
There are other pirates from the Rocks Pirates,
who later became infamous.
Shiki the Golden Lion who used to be a big name
and even vied for supremacy in the New World.
There were still others
like Silver Axe, Captain John, and Wang Zhi...
You've got to be kidding!
They're all big-name pirates!
Why was such a pirate group lost to history?
One of the reasons is that they disliked each other so much,
they took no pride in publicizing their exploits.
Secondly...
Captain Rocks had the ambition
to become the king of the world...
So they showed their teeth at the World Government
as if they were a terrorist group,
and the Government has been
covering up incidents since.
But everyone knew how threatening they were
at that time...
A particularly fateful incident took place at God Valley
38 years ago.
38 YEARS AGO
It was reported on the news that the world's
strongest Rocks Pirates were annihilated on that island...
No one could stop the advancement of the evil,
but Navy HQ Vice Admiral Garp was able to!
His name became known throughout the world
and people started calling him the hero of the Navy.
So that's the beginning of
Vice Admiral Garp's many tales of heroism!
There are countless tales of heroism
involving Vice Admiral Garp,
but I didn't know
there was yet another great episode like that!
He's really something!
Big Mom and Kaido?!
Enough already...
But he often refuses to talk about it.
What? Why?
I'll fill you in
so you can learn some history...
One of the reasons he doesn't share
was never reported in the papers.
It was necessary to work alongside a pirate
to fight that battle.
A pirate?!
The other reason is he happened to
save the Celestial Dragons.
What?!
The Celestial Dragons were part of that story?!
Well, it's a Navy soldier's duty
to protect the Celestial Dragons.
What's wrong with that?!
Garp's moral compass tells him that it's not his duty.
One of the reasons that Garp refuses
to become the admiral is...
...because admirals are
the Celestial Dragons' direct subordinates.
He openly shows disrespect for them, but he is spared
because of his achievements and popularity.
Now, the truth of the matter is...
...to protect the Celestial Dragons and their slaves
at God Valley,
Garp and Roger who happened to be there
worked together and defeated the Rocks Pirates!
It's known as the God Valley Incident!
RETIRED
Worked together with...
...the King of the Pirates...
...and fought?!
The Celestial Dragons and Roger and Rocks?!
I can't believe they were all at the same place at the same time!
What was on that island?!
I've never heard of God Valley!
It's no wonder...
The name, God Valley...
...is nowhere to be found on any map now.
In fact, it disappeared without a trace...
The island that the World Government wanted to hide
disappeared...
Do you still wanna know about the island?
Once, the ambitious Rocks tried to become
the king of the world,
but broke one too many taboos,
so information regarding him is no longer available...
He is only remembered by
some Navy soldiers of our generation.
Even it was a long time ago,
I can't believe there was a man who led three pirates
who'd later be called the Emperors of the Sea!
For Roger, maybe Rocks was
his first and strongest enemy...
Strangely enough,
Roger and Rocks had something in common.
Rocks' full name is Rocks D. Xebec.
Even though he has already died,
he was one of those pirates
who have the name "D."!
Let me return to my story.
RETIRED
It's true that Kaido and Big Mom
were on board the same ship...
But their capabilities are totally different
from 38 years ago.
If they really team up,
we're about to see the world's worst pirate group.
Brannew! How much are their bounties now?
Right, yeah, we have to decide new bounties for
those who were stripped of their title of Warlord, too.
Let's go over all of their numbers.
Starting with Blackbeard who started to be
called an Emperor of the Sea about a year ago...
He recruited some powerful subordinates
when he raided Impel Down two years ago,
and now has gained control over
the Pirate Island of Fullalead.
He's still extending his influence
taking Whitebeard's place!
The commodore of the Blackbeard Pirates, Marshall D. Teech!
2 billion 247 million 600 thousand berries!
Next up, he has only been called an Emperor of the Sea
for six years...
He's the youngest of the four
and deeply trusted by his subordinates...
Beckman.
Roux.
Yasopp.
His top officers gained notoriety individually,
and his undefeatable group has a high average bounty
and the best balance of any groups...
The chief of the Red-Hair Pirates...
Red-Hair Shanks!
4 billion 48 million 900 thousand berries!
Next is...
She's a natural-born monster who allegedly
destroyed the village of Elbaph when she was little...
She only trusts her blood relatives
and along with her 85 children,
this autocratic queen built Totto Land,
the queendom made of candy!
The captain of the Big Mom Pirates!
Charlotte Linlin!
4 billion 388 million berries!
And in the old Rocks Pirates,
he was just an apprentice pirate...
But thereafter, he earned the respect of
vicious pirates by his strength alone,
and ended up being called an Emperor of the Sea!
The Supreme Commander of the Animal Kingdom Pirates!
King of the Beasts Kaido!
4 billion 611 million 100 thousand berries!
I feel depressed...
By the decision at the Reverie,
we can't deploy the Seven Warlords
to fight these Four Emperors anymore!
Whether removing that poison was correct or not...
It's up to how well SSG,
the Navy's Special Science Group, performs.
For your reference,
here are the bounties of other legendary figures!
The captain of the Whitebeard Pirates!
Edward Newgate!
5 billion 46 million berries!
The captain of the Roger Pirates!
The King of the Pirates Gold Roger!
5 billion 564 million 800 thousand berries!
No pirates have ever surpassed these two...
but once Kaido and Big Mom's alliance is formed,
the sum of their bounties will surely top those numbers!
But now in the Land of Wano
which isn't affiliated with the Government...
Fleet Admiral Sakazuki!
Forget about the Land of Wano!
We have no resources to put towards it, Sengoku-san!
Of course, I wasn't intending to get involved...
I was just conveying my knowledge as an old soldier
to young soldiers.
Even pirates have relationships.
They have purposes for their actions.
You can't see what'll come next
if you don't know history.
Oh, yeah... There was a pirate from the Land of Wano who
was favored by Whitebeard, Roger, and Red-Hair.
You mean Kozuki Oden? The man who once served
as a commander on Whitebeard's ship...
Oden was later headhunted by Roger
and accompanied him on his last journey...
There's no way that Oden has something to do
with what's happening...
But why do those big-time pirates
who disturb the world...
...always get involved with the Land of Wano?
I think it's too much of a coincidence...
Sakazuki!
On the day of the annual Fire Festival,
at the rendezvous point, Luffy and his clan are nowhere to
be found and Kin'emon and the others stand helplessly by!
Here comes a storm!
Will they give up on the raid plan?!
Raging waves and sea wind
seem like they're trying to block their way to Onigashima!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Rendezvous Port! The Land of Wano Act Three Begins!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!