Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Catch the wind
kaze ni nore
Don't give up, if I'm determined
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
I'll never turn back
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
Laugh on through troubled waters
waraitobase aranami
Shout it out, to save your spirit from breaking
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Your friends are there for you
nakama ga irun da
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Even when the darkness tries to tear you apart
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Come on, brave it out
hora Brave it out
It's going to be all right
daijoubu sa
Strong bonds will break through
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
The flag that called forth oaths
chikai atsumeta hata
Keep fighting on
tatakai tsudukete iku
Stay true to yourself
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Seize it, dreamin' on
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
I can't lose, I'll never run away
makerarenai nige ya shinai
Transcend meetings and partings and keep going
deai wakare koe ikou
They're all treasures
zenbu takaramono
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Raise your fist
ko wo agete
25 YEARS AGO
Rewinding to 25 years ago...
A little before the Great Pirate Era began...
Is everybody having a good time?!
I am glad that I followed you.
Roger!
Huh?!
Why are you saying such a thing now, idiot?!
Oden!
We must thank you instead!
You're drinking too much!
Control yourself!
Shut up!
I won't take advice from a drunken doctor!
I'm concerned about your health!
You bastard!
Lie there quietly!
Ow, ow, ow...
That hurt.
That was the cure for stupidity.
Cut it out!
Damn you!
I must go back...
To the Land of Wano?
Yeah, there is still something major left to do...
Is there anything we can do to help, Oden?
If you need a hand...
I can lend one, Oden-san!
You fool!
You'll get in his way instead!
Hey, Oden-san. I'm sure I can help!
Rayleigh...
Redtaro, Buggyjiro...
Thank you!
But...
We, the Kozuki, must do it!
I've asked you so many times,
why do you call me "jiro (second son)"?
Let it go!
Oh, yeah. The Kozuki, huh?
I learned a lot through this journey...
I always wondered
why the Land of Wano closed its door.
I left the country by my own choice, so I won't say
a selfish thing like, "Let me become the Shogun"...
But I must pass this will on at any cost!
With my great retainers that I left behind,
I will open up the Land of Wano!
And I will wait for the "future"
that will come more than 20 years from now!
Let's do it, Oden!
Yeah!
I will do it, Roger!
25 YEARS LATER
Now 25 years have passed.
LAND OF WANO ACT THREE
OROCHI
HABU PORT, HAKUMAI
Orochi-sama!
"The Rendezvous Port!
The Land of Wano Act Three Begins!"
Today is a good day!
Look at that view!
It is a perfect day for a banquet.
Our Orochi-sama is even favored by good weather.
This time, Kyoshiro will stay at the capital to look after it!
Tell him we are counting on him!
Yes, sir!
Poor guy! He can't attend the banquet!
This Habu Port in Hakumai
is known as the largest port in the Land of Wano.
Maple trees line the giant pier
which projects from the shore into the sea,
and the lovely scene of fluttering red leaves
sends ships off.
It is a good day!
Bring sake! Let's have a cup
while admiring those red leaves!
Orochi-sama, you should not drink
until you see Kaido-sama...
Who cares! I know he is drunk, too!
It is a big banquet with 30 thousand guests!
Let's have a great time as always!
On the night of the annual Fire Festival,
the two leaders who rule the Land of Wano
come together at Onigashima.
And they throw a big banquet
at which all of Orochi's army and Kaido's army gather.
FLOWER CAPITAL ON THE DAY OF THE FIRE FESTIVAL
Hey! Hurry up!
Hurry up! It's already started!
Wait! I don't like the way my bangs look!
Come on! Dance!
Drink! Sing!
It's the Fire Festival in the capital today!
The only day we're allowed to drink!
We'll drink hard and have a good time today!
Oh...
The sky's so clear!
We'll see a beautiful full moon tonight!
The seasons of each region of the Land of Wano
differ wildly.
TOKAGE PORT
The weather also varies tremendously
by location.
At that same moment,
at the rendezvous point, Tokage Port...
AT THE SAME MOMENT
THE RENDEZVOUS POINT, TOKAGE PORT
Not a single ship is in sight!
Where are the four thousand soldiers?!
I am positive we conquered Udon!
But no one is there at the labor camp, either.
It seems like this port was attacked!
It appears the cat couldn't make it.
The Smail is not responding.
We cannot contact anyone...
At twilight on the day of the Fire Festival,
at Tokage Port!
This is the rendezvous port!
Why hasn't anyone come?!
Where did they go?!
It has been only a day...
What is this all about?!
Something happened to everyone?!
Heave ho! Heave ho! Heave ho!
Dance! Dance!
It's the annual Fire Festival!
Why don't you let loose
and burn off some stress tonight?!
Luffy-dono, where are you?!
Hyogoro-dono, please respond!
Dogstorm Musketeers!
Law-dono!
Jibuemon of Kibi!
We are Kozuki Oden's retainers!
From 20 years ago...
We came from 20 years ago
to avenge our lord!
We should have died at that time!
So we came to die for a cause!
However,
it takes more than just our lives!
The enemy has 30 thousand soldiers!
We need help!
I am begging you!
Somebody, please help us!
Somebody, respond!
Please help!
Enough, Kin'emon!
Look at the sky and sea!
We are already abandoned even by heaven!
No one will help us!
Something must have happened to everyone...
TWO DAYS AGO
Rewinding to two days before the Fire Festival...
AMIGASA VILLAGE
Mm-hm. Now we have 4,200 soldiers.
I am glad... I am glad that they joined us...
Everyone...
Thank you for your work!
Use the remaining time for
travel and preparations.
Well then...
See you at the rendezvous port!
ITACHI PORT, KURI
Finish fixing enough ships
to carry five thousand people!
Yes, sir!
Bring those ships to the port by the appointed time!
Can you do it?!
Count on us, Big Bro Franosuke!
All right!
ITACHI PORT
AMIGASA VILLAGE
Then, we'll meet up with our friends
in Amigasa Village,
and come by the Sunny on that day!
We'll leave the rest to you!
Yeah! Thank you for helping us!
You guys are great shipwrights!
Thanks! Let's take those Animal Kingdom Pirates...
...and kick their asses, guys!
UDON
No matter how much timber we have,
it's never enough! Cut up everything!
Ocho's group will bring
swords and the like from Ringo!
So...
We'll craft armor from whatever we have!
I don't know if they're usable,
but we have tons of weapons and those sorts of things
for export here!
Good!
If we go to the rendezvous point too early,
we will draw people's attention.
KIBI
But...
...on the morning of that day, the Shogun's procession
will wind from the capital to the port.
HABU PORT            FLOWER CAPITAL
Once they leave for Onigashima,
the Fire Festival will take place in the capital!
No one will pay us any mind!
"Two birds..."
We better get there before twilight...
UDON
But some officials will still be on the mainland!
ITACHI PORT
KIBI
We cannot let them report to Onigashima,
so stay alert the whole way!
Okay!
Are you allowing us to use these?!
Wow! It's a samurai helmet!
I wanna show it to Usopp, too!
We're warriors!
Your enemy is that ill-famed Kaido.
Are you all prepared?!
Kaido?
That loser...
...is about to be sliced up!
I don't think we'll lose!
Bring it on!
Chobro and the others look good!
Oh, how cute. Just like bugs.
Bugs?!
C-Cute...?
Why don't you wear one, too?
No, it'll just slow me down.
Wear it.
Since your bounty is so low!
Enma!
Do you wanna fight?! I'll kill you!
Try it, you bastard!
What are you fools doing?!
Orochi said that it's winter
at the entrance to Onigashima.
What? Is it cold?
What do you mean by "entrance"?
The mainland of the Land of Wano
has different seasons in different areas.
We're coated with fur,
so we're okay with cold weather.
DOGSTORM THREE MUSKETEERS
Yeah, for us, the weather is more crucial...
CONCELOT     SHISHILIAN     GIOVANNI
...than the season!
It's supposed to be a full moon that day,
but if it hides behind the clouds, it's useless.
You're right!
If all Minks transform like Carrot,
that'll help us a lot!
Garchu!
But the Sulong transformation
will depend on luck.
It's more important to have
Master Cat Viper and Guardians here...
What's wrong, Luffy?
Big Mom is here...
But Jimbei isn't here yet!
Thanks to him, we got away from Big Mom!
I'll be waiting for you at the Land of Wano!
Come at any cost!
Thank you!
Jimbei!
Don't die no matter what!
He joined us after he settled things!
We're happy to have him...
We've still got time... He'll come!
If he's alive.
I'm sure he is!
He'll come!
EBISU TOWN, OUTSIDE OF THE FLOWER CAPITAL
Hey, guys! Come here! Ushimitsu Kozo came!
But there's no talk of a robbery in the capital!
He's the only person who would do this!
We can't take part in the Fire Festival tomorrow,
but let's drink water with these!
We burned down the mountain bandit's mountain!
But instead of seeking revenge,
they keep stealing tons of food from our farm!
OKOBORE TOWN, KURI
Do you guys have something to do with it?!
W-We don't know anything!
I heard samurai are preparing to make a raid...
Is that why, maybe?!
If so, we can't let them know!
What are you guys whispering about?!
I will guide you!
OTSURU - KIN'EMON'S WIFE
So do not hurt anyone!
O-Otsuru-san!
Guide me?
Do you know anything about this?
You will see once you get there.
It is a little far though...
You must need tons of food
because you are with so many allies!
Huh, Kin-san?
You are here in the Land of Wano, right?
I was stunned when I saw Kikunojo...
Kin-san...
Kin-san, let me handle this!
I will draw their attention!
I will not let them search for you all!
Kin-san... Take back Kozuki's country!
No, Otsuru-san!
You don't have to cover for us!
It's okay now!
We just wanted to eat as much as we wanted before we die!
What?
So it's you guys who did it!
TOKAGE PORT, UDON, THE PRESENT
There is a small boat...
We can use it.
What are you doing, Dogstorm?! Stop it!
Let's do this another day, Kin'emon!
That is not an option...
Kin-sama!
Let go of me, Shinobu!
Kin-sama, we can't do this tonight!
We must do it tonight!
You know that, Shinobu.
It has got to be tonight!
An incident had already taken place
the night before.
The Sunny is blown up!
Not knowing of Luffy and the others' safety
Akazaya samurai move on with
their lord's words in their hearts!
The hero of the age, Oden, went his own way.
Now, how he lived replays
like cherry blossoms taking flight!
On the next episode of One Piece! "The Number-One
Samurai in the Land of Wano! Here comes Kozuki Oden!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!