Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Catch the wind
kaze ni nore
Don't give up, if I'm determined
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
I'll never turn back
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
Laugh on through troubled waters
waraitobase aranami
Shout it out, to save
your spirit from breaking
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Your friends are there for you
nakama ga irun da
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Even when the darkness
tries to tear you apart
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Come on, brave it out
hora Brave it out
It's going to be all right
daijoubu sa
Strong bonds will break through
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
The flag that called forth oaths
chikai atsumeta hata
Keep fighting on
tatakai tsudukete iku
Stay true to yourself
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Seize it, dreamin' on
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
I can't lose, I'll never run away
makerarenai nige ya shinai
Transcend meetings and
partings and keep going
deai wakare koe ikou
They're all treasures
zenbu takaramono
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Raise your fist
ko wo agete
This is the rendezvous port!
Why hasn't anyone come?!
I am begging you!
Somebody, please help us!
An incident had already taken place
the night before.
"The Number-One Samurai in the Land of Wano!
Here comes Kozuki Oden!"
NIGHT BEFORE THE GREAT BATTLE
Akazaya...
And...
...Oden!
I am going to show you hell!
BEACH OF KURI
--Did you find the ship?
--Yes.
We found it.
But you sure about this?
Just do as I say!
Do it!
Roger!
Mission complete!
I will not let them have their way!
Next, bridges!
GREAT BRIDGE BETWEEN KIBI AND UDON
The great bridge between Kibi and Udon
has been blown up!
Destroy them!
GREAT BRIDGE BETWEEN KURI AND UDON
The great bridge between Kuri and Udon
has been blown up!
They had it coming!
GREAT BRIDGE BETWEEN RINGO AND HAKUMAI
Look!
The great bridge that connects the regions is...!
Why, all of a sudden?!
We cannot get to the other side now!
All that remains is the port!
Orochi-sama! All the ships
have been destroyed!
ITACHI PORT, KURI
That is fine. We will rebuild
once everything is over.
I still have not seen the Akazaya members
or samurai troops who they recruited with my own eyes.
People skipped forward in time
from 20 years ago?!
How can anyone believe that?!
Unless they see one of their heads.
No, even if they see it,
it is still hard to believe.
And that damn fool, Yasuie,
made it sound even more ridiculous!
But the information is credible.
The Akazaya members are alive!
I do not care if my men think
that I am talking nonsense.
I have authority to take action!
I have blocked all the routes to Tokage Port.
TOKAGE PORT
Four thousand troops?
Good job recruiting so many.
But no one will make it to the port!
I will not give them even
a chance to get revenge!
Damn you Akazaya ghosts!
Wallow in the despair from
being isolated and helpless!
Stop, you all!
Taking that small boat is like suicide!
Let's regroup and begin again
when we get another chance!
If we miss this opportunity...
we have to wait for a year.
But we cannot hide anymore.
They will find out that we took control of Udon soon.
Kaido's whole army will come to hunt rebels.
We cannot continue to steal
their food anymore, either.
Before we left Kuri,
you surely heard what happened.
The people of Okobore Town
who were believed in our great battle...
...were burned alive.
Among them...
...was my wife.
Please allow us to go!
No.
Do you want us to flee
and live in disgrace?!
What about me?
We want you to live with Hiyori-sama!
Do not be so selfish!
Even your father had no support at first!
If we had not met Oden-sama...
We would not be samurai
since we were all immature.
That is why we want to be...
...Oden-sama's samurai
retainers until the end.
Do not go!
Do not go, Kin'emon!
I do not want to lose even one more person!
Listen, men!
This centuries old national isolation
is deeply tied to Kozuki...
And...!
The time will eventually come!
Before the world starts to change,
open up the Land of Wano!
Forty one years ago, in the Flower Capital...
Kozuki Oden is back!
--Hide your wives!
--And daughters!
Hide the livestock!
--He failed to set sail again!
--He wants to get out of here that badly?!
There was a very popular man in the capital.
It is so restrictive!
It is so restrictive
that I might be squeezed to death!
I...
Here I come! Here I come!
...want to see the big world!
As I like!
Oops... I want to eat oden!
A vast expanse of green forest.
Through flowers, plants, and trees that are growing thick,
a fresh stream runs.
And a beautiful sea.
This is a story that takes place in the Land of Wano
when it was still teeming with life.
TEAHOUSE
You got away from a moving mountain?!
That's right!
It was groaning.
Maybe the mountain god became angry!
Just kidding!
Anyway, you all look so happy.
What happened?
MISS TSURU, WAITRESS AT
THE MOUNTAIN PASS TEAHOUSE
We finally caught it!
What a splendid boar!
If we take it to the capital,
we'll get one Platinum coin!
What?!
That's enough to build a decent house!
Yeah! The Kurokoma boss is looking for
a legendary white boar to display in his storefront,
so he posted a reward for one.
He shouldn't display it!
White boars are divine messengers.
Kin'emon!
Ow, ow, ow...!
You stole money from our store again!
KIN'EMON - TOWN THUG
Miss Tsuru!
We've known each other since childhood!
I'm like your big brother
and I need money!
That's because you gamble!
Do you know how much you owe me?!
The next time you put your hands on my money,
I'll sell your organs!
If you cannot pay me back,
leave all your clothes!
KIN
Damn Tsuru!
She really stripped me naked!
But I got to hear a money-making idea.
KATSUZO
Grandpa Katsuzo!
A CREMATORY, FLOWER CAPITAL
Don't cry. I mean...
It's a funeral so you get to cry...
What's the matter?
The cremation is finished,
so we were about to gather his bones.
Then, that man...!
We found him cooking oden
with the flame that burned my father's body!
Seems like Oden-sama is
not capable of sailing.
It was his 38th attempt
to leave the country illegally.
How could he return alive?
I suspect you probably know,
but let me tell you briefly of his life.
KOZUKI SUKIYAKI (ODEN'S FATHER)
SHOGUN OF THE LAND OF WANO
When he was not even a year old yet,
he sent his nanny flying.
When he was two,
he caught two rabbits at once.
When he was four, he threw a boulder
and knocked out a bear!
When he was six, he spent all his time
at the pleasure hall wasting the castle's money.
When he was eight,
he went to a gambling parlor by himself,
and started a brawl
with some hot-blooded gamblers.
When he was nine, he was blacklisted by yakuza
and repaid them...
...by setting their gambling parlor on fire,
instigating a gang war.
Then, he got arrested for assault.
That was at the age of 10.
While serving his time at quarries,
he showed his ability.
He even became a master stonemason!
It must be in the Kozuki's blood!
Then he came back on the street
as a better person!
When Oden-sama was 14 years old!
The capital suffered a drought.
Wells dried up
and he could not stand watching people suffer.
So he changed the river's course
and made it flow to the capital.
But it caused a massive flood.
And an arrest warrant was issued again.
He tried to flee from the country
through the channel.
But he failed quite miserably!
Then when he was 15, he strong-armed
a mountain temple master and stayed hidden there.
He brought back women from the capital every night
and formed a harem!
He must be some kind of monster...
I should add that
all those women were always free to leave.
But some people became furious
and stood up.
They were those women's boyfriends,
parents, and husbands!
A group of strong samurai backed them up!
Oden-sama welcomed their challenge
and fought back!
That is what is known as the Harem War!
Even the Hyogoro Family who tried to stop them
got involved,
and a great scuffle took place!
Enough!
Oden-sama is now 18 years old.
He has made trouble at a steady pace up to today.
That is all I have to report.
I do not need your commentary,
just deliver this to Oden.
NOTICE OF DISAVOWAL
I will break off my relationship with him!
Katsuzo.
The next time we drink together,
it'll be in the afterlife.
Take it easy.
FLOWER
Now, if you'd excuse me,
ladies and gentlemen of the bereaved family.
What was that? So cool...
Is that it?
This must be the Oden
speech people talk about!
Now I am in luck.
This is like winning the lottery.
If I give this to the Kurokoma boss,
I will...
Come on! Give me all your clothes!
I won't let you get away today!
Whoa-whoa-whoa! Wait!
I'm about to get big money!
Don't lie!
It's true!
Let me go to the Kurokoma Family's mansion!
Kin'emon?
Oh, that kid who stole our money!
Catch him and flay him alive!
HYOGORO THE FLOWER
A YAKUZA OF THE CAPITAL
But do not engage one-on-one.
He is stronger than you guys!
I was entrusted with 60 Silver coins!
If I just use it, it'll be gone!
Can I have the smaller pot?
I'm running an errand for someone.
Okay. It's 30 Silver coins!
--Here you go.
--Thanks!
Oh, I bought the wrong pot.
I needed the bigger one.
The bigger one is 60 Silver coins.
60 SILVER COINS
I've already paid you 30 Silver coins,
so giving you this pot makes it 60.
Okay!
Thank you!
That brat fooled that man
and saved 30 Silver coins!
Easy money!
DENJIRO - AN ORPHAN IN THE CAPITAL
Hey, Denjiro.
Oh, Kin-san!
Look at this!
I got a pretty valuable thing!
You came to arrest me?
Yes...
But it's not like I really wanna arrest you,
so you can bribe me...
Now why isn't everyone avoiding me?
Seems like all they care about is a fire.
You don't know it, Kin-san?!
You shouldn't bring that!
What? You mean this white boar?
Kurokoma boss is trying to destroy the Hyogoro Family
by using it as a decoy!
What do you mean?!
I mean wherever that little boar is,
its parent boar will come
charging any minute!
All right!
Parent boar?
According to an ancient document,
it's a massive white boar like a mountain!
That's why they call it the mountain god!
What?!
One story tells that several centuries ago,
it destroyed the whole region in one night.
I thought it was just a myth,
but...
...since the white boar really exists...
The mountain god really exists!
It'll swallow us and kill us!
It's already right there! Run!
Oh, no! It's my fault that the capital is...!
Ko...
Kozuki Oden!
That was an interesting conversation.
What?
I don't know who you are...
...but give that white boar to me!
The daring Oden's unrivaled
strength impresses Kin'emon!
Kin'emon pledges his loyalty to Oden
and they meet imperfect allies across the country!
Oden and Akazaya Nine later become legend
in the Land of Wano!
This is how they began their
rollicking, vagrant journey!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Tearfully Swearing Allegiance! Oden and Kin'emon!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!