mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
kaze ni nore
Catch the wind
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
Don't give up, if I'm determined
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
I'll never turn back
waraitobase aranami
Laugh on through troubled waters
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Shout it out, to save
your spirit from breaking
nakama ga irun da
Your friends are there for you
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Even when the darkness
tries to tear you apart
hora Brave it out
Come on, brave it out
daijoubu sa
It's going to be all right
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Strong bonds will break through
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Have the courage to take a step forward
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
chikai atsumeta hata
The flag that called forth oaths
tatakai tsudukete iku
Keep fighting on
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Stay true to yourself
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
Seize it, dreamin' on
makerarenai nige ya shinai
I can't lose, I'll never run away
deai wakare koe ikou
Transcend meetings and
partings and keep going
zenbu takaramono
They're all treasures
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Have the courage to take a step forward
ko wo agete
Raise your fist
You don't know it, Kin-san?!
You shouldn't bring that!
Ko...
Kozuki Oden!
That was an interesting conversation.
What?
Give that white boar to me!
"Tearfully Swearing Allegiance!
Oden and Kin'emon!"
AN HOUR AGO
Let go of me!
Shut up! You're a hostage!
If you resist, you'll get hurt!
W-What is it?!
Kin-chan!
Just on account of this little one,
the capital will really be...!
Stop squealing!
That's why I said, "Give it to me"!
No, wait! This boar costs one Platinum coin!
That's a lot of money!
I can pay back all my debts
and use the rest as capital to make more money!
K-Kozuki Oden! It's really him!
I look down on all stupid adults.
He's the only person I respect!
The only time the mountain god comes near human dwellings
is when someone kidnaps its child!
So someone brought its child to the capital?!
We must placate the mountain god!
Find a small white boar!
If we can't send the white boar back to the mountain,
the capital will be destroyed!
Help me! Help!
--Houses are getting swallowed with people in them!
--Dad!
What a nightmare!
Evacuating the people is top priority!
Those who are prepared to die, follow me!
There you are! I've been looking for you!
You're the boar kidnapper!
But you took it from me!
Send it back to the mountain already!
That monster will come straight for us
if it catches a whiff of the little one!
What?!
We didn't expect any of this...
My two accomplices whose clothes smelt like the boar
were swallowed by the mountain god!
Along with your friend Otsuru!
Why her?!
To get back the white boar from you,
we took her hostage and were going down the mountain...
Everyone got swallowed! It's all your fault!
Kin-san!
That monster will come straight for us
if it catches a whiff of the little one!
Get out of my way!
It's coming this way!
What? Kin-chan stole something again!
I'm sorry! Let me pay for it!
Kin-chan, you must get a job.
You're always chased by the yakuza!
You'll get killed!
Who cares!
No one will mourn my death!
Ouch! Don't hit me with a rock!
Give me back Tsuru!
Stop it, kid! If you harm the mountain god,
the Land of Wano will be ruined!
I'm gonna cut that belly open!
You call yourself a god?!
Give me back Tsuru!
Kin-san!
Kin-san! Stop it!
He has guts...
If Tsuru dies because of me...
I wanna die, too!
Dammit!
Isn't this what you're looking for, boar?!
Kozuki Oden! The prodigal son!
It's him again! He must've
caused all of this!
It'll make a good boar hotpot...
How could you do this to us?!
Give my mother back!
No...
It's a misunderstanding...
Give my daughter back!
I brought that white boar here!
It's my fault that the
capital got into this mess!
Oden Two-Sword Style!
Paradise Waterfall!
What?!
He's something.
Let's go home.
Otsuru!
Kin-chan?
Kin-chan!
They said the people and houses
that got swallowed...
...could have formed a new town
in the boar's stomach.
A quarter of the capital was destroyed,
but miraculously, no one died.
Oden, that was so cool...
So cool that I almost screamed...
I at least wanna say thank you!
But I can't!
This is all his fault! He's evil!
Everyone, listen up!
What really happened was...
Don't even think about it!
Oden-sama!
NOTICE OF DISAVOWAL
So this is from my father...
I'm sorry to give you this
at a time of revelry...
I see. So I'm disavowed
and expelled from the capital!
This is laughable, Shogun-dono!
I guess you and the Flower Capital
cannot handle me anymore!
I accept the disavowal!
I'm leaving!
When night falls, wherever I am is where I'll sleep!
Oh, I'm hungry!
The mountain god incident in the Land of Wano
happened when Oden was still young.
Are you crying, Kin-chan?
I'm not crying at all!
Otsuru, I would die for him!
You're crying!
Me, too! I would die for him!
Hey! Wait, Denjiro!
Oh, Kin-chan!
Kozuki Oden! Kozuki Oden! Kozuki Oden!
He's really something!
I've decided!
I'm gonna follow him for the rest of my life!
I was fascinated with him first!
Not as much as I was!
I'm his first follower!
I wish I was free like them!
They said because the men took a step forward,
but restrained themselves from following Oden,
the capital leaned slightly forward...
HAKUMAI
Please come in, Oden-sama!
What an honor to see you!
Yasuie-sama has been waiting for you!
Don't lie! I know he's not!
SHIMOTSUKI YASUIE
DAIMYO OF HAKUMAI
Why would I wait to see a fool...
...who was expelled from the capital?!
What do you want, Oden?!
With those followers, you think you are someone?
Hey, Uncle!
Don't speak to me like that!
Oh, wait! There is a puddle of water!
Please go ahead and step
on my back to cross over!
He creeps me out!
He is a new servant.
That's right! Yasuie-sama took me in!
KUROZUMI OROCHI
My name is Orochi and I'm a servant.
What?! Oden-san, are you leaving?!
There'll be less trouble, but we'll miss him.
I heard there is a monster living in Kuri.
His name is Ashura Doji!
Kuri is a cancer in the Land of Wano...
Even Sukiyaki-sama cannot handle it.
Once a criminal takes refuge in Kuri,
the authorities cannot catch him.
But if he is not strong enough,
he will not be able to survive there.
The region is lawless
and is altogether like a different country...
Interesting! I'm going
to tour the Land of Wano!
Oden! Take care!
Kin! Denjiro! Come visit us again!
See you!
He comes and goes as he likes.
He is very free...
Yasuie-sama!
We have a problem!
Look at the room he stayed in!
What did he do to it?!
We must charge him for the repairs!
Well, let's just pretend
we were struck by a natural disaster...
You're too soft on him!
Yasuie-sama!
What now?
Money is missing?!
Yes! It was surely in the safe!
Um...
It pains me to say this...
but I saw it!
Um, Oden-sama tucked the money away
in his inside breast pocket...
I knew he did it!
He bit the hands that fed him!
It's unforgivable!
I think Oden would take it openly.
Are you sure, Orochi?
Yes! I'm sorry!
I was scared and I couldn't stop him!
After leaving Hakumai, Oden's group
kept causing trouble all over the Land of Wano...
...as they headed towards Kuri!
How much longer are you gonna follow me?!
--Forever!
--We like you so much!
He's annoyed!
Hey! Why are you standing there?!
We're your retainers, we guard you!
Come in, you idiots!
Oden-san!
What are you doing?
I'm writing a journal.
I heard navigators overseas write one every day
on their ships.
The following are Oden's words in his journal
about this journey.
RINGO
In Ringo,
we met some starving, ragged little runts.
IZO - A SON OF A FORMER HANAYANAGI DANCE MASTER
KIKUNOJO - IZO'S LITTLE BROTHER
Go away!
They were trying to earn money by dancing,
but people were so cold.
Why are you guys following me?!
Stop eating, you brats!
--I want more.
--I said stop!
Don't give him anymore!
They said they were sons of a dance master,
but their father got arrested
and their family broke up.
They brazenly ate our oden without my permission
while sobbing.
KIBI
In Kibi, there was a ghoul that cut living people's hair
as well as dead people's hair and took it.
He was a freak
who made brushes and sold them to make a living.
KANJURO - GHOUL OF KIBI
Whoa! I give up! I give up! I give up!
I thought you were a dead person!
He came after my hair so I punched him,
but then he followed me.
He claimed to have suffered persecution in the past
although he deserved it.
UDON
In the forest-covered Udon,
people were talking about a notorious mountain bandit.
They said women would be abducted
and men would be badly beaten.
Why are you following me?!
Isn't that right?
Is that the mountain bandit?!
Oden-sama!
RAIZO
A FORMER MEMBER OF KOZUKI CLAN'S ONIWABANSHU
He quit the Kozuki Clan's Oniwabanshu...
...after a kunoichi broke his heart.
He is a gifted ninja, Raizo.
I do not want to live my life hiding anymore!
He is annoyed!
LAWLESS LAND OF KURI
ASHURA DOJI - STRONGEST MONSTER IN KURI
Kozuki Oden came to Kuri?
He's a son of the Shogun...
I wanna kill him myself!
Catch him and bring him here!
Yes, sir!
The people in power... We hate them the most!
Where's Oden-san?
He went south of here to take a dump.
That was yesterday.
He sometimes disappears
on a whim for one or two days, right?
Hey Raizo!
There's a gate to Kuri in the south!
What?!
Oh, no! I was determined to die for him,
but I let him go to the battlefield by himself!
KURI
That place was filled with the stench of
death, blood, and violence!
It was like a different world.
They all had an urge to kill me!
I'll lop off your head, Kozuki Oden!
Oden tames a lawless land
and the Akazaya members are transformed!
Soon after, Oden becomes the Daimyo!
But something that adds fresh fuel to
his already eventful life occurs!
Will it change Oden's destiny?
That pirate group finally comes to the Land of Wano!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Changing Destiny! The Whitebeard Pirates Cast Ashore!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!