Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Catch the wind
kaze ni nore
Don't give up, if I'm determined
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
I'll never turn back
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
waraitobase aranami
Laugh on through troubled waters
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Shout it out, to save
your spirit from breaking
nakama ga irun da
Your friends are there for you
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Even when the darkness
tries to tear you apart
hora Brave it out
Come on, brave it out
daijoubu sa
It's going to be all right
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Strong bonds will break through
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Have the courage to take a step forward
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
chikai atsumeta hata
The flag that called forth oaths
tatakai tsudukete iku
Keep fighting on
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Stay true to yourself
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
Seize it, dreamin' on
makerarenai nige ya shinai
I can't lose, I'll never run away
deai wakare koe ikou
Transcend meetings and
partings and keep going
zenbu takaramono
They're all treasures
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Have the courage to take a step forward
ko wo agete
Raise your fist
"Whitebeard's Little Brother!
Oden's Great Adventure!"
Are you all right?!
What? Oh, yes, I am.
Don't tell me...
...you came to save me?!
Yeah, that's right...
I'm glad... that you're okay...
A-Are you all right?!
Stay with me!
Please stay with me!
Oden's gone!
Where did he go?!
Damn! There were only a few minutes to go!
It's a shame,
but he couldn't take it any longer!
Pops! You did a terrible thing to him!
He did his best!
Why didn't you let him pass?!
Oden-sama!
Hey, stop!
--Get off of me!
--Calm down!
What should we do, Pops?!
--Unhand me!
--Stop! Calm down!
--Let go!
--Relax!
Oden-sama! Oden-sama!
Oden-sama!
He is recovering so fast!
I could not tell, but he is a human...
Man!
I couldn't get on board Whitebeard's ship!
I thought if I could board it,
I could go to various countries...
But that's okay!
I set foot on a foreign island
for the first time instead!
I did it!
Look at him...
He looks so happy!
I finally got out of the Land of Wano!
My adventure has begun!
All right!
Do not move around so much!
You are not fully recovered yet.
Miss! Looks like you took care of me!
Oh, yes, I did!
Thank you!
No! You saved me first!
Thank you very much!
Oh, I see! I'm glad that you're okay!
Anyway, did you say
you came from the Land of Wano?
Yeah, that's right...
By the way, Miss...
I came all the way to a foreign land,
but look at your outfit.
I wish you wore something a bit more exotic!
The truth is I have always wanted to go to the Land of Wano
since I was little!
Will you take me to the Land of Wano?!
Oh... Um...
Oh, well...
He is annoyed!
There she is!
We're counting on you, Captain Karma!
KARMA - CAPTAIN OF THE CEPHALOCTOPUS PIRATES
Six arms?! How interesting!
I've never seen such a person in the Land of Wano!
Hey, where's the monster
that you guys encountered?!
What? It's got to be...
Did it vanish?!
Where did the Sea Spirit go?!
Hey, guys! You came back!
Who the hell are you?!
Why do you know about us?!
What are you talking about?!
I see... You hired a bodyguard!
Classy women fetch high prices!
We'll sell both of you!
Let's run!
There are too many of them!
This is my first fight overseas...
All right!
I'm getting excited!
Go to hell!
Is that all you've got?!
Impressive!
What a useless bodyguard!
It's time for me to finish you off!
It's the Whitebeard Pirates!
This man, Karma, eventually became a subordinate
of the Whitebeard Pirates,
and fought in the Paramount War.
Come aboard, Oden!
What? But I let go of the chain...
A woman's scream made you
give up your ambition?
You're kind of naive.
All right, let's go!
We'll set out on a great adventure
beyond your wildest imagination!
My little brother!
Are you sure, White-Kichi-chan?!
White-Kichi-chan?!
Let's go!
Oden!
I'm glad that you're okay!
Good to see you again!
We're happy to have you!
Thank you all!
Pops gave you a pretty rough time!
He totally did!
Absolutely!
Y-You fools!
O-Oden-sama!
I am glad that you are all right!
Yeah! As you see, I'm fine!
Oden-sama!
Dogstorm! Cat Viper!
Why are you here?!
We were sure that you'd board this ship somehow,
so we were hiding in it!
We'll follow you wherever you go!
Stowaways!
Pops! What should we do about them?!
You said you wouldn't forgive me...
So are you going to throw us into the sea?!
I'll do so when I feel like it!
Miss! What's your name?
Oh, yes!
My name is Toki!
Um...
I want to go to the Land of Wano!
He is annoyed!
I-I would do anything! So please!
Let me stay on board this ship!
Do as you like!
I'll welcome you, Oden!
Me, too!
A great adventure
beyond my wildest imagination, huh?
It'll finally start!
Oden-sama!
All right! Let's go!
I'm gonna see the world!
The things I see and hear overseas...
I will write them down in my journal.
Hostile vessel ahead!
Get ready to fight!
Here we go! Here we go!
Hey, wait!
--Stop!
--Oden!
Look at that! You see?!
I sank it!
You idiot! What are you doing?!
How can you call yourself a pirate?!
We didn't have a chance to plunder it!
W-What have I done?!
I-I'm sorry!
Things I have never experienced before...
What's this place?!
Buildings I've never seen!
The jelly-like jiggly trees!
--Oden, wait!
--We must examine the place first!
This world I have never seen...
I-Is that...?!
Oden!
A chill I have never experienced...
Ow, ow, ow...
A heat I have never experienced...
Oden!
Are you okay?!
Ouch!
This is an adventure! An adventure!
Strange plants...
Strange animals...
Giant humans...
So big!
Back off!
All right!
Overwhelming strength...
And ideas...
Everything is different from before
and each day is an eye-opening experience!
Everything is beyond my imagination!
I am only a tiny piece of the world!
How old am I?
I am 26 years old.
26 years old!
That's a perfect age to get married!
But I was born about 800 years ago.
It's been 800 years since you were born?!
You're seriously old!
Well, even that is possible.
The world is big. Anything could happen!
This world consists entirely of
four seas and a band of ocean.
And I heard that the world is round
like a rice cake ball!
How intriguing!
Toki, how's the voyage?
I am having a good time.
I want to see more of the world!
I see! It's good to hear that!
Is that a map?
Yeah...
SOUTH BLUE   EAST BLUE
WEST BLUE   NORTH BLUE
In the world so vast, the
Land of Wano is tiny.
Where were you born, Toki?
I don't know...
All I know is my parents
were from the Land of Wano.
That is why the Land of Wano
is the only place I want to go...
But this ship probably won't go there
for a while...
I'm sorry...
That is fine! It is so fun to be with you!
When I am with you,
I feel like I am right where I want to be!
--I wonder why...
--Yeah, I do not know why either...
--It's strange...
--Yes, it is strange!
Hey!
Where's Oden-sama?
Over there?
Don't go, stupid cat!
Even Whitebeard has a sworn enemy...
It's the Navy! Get away!
Did we shake them off?
Why did we have to flee?!
They looked strong!
We should fight them!
They're the Navy!
They think they carry the justice of the whole world
on their shoulders...
It's a big organization.
Even if we take them down today,
more and more of them will come.
So it's the organization
that governs the world?!
There are such mighty people!
Wait until you see the world
to judge their might...
Your country is still free!
28 YEARS AGO
SECOND YEAR OF ODEN'S JOURNEY
28 years ago, the second
year of Oden's journey...
The baby was born!
Tamago!
Konbu!
Chikuwa!
Tsukune!
Hey, stop!
I can come up with something better than that!
It's Toki's and my child!
The word stands for peerless...
Your name is Kozuki Momonosuke!
There are even wanted posters for Oden-sama.
You are now considered a criminal overseas.
If you care about Toki-sama
and Momonosuke-sama,
why don't you consider returning
to the Land of Wano?
But, Izo, I haven't found the answer yet!
We will be fine. Do not worry!
There is a thing called a newspaper,
but we can't get any information about the Land of Wano...
They have no way to share information
regarding their country, just like Zou...
I wonder how Kin and the
others are doing-meow...
Meanwhile, in the Land of Wano...
Special Report! Special Report!
The Shogun Sukiyaki-sama
is in critical condition!
--Sukiyaki-sama is...
--...in critical condition?!
Sukiyaki-sama!
I want Oden to succeed me as Shogun.
Of course, Sukiyaki-sama!
But since Oden is not here now,
I need a proxy until Oden returns,
in case anything happens to me.
A proxy?
It will be this man
who Oden cared for as if he was his little brother...
His name is Kurozumi Orochi!
Orochi?!
Why are you here?!
Oden cared for as if he
was his little brother?!
What?! You'll assign commanders?!
We have more crewmembers now.
What do you think of
dividing them up into five groups?
That's a good idea, Pops!
I wanna be a commander!
Me, too!
Oden!
I want you to lead the 2nd division!
Well... Um... Uh... Um...
Do it!
Just like we did,
sometimes a newcomer joins the group...
Listen! We're no fishermen! We're pirates!
P-Please!
I've got no place to go!
Hey! Stop it!
What's your name?
Teech!
All right. Come aboard!
Thank you very much!
We have got another orphan...
Did you see it?! Something's flying!
No matter how far I go on the sea,
I am never satisfied!
Commander!
We must examine the place first!
I do not know how to end an adventure!
Nothing in the papers again...
Is this a story on Whitebeard again?!
We're causing trouble, too!
Hey! I'm still reading!
Anyway, the samurai from the Land of Wano
who serves Whitebeard is still
doing reckless things...
Captain!
A samurai from a closed country...
I hope I'll get to see him one day!
GOLD ROGER - A GREAT PIRATE
He is unstoppable!
Oden becomes infamous as a pirate
and Gol D. Roger, the great pirate
taking the world by storm, closes in!
Their search for the strong leads to
a spark-flying fateful encounter,
and Boss Whitebeard can't stand by!
A huge battle involving
troops on both sides starts!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Crossing Swords! Roger and Whitebeard!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!