Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Catch the wind
kaze ni nore
Don't give up, if I'm determined
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
I'll never turn back
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
Laugh on through troubled waters
waraitobase aranami
Shout it out, to save your spirit from breaking
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Your friends are there for you
nakama ga irun da
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Even when the darkness tries to tear you apart
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Come on, brave it out
hora Brave it out
It's going to be all right
daijoubu sa
Strong bonds will break through
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
The flag that called forth oaths
chikai atsumeta hata
Keep fighting on
tatakai tsudukete iku
Stay true to yourself
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Seize it, dreamin' on
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
I can't lose, I'll never run away
makerarenai nige ya shinai
Transcend meetings and partings and keep going
deai wakare koe ikou
They're all treasures
zenbu takaramono
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Raise your fist
ko wo agete
In order to ride Whitebeard's ship,
Oden pushed himself to his limits,
but he was swallowed up by the sea
at the last minute,
and drifted ashore on an unknown island
where he met a woman.
It's Toki's and my child!
The word stands for peerless...
Your name is Kozuki Momonosuke!
A samurai from a closed country...
I hope I'll get to see him one day!
"Crossing Swords!
Roger and Whitebeard!"
Sukiyaki-sama...
Big news!
The Shogun, Sukiyaki-sama, is in critical condition!
Sukiyaki-sama!
In the Land of Wano,
a serious matter occurred
which brought the Daimyo of each region to the Flower Capital.
I want Oden to succeed me as Shogun.
Of course, Sukiyaki-sama!
But since Oden is not here now,
I need a proxy until Oden returns,
in case anything happens to me.
It will be this man
who Oden cared for as if he was his little brother...
His name is Kurozumi Orochi!
Orochi?!
Why are you here?!
Oden cared for as if he was his little brother?
Really?!
Thank you for giving me this opportunity
to clear Kurozumi's name!
I would never be able to look Sukiyaki-sama
and Oden-sama in the eye!
To compensate for my grandfather's foolish act
and for other things,
I will assist
Oden-sama's enthronement to the best of my ability!
I will temporarily become
a puppet until Oden-sama's return,
so I must ask for everyone's support!
If this is Sukiyaki-sama's decision,
there is no way we can disobey it.
My lord!
Orochi.
So you're Kurozumi....
Why didn't you tell me?
Oh, I am sorry!
I am sorry...
KUROZUMI OROCHI'S PAST
Hey, wait! Damn you!
Kurozumi!
Kurozumi! Where did you go?!
He's fast when running away!
Oh, there he is! Kurozumi!
--Catch him!
--Wait!
Damn! Damn!
Damn!!
Where are you, Kurozumi?!
The Kurozumi Clan needs to be exterminated!
Damn!
We can't let him get away!
The Kurozumi Clan is the vermin of the Land of Wano!
I'm sure he's still around here.
We must find him and kill him!
Yeah!
Kurozumi! You people are all criminals!
We'll make you pay for your crime!
Come on out!
Why do I have to go through this
because of what that old geezer of mine did?!
Why do I have to be hated
just for being a Kurozumi?
Damn!
Damn! Damn!
You scared me! W-What do you want?!
I can see it! I can see the future!
You'll...
...become the Shogun!
Don't scare me, granny!
Who the hell are you?!
You don't know what happened to your grandfather?
I don't know the details,
but I heard he committed seppuku.
No! He was killed by Kozuki!
What?!
But I heard he committed some kind of crime!
Engaging in a power struggle
isn't a crime!
A power struggle?
If you take the reins,
you can make the laws.
You can legitimize any crime!
The previous Shogun from the Kozuki Clan
couldn't have children!
No heirs!
Five clans that served under the Kozuki Clan
became unsettled...
SHIMOTSUKI CLAN
Who is going to be the next Shogun?
KUROZUMI CLAN
UZUKI CLAN
While everyone was proudly thinking, "I am,"
AMATSUKI CLAN
FUGETSU CLAN
your grandfather was making preparations!
He was preparing to kill those annoying Daimyos
one by one with poison!
He got rid of them one after another
making them all look like inside jobs!
The Shogun stressed over
the series of Daimyo deaths,
and eventually became ill.
The plan went well!
When he was within reach of taking the reins...
He was born!
The heir, Kozuki Sukiyaki!
--Yes!
--We're overjoyed for you!
A curse on you, Sukiyaki!
Power was almost within his reach!
The Kurozumi Clan couldn't take the reins
and on top of that, the plan was exposed!
Your grandfather committed seppuku
and the clan was put to an end!
Their territory, castle, and power
were all taken away.
People grew to despise the name, Kurozumi,
and the members of the clan
ended up in the streets!
Whose fault is that?!
Who made your life so miserable?!
Who's responsible for your poverty?!
Whose fault is that?!
It's because he was born!
Kozuki Sukiyaki!
That's right!
If he wasn't born,
you'd have become the Shogun one day!
Shogun-sama!
I love you!
--Shogun-sama!
Shogun-sama!
What beauties!
I'd have become the Shogun?!
That's right!
Oh, how aggravating, how galling!
Don't tell me you're my...
the Kurozumi Clan's blood relative?!
It doesn't matter who I am!
I was out of the country all this time.
It was tough...
Watch my face.
What?!
Is that my face?!
It's the power of the Clone-Clone Fruit.
If you're gonna do as I tell you,
I'll give you special power.
The power you need to become the Shogun!
I'll do it...
I'll do anything!
Save money and produce weapons.
The craftsmen in the Land of Wano
have great skill!
Use them as bait
to win the backing of someone important!
I understand!
HAKUMAI
My name is Orochi.
My whole family has fallen ill,
so I must feed them all somehow...
I feel sorry for you. You can work here.
Thank you very much!
A MONTH LATER
Yasuie-sama!
What? Orochi has disappeared?
Yes, sir.
And I think it's just a coincidence,
but the money in the safe is gone, too...
What?
The money is gone, too?!
KURI
I met you at Yasu-san's place...
My name is Orochi! Yes, yes.
The thing is my family's illness got worse,
and I need money...
Oh...
I owe Yasuie-sama so much,
I can't borrow money from him...
Uh-huh. I see. Count on me.
--Oden-sama?!
--Thank you!
Lend me money!
Again?!
Please lend me money!
I can pay you back for sure this time!
I'm begging you!
Oden-sama!
We are not doing well financially, either!
He says he's gonna pay it back!
Is this enough?!
No, it's not even close to being enough
to produce a massive amount of weapons!
I know a place that has more money...
The next target is...
FLOWER CAPITAL
KOZUKI SUKIYAKI (ODEN'S FATHER)
Oden?! Why did you suddenly come?!
SHOGUN OF THE LAND OF WANO
And without your retainers.
I came to ask you a favor.
Could you let him stay here?!
He works hard and can prepare medicine.
He's like my little brother.
My name is Orochi.
Everyone, take good care of Orochi!
Aye-aye, sir!
The Shogun Sukiyaki!
I've finally made it this far!
YEARS LATER
Sukiyaki-sama! Stay with us!
--Sukiyaki-sama!
If anything happens to me...
I'm counting on you, Orochi!
Yes, certainly!
You, too, guys.
Support Orochi for me.
Yes, sir.
Sukiyaki-sama!
--I-I'll go get a doctor!
--We'll be right back!
Help! Is somebody there?!
Get a doctor!
Sukiyaki-sama! Are you all right?!
Sukiyaki-sama!
Take care of everything, Orochi!
You mustn't be so weak, Sukiyaki-sama!
You're gonna become the Shogun!
Not so long afterward,
the news of the Shogun Sukiyaki's death
spread across the Land of Wano.
One day in the fourth year of Oden's journey...
What?!
What's going on?!
The fish are going crazy!
Is this a premonition of a natural disaster?!
They're heading away from that island,
White-Kichi-chan!
Yeah.
Maybe some kind of monster lives there.
Marco, go check!
No way! I don't wanna spoil the fun!
Don't worry, Hiyori!
Momonosuke, it's nothing!
Should we check it out, Pops?
Yeah...
Let's go ashore!
Yeah!
What? You've got to be kidding!
Are those savage animals running away?
Something's got to be on this island...
If you wanna catch me,
bring Garp or Sengoku!
It's no fun fighting against you guys!
Captain!
There's Whitebeard's ship
on the opposite side of the island!
Seems like they noticed us!
We just finished fighting, Roger.
Whitebeard, huh? It's been a while.
The birds seem distressed...
They must've come ashore.
All right!
Let's do it! We're only able to fight each other
while we draw breath!
My end is nearing!
This could be the last time I see you,
Whitebeard!
Who's that?! He runs so fast!
Is he a samurai?!
A samurai?!
That one everyone's talking about?!
Catch up already!
Commander Oden! Wait!
Should I plunder their treasure?!
This is a totally different situation!
The Roger Pirates are dangerous!
He's not listening at all!
Gun Modoki!
He's as strong as they say.
Should we stop him already, Rayleigh?
Yeah!
Wait, Gaban, Rayleigh!
I don't want you to get hurt!
You just wanna fight him.
I smell a beast!
Hey, samurai!
Divine Departure!
What the hell was that?!
Damn! I can't let that slide!
Here he comes!
They aren't touching each other!
Roger's earnest desire!
His dream to get to the last island on the Grand Line!
The key is the forbidden cultural heritage
of the Ponegliffs and Kozuki Oden!
Led by fate, these mighty two team up
and set sail for the place where no one has gone before!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Roger's Wish! A New Journey!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!