Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Catch the wind
kaze ni nore
Don't give up, if I'm determined
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
I'll never turn back
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
Laugh on through troubled waters
waraitobase aranami
Shout it out, to save
your spirit from breaking
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Your friends are there for you
nakama ga irun da
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Even when the darkness
tries to tear you apart
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Come on, brave it out
hora Brave it out
It's going to be all right
daijoubu sa
Strong bonds will break through
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
The flag that called forth oaths
chikai atsumeta hata
Keep fighting on
tatakai tsudukete iku
Stay true to yourself
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Seize it, dreamin' on
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
I can't lose, I'll never run away
makerarenai nige ya shinai
Transcend meetings and
partings and keep going
deai wakare koe ikou
They're all treasures
zenbu takaramono
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Raise your fist
ko wo agete
After Oden joined, the Whitebeard
Pirates arrived an island
where the Roger Pirates happened to be.
Captain!
There's Whitebeard's ship
on the opposite side of the island!
Seems like they noticed us!
We just finished fighting, Roger.
Whitebeard, huh? It's been a while.
The birds seem distressed...
They must've come ashore.
All right!
Let's do it! We're only able to fight each other
while we draw breath!
My end is nearing!
This could be the last time I see you,
Whitebeard!
Gun Modoki!
He's as strong as they say.
Should we stop him already, Rayleigh?
Yeah!
Wait, Gaban, Rayleigh!
I don't want you to get hurt!
You just wanna fight him.
I smell a beast!
Hey, samurai!
Divine Departure!
What the hell was that?!
Here he comes!
"Roger's Wish!
A New Journey!"
You look great!
Roger!
How long has it been?!
Newgate!
MARCO
VISTA
JOZU
ANDRE
RAKUYO
FOSSA
WHITEY BAY
TEECH
RAYLEIGH
GABAN
NOZUDON
SAMBEL
SHANKS AND BUGGY
Whatever you've got, hand it over!
Get them!
Rob them!
The two great pirates of the age clashed!
The Roger Pirates vs. the Whitebeard Pirates.
SECOND DAY
The tense, fraught battle lasted
three days and three nights.
Don't push your luck!
I'm always serious.
Young man.
THIRD DAY
Then, three boxes of
dried meat for a barrel?!
FOURTH DAY...
Deal!
I like this shirt! Where did you get it?!
--Let me have more!
--Wait! You took too much!
It's basically an equal exchange!
Sorry.
You've got something, too, right?
Yeah!
We were trying to plunder each other,
but now it's a gift exchange...
Are they apprentices?
Come to think of it, they
were always with us...
They don't look strong...
But they behave...
...like veterans.
Hey, Shanks!
What?
You see the guy with the hat over there?
Yeah.
I heard he didn't sleep yesterday or the day before
during the ceasefire at night!
Why? He wanted to show off?!
No!
They say he's never slept even once
since he was born!
What? Is there such a person?
That's great. I wonder if he enjoys life
twice as much as us!
Idiot! It's not that simple!
--He must be a monster!
--A monster?
Hey, Oden! Can you really read it?!
Yes, I can.
I can read it, but why do
you have this writing?!
Knowledge of this script has
been passed down from father to
only one son per generation
in the Kozuki Clan.
It's already been 13 years...
We finally made it to Lodestar Island,
the last island that the Log Pose points to,
which no man has ever set foot upon.
LODESTAR ISLAND
But we noticed when we
cheerfully disembarked...
...that that wasn't the last island!
The needles on the Log Pose just kept spinning
and didn't point to anywhere!
I was convinced.
There was one more island!
When I make it there,
I'll be the first person ever to travel all around the world!
And the location of the island is detailed
in the writings on four of these red stones!
But the World Government has always forbidden anyone
from deciphering them.
They are called Ponegliffs.
I thought they were just cultural artifacts,
LODESTAR ISLAND
but they were actually
an important map for us
which indicates the location
of the last island.
The Government is telling us
not to go to the last island
which could hold a vast amount of treasure!
That makes it even more tantalizing!
If we can get there,
we'll be in both name and deed...
...the world's greatest pirate group!
The world's greatest?
You must be surprised, Newgate!
That's right! Then I'll...
I could not move.
I was amazed for the second time today.
What is with this guy?!
What are you talking about, Roger?!
That's a child's fantasy!
I'm serious, Newgate!
Please!
Just for a year will do.
Let me borrow Oden!
This is a once-in-a-lifetime request!
With him, I'm sure I can
get to the last island!
Hey, don't be selfish!
Please, Newgate!
I'm begging you!
Hey, stop, Captain Roger! He's our enemy!
Stop! That's pathetic!
Don't bow your head!
Please, Oden!
Accompany us on our journey
just for a year!
Screw you!
Roger! Are you trying to
take my family member away from me?!
But I could not help feeling excited!
Why can the Kozuki Clan read the script?
Did I meet him now for a reason?
Before I knew it,
the words popped out of my mouth!
White-Kichi-chan!
I wanna go!
Please allow me to go!
I wanna see the last island
that he talked about!
He's annoyed!
Of course, I am!
You and I are like brothers!
It's just for a year, White-Kichi-chan!
Please!
Take care!
Yeah!
We are going to stay!
We like this ship.
We will wait for your return here.
Sure thing.
You guys are full-fledged pirates now.
Let's do as we like!
Pops! Aren't you gonna send him off?
Roger left us gifts in thanks.
A huge amount of treasure!
An immense quantity of food!
What?!
You idiots!
Give the food back to them!
I won't forgive them
if they let Kozuki Oden's family go hungry!
Hurry up!
--Yes!
--Right away!
Oden-sama!
See you!
Everyone!
Do your best!
Can't wait to hear the story of your journey!
Take care!
The second chapter of my life as a pirate...
A new adventure began!
White-Kichi-chan is great,
but Roger has incalculable depth, too.
I'm so lucky!
Oh, good girl, good girl.
Up, up!
We haven't held a baby for a long time!
Yeah, it brings back memories.
Momonosuke and Hiyori, huh!
Peek, peek-a-boo!
--There, up you go!
--Good boy, good boy...
Okay? Here we go! Boo!
--What the?!
--Something's in here!
Huh?! What is it?!
Captain Roger! We have a stowaway!
Oden-sama!
Dogstorm!
Cat Viper!
Why are you here?!
We enjoy hanging out with Oden-sama
more than anything!
White-Kichi-chan must be mad by now!
The dog and the cat have disappeared!
Those fools!
I know this wasn't the plan,
but can they stay, too?
I think you have the wrong idea.
Oden. Captain is only using you
for your knowledge.
Understood?
MOCK TOWN, JAYA
Hey, have you gotten money, Shanks?!
Yeah, let's go buy food!
Potatoes and...
...burdock!
I'll take these.
Where's my money?!
Mister?!
Next, radishes!
Thief! Hey, wait!
He's stealing from an ordinary citizen!
Captain's gonna kill him.
That fool!
Oden! Don't mess with ordinary people!
I need more ingredients!
Ingredients for what?!
Egg! Konnyaku!
Chikuwa! Beef tendon!
Thief!
Hey, I said you must pay
money to ordinary people!
I wanna cook super delicious
oden for you guys!
Oden is food?!
Yeah! It's the most delicious meal
in the Land of Wano!
There he is! It's him!
You've got some nerve!
What?! Is this town lawless?
Gaban, they're...
Yeah, they don't look like ordinary people.
Oden!
Run, Oden!
He took it full on!
Oden!
Oden! You...
He's alive!
Wow!
Gaban, they're not ordinary people, right?
No, they're not...
Oden.
Okay.
I haven't gotten kelp yet.
--Kelp?!
--I can make good broth out of it.
You're so strange.
Gee! Who cares!
Get them!
It smells good!
Okay! I think it's ready.
This is the Land of Wano's...
...most delicious meal!
All right, everyone, dig in!
How is it? Is it delicious?
So delicious!
I didn't know that oden is so good!
It's the perfect drinking food!
Good! So you like it!
It's too hot!
Your tongue's too sensitive!
Guys!
Let's have a big welcome party
for our new members!
Yeah!
Oden!
Roger!
Let's party all night!
Yeah!
Oden!
Oh, radish, ganmo!
Chikuwa and eggs!
One, two, three, go ahead and eat!
Oden wouldn't be oden...
...if it wasn't boiled!
Yo! Kozuki!
A big, crazy adventure,
singing out loud with jolly crewmembers!
Soaring up into the sky and being excited
by the mystery at the sea bottom.
Oden deciphers the secret of the world which
will lead them to the farthest
land the Ponegliffs hint at!
Keep going!
The Roger Pirates advance!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Devoting His Life! Roger's Adventure!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!