mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
kaze ni nore
Catch the wind
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
Don't give up, if I'm determined
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
I'll never turn back
waraitobase aranami
Laugh on through troubled waters
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Shout it out, to save
your spirit from breaking
nakama ga irun da
Your friends are there for you
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Even when the darkness
tries to tear you apart
hora Brave it out
Come on, brave it out
daijoubu sa
It's going to be all right
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Strong bonds will break through
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
The flag that called forth oaths
chikai atsumeta hata
Keep fighting on
tatakai tsudukete iku
Stay true to yourself
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Seize it, dreamin' on
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
I can't lose, I'll never run away
makerarenai nige ya shinai
Transcend meetings and
partings and keep going
deai wakare koe ikou
They're all treasures
zenbu takaramono
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Raise your fist
ko wo agete
The battle between the Roger Pirates
and the Whitebeard Pirates lasted three days and three nights,
and turned into a banquet at the end.
At the same time, Roger found out
that Oden could read the script on the Road Ponegliff
which details the location
of the last island...
Just for a year will do.
Let me borrow Oden!
Please, Newgate!
I'm begging you!
Screw you!
Roger! Are you trying to
take my family member away from me?!
White-Kichi-chan!
I wanna go!
Please allow me to go!
"Devoting His Life!
Roger's Adventure!"
Gather up all of the crew!
Time to ship out Binks's Brew!
Sea wind blows to where, who knows?
The waves will be our guide!
O'er across the ocean's tide,
the sunset is goin' wild
See the sky! Birds singing
in circles passing by!
Bid farewell to weaver's town!
Say so long to port renowned!
Sing a song, it won't be long
before we're casting off!
Cross the gold and silver waves,
changin' into water sprays!
Sailing out on our journey
to the ends of the sea!
I like this ship.
Me, too...
I wanna travel like this forever!
Yes, as long as time allows...
Do it now!
Shut up! Don't move!
Hm? Captain, did you catch a cold?
Yeah, but it's nothing.
It is something, you fool!
He's only got a year to live at most!
What?!
I'm living life at top speed.
The Log Pose is pointing at the sky...
Is it broken?
It's not... Let's go.
Go where?
To the sky!
It's coming... The Knock Up Stream!
I'm gonna die!
There's an island!
So that's...
The Sky Island!
Welcome, all the way from the Blue Sea.
--Heso!
The world is big! There is
still so much more to it!
Even Buddha couldn't imagine
that there were people living in the sky!
It takes at least 10 years to handle a waver.
Run!
So this is the City of Gold, Shandora!
Wow!
"Hold our true motive in your hearts
and speak not of it.
We are the ones who weave history...
With the sounding of the grand belfry..."
The grand belfry?
I found it!
This is where it was?!
This must be Shandora's grand belfry!
It's pure gold!
Captain, how should we take it?!
I don't have time.
Once you become a captain,
come get it yourself, Buggy.
What?! At least a piece of it now!
This stone is easy to find
since it has a strong voice inside.
It's talking about a great power, isn't it?
The writing is about a weapon named Poseidon.
I see...
Oden, you can also write the script, right?!
Yes, of course.
Then carve this message!
Roger is near the end of his life...
It is hard to believe, but if
he is living with such urgency,
I will accompany him all the way!
How is it?
Mm-hm... It's perfect, Oden!
"I made it here. I will guide
this text to the ends of the earth.
Pirate Gol D. Roger."
I must see it, Roger.
The final chapter of the great adventure
that you're devoting your life to!
Guys! Let's go back to the Blue Sea!
Yeah!
Heso!
If nothing is done,
we'll be smashed against the waves and broken to bits!
Here we go!
Skypiea's famous Octo-Balloon!
An octopus?!
Damn!
What the?!
What? What?
--It's a balloon!
--How interesting!
The octopus is deflating!
Ouch!
It's cold!
--That was scary-meow.
--Was it an air leak?
We managed to come down alive...
With the help of Ganfor, the god above the clouds,
we reached the sea safely.
It's the North Pole!
No, it's the South Pole!
--The North Pole!
--The South Pole!
You gonna keep it up?!
Yes, I am! Because I'm right!
Enough!
You guys fight all the time!
Who cares which one is colder,
the North Pole or the South Pole!
If you really wanna know,
go to both places and see yourself!
Cool your heads, idiots!
I wanna go to both the North
Pole and the South Pole!
Roger, where should we go next?
Of course, our destination is
the last island on the Grand Line!
But to get there,
we need copies of all four Road Ponegliffs.
The stone that we found on the Sky Island?
There is one in the Land of Wano.
Our Mokomo Dukedom has one, too-meow.
Those countries you guys are from
have that stone?!
Unlike the one on the Sky Island...
It's red though!
That's the one I wanted most!
Why didn't you tell me?!
So we'll have two out of four!
No, I've got a copy of Linlin's Road Ponegliff
which I took by force.
And I think I know where
the remaining one is.
Great, Roger!
Yeah, I can't believe it!
We'll really have all four!
Sorry to ruin the fun,
but something is wrong with the ship.
What?!
With my untrained eye,
I can't tell what is broken.
--Okay, I know where we should go.
--Where?
Water Seven, the City of Water!
--The City of Water?
--Sounds romantic!
Guys, let's go!
Yeah!
Thus, we headed for the shipbuilding town
to repair the ship.
An island!
I see an island!
W-What's that?!
That's Water Seven!
WATER SEVEN, CITY OF WATER, GRAND LINE
I've never seen such massive water magic!
Those are fountains.
The ones they have here sure are gigantic.
This place is beautiful.
The City of Water, huh?
Nice.
TOM - SHIPWRIGHT WHO BUILT ROGER'S SHIP
You made it here like, "boom"! Roger!
Tom!
Tom-san!
It's been a while, guys!
Yeah, I missed you!
Have you completed the train?!
You mean the Sea Train?! No way!
I'm still designing it!
Now, what did you break?!
You only come here
when your ship needed repairs.
Yeah, it fell from a high place.
You went to the Sky Island?!
Yeah! Like, "boom"!
But after that, boom!
We fell to the sea!
I see.
KOKORO - A GOOD-LOOKING
SECRETARY, TOM'S WORKERS
You guys are as noisy as always!
Hey, Kokoro!
We wanna hear all about your journey,
but why don't you eat first?
Some food is ready for you!
Oh! You're working in your underwear,
what a high-spirited kid!
Don't bother me, go away!
Are you an orphan?!
Do you want me to introduce you to our Captain?
You guys are pirates, right?
So what?
Then, no!
I was just abandoned by pirates.
Abandoned?!
Bad timing!
Gather up all of the crew!
Time to ship out Binks's Brew!
Pirates we, we'll divide
and conquer all the seas!
With the waves to rest our heads,
ship beneath us as our bed!
Hoisted high up on the mast
our Jolly Roger flies!
Somewhere in the endless sky,
a storm has started comin' by!
Waves are dancing having fun,
it's time to sound the drums!
TEQUILA WOLF - A COUNTRY ON A BRIDGE
If we let blow winds of fear,
then the end of us is near!
Even so, tomor-row the sun will rise again!
SABAODY ARCHIPELAGO
Let's set sail!
The Fish-Man Island, huh?
I've been there with White-Kichi-chan!
Don't drop your guard!
No matter how many times you go,
your chances of dying won't change!
Will be born...
Our ruler will be born.
Rayleigh! Did you hear that?
What are you talking about?
It's the silent deep sea.
No, I can hear it, too.
You, too, Oden?
Who's talking this deep in the water?!
Toki! That's the Fish-Man Island!
How interesting...
It seems like the whole island is in a bubble...
That's...!
--The Fish-Man Tribe?!
--They're all around us!
What do you want, surface dwellers!
Depending on how you answer,
you might be exterminated!
NEPTUNE - KING OF THE RYUGU KINGDOM
Whoa, wait, wait. Look closer!
It's me! Roger! Great Knight Neptune!
Roger?
Oh, I see! So you guys are gonna do it!
We're not up to anything bad!
MERMAID INLET, RYUGU KINGDOM
Come on, why are you scared of a prophecy?
You're better than that!
The prophecy says someone will break
the gate of the Fish-Man Island soon!
And now you guys are here
so most likely...
Neptune-sama, it's been broken!
The Sea Kings chewed up the gate!
What?! The gentle Sea Kings did such a thing?!
It can't be true!
It came true...
--There is a hole in the outer bubble!
--Patch it up! Give it a quick fix!
We couldn't prevent it!
See?! It wasn't us!
SHARLEY - A PROPHET GIRL (THREE YEARS OLD)
The Sea Kings are going crazy because
they're waiting for the Mermaid Princess to be born.
The Mermaid Princess?!
That's another prophecy.
Then the king will have a baby?!
We have to celebrate!
Wait, wait! I'm not even married yet-jamon!
I was only enthroned a few months ago-jamon!
But Neptune-sama!
She even divined the day that
the former king would die!
And that sexy...
I mean, that hateful Mermaid Otohime's political demonstration
the other day was predicted by her, too!
Otohime?!
I-It's not like it brought me any comfort!
FOREST OF THE SEA, RYUGU KINGDOM
These days, the whole country is swayed
by that girl's prophecies...
We're not here to listen to your personal story,
Neptune!
Oh, that's right.
--How is it, Oden?
--Well...
There are two,
so I thought we could get a lot of information,
but one of them isn't so important.
It's an apology letter
from someone named Joyboy.
I can't believe it! He
really can read the script!
Yeah, by the way, do you have a weapon
to control the Sea Kings?!
A weapon?!
The Sky Island's stone says it's here.
The Ancient Weapon that has a god's name...
"Poseidon."
To tell you the truth...
I had a slight chill
when I heard Sharley's prophecy earlier-jamon.
Once every few centuries in this country,
a Mermaid who can talk
to the Sea Kings is born.
Maybe, that Mermaid is...
So your daughter will become the weapon
that will destroy the world someday?!
It's just a prophecy-jamon!
And even if it's called an Ancient Weapon,
it doesn't have to be used as one!
I never thought that Poseidon was a Mermaid!
Hey, Sharley,
when will the Mermaid Princess be born?
10!
I guess it's 10 years from now...
But, Roger, I can't believe you're interested in such a weapon!
I'm disappointed in you!
Neptune, what we want is the
vast amount of treasure that was left
by the people who called it a weapon!
Are you relieved?
We won't come to kidnap your hairy daughter
who'll be born someday!
She won't be hairy!
Gather up all of the crew!
Time to ship out Binks's Brew!
Could be today, could be
tomorrow. Twilight dreaming
No longer can we now see,
shadow hands still waving free
Why worry, there's sure to
be a moonlit night again
Gather up all of the crew!
Time to ship out Binks's Brew!
Sing a song, a lively song
for all the oceans wide!
After all is said and done,
we all end up skeletons!
Endless, aimless, this story
on the uproarious seas!
Unprecedented! Unreachable!
Roger nears his goal of traveling around the world!
He bolsters up his body
which is wracked by disease
and under the flag of the pledge,
he takes control of his own fate and navigates the sea.
At the farthest land of the Grand Line,
he becomes the conqueror of the sea and...
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The King of the Pirates is Born!
Arriving at the Last Island!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!