mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
kaze ni nore
Catch the wind
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
Don't give up, if I'm determined
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
I'll never turn back
waraitobase aranami
Laugh on through troubled waters
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Shout it out, to save your spirit from breaking
nakama ga irun da
Your friends are there for you
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Even when the darkness tries to tear you apart
hora Brave it out
Come on, brave it out
daijoubu sa
It's going to be all right
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Strong bonds will break through
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Have the courage to take a step forward
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
chikai atsumeta hata
The flag that called forth oaths
tatakai tsudukete iku
Keep fighting on
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Stay true to yourself
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
Seize it, dreamin' on
makerarenai nige ya shinai
I can't lose, I'll never run away
deai wakare koe ikou
Transcend meetings and partings and keep going
zenbu takaramono
They're all treasures
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Open the borderless map
hateshinai ano basho e
Towards the place that has no end
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Have the courage to take a step forward
ko wo agete
Raise your fist
Oden became a crewmember of the Roger Pirates
and proceeds along the Grand Line
to the last island.
The Sky Island!
I found it!
This is where it was?!
This must be Shandora's grand belfry!
"I made it here. I will guide
this text to the ends of the earth.
Pirate Gol D. Roger."
Have you completed the train?!
You mean the Sea Train?! No way!
I'm still designing it!
Will be born...
Our ruler will be born.
Toki! That's the Fish-Man Island!
How interesting...
It seems like the whole island is in a bubble...
I can't believe it! He really can read the script!
Yeah, by the way, do you have a weapon
to control the Sea Kings?!
Once every few centuries in this country,
a Mermaid who can talk to the Sea Kings is born.
Maybe, that Mermaid is...
So your daughter will become the weapon
that will destroy the world someday?!
I never thought that Poseidon was a Mermaid!
Hey, Sharley,
when will the Mermaid Princess be born?
10!
I guess it's 10 years from now...
Looking for the Road Ponegliff
that details the location of the last island,
Oden and the others headed for the Land of Wano.
"The King of the Pirates is Born!
Arriving at the Last Island!"
This sea looks familiar.
I didn't know the Road Ponegliff was
in your home country...
We're only a step away from the last island.
The last island.
A vast amount of treasure sits there!
Can't wait, huh? Roger!
Hard a starboard!
We're going to the Land of Wano!
Guys, get fired up!
Yeah!
Oden-san!
What's wrong, Redtaro?
Toki-san collapsed!
What?!
Toki!
You'll be fine! I'm here with you!
Oden...
Toki has been following you
and traveling the world,
but her original goal was the Land of Wano.
As the Land of Wano draws nearer,
she's lost some steam,
and the fatigue of the long journey has hit her.
Will she be able to keep on traveling?
If she continues, she could die.
She should get off the ship at the Land of Wano
and end her journey.
Oden-sama, in that case, you must leave
Momonosuke-sama and Hiyori-sama at the Land of Wano, too.
With Toki-sama.
Kin'emon and the others don't know Toki-sama well.
So Dogstorm and I will accompany her.
The place is unfamiliar to them,
so I'm sure they'll feel lonely.
Leave Toki-sama to us.
No, of course, I...
Toki?!
You should go, Oden-san!
What are you saying?!
Don't try to act strong!
"It is so restrictive."
What about those words?
That's all the passion you have for adventure?
If you quit over a little thing like this,
I...
...will dissolve our marriage!
KURI, LAND OF WANO
Why are you in such a hurry, Raizo?
Kin'emon!
A ship is coming from the outside world!
It's a pirate ship!
Could it be Oden-sama?!
It looks different from Whitebeard-dono's ship...
If they are pirates, we must fight back!
That is...
Oden-sama!
Guys!
It has been a while, Oden-sama!
Yeah!
You do not seem to have changed...
This is my wife and children.
What?! Guess some things have changed!
My name is Toki. This is Hiyori.
And that is Momonosuke.
I wish I were him!
That is our Oden-sama!
My lady!
It is nice to meet you.
He is the boy on whose shoulders
the future of the Kozuki Clan rests...
Oh, he looks so intelligent!
It is great that he does not look like Oden-sama at all!
What did you say?!
By the way, what's with your outfits?
We were eagerly waiting for Oden-sama's return!
We tried our best to take care of Kuri
while you were away, but...
Not just Kuri but the whole Land of Wano is...
Wait!
If you really care about Oden-san...
Please! Let him go!
My lady!
I...
I will be away for a little longer.
Oden-sama!
Please wait!
Come back!
Oden-sama!
I am begging you!
I could tell that something about the Land of Wano
was changed even as I turned my back.
I knew that I'd never set out to sea
if I turned around.
Damn you, Oden-sama! You bastard!
I quickly took a copy of the Ponegliff in the Land of Wano
and went back to the sea.
I came home for the first time in four years,
but I only stayed for a few hours.
You bastard...
Can you read the script then?!
I'm sorry, Oden.
Oden is married with two children?!
I can see... I can see the future.
Even if Oden leaves the Land of Wano,
that child will surely cause you harm.
Kozuki's heir!
What a pain...
Next, we headed to Mokomo Dukedom
where Cat Viper and Dogstorm are from.
That country was said to be
on the back of an elephant.
I was told that we could only get to Zou
with this Vivre Card.
You're right! It's not an island!
An elephant?!
Whose voice is this?
Oden-san, what's the matter?
Well, it's nothing, but it feels strange...
MOKOMO DUKEDOM
DUKE GENGHIS BAAN, MOKOMO DUKEDOM
The letter from Dogstorm and Cat Viper.
So they're alive! Those unruly boys...
It made a big fuss when they went missing!
Thank you for notifying me.
I feel uneasy...
Are you okay, Oden?
That doesn't sound like you.
I know how you feel, Oden.
You, too, Captain Roger?!
It kind of feels like
I'm being watched by something really big...
Here it is! The last Road Ponegliff!
Kozuki's family crest!
So it's true that the Minks and we are like brothers.
Now we've got all the Road Ponegliffs...
Let's go, guys! To the last island!
Yeah!
Roger! Oden-sama! Take me with you!
Come on, please! Take me!
Kid, you still have to wait.
Listen...
Everyone has their own turn.
My turn?!
When it comes, help me.
Okay! I'll help you at any cost!
Goodbye, Pedro.
We got several Real Ponegliffs
and four Road Ponegliffs.
The goal of our adventure is approaching.
The four Road Ponegliffs that we've got...
The lines from those four will cross at the center
and that's where the last island is.
Captain, are you okay?!
Have you figured out where the last island is?
Yes, we have.
When should we leave?
Immediately!
Okay!
All right! Let's go!
H-Hey, Buggy?
Buggy?!
Lucky or not, the apprentice Buggyjiro
suddenly got a high fever,
and gave up the journey to the last island.
Only a damn kid would catch a cold
right before a great adventure.
Shut up! I said I'm better now!
Your face is red and you're burning up
so lie quietly.
Whose nose is red and big you said?!
I didn't say that!
Go, go!
Fight!
Don't incite them, Roger, Oden!
Flashy treasure's waiting for me!
Don't push yourself, idiot!
I'm coming, too!
Captain, take me with you!
Are you a monster or something?
Although they argue a lot, in the end,
Redtaro took it upon himself to look after him.
I don't know if they're good friends or not.
Take me with you...
He's still saying it.
Buggyjiro has guts...
Buggyjiro is making such a fuss over it,
but you're okay with it, Redtaro?
Oden-san, Captain.
If we wanna go there,
we'll make it with our own ships someday!
The Roger Pirates finally did it!
The pirate Roger traveled around the world
for the first time in history!
Now there is a conqueror of the sea!
He's the king of the sea!
The King of the Pirates!
GOLD ROGER, KING OF THE PIRATES
The day we reached the last island,
we learned everything about the world.
What is the 100-Year Void?
What is the People of the D?
What are the Ancient Weapons?
The Land of Wano was once
connected with the rest of the world.
With the extraordinary treasure
that sat there before our eyes,
at that moment, Roger was...
...laughing.
So were we.
We laughed so hard that we cried.
Joyboy, I...
...wish that I had lived in the same era as you.
How could you leave this stupendous treasure!
It's such a funny story...
Hey, everyone...
Why don't we name this last island
where no man could reach for 800 years something like...
Laugh Tale!
As the new era begins,
the King of the Pirates leaves the ship alone.
The determination of a man! Oden takes it to heart
and heads for his home country,
the Land of Wano, where vice thrives and
people suffer under Orochi's tyranny!
The stunning truth awaits Oden.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"To the Land of Wano! The Roger Pirates Disband!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!