Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Let's sail on, raise high the sails
Let's sail on takaku ho wo agete
Catch the wind
kaze ni nore
Don't give up, if I'm determined
Don't give up kakugo kimetano nara
I'll never turn back
hikikaeshi wa shinai sa
Laugh on through troubled waters
waraitobase aranami
Shout it out, to save your spirit from breaking
Shout it out kokoro kudakenai youni
Your friends are there for you
nakama ga irun da
Hey, you don't ever need to act tough
hora tsuyogari nante iranai itsudatte
Even when the darkness tries to tear you apart
yami ga hikisakou toshitemo
Come on, brave it out
hora Brave it out
It's going to be all right
daijoubu sa
Strong bonds will break through
uchiyaburu saikyo no kizuna
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
The flag that called forth oaths
chikai atsumeta hata
Keep fighting on
tatakai tsudukete iku
Stay true to yourself
"jibunjishin" tsuranuke
Seize it, dreamin' on
tsukami toru Dreamin' on
I can't lose, I'll never run away
makerarenai nige ya shinai
Transcend meetings and partings and keep going
deai wakare koe ikou
They're all treasures
zenbu takaramono
Open the borderless map
mugendai no chizu hiroge
Towards the place that has no end
hateshinai ano basho e
Have the courage to take a step forward
fumidase yuuki no ippo
Raise your fist
ko wo agete
So this is Onigashima!
Luffy and the others
have finally landed on Onigashima.
My fellow warriors!
This is Onigashima, Kaido's stronghold!
Avoid unnecessary battles whenever possible,
and try to reach the castle for the final battle!
Good luck!
"Luffy Goes Out of Control?!
Sneaking into Kaido's Banquet!"
Woo hoo! Woo hoo!
Orochi-sama, you're so good!
Is this what you want?
No, Orochi-sama.
Why not?
Orochi-sama! Drink with us, too!
Orochi-sama!
Oh! Come closer! Come closer!
Drink more and more!
No problem! No problem!
Orochi-sama!
That hits the spot!
Now that we're free from
the ghosts of the Kozuki Clan,
booze tastes so heavenly!
Orochi is feeling carefree.
This is because Kanjuro the spy
has informed him of the Akazaya's plans,
enabling him to counter their insurrection
with a foolproof plan.
Their rendezvous point is Tokage Port!
Destroy all the routes that lead there!
GREAT BRIDGE BETWEEN KURI AND UDON
GREAT BRIDGE BETWEEN RINGO AND HAKUMAI
ITACHI PORT, KURI
The Akazaya members are alone and helpless!
Make sure to kill them all!
He will no longer be tormented by
the Kozuki Clan ghosts.
ONIGASHIMA
However, at Onigashima...
THE RAID HAS KICKED OFF
The raid has kicked off!
EASTERN FORCES
The Eastern Forces led by Kin'emon.
SOUTHERN FORCES
The Southern Forces led by Denjiro.
Combined, there are more than 5,000 troops.
POLAR TANG
The pirate Law's submarine...
KAIDO'S CASTLE   LAW
SOUTHERN FORCES   EASTERN FORCES
...went underwater with the Akazaya samurai on board...
...aimed at reaching the castle
where Orochi and Kaido are.
Their enemies are still unaware of
the over 5,000 troops advancing.
All right! We should get going, too!
Yeah!
Before that, Luffy,
I have super toys ready for an occasion like this!
Let's put them to good use!
Okay!
You mean those awesome ones?!
All right, let's do this!
You're so well-prepared, Franky!
Let's get going!
Okay, let's go!
I'm the one who'll take Kaido's head!
And me!
That bastard!
Hey! Damn Jaggy!
Why are you going your own way?!
You're not following Kin'emon and the others' plan!
I don't care about the samurai.
Everything in the Land of Wano
is at stake in this battle!
Do you have any idea what they've been through?!
Don't get the wrong idea about us!
We're not gonna join hands with anyone.
We came here to take down Kaido
and happen to be headed the same way as you all.
That's it.
Those fools!
Okay!
I'm gonna go stop them!
Wait, Luffy!
He'll only make things worse.
I'm gonna go stop him!
But...
Hey, Luffy!
Wait!
What's the matter, Kiku?
I'm a bit worried about Luffytaro-san.
If Tra-guy-san's prediction is correct,
he should be heading to Kaido's castle
head on by now.
No matter what kind of plan you make,
we know there are two idiots
who'll try to charge in through the front door!
IDIOTS
Those idiots will be good decoys for us.
And they're stronger than ordinary decoys.
In order to stop those idiots,
tons of Kaido's underlings will be sent to the front.
If we use Luffytaro-san who we're indebted to
as a decoy,
and something ends up happening to him...
There's no point in worrying about it.
Idiots won't go down that easily.
You have a lot of trust in your friend!
He's not my friend!
Cheers!
How unlucky.
I can't believe I have to stand guard down here
during the festival.
We've got booze, so let's enjoy it.
I don't think any samurai can get this far.
You're right.
Who are you?!
Is he one of the Akazaya...
Hey! Keep walking!
Kanjuro who kidnapped Momonosuke
and escaped to see Orochi...
...hasn't seen Orochi yet,
just as Kin'emon expected.
There's a fork again.
I've never been here before.
I didn't know it was this complicated.
To those lowest-level underlings who don't know anything,
I'm still one of the Akazaya members...
I must report on Kin'emon and the others
as soon as possible.
How can I get to Orochi-sama?!
This way. Let's go.
Wait!
Jaggy!
Cheers!
Where are you?!
Damn Luffy! Where did he wander off to?
Hey!
Whoa-whoa, why are you looking so serious?
Today's a banquet. Drink.
Good booze.
How did you know?
I can tell without drinking it.
I'm sure you can! Today's a banquet.
You've got to drink, too!
I'm looking for someone now.
Bye.
We have tons of booze that the people in Ebisu Town
and Okobore Town will never be able to drink!
Okobore Town?
Hey, what's taking you so long?
Hurry up, Franky!
Everyone's already left.
Give me a second.
We can catch up to them.
If we use this!
Black Rhino FR-U4!
BLACK RHINO FR-U4
Yes!
I saw it during the battle at the Fish-Man Island!
Not "it," Jimbei!
Call this baby "Black Rhino"!
And there's another one!
Brachio Tank 5!
BRACHIO TANK 5
I'm a tank commander!
COMMANDER CHOPPER
Commander Chopper!
We're counting on you, Chopper!
Great! We can get there safely!
Chobro, you're so cool!
You can count on me!
I'm a sniper!
Chopper!
Usopp!
Franky!
WE'RE HERE!
We're here!
Now we're all ready!
Where's Luffy?
Well,
because Eustass Kid and his people
went into the island head-on...
Okay! I'm gonna go stop them!
Don't worry!
He'll definitely make things worse!
Why didn't you stop him?!
But Roronoa Zoro said what you just said and...
He'll only make things worse!
I'm gonna go stop him!
He'll just lose his way for sure!
I see...
Oh, come on...
Those two went off by themselves...
Who knows what's gonna happen.
Forget about that idiot,
and let's go for a drive through the battlefield,
Nami-san!
It's full!
Isn't this too tight, Usopp?!
It can't be helped. There are so many of us.
It's too hot!
Get out, Usopp!
Damn you! You're in heaven!
I'm sorry that you don't have shooting skills!
Get over it!
I know mature women are irresistible,
but you can't force your way into here, young man.
Would you like to ride on the back?
Can I? I'm happy to.
Ready?!
Okay, I'm ready.
You?!
How about a little bromance?
Well, okay.
Commander Chopper!
Meet me at the back of the island
and we'll combine these vehicles.
Good luck!
"Combine"!
Super!
Roger!
I feel like a rock star!
Are you a haunted doll or something?!
We should go, too!
Robin-chan!
Come with me!
No thanks. You'll get dirty with dust
on the top of the tank.
Shall we walk?
Yeah.
You guys are as lively as ever.
I can't wait to finish the fight
and have a welcome party for you.
Yeah, until then,
I have to stay as calm as possible.
In a battle where everyone's so excited,
someone who calmly perceives the situation is crucial.
You're so mature.
It's reassuring to have you here.
I want to be helpful
in my first fight with this group!
I'm bored! I'm bored! I'm bored!
Hey, Pay-Pay,
tell me some interesting stories-arinsu.
I don't have any.
You don't?!
All that living and not one interesting story?
How...
How sad, Pay-Pay!
Let me comfort you-rinsu!
Stop, you're heavy, Big Sis!
"Stop... you're heavy"?
Did you say "Stop"?!
Who are you to tell me that?!
I'm heavy, terrifying,
and a pain in the ass, you say?!
I didn't say that!
Shut up, you brat!
Can't you be quiet?!
"Shut up"?
Did you say "Shut up"?
What do you mean "Shut up"?!
How did Pay-Pay bother you?! Say it!
I don't think he's talking about Pay-Pay.
You're messing with my Pay-Pay too much!
If you make him cry,
are you willing to take responsibility?!
Damn you...
Thank you for waiting!
Kaido-sama is calling for you!
Tsk! What took you so long, Kaido?!
Like I said, don't snap at him!
I'm finally gonna be freed from those shitty brats.
I really enjoyed Ul-chan's snapping show.
Oh! I like how you drink!
You don't need to hold back.
We have plenty!
There's a lot of good booze here.
You just noticed that? That's because
this is Kaido-sama and Orochi-sama's stronghold.
There's more than enough booze here...
...which none of the commoners
will ever get to taste.
If I had to live miserably and pathetically
like the people in Ebisu Town and Okobore Town,
I'd rather die!
Me, too!
Don't you agree?!
You don't care about what you're putting
the people in Ebisu Town and Okobore Town through.
That's how much you like this booze.
Yeah, it's really good!
Well then...
Drink up!
Whoa-whoa! He's almost drowning!
Hey, stop! You bastard!
What are you doing?!
--What's wrong?
--What happened?
Don't worry.
They just had too much of that fine liquor.
What is that?
They made too much.
Don't bring it here!
We had no choice.
Jaggy! Where are you?!
He doesn't even know Oden's wishes!
How could he do whatever suits him?!
Hey! Did you see Jaggy?!
Jaggy? Who is that?
If I get thinner, I'll be too popular
So I don't get thinner, that's my kind of...
...funk!
That's Balloon!
You're late! Why don't you eat, too?
--This way! This way!
--Yeah.
Wow! Everything you've got there looks delicious!
--Why don't you eat some, too?
--Is it okay?!
Paradise Farm products are for us alone to enjoy!
If the people of Okobore Town eat them,
they'll die of shock since they're so delicious!
How many days do you think it's been
since she ate?!
Even if she busily weaves hats every day
and sells them,
we can only earn barely enough for
one person to live!
Sometimes we get to eat barnyard grass
and that's it.
But at least, twice a year,
on her birthday and New Year's,
I want her to eat rice!
So I gave her money today
and sent her to the town
to buy rice for her eighth birthday!
--I said "Take it"!
--I said "I don't want it"!
After we make a toast,
there'll be even better grub.
Ouch! Ow, ow, ow!
Hey, what's that? It's red-bean soup!
We're drinking now! Screw you!
Red-bean soup?
They made too much,
so it's been given to us.
Idiot! It doesn't go with alcohol!
There are many other things to eat!
Dump this sickeningly sweet soup!
Spill it over Okobore Town!
Good idea!
They'll happily sip it off the ground!
It's so yummy!
This soup is so delicious!
What? Is this your first time having it?!
Yes! There are some rice cakes in it!
What a sumptuous treat!
This is the greatest day of my life!
Damn beggars! Just be happy you're alive!
The solid promise he made with his friend.
The Gifters trample on Otama's wish for recovery
and her struggle to survive with their petty behavior.
Luffy trembles with anger!
His all-out Elephant Gun blasts!
The battle begins at Onigashima.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Thinking of Otama! Luffy's Furious Strike!"
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!